"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60506","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many jobs have been created by One3One Solutions (a) in England and Wales and (b) in each Prison Service region in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199504","199504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60507","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners were in employment provided by One3One Solutions in (a) England and Wales and (b) each Prison Service region in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199505","199505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60508","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with which countries the UK is currently negotiating prisoner transfer agreements.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199506","199506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60509","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what financial penalties have been incurred by Sodexo Ltd in relation to its contract to run HM Prison Northumberland.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199495","199495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60510","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what financial penalties have been incurred by Serco in relation to its contract to run Hassockfield Secure Training Centre since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199496","199496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60511","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners serving custodial sentences for serious violent and sexual assaults were held in open prisons on 1 May (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199513","199513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60512","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) sex offenders and (b) sex offender treatment programme places there were in each prison in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199530","199530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60513","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 28 April 2014, Official Report, column 623W, on procurement, what contracts his Department holds with (a) G4S, (b) Sodexo and (c) Serco for (i) HM Prison Altcourse, (ii) HM Prison/Young Offender Institution Parc, (iii) HM Prison Rye Hill, (iv) HM Prison Bronzefield, (v) HM Prison/Young Offender Institution Forest Bank, (vi) HM Prison Peterborough, (vii) HM Prison Ashfield, (viii) HM Prison Lowdham Grange and (ix) HM Prison Thameside.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199526","199526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60514","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners were held in open prisons on 1 May (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199528","199528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60515","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time for a sex offender treatment programme is (a) across the whole prison estate and (b) in those prisons holding sex offenders.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199531","199531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60516","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, of what offences had prisoners released on temporary licence in each of the last four years been convicted.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199532","199532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60517","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of a judge recusing themselves there were in each of the last four years; and what the reasons were for each recusal.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199534","199534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60518","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners were released on temporary licence in each of the last four years (a) on compassionate grounds or to receive medical treatment, (b) to engage in work, paid employment or volunatry work, (c) to receive instruction or training which is not available in prison, (d) to take part in court, tribunal or inquiry proceedings, (e) to consult with his legal adviser, where this cannot reasonably be done within the prison, (f) to help the police with their enquiries, (g) to facilitate the prisoner's transfer between prisons and (h) to help him maintain family ties or to ease the transition from prison life to freedom.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199533","199533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60519","2014-06-10","Department of Health","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of HIV were reported in prisons in England and Wales in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199548","199548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60520","2014-06-10","Department of Health","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many incidences of sexually transmitted diseases were reported in prisons in England and Wales in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199549","199549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60521","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-consensual sexual acts, of what type, there were in prisons in England and Wales in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199550","199550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60522","2014-06-10","Department of Health","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings have taken place with the (a) OECD, (b) WHO and (c) European Commission following the G8 Dementia Summit; and what the outcome of these meetings was.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199458","199458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60523","2014-06-11","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what progress the Cabinet Secretary's review into the provision of assistance for unemployed young people has made.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199542","199542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60524","2014-06-11","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-06","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, when the findings of the Cabinet Secretary's review into the provision of assistance for unemployed young people will be published.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199543","199543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60525","2014-06-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 24 March 2014, Official Report, column 140W, on the national apprenticeship service, how many times the search function 'find an apprenticeship provider' on the national apprenticeship website has been used.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199544","199544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60526","2014-06-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeship starts relate to (a) existing employees of the organisation concerned and (b) new employees in the 2012-13 academic year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199545","199545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/60527","2014-06-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will provide a breakdown of the Employer Ownership Pilot funding for the unified communications sector.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199546","199546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58248","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to support former armed services' personnel to readjust to civilian life by providing (a) low cost mortgages, (b) low interest loans to start a business, (c) payment of tuition fees and living expenses for university or vocational educational and (d) health care bespoke to individual needs.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199323","199323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58249","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will estimate (a) the number of households which were on social tariffs for their energy supplies before such tariffs were withdrawn and (b) the number of those households which included people considered especially vulnerable to cold-related illnesses.","Biography information for Sir Robert Smith","Sir Robert Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199430","199430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58250","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many withdrawals of nuclear materials from safeguards applied under the tripartite UK-Euratom-IAEA Voluntary Safeguards Agreement there have been since May 2010; and how many such withdrawals were permanent.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199177","199177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58251","2014-06-09","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-05","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what guidance the Electoral Commission follows in determining whether statistics in answers to parliamentary questions are (a) provided in full, (b) provided via a link to a website and (c) placed in the Library.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199268","199268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58252","2014-06-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will provide a detailed itemised inventory of what works of art from Government collections were on loan to the British Embassy and Residence in Tehran at the time of the riots in November 2011; and what claims for compensation for loss, damage or destruction have been made by the Government to insurers in respect of those items.","Biography information for Michael Ellis","Michael Ellis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199398","199398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58253","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 28 April 2014, Official Report, column 437W, on telecommunications: databases, whether she has yet completed her assessment of (a) the consequences for the UK of the decision of the European Court of Justice in Joined Cases C-293/12 and C-594/12 (Digital Rights Ireland and Seitlinger and Others) and (b) what implication that decision has for (i) enforcement of the Data Retention (EC Directive) Regulations 2009 and (ii) her powers to reimburse any expenses incurred by a public communications provider in complying with those Regulations.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199250","199250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58254","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to commence each section of the Immigration Act 2014.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199249","199249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58255","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will abolish prescription charges for asthma medication.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199363","199363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58256","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what basis the conditions exempt from prescription charges are decided.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199364","199364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58257","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that children's heart surgery units receive equal and sufficient levels of scrutiny across the country.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199258","199258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58258","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to release the second stage of the review into the closure of surgery at Leeds Children's Heart Unit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199256","199256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58259","2014-06-19","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable for the new congenital heart disease review is.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199257","199257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58260","2014-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contacts and discussions (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have had with the African National Congress regarding a possible successor to President Mugabe of Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199309","199309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58261","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list the people who have received the Royal Prerogative of Mercy by Letters Patent in the last 20 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199269","199269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58262","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether there has been any occasion when the exercise of the Royal Prerogative of Mercy has been granted by way of Letters Close (Litterae Clausae); and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199270","199270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58263","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the (a) Crown Office and (b) Office of the Lord President of the Council maintains a list of all Letters Patent issued in the last 20 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199271","199271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58264","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library a copy of the guidance notes used in his Department and in the Office of the Lord President of the Council regarding the wording, drafting, formatting, production, approval and processing of Letters Patent.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199272","199272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58265","2014-06-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the exercise of the Royal Prerogative of Mercy has been granted in Northern Ireland in the last 20 years by means of Letters Close (Litterae Clausae); and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199281","199281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58266","2014-06-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the Answer of 1 May 2014, Official Report, column 762W, on terrorism, what steps she is taking to recover information for the period 1987-97 for which records could not be found; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199283","199283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58267","2014-06-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, by which (a) documents and (b) other means the recipients of a Royal Pardon, following the exercise of the Royal Prerogative of Mercy, are able to demonstrate to a court or any law enforcement agency, that they are the beneficiaries of exercise of the Royal Prerogative; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199282","199282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58268","2014-06-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the Answer of 1 May 2014, Official Report, column 762W, on terrorism, if the exercise of the Royal Prerogative of Mercy to which she refers was by way of Letters Patent; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199279","199279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58269","2014-06-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will list the people who are known to have received the Royal Prerogative of Mercy by Letters Patent or under any other authority, in the last 20 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199280","199280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58270","2014-06-10","HM Treasury","2014-06-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the contribution by the Deputy Leader of the House, Official Report, columns 841-2, on New clause 1 of the Deregulation Bill, how the information-sharing gateway will operate.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199417","199417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58271","2014-06-10","Cabinet Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress his Department has made on (a) the Cabinet Office capabilities plan published in April 2013 and (b) the key area specified in that plan on redesigning services and delivering them digitally.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199432","199432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58272","2014-06-10","Cabinet Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many full-time equivalent staff (a) were employed by, (b) left and (c) joined the Government Procurement Services Commissioning Academy in each quarter since its introduction; how many students passed through the Commissioning Academy in each quarter; and what the average length was of courses taken by those students.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199431","199431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58273","2014-06-10","Cabinet Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many full-time equivalent staff in his Department are working on G Cloud.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199418","199418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58274","2014-06-09","HM Treasury","2014-06-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what resources will be available for targeted enforcement of the National Minimum Wage amongst employers in the maritime sector in the next two financial years.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199357","199357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58275","2014-06-09","HM Treasury","2014-06-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will outline the content of the Service Level Agreement between his Department and HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) on the work of the HMRC National Minimum Wage Enforcement Team; what resources have been allocated to the enforcement team for work in the maritime sector; and what period the Agreement covers.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199359","199359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58276","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent (a) correspondence and (b) discussions he has had with individual employers in the maritime industry about pay rates below the National Minimum Wage (NMW) for seafarers subject to UK National Insurance employed on vessels working from UK ports; and if he will take steps to enforce in the maritime sector his Department's policy on enforcement, prosecutions and naming employers who break the law on the NMW.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199360","199360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58277","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) UK Chamber of Shipping and (b) European Community Shipowners Association on pay rates for seafarers subject to UK National Insurance employed on vessels working from UK ports who are paid hourly rates below the National Minimum Wage; and if he will request data on such pay rates from maritime employers' associations.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199356","199356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58278","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) UK Chamber of Shipping and (b) European Community Shipowners Association on pay rates for seafarers subject to UK National Insurance payments employed on vessels working from UK ports; and if he will request data on pay rates from maritime employers' associations.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199358","199358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58279","2014-06-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to monitor the delivery of the Mobile Infrastructure Project and to bring adequate mobile telephone coverage to people living in remote and rural areas.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199164","199164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58280","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 23 April 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr S Kneale.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199218","199218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58281","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 24 April 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Michael Adebayo Johnson.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199215","199215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58282","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 28 April 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Tanvir Shah.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199216","199216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58283","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 22 April 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr A Mehmood.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199217","199217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58284","2014-06-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to meet victims of press abuse and their representatives.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199346","199346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58285","2014-06-10","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-06-05","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the electoral registration figures were in each ward in the recent conformation dry run conducted in the (a) Makerfield constituency and (b) Borough of Wigan.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199308","199308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58286","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the review Sexualisation of Young People by Dr. Linda Papadopoulos.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199353","199353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58287","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will introduce the teaching of the dangers of pornography into the school syllabus.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199200","199200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58288","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's policy is on the easy visibility and access for children to overly sexualised and graphic magazines and periodicals in retail stores.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199203","199203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58289","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if she will establish an ombudsman to cover complaints on the use of overly sexualised content on images and displays on high streets and other business advertisements easily visible to the public which are not covered by the Advertising Standards Association or Police and Crime Commissioners.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199202","199202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58290","2014-06-10","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he will respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Stoke-on-Trent Central received by his office on 29 May 2014, relating to the recent situation in Birmingham.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199163","199163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58291","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) rank and (b) length of service was of each RAF engineer (aerosystems) officer who left the service in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199373","199373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58292","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has plans to introduce maritime remotely-piloted air systems; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199377","199377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58293","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the reason was for the time taken to produce the Defence Air Safety Annual Report July 2012 to August 2013, published on 3 April 2014; and if he will make it his policy to publish future such reports within three months of the end of the relevant year.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199374","199374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58294","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to mitigate the risks to defence aviation safety systems and culture referred to in the Defence Air Safety Annual Report July 2012 to August 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199375","199375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58295","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) outflow and (b) inflow was for RAF (i) engineer (aerosystems) officers and (ii) aircraft tradesmen in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199376","199376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58296","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the gross value added per capita was for the (a) Brighton and Hove and (b) South Hampshire built-up areas in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199400","199400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58297","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the gross value added was for the (a) Brighton and Hove and (b) South Hampshire built-up areas in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199401","199401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58298","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on how many journeys were made between Portsmouth and Brighton by (a) car, (b) rail and (c) bus in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199402","199402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58299","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on how many journeys were made between Southampton and Brighton by (a) car, (b) rail and (c) bus in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199403","199403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58300","2014-06-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the average broadband speed in (a) Glasgow North West constituency, (b) Glasgow, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199154","199154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58301","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of provision of information for carers on affordable energy.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199155","199155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58302","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with energy companies on the affordability of energy tariffs for carers.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199156","199156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58303","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government Minister for Transport and Veterans on the possibility of providing free or discounted travel for carers in Scotland.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199235","199235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58304","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of employment and support allowance applicants who have been waiting to be given an assessment appointment for more than (a) three, (b) four, (c) five, (d) six and (e) seven months.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199153","199153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58305","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the time between applications for employment and support allowance and an assessment appointment for people who applied in (a) September 2013, (b) October 2013, (c) November 2013, (d) December 2013, (e) January 2014, (f) February 2014, (g) March 2014 and (h) April 2014 in (i) Glasgow North West constituency, (ii) Glasgow, (iii) Scotland and (iv) the UK.","Biography information for John Robertson","John Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199352","199352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58306","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the value of universal credit assets is; and what changes there were to this value.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199313","199313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58307","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that his Department is able to cross-check data on housing costs within the universal credit programme in order to counter fraud.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199312","199312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58308","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his most recent estimate is of the useful life of IT assets listed in his Department's annual report and accounts; and whether these will be amortised over a five year period.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199310","199310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58309","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many couple claims have been made for universal credit.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199315","199315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58310","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time equivalent staff are employed by his Department to work exclusively on universal credit in (a) total, (b) communications, (c) IT development and (d) project delivery.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199314","199314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58311","2014-06-09","Department for International Development","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether any UK aid given to the Palestinian Authority has been distributed to prisoners convicted of terrorism-related activities in the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199230","199230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58312","2014-06-09","Department for International Development","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether any UK aid given to the Palestinian Authority has been distributed to individuals released from prison after serving sentences for terrorism-related activities.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199231","199231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58313","2014-06-09","Department for International Development","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what arrangements are in place to monitor the use of funds given to the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199229","199229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58314","2014-06-09","Department for International Development","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much aid her Department has given to the Palestinian Authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199228","199228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58315","2014-06-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to respond to the letter of 5 May 2014 from the hon. Member for Cardiff South and Penarth on British Army processes of justice and requesting an urgent meeting.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199311","199311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58316","2014-06-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of (a) the number of British armed forces personnel operationally deployed to Northern Ireland in each year from April 1984 to April 2010 and (b) the number of such personnel who were accompanied by (i) a spouse or (ii) a civil partner in each of those years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199300","199300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58317","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to swimming lessons for schoolchildren.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199325","199325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58318","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the current average waiting time is for elective surgery in (a) St Albans constituency, (b) Hertfordshire, (c) the East of England and (d) England.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199445","199445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58319","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many operations have been cancelled because of scheduling error in (a) St Albans, (b) Hertfordshire and (c) England since 2005.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199361","199361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58320","2014-06-10","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cases of uninsured drivers have been reported, by region, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199253","199253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58321","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases of car insurance fraud have been reported, by region, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199252","199252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58322","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to introduce clinical guidelines for the diagnosis, treatment and management of obstructive sleep apnoea; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199292","199292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58323","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that commissioning of service provision for obstructive sleep apnoea is appropriate to the predicted prevalence in local areas in England.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199266","199266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58324","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what body has responsibility for the implementation of recommendations made by his Department's former Obstructive Sleep Apnoea Working Group.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199267","199267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58325","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to introduce a quality standard for the diagnosis and treatment of sleep disordered breathing covering the range of conditions from simple snoring to obstructive sleep apnoea.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199286","199286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58326","2014-06-10","Cabinet Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 23 January 2014, Official Report, column 316W, on museums and galleries, what the financial contribution required from each institution in the museums and galleries sector is from the transfer in employers' contributions following the Cabinet Office review of the Civil Service Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199321","199321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58327","2014-06-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 1 May 2014, Official Report, columns 809-10W, on Arts Council England, how much Arts Council England spending on libraries was obtained from (a) grant-in-aid and lottery funding in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199319","199319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58328","2014-06-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 1 May 2014, Official Report, columns 809-10W, on Arts Council England, how much the Museums, Libraries and Archives Council spent on libraries in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199320","199320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58329","2014-06-10","Women and Equalities","2014-06-05","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Government Equalities Office press release of 13 May 2014 entitled £1 million to help women start or grow their own business, whether that sum will be drawn from the budget of the Super Connected Cities programme.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199322","199322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58330","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 14 May 2014, Official Report, column 597W, on renewable energy, what the evidential basis was for the statement made in the Government's response on competitive allocation that Power Purchase Agreements could be signed on a conditional basis before a strike price needs to be submitted, allowing independent generators to receive indicative financing terms from lenders; and what representations he has received from generators on that statement.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199182","199182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58331","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 14 May 2014, Official Report, column 597W, on renewable energy, what assessment his Department has made of what the market conditions that will enable independent generators to use short-term Power Purchase Agreements (PPAs) and a wider variety of PPA counterparties will have developed in time for independent generators to secure necessary finance terms ahead of the first CfD auctions which are scheduled for October 2014.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199181","199181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58332","2014-06-12","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether HM Passport Office is meeting the 2013-14 performance targets (a) to process 99.5 per cent of straightforward passport applications within 10 working days, (b) where additional information is required from customers to process 93 per cent of applications within 29 working days, (c) to process 99.5 per cent of premium and fast track applications within four hours or seven days and (d) to achieve a customer satisfaction rating of at least 90 per cent.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199399","199399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58333","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-05","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what meetings he has had with (a) the First Minister, (b) the Deputy First Minister and (c) both the First and Deputy First Ministers of Northern Ireland in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199366","199366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58334","2014-06-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-05","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, when he last attended a meeting of the British-Irish Council summit.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199386","199386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58335","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department has invited representatives of the devolved administrations to join the ad hoc ministerial-led steering group on the implementation of his Department's national space security policy.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199367","199367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58336","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that industry and academia in Northern Ireland are able to benefit from opportunities in support of national space security interests.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199368","199368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58337","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether public sector organisations in Northern Ireland will be eligible for the terms of use for postcode address finder from 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199370","199370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58338","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions officials in his Department had with their counterparts in the Northern Ireland Executive before publication of the National Space Security Policy.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199371","199371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58339","2014-06-10","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of (a) staff and (b) senior staff in her Department are female.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199397","199397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58340","2014-06-10","Prime Minister","2014-06-05","To ask the Prime Minister, when he last attended a British-Irish Council summit; and how many such summits he has attended since becoming Prime Minister.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199388","199388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58341","2014-06-10","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many (a) permanent and (b) non-permanent staff were employed in her Department on 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199419","199419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58342","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps officials in her Department have taken with their Northern Ireland counterparts to ensure that best practice on the prevention of hate crime is shared across all administrations of the United Kingdom.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199387","199387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58343","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the Passport Agency's average process time for applications was in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199385","199385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58344","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the longest time is for which a passport application has been waiting to be processed from receipt at the passport office to delivery to applicant for (a) new applications and (b) applications for renewal of passport in the period from 1 January 2014 to 31 May 2014.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199391","199391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58345","2014-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which companies have been (a) given warnings because of breaches of environmental law and (b) prosecuted for such breaches in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199354","199354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58346","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average charge levied by healthcare professionals for written reports requested by patients who require them for (a) setting up power of attorney and (b) other purposes is in each commissioning area.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199246","199246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58347","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people (a) sought chlamydia screening and (b) tested positive in each local authority in 2012-13.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199243","199243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58348","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the costs of a patient who presents with eye conditions as a first point of call (a) a GP, (b) a hospital eye service, (c) an accident and emergency department and (d) a primary eyecare acute referral scheme.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199248","199248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58349","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding was available through the Skills Funding Agency for (a) adult learning courses to support return-to-work programmes and (b) English as a Second Language courses in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199410","199410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58350","2014-06-09","HM Treasury","2014-06-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the levels of (a) public sector investment, (b) private sector investment, (c) investment in intangibles and (d) other investment was in each G7 country in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199413","199413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58351","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects to put out to tender the contract to provide military air traffic management at British and overseas bases.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199408","199408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58352","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to publish a white paper in advance of the next Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199245","199245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58353","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects to confirm the decision to allow a process change to enable the Rivet Joint signal intelligence aircraft to be certificated under Military Aviation Authority regulations.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199247","199247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58354","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the MRV-P programme concept phase to be completed; whether funding for a demonstration has been approved; and what funds have been allocated for this purpose.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199355","199355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58355","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the MQ-4C Triton unmanned aerial vehicle; and how much his Department has spent on the assessment process to date.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199414","199414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58356","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many contracts have been awarded by his Department to Boskalis over the last five years; and on how many occasions during the contract period such contractors have been found responsible for breaching environmental guidance, thereby committing an offence.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199409","199409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58357","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 18 December 2013, Official Report, column 636W, on defence: procurement, what the final costs are of establishing a Golo and running the tendering process.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199274","199274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58358","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 12 May 2014, Official Report, column 401W, on mental health services, whether the Mental Health Intelligence Network has been established.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199324","199324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58359","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many secure places there are in the South West region for children with mental health conditions involving violent behaviour.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199412","199412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58360","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many probation officers his Department plans to recruit in the next 12 months; in which countries those posts will be advertised; and what his Department's budget for that advertising is.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199404","199404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58361","2014-06-09","Leader of the House","2014-06-05","To ask the Leader of the House, how many questions to each department did not receive a substantive answer by the time of prorogation; and how long each question had been waiting for an answer.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199244","199244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58362","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of seafarer fatigue on maritime safety; and what steps his Department is taking to enforce manning levels on vessels.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199411","199411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58363","2014-06-11","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans she has to reappoint the Parliamentary Boundary Commission for Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199255","199255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58364","2014-06-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the Government's proposed Deregulation Bill on tourism employment in England.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199379","199379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58365","2014-06-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the economic effects of deregulating school holidays on (a) tourism-related jobs in seaside and coastal areas and (b) seaside economies in general.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199378","199378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58366","2014-06-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Ministers or officials in his Department have had with colleagues in the Department for Education on the effect of deregulating school holidays on the tourism industry.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199380","199380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58367","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants in the Employment and Support Allowance Work Related Activity Group are currently on the Work Programme; and how many such claimants had the period before they were fit for work assessed as (a) up to three months, (b) three to six months, (c) six to 12 months and (d) over 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199390","199390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58368","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff will be employed in the specialist housing teams that will be established in univesral credit centres.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199393","199393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58369","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a jobcentre is permitted to require a jobseeker to attend a voluntary employment support project in receipt of no statutory funding without the consent of that project.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199395","199395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58370","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of employment and support allowance referred to the Work Programme since June 2011 had an estimated period before they were fit for work of (a) up to three months, (b) three to six months, (c) six to 12 months and (d) over 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199394","199394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58371","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people gaining work through the Work Programme have entered self-employment since the inception of that programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199396","199396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58372","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many houses built in each of the last five years are (a) wheelchair accessible and (b) built to lifetime homes standards.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199276","199276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58373","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many houses not compliant with Part M building regulations were built (a) in the last two years and (b) since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199291","199291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58374","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities in the UK maintain a register of accessible or adapted homes; and what guidance his Department issues to local authorities on registers of accessible housing.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199290","199290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58375","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the demand for (a) homes built to lifetime home standards and (b) wheelchair accessible homes.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199278","199278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58376","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people in receipt of disability living allowance or personal independence payments have received support from the Help to Buy scheme.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199284","199284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58377","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average waiting time was in each local authority for an assessment for a disabled facilities grant in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199285","199285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58378","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will provide incentives to developers to ensure that new homes planned for construction in 2014-15 will be (a) wheelchair accessible and (b) built to lifetime homes standards.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199265","199265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58379","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to ensure accessible housing, meeting internationally recognised visitability standards, for people who become disabled in 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199287","199287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58380","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of homes in (a) Ebbsfleet and (b) other planned garden cities will be (i) wheelchair accessible and (ii) built to lifetime homes standards.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199288","199288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58381","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2014, Official Report, column 515W, on Western Sahara, if the Minister for the Middle East and North Africa will also meet representatives of POLISARIO, the UN-recognised body, to discuss issues relating to Western Sahara.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199433","199433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58382","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on how the ongoing conflict in Western Sahara affects the ability of terrorist and criminal gangs to recruit disaffected youth in the refugee camps or the occupied territory.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199262","199262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58383","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital day beds were taken because of delayed discharge relating to inaccessible housing available for disabled outpatients in (a) 2013-14 and (b) May 2014.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199260","199260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58384","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of a Fund for European Aid to the Most Deprived on deprived communities in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199263","199263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58385","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the UK Government voted against the establishment of a Fund for European Aid to the Most Deprived.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199259","199259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58386","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department takes to ensure that people do not face delayed discharge from hospital because there is no suitable housing for them to be discharged; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199264","199264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58387","2014-06-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the reason is for the time taken to make a decision on the Rushden Lakes development; and when he plans to announce that decision.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199254","199254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58388","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence his Department holds or has assessed on the effects of conversion to academy status on the test results of children in primary schools.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199446","199446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58389","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the collection and reporting of data relating to the incidence of cancer of the unknown primary.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199343","199343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58390","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the incidence of patients with cancer of the unknown primary first presenting at accident and emergency.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199342","199342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58391","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the amount of research undertaken into ways to detect the origin of primary cancer in those suffering from cancer of the unknown primary.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199372","199372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58392","2014-06-10","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government plans to respond to the recommendations set out in the report of the All Party Parliamentary Group on Skin on sunbed regulation published in 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199381","199381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58393","2014-06-10","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential cost of extending the human papilloma virus vaccination programme to include all boys aged 12 and 13 years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199382","199382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58394","2014-06-10","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the Government's assessment is of the effectiveness of warning labels on alcoholic beverages regarding drinking during pregnancy; and what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of making such labels mandatory.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199389","199389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58395","2014-06-10","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the running costs for each of the academic health science networks are.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199345","199345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58396","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the importance of psychological support services for patients suffering from cancer of the unknown primary.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199344","199344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58397","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to maintain and improve specialist services for children suffering from brittle bone disease.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199226","199226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58398","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent progress he has made on ensuring that mental health has equal standing with physical health.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199224","199224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58399","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to educate adults in literacy, numeracy and ICT skills.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199220","199220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58400","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to assist homeowners facing problems paying their mortgages and to provide practical advice and support.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199225","199225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58401","2014-06-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage primary school children to become active and involved in local sports organisations.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199221","199221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58402","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to prevent modern slavery.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199227","199227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58403","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that costs of public transport do not increase.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199223","199223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58404","2014-06-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the Giro D'Italia in Northern Ireland; and what plans she has to ensure a positive legacy from the event.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199222","199222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58405","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 6 May 2014, Official Report, column 87W, on holiday leave, what assessment his Department has made of the conclusions of the Citizen's Advice Bureau's Report entitled Give us a Break on the lack of awareness and denial of paid holiday entitlement to UK workers.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199434","199434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58406","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department takes to record and identify instances where non-pharmacological treatments have caused adverse reactions in patients.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199201","199201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58407","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent reports that Hamas leader Khaled Mashaal said that his organisation will not renounce violence or recognise Israel.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199277","199277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58408","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to European governments to secure as quickly as possible restitution for British citizens who had assets seized by the Nazis.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199234","199234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58409","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department gives local authorities on the suspension of school staff.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199180","199180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58410","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of fly-tipping in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199238","199238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58411","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of fly-tipping in South Staffordshire in each year since 2009-10; and how many such people received the maximum allowable sentence.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199178","199178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58412","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of those convicted of fly-tipping were handed the maximum possible sentence in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199179","199179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58413","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK have received support through the Access to Work scheme in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199328","199328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58414","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what funding has been provided to disabled people in Scotland and the UK through the Access to Work scheme in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199329","199329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58415","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to promote the Access to Work scheme to disabled people in Scotland.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199330","199330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58416","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he intends to take to endure that literature distributed by abortion clinics informing women about adoption as an alternative to abortion under the new Revised Standard Operating Procedures for the Approval of Independent Places for the Termination of Pregnancy is of the highest possible quality and objectivity.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199240","199240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58417","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Revised Standard Operating Procedures for the Approval of Independent Places for the Termination of Pregnancy, what assessment he has made of the possibility that inaccurate diagnoses will follow his Department's decision to allow women to refrain from informing their GP of a prior abortion.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199241","199241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58418","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Revised Standard Operating Procedures for the Approval of Independent Places for the Termination of Pregnancy, what steps he is taking to ensure that patients seeking abortion counselling are not subject to pressure to agree to the procedure as a result of his Department's requirement that abortion treatment must be delivered within 10 days of the first appointment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199239","199239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58419","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many abortions were performed beyond the 24 week limit where feticide was declined in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199205","199205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58420","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many abortions were performed for foetal abnormality in each of the last five years which were reported to a foetal abnormality register but were not notified through the submission of an HSA4 abortion notification form to the Chief Medical Officer.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199204","199204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58421","2014-06-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the findings from the US Senate Intelligence Committee, what information his Department holds on the number of detainees held in Diego Garcia.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199176","199176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58422","2014-06-10","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-05","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the Electoral Commission's efforts to improve the conduct of elections in the London Borough of Tower Hamlets.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199175","199175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58423","2014-06-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's policy is on beak trimming of chickens; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199160","199160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58424","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of delays on the border from British Gibraltar territory into Spain on vehicles crossing that border.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199447","199447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58425","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the European Commission in respect of petitions from the government of Gibraltar for a representative to monitor the border crossing.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199448","199448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58426","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the trends in the incidence of dental caries among school children (a) in Bolton and (b) nationally since 2010.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199206","199206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58427","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to co-ordinate healthy eating initiatives among the homeless.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199209","199209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58428","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the five most common causes of admission to hospital have been for (a) children and (b) adults in Bolton since 2010.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199210","199210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58429","2014-06-09","HM Treasury","2014-06-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been paid through working tax credits to people in Bolton North East constituency in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199151","199151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58430","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many rough sleepers there were in each local authority in the North West in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199273","199273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58431","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) headteachers, (b) deputy headteachers and (c) teachers in Bolton Local Education Authority took early retirement on the grounds of ill-health in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199211","199211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58432","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure that overcrowding on trains is (a) regulated and (b) effectively monitored.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199443","199443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58433","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent research his Department has (a) commissioned and (b) evaluated relating to age discrimination in (i) the work place and (ii) Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199242","199242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58434","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people resident in (a) Bolton North East constituency and (b) Bolton have received pension credit since 2010.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199150","199150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58435","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy to release statistics on the number of refusals by the Legal Aid Agency to pay legal aid in cases settled before the permission stage.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199207","199207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58436","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the new judicial review regulations on people who are fighting eviction or the repossession of a house.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199208","199208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58437","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to ensure that funds devolved to the budgets of police and crime commissioners for victims' services are allocated according to crime rates.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199327","199327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58438","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect on funding available for victims' services of devolution to police and crime commissioners.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199326","199326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58439","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he expects to receive the Sentencing Council's review of sentencing guidelines for death by drink-driving; and what discussions he has had with that body on its progress on that programme of work.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199428","199428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58440","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the change in waiting times for an initial decision for Tier 1 (Entrepreneur) visa applications in the last year; what the average waiting time is for an initial decision for a Tier 1 application; and what assessment she has made of the economic effect of the time taken for such decisions on economic growth.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199152","199152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58441","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential need for a separate national policy on the collection, use and retention of data gathered by unmanned or other surveillance aircraft operating in the UK.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199442","199442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58442","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the reasons for the reduction in businesses fined for employing illegal immigrants since 2010.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199441","199441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58443","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are currently detained for immigration purposes at HM Prison The Verne.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199157","199157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58444","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the suitability of HM Prison The Verne for detaining individuals for immigration purposes.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199158","199158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58445","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are currently being held in prisons solely under immigration powers.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199159","199159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58446","2014-06-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the ability for individuals detained for immigration purposes at HM Prison The Verne to access (a) legal and (b) health services.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199170","199170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58447","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will hold an inquiry into trends in the number of deaths of individuals detained in immigration detention.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199416","199416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58448","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of removing dedicated funding for local welfare assistance; and if he will review the current local welfare assistance arrangements introduced in 2013 before any such change is made.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199275","199275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58449","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of the operation of (a) section 1 and (b) section 2 of the Warm Homes and Energy Conservation Act 2000; what recent representations he has received on the operation of this Act; and what responses he gave to such representations.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199187","199187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58450","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have had with their counterparts in HM Treasury on the operation of the Warm Homes and Energy Conservation Act 2000; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199186","199186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58451","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many human embryos have been (a) created for the purposes of experimentation and (b) created for the purposes of extermination and subsequently destroyed in each year since 1991.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199195","199195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58452","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which Directorate in his Department produced guidance on the provision of non-judgemental counselling; which Directorate has policy responsibility for implementation of this guidance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199212","199212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58453","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) formal and (b) informal discussions officials had with (i) pro-life organisations, (ii) the British Pregnancy Advisory Service, (iii) Marie Stopes International and (iv) pro-choice organisations before the publication of guidance on the provision of non-judgemental counselling; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199214","199214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58454","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how he plans to mark the 70th anniversary of Raoul Wallenberg's arrival in Hungary; what recent discussions he has had with the government of (a) Sweden and (b) Hungary on this anniversary; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199191","199191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58455","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) males and (b) females of what age group and in which police force area found guilty of an offence under section 14(3) of the Road Traffic Act 1988 opted to attend a driving safety course paid for by the offender that includes instruction on the benefits of wearing seat belts in lieu of a fine in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199213","199213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58456","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) prosecuted for and (b) convicted of failure to return a completed abortion notification form in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199193","199193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58457","2014-06-09","Prime Minister","2014-06-05","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will discuss with the administrators of the Chilcot Inquiry into the Iraq war a final date for publication; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199196","199196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58458","2014-06-09","Prime Minister","2014-06-05","To ask the Prime Minister, what discussions he has had with the (a) Chairman and (b) Secretary of the Chilcot Inquiry on the publication of its report since March 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199188","199188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58459","2014-06-09","Prime Minister","2014-06-05","To ask the Prime Minister, how many documents provided by the Government to the Chilcot Inquiry into the Iraq war have been declassified; how many such documents he estimates will be declassified within the next six months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199185","199185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58460","2014-06-09","Prime Minister","2014-06-05","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent representations (a) he, (b) other Ministers and (c) officials of (i) 10 Downing Street and (ii) the Cabinet Office have made to the (A) Chairman and (B) secretariat of the Chilcot Inquiry on delays in publication of its report due to responses from officials of the US administration; what response was received to these representations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199199","199199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58461","2014-06-09","Prime Minister","2014-06-05","To ask the Prime Minister, when he expects the report of the Chilcot Inquiry into the war in Iraq to be published; what discussions Sir John Chilcot has had with those expected to be criticised in his report; if he will ensure that hon. Members are provided with a full paper copy of the report and all (a) oral and (b) written evidence that was presented to the Chilcot Inquiry into the Iraq war; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199189","199189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58462","2014-06-09","Prime Minister","2014-06-05","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will seek the agreement of the US President to the publication of classified documents by the Chilcot Inquiry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199190","199190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58463","2014-06-09","Prime Minister","2014-06-05","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with the US President on the publication by the Chilcot Inquiry of conversations between (a) Tony Blair and George W. Bush and (b) the right hon. Member for Kirkcaldy and Cowdenbeath and George W. Bush in the period (i) leading up to the conflict in Iraq and (ii) after the invasion of Iraq; what response was received from the President; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199197","199197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58464","2014-06-09","Prime Minister","2014-06-05","To ask the Prime Minister, if it remains his policy to publish the report of the Chilcot Inquiry in full; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199198","199198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58465","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women (a) of each age group, (b) in each health authority area and (c) suffering from each type of complication suffered health complications following abortion procedures in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013 and (iii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199194","199194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58466","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many women (a) of each age group, (b) in each health authority area and (c) of each type of complication and cause of death died following health complications after abortion procedures in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013 and (iii) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199192","199192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58467","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has (a) conducted and (b) evaluated into the circumstances in which a typical abortion is performed on the grounds that it is necessary to prevent the physical or mental health of any existing children of the family of the pregnant woman; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199183","199183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58468","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff of each grade are employed in his Department's Sexual Health Policy Team.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199184","199184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58469","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 16 January 2014, Official Report, column 656W, what change there has been in the proportion of pupils at the end of Key Stage 4 achieving five or more GCSEs or equivalent at grades A*-C including English and maths in those (a) schools and (b) academies that have established a sixth form since September 2011.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199349","199349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58470","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 14 May 2014, Official Report, column 637W, on sixth form education: student numbers, how the approximate total net cost of unfilled student places in school sixth forms, academy sixth forms and 16 to 19 free schools was calculated.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199347","199347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58471","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 14 May 2014, Official Report, column 637W, on sixth form education: student numbers, what these costs were per student.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199348","199348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58472","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in schools in Nuneaton will receive free school meals from 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Jones","Mr Marcus Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199236","199236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58473","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was spent on improvements to the railways in England and Wales in Control Period 4; and what estimate he has made of how much will be spent in Control Period 5.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Jones","Mr Marcus Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199233","199233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58474","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department allocated to projects relating to cycling between (a) 2005 and 2010 and (b) 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Jones","Mr Marcus Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199232","199232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58475","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to ensure proper support and welfare is available to asylum seekers accommodated in hotels and other establishments that provide lodging paid on a short-term basis.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199174","199174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58476","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers were accommodated in (a) hotels and (b) bed and breakfasts, hostels and other establishments that provide lodging paid on a short-term basis in (i) Barnsley, (ii) Yorkshire and Humberside and (iii) the UK in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199171","199171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58477","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been spent from the public purse on accommodating asylum seekers in (a) hotels and (b) bed and breakfasts, hostels and other establishments that provide lodging paid on a short-term basis in each year since May 2010; and how much was spent in each region.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199172","199172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58478","2014-06-10","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure oversight and scrutiny of private contractors responsible for the accommodation of asylum seekers.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199173","199173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58479","2014-06-09","HM Treasury","2014-06-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many internal reports, briefings or analysis papers HM Revenue and Customs has produced on the taxation arrangements for bareboat charters in the oil and gas sector since 2007; and what the findings were of each such report.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199293","199293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58480","2014-06-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average rent is for (a) privately rented homes and (b) new homes built under the Affordable Homes Programme in (i) Warrington and (ii) Warrington North constituency.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199161","199161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58481","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Warrington North constituency received universal credit at any time since the start of the Warrington pilot; and how many were in receipt of it on 1 April 2014.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199162","199162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58482","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many surveillance aircraft with capacity to intercept telephone or other electronic telecommunications his Department operates.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199427","199427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58483","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK service personnel are stationed in Yemen; and what the (a) rank, (b) squadron and (c) function is of each officer stationed in that country.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199426","199426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58484","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any UK service personnel are embedded or otherwise stationed in (a) Ethiopia and (b) Chad.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199425","199425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58485","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of lethal targeting by remotely-piloted air systems on security in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199351","199351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58486","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 473W, on unmanned air vehicles, when the Joint User Group for Reapers will become active; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199415","199415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58487","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has procured any contracts for life cycle maintenance of the Reaper fleet; and for what periods.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199429","199429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58488","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether Joint Services Publication 398 on UK Rules of Engagement has been amended to reflect use of remotely piloted aircraft systems.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199299","199299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58489","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 4 February 2014, Official Report, column 169W, on Djibouti, from which squadron armed forces have been deployed at Camp Lemonnier; and what role is undertaken by each UK officer embedded with US forces at that location.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199424","199424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58490","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 15 January 2014, Official Report, column 578W, on unmanned air vehicles, whether his Department maintains munitions records from the UK Reaper fleet on a sortie-by-sortie basis or for each operation carried out.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199422","199422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58491","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department maintains (a) mission reports, (b) guided missile firing reports, (c) weapon system videos and (d) any other munitions release records for the UK Reaper fleet following the change of operational command to US pilots.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199421","199421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58492","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 25 March 2014, Official Report, column 180W, on Africa, whether any service personnel are embedded with host forces or otherwise stationed in (a) Niger, (b) Nigeria and (c) the Seychelles.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199405","199405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58493","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 10 February 2014, Official Report, column 474, on unmanned air vehicles: guided weapons, if his Department will publish the method and results from the UK-US firing trials of Brimstone missiles from MQ-9 Reaper.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199420","199420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58494","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the advice of Jemima Stratford QC to the All Party Parliamentary Group on Drones; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199350","199350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58495","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the advice of Jemima Stratford QC to the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Drones; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199444","199444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58496","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has provided any advice to public communications providers on the consequences of the decision of the European Court of Justice in Digital Rights Ireland and Seitlinger and Others on data retention by those companies.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199437","199437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58497","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what role the Information Commissioner's Office has in (a) the trial of the Aeroyn Skyranger drone around Gatwick Airport and (b) any other use of other surveillance aircraft operated by Government departments, agents or public bodies in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199439","199439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58498","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what role her Department's Centre for Applied Science and Technology has in (a) the trial of the Aeryon Skyranger drone around Gatwick Airport and (b) the trial or use of any other surveillance aircraft operated by government departments, agents or public bodies in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199440","199440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58499","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether public communications providers have sought advice from her Department on the consequences of the decision of the European Court of Justice in Digital Rights Ireland and Seitlinger and Others on data retention by those companies.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199438","199438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58500","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 6 February 2014, Official Report, column 383W, on Energy Companies Obligation, what progress he has made on publishing proposals on the form, level and date for a new fuel poverty target in England; and when he expects to publish those proposals.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199295","199295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58501","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students received disabled students' allowance in Brighton and Hove local authority area in (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199423","199423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58502","2014-06-10","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people working in (a) HS2 Ltd and (b) his Department are (i) on secondment, (ii) on loan and (iii) paid for by another company; and in each case what the parent company or organisation of such people was.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199305","199305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58503","2014-06-10","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the costs to date has been of the preparation work for the connection of High Speed 2 to High Speed 1.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199307","199307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58504","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department provides to reserve military personnel forced to leave military service as a result of injury sustained in the course of duty.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199237","199237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58505","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the review of personal independence payment operational systems and problems recommended by the National Audit Office in February 2014 was undertaken; what the outcome of the review was; and when it will be published.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199316","199316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58506","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions have been held with HM Treasury about changes in costs of administering the personal independence payment assessment process; what the outcomes of those discussions have been; and how they affect the current Spending Review benefits savings target and the proposed cap on benefit expenditure.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199317","199317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58507","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of current performance towards achieving the target of assessing all current disability living allowance claimants for personal independence payment by 2018; and if he will estimate the potential additional costs in (a) the amount of benefit claimed and (b) the cost of processing claims if the current rate of assessments were to be maintained.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199318","199318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58508","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many organisations hold the Help and Support for Separated Families Mark; and what the total cost to his Department has been of developing, awarding and promoting the mark.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199451","199451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58509","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the Help and Support for Separated Families Co-ordinated Telephone Network started full operation; and which organisations are taking part.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199450","199450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58510","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to his Department has been of implementing and evaluating the Help and Support for Separated Families Co-ordinated Telephone Network to date; and what estimate he has made of the future costs of that initiative.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199452","199452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58511","2014-06-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what funding has been paid from the Help and Support for Separated Families (HSSF) Innovation Fund to each of the HSSF projects which signed contracts for delivery in April 2013.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199449","199449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58512","2014-06-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what specialist one-to-one study skills support will be available for students with specific learning difficulties following the review of the disabled students allowance; and who will provide that support.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199301","199301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58513","2014-06-10","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the changes in the level of access to prostate cancer treatments since 2010.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199302","199302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58514","2014-06-10","Cabinet Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people died from prostate cancer in (a) Plymouth, Sutton and Devonport constituency and (b) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199306","199306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58515","2014-06-10","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what treatments for prostate cancer are routinely funded by NHS England.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199303","199303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58516","2014-06-10","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of outcomes for men with advanced prostate cancer.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199304","199304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58517","2014-06-10","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish a breakdown by firm of expenditure by his Department on (a) consultants and (b) consultancy firms in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199392","199392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58518","2014-06-10","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many passengers used Greenfield station in Greater Manchester in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199383","199383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58519","2014-06-10","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with train operating companies in Greater Manchester on last minute reductions in train configurations.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199384","199384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58520","2014-06-09","HM Treasury","2014-06-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that Natwest and other subsidiaries of RBS remain as competitive as possible in the banking sector.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199219","199219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58521","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 31 March 2014, Official Report, columns 408-9W, on High Speed 2 railway line, whether his Dedpartment has subsequently compared double-decking with revised estimates of the costs and effects of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199261","199261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58522","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 28 April 2014, Official Report, columns 517-8W, on railways: passengers, what the evidential basis is for the stated forecast of increases in passenger numbers on the West Coast Main Line over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199294","199294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58523","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, where the greatest overcrowding on the rail network is; and how High Speed 2 will reduce that overcrowding.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199331","199331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58524","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how he expects High Speed 2 to reduce overcrowding at London Waterloo.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199332","199332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58525","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how High Speed 2 improve reliability and reduce overcrowding on regional links between towns and cities in the North West.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199339","199339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58526","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of people who will move home as a result of the construction of High Speed 2 because of (a) demolition for construction of the line and (b) blight.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199340","199340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58527","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 31 March 2014, Official Report, column 408W, on High Speed 2 Railway Line, what the evidential basis is for the expense and disruption caused by double-decker carriages being greater than that caused by High Speed 2.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199296","199296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58528","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish an updated cost benefit analysis for High Speed 2 in light of the decision not to link High Speed 2 with High Speed 1 and Eurostar services.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199334","199334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58529","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 31 March 2014, Official Report, column 408W, on High Speed 2 Railway Line, what the evidential basis for double-decker carriages not releasing sufficient capacity for commuter services is.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199298","199298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58530","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 31 March 2014, Official Report, column 408W, on High Speed 2 Railway Line, what the evidential basis is for the practical limit to the expansion of capacity on the West Coast Mainline being lower than predicted growth for that line.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199297","199297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58531","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the excess capacity on peak High Speed 2 services.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199333","199333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58532","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what resources his Department has allocated to help carers of dementia patients.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199341","199341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58533","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve standards of NHS care for dementia sufferers.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199335","199335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58534","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many local authorities have signed up to become dementia friendly since the launch of the Dementia Challenge; and what other progress has been made since that date.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199337","199337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58535","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to help Malpas to develop a dementia friendly community.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199338","199338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58536","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funds his Department has provided for research into cures for dementia since 2012; and what progress has been made on such cures since the launch of the Dementia Challenge.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199336","199336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58537","2014-06-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of 2014DIN04-053 Declaration of obsolete-medical, central and veterinary equipments.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199165","199165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58538","2014-06-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of 2014DIN03-010 Impact to outputs of defence electronic warfare center due to five yearly electrical testing.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199166","199166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58539","2014-06-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of 2014DIN05-011 Claims and insurance provisions for the use of Ministry of Defence vehicles in the UK and overseas and the process for ordering new motor insurance certificates or green cards.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199167","199167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58540","2014-06-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of 2014DIN03-007 Notification of a change in CBRN policy.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199168","199168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58541","2014-06-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of 2014DIN04-056 Sea King Helicopter drawdown and disposal.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199169","199169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58542","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether the new protocol to the EU-Morocco Fisheries Partnership Agreement will benefit the Saharawi population or Moroccan settlers.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199435","199435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58543","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of how the ongoing conflict in Western Sahara affects the ability of Al Qaeda to recruit disaffected youth in Western Sahara.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199436","199436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58544","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the Maritime and Coastguard Agency's capacity to discharge its statutory duties to survey and inspect (a) domestic and (b) international shipping.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199365","199365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58545","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) services and (b) jobs within the Passport Office were transferred to the private sector in the last five years; and when those transfers took place.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199369","199369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58546","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to address the current backlog of applications within the Passport Office.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199407","199407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58547","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passport (a) applications and (b) renewal applications were received by the Passport Office in each (i) month and (ii) year of the last five years.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199406","199406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58548","2014-06-10","Department for Transport","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of rail freight access and path allocation over the Welwyn Viaduct beyond January 2018; and what discussions he held with rail freight (a) operators and (b) industry groups regarding future freight access over the Welwyn Viaduct before he approved the InterCity East Coast invitation to tender.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199251","199251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/58549","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will allow universities offering Initial Teacher Training programmes to apply for additional places when they fill their annual allocation.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199362","199362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57602","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are taken to verify the competence of (a) doctors and nurses and (b) staff of pharmaceutical companies involved in the conduct of clinical trials.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198571","198571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57603","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many days of employee absence there were in each Government department in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198582","198582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57604","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average distance is between an onshore windfarm and its connecting sub-station.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198618","198618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57605","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on how many occasions and relating to which locations proposals for overground cables between onshore windfarms and the connecting sub-station have been rejected in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198619","198619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57606","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will take steps to ensure that onshore windfarm developers take into account the costs of (a) overground cables and (b) underground cables between a windfarm and its sub-station when taking decisions on laying such cables.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198614","198614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57607","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether his Department makes funding available for onshore windfarm operators to place cables underground between the windfarm and the connecting sub-station.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198610","198610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57608","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what length of cables between onshore windfarms and connecting sub-stations has been placed (a) above ground and (b) underground in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198611","198611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57609","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many onshore windfarms have been connected to sub-stations in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198612","198612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57610","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, in which locations cables between onshore windfarms and connecting sub-stations have been placed completely underground in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198613","198613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57611","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of potential health risks arising from (a) above-ground and (b) underground electricity cables which connect onshore windfarms to sub-stations.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198609","198609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57612","2014-06-10","Department for Transport","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made by his Department's Justice for Vulnerable Road Users Working Group.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198917","198917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57613","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the recent destruction of fruit trees at the Tent of Nations farm on the West Bank.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198634","198634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57614","2014-06-09","HM Treasury","2014-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding for the extraction of North Sea oil has come from (a) the Government, (b) the Scottish Executive and (c) the private sector in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198595","198595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57615","2014-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what basic measures his Department takes in relation to (a) controls on abstraction and (b) prevent and control pollutants from diffuse sources in order to comply with Article 11.3 of the Water Framework Directive.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198576","198576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57616","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the UK Border Agency's handling of the case of Aidah Asaba.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198569","198569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57617","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to promote human rights in North Korea.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198570","198570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57618","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 6 May 2014, Official Report, column 66W, on asylum: children, which local authorities have been granted extra funding because of their special circumstances.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198606","198606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57619","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 6 May 2014, Official Report, column 66W, on asylum: children, which local authorities have used the fund and how much to support asylum seekers who are care leavers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198605","198605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57620","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 7 May 2014, Official Report, column 222W, on teachers: guidance, if she will place in the Library a copy of the guidance her Department provides to police services as to whether or not to notify arrests to regulators.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198603","198603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57621","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions British passport holders were questioned on return to the UK in regard to problems with their child's name on documentation in the last three years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198584","198584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57622","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department gives on appropriate action to be taken by border staff dealing with a parent with a British passport entering the UK with their child who has a different surname.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198583","198583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57623","2014-06-09","Department for International Development","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will publish a list of all consultancy groups and sub-contractors used by her Department on the Bost Agri-Business and Airfield projects in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198544","198544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57624","2014-06-09","Department for International Development","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what official agreements were made between her Department and the Afghan Investment Support Agency for any work relating to the (a) Bost Agri Industrial Park and (b) Bost Airfield.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198581","198581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57625","2014-06-09","Department for International Development","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Answer of 5 September 2013, Official Report, column 461W, on Afghanistan, what works at the Bost Agri Park and Bost Airfield were left by USAID upon her Department taking control of the project in 2009.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198594","198594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57626","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what records his Department maintains of instances where a teacher has had a sexual relationship with a student under the age of 16 years in (a) maintained schools and (b) independent schools.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198580","198580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57627","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations his Department has received from families groups on allowing the names of parents and legal guardians to be included on a child's passport.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198577","198577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57628","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 6 May 2014, Official Report, columns 59-61W, on private education: offences against children, how many referrals the National College for Teaching and Leadership has (a) received and (b) acted upon since that body's establishment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198607","198607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57629","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 12 May 2014, Official Report, columns 366-7W, on children: databases, what his Department's policy is on sharing information in respect of vulnerable children and children at risk.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198604","198604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57630","2014-06-09","HM Treasury","2014-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many homes in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Birmingham have been bought under the Help to Buy mortgage guarantee scheme to date.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198626","198626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57631","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to research the use of non-slip surfaces for man-holes in order to reduce the number of accidents involving motor cycles.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198631","198631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57632","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what scientific purposes she has licensed procedures on animals that were likely to cause severe suffering since 2010; and what steps the Government is taking to reduce the number of animals experiencing severe suffering in scientific procedures.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198600","198600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57633","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she will measure changes in the number of animals used in scientific procedures in the UK following publication of Working to reduce the use of animals in scientific research in July 2011.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198633","198633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57634","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many animals have experienced severe suffering in scientific research funded by the Government since 2010; and if he will provide funding aimed at developing scientific advances allowing the reduction or avoidance of severe suffering of animals used in procedures.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198601","198601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57635","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support people affected by recent flooding in the Balkans","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198545","198545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57636","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on treating (a) anal cancer, (b) penile cancer, (c) cervical cancer, (d) vaginal cancer, (e) vulval cancer, (f) oropharyngeal cancer, (g) genital warts and (h) recurrent respiratory papillomatosis in the last year.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198632","198632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57637","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much core grant was provided to fund Victim Support services in the (a) Crown Court Witness Service and (b) Magistrates' Court Witness Service in North Yorkshire in each year since 2004-05.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198526","198526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57638","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent on (a) civil and (b) criminal legal aid in (i) cash and (ii) real terms in (A) England and (B) York in each year since 1995.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198527","198527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57639","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people with cases before (a) civil and (b) criminal courts received legal aid in (i) England and (ii) York in each year since 1995.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198528","198528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57640","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victims of crime and witnesses were supported by the Witness Service at (a) York Crown Court and (b) York Magistrages' Court in each year since 2004-05.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198529","198529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57641","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many custodial sentences were handed down at (a) York Magristrates' Court and (b) York Crown Court in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198530","198530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57642","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much revenue funding her Department has allocated to the North Yorkshire Police Authority in (a) cash and (b) real terms in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198504","198504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57643","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time equivalent police officers of each rank and grade were employed by North Yorkshire police on (a) 31 March and (b) 30 September in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198505","198505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57644","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time equivalent (a) police officers, (b) police community support officers and (c) police civilian staff were employed by North Yorkshire police on (i) 31 March and (ii) 30 September in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198506","198506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57645","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the crime detection rate was for North Yorkshire police force in each year since 2004-05.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198507","198507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57646","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many offences of (a) crime related to vehicles, (b) burglary of a dwelling, (c) other burglary, (d) criminal damage, (e) theft, (f) violence and (g) other crimes were committed in York in each year since 2004-05.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198508","198508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57647","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many crimes were reported to the police in York in each year since 2004-05.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198509","198509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57648","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate the UK Statistics Authority has made of the number of (a) men and (b) women who were employed (i) full-time and (ii) part-time in York Central constituency for the 12-month Annual Population Survey periods ending in September in each year since the inception of the survey.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198531","198531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57649","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate the UK Statistics Authority has made of the median gross weekly earnings of (a) men, (b) women and (c) all people employed (i) full-time and (ii) part-time in the areas covered by (A) York travel to work area, (B) City of York local authority area and (C) York Central constituency (1) in cash terms and (2) at constant prices in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198532","198532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57650","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average weekly gross earnings of full-time (a) men, (b) women and (c) people in York has been in (i) cash terms and (ii) at constant prices in each year since 2006-07.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198533","198533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57651","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate the UK Statistics Authority has made of average net weekly household income in the City of York Council area in each year since 2004-05 in (i) cash terms and (ii) at current prices.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198534","198534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57652","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths there were from (a) drug poisoning and (b) drug misuse in (i) York local authority area, (ii) North Yorkshire and York Primary Care Trust, (iii) Vale of York Clinical Commissioning Group area and (iv) England in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198535","198535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57653","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many full-time equivalent civil servants of each Department or Executive Agency were employed in (a) the City of York and (b) the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs central science laboratory at Sand Hutton on 31 March in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198536","198536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57654","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many businesses there were in City of York local authority area in each year since 2001.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198537","198537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57655","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding has been allocted to (a) York College and (b) Askham Bryan College by the Skills Funding Agency and the Young People's Learning Agency in (i) cash and (ii) real terms in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198510","198510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57656","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate the UK Statistics Authority has made of the number and proportion of young people aged 16 to 24 in York in (a) training, (b) employment and (c) education in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198511","198511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57657","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many young people from (a) York Central constituency and (b) City of York local authority area (i) applied for and (ii) started a degree course in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198512","198512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57658","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much capital funding the Government allocated to (a) York College, (b) Askham Bryan College, (c) the University of York and (d) York St John University in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198513","198513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57659","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding for each (a) undergraduate and (b) postgraduate student the Higher Education Funding Council for England allocated to (i) the University of York and (ii) York St John University in (A) cash and (B) at current prices in each year since 1997-98.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198514","198514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57660","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many applications for undergaduate study were made to (a) the University of York, (b) York St John University and (c) all English universities in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198515","198515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57661","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many business start-ups there were in City of York local authority area in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198516","198516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57662","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in Yorkshire and the Humber were exporting to (a) the EU and (b) all countries in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198517","198517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57663","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many bankruptcies were registered in (a) York, (b) Yorkshire and (c) England in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198518","198518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57664","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much foreign investment in Yorkshire and the Humber there has been in each year since 2008; and what estimate he has made of the number of (a) new and (b) safeguarded jobs generated by such investments.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198519","198519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57665","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) York Central constituency and (b) City of York local authority area were claiming jobseeker's allowance per Jobcentre Plus vacancy in each year since May 2007.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198520","198520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57666","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many young people (a) started and (b) completed apprenticeships in (i) York Central constituency, (ii) York local education authority, (iii) Yorkshire and the Humber and (iv) England in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198521","198521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57667","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in Yorkshire and the Humber received how much funding from the Regional Growth Fund in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198522","198522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57668","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in Yorkshire and the Humber received how much funding from the Yorkshire Regional Development Agency in each year that body was in existence.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198523","198523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57669","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses in Yorkshire and the Humber received how much funding from Local Enterprise Partnerships in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198524","198524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57670","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many UK-domiciled (a) undergraduate and (b) postgraduate students enrolled at the (i) University of York and (ii) University of York St John in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198525","198525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57671","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 10 April 2013, Official Report, column 1119W, on energy prices, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) wholesale and (b) retail cost of (i) electricity and (ii) gas in 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198625","198625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57672","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 10 April 2013, Official Report, column 1119W, on energy prices, what estimate his Department has made of changes to the wholesale cost of (a) electricity and (b) gas in (i) 2013 and (ii) January to May 2014.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198624","198624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57673","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise the release of political prisoners in Eritrea with his Eritrean counterpart.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198578","198578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57674","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss sexual violence against women in India with his Indian counterpart.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198579","198579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57675","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase the manufacture of electronic components in the UK.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198575","198575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57676","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much public interest lawyers have received in legal aid for cases against the Department for Work and Pensions in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198669","198669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57677","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of applicants from the Borough of Warrington passed their driving test in each year since 2007.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198615","198615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57678","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many approved driving instructors were registered in the Borough of Warrington in each year since 2007.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198608","198608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57679","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for citizenship were made in each year since 2009 from males recruited into the armed forces from Belize; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198550","198550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57680","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many foreign and Commonwealth personnel from each country of origin who were made redundant from the armed forces in each year since 2010 were subsequently unable to meet the five-year rule to apply for citizenship; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198549","198549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57681","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the killing of two Palestinian teenagers at Ofer on 15 May 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Love","Mr Andrew Love","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198596","198596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57682","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many workplace capability assessments have been passed from his Department to Atos for processing in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198555","198555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57683","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many workplace capability assessments have been processed by Atos within 35 working days to date.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198556","198556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57684","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the current actual average clearance time is for a workplace capability assessment.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198557","198557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57685","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what penalties his Department is able to levy on workplace capability assessment providers who miss targets.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198558","198558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57686","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many workplace capability assessments have been submitted to Atos, processed and returned within 35 working days in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) West Lothian local authority area in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198559","198559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57687","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to improve job security for people employed indefinitely on temporary or fixed-term contracts.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198616","198616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57688","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of people on (a) temporary and (b) fixed-term contracts in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198617","198617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57689","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions the Prime Minister has had with the US President and others on the release of the files held by Boston College relating to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198589","198589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57690","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on human rights abuses in Tibet.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198551","198551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57691","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has received from (a) the Tibetan government in exile and (b) human rights charities on human rights abuses in that country.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198552","198552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57692","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce human rights abuses in Tibet and to offer support for victims of such abuses.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198554","198554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57693","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Nigerian counterpart on the abduction of schoolgirls in Chibok, Nigeria.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198588","198588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57694","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on Tibetan independence.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198590","198590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57695","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent meetings he has had with NHS England on the contracting of provision of television services in hospitals.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198561","198561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57696","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients resident in England but receiving health care in Wales have requested that their treatment be delivered in England in the last year.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198553","198553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57697","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients resident in England have requested that their treatment be delivered in Wales in the last three years.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198560","198560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57698","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of women in Pendle were in work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198562","198562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57699","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will issue a statement cautioning UK businesses against investing in Moroccan-occupied Western Sahara.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198630","198630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57700","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will instruct UK Trade and Investment to issue a statement cautioning UK businesses against trade and investment in Moroccan-occupied Western Sahara.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198629","198629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57701","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 7 May 2014, Official Report, column 230W, on abortion, whether his Department has formed a view as to when the Royal college of Gynaecologists and Obstetricians publication, The Care of Women Requesting Induced Abortion, should be updated in order to take into account new research; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198620","198620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57702","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital beds per head of population there were in (a) Bury St Edmunds, (b) Suffolk and (c) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198567","198567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57703","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were arrested and charged with possession of class (a) A, (b) B and (c) C drugs in (i) Bury St Edmunds, (ii) Suffolk and (iii) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198565","198565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57704","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of working time police officers in each police force spent on frontline policing duties in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198566","198566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57705","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent on housing benefit in (a) Bury St Edmunds, (b) Suffolk and (c) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198592","198592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57706","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many persistent young offenders were registered in (a) Bury St Edmunds, (b) Suffolk and (c) England and Wales in each of the last five years; and how many and what proportion of total offences were attributable to such offenders in that period.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198564","198564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57707","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has allocated to each local authority in the East of England for road improvement in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198593","198593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57708","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many undergraduate students were resident in (a) Bury St Edmunds, (b) Suffolk and (c) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198591","198591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57709","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free early years education places were provided in (a) Bury St Edmunds, (b) Suffolk and (c) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198568","198568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57710","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what change there was in the number of homelessness acceptances arising from the end of a private sector tenancy in (a) Bury St Edmunds, (b) Suffolk and (c) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198572","198572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57711","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the cost was of translation and interpreter services used by each borough and county council in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198563","198563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57712","2014-06-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations his Department has received from UNESCO on the proposed Navitus Bay Wind Farm development.","Biography information for Conor Burns","Conor Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198602","198602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57713","2014-06-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions have taken place under the Cancer Act 1939 in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198623","198623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57714","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the adequacy of the sentences available under the Cancer Act 1939 for people convicted of fraudulently advertising offers to treat cancer.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198621","198621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57715","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to raise the plight of persecuted Christians abroad; and what steps he is taking to raise the case of Meriam Ibrahim with his Sudanese counterpart.","Biography information for Guy Opperman","Guy Opperman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198585","198585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57716","2014-06-09","Department for Education","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much in pupil premium has been paid to (a) first, (b) middle and (c) upper schools in (i) Hexham, (ii) Northumberland and (iii) the North East to date.","Biography information for Guy Opperman","Guy Opperman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198548","198548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57717","2014-06-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many people in Warrington North constituency are currently in receipt of a free television licence.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198622","198622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57718","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the advice provided by Jemima Stratford QC to the All-Party Parliamentary Group on drones, if his Department will take steps to investigate activities carried out at US bases owned by his Department which may be unlawful under domestic law.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198639","198639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57719","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 30 January 2014, Official Report, column 691W, on Yemen, whether his Department has undertaken any impact assessment of drone strikes in Yemen.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198640","198640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57720","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had with its US counterpart on identifying how the US will support the new Joint User Group for Reaper.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198641","198641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57721","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where his Department plans to base the Watchkeeper remotely piloted air systems following completion of training at Salisbury Plain and West Wales Airport.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198643","198643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57722","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will carry out an independent qualitative assessment of the psychological and workplace stresses on the operators of remotely piloted air systems.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198644","198644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57723","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the advice provided by Jemima Stratford QC to the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Drones, if he will agree a new Memorandum of Understanding or other bilateral agreement with the US on data transfer and use.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198638","198638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57724","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the advice provided by Jemima Stratford QC to the All-Party Parliamentary Group on Drones, if her Department will take steps to prevent any unlawful practice by GCHQ.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198637","198637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57725","2014-06-09","Department for International Development","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of lethal operations in Yemen on (a) the civilian population and (b) security in that country.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198642","198642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57726","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of the potential need for additional gas storage capacity in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198546","198546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57727","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to reassess the need for additional gas storage capacity in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198547","198547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57728","2014-06-09","Department for Transport","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of changing the national urban default speed limit to 20 mph on (a) air pollution and (b) other environmental conditions; what similar studies in other developed nations his Department has assessed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198586","198586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57729","2014-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Answer given in the House of Lords of 28 October 2013, Official Report, column 208W, on Agriculture: Pesticides, if he will place in the Library a list of the (a) published research being considered by the current review of the EU approval of glyphosate and (b) ongoing or completed research relating to potential links between glyphosate and chronic diseases and conditions in humans.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198628","198628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57730","2014-06-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance he has issued on the use of glyphosate to (a) national park authorities and (b) managers of public parks in urban areas; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198627","198627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57731","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether (a) he and (b) other Ministers in his Department will be attending the high-level Ministerial Dialogue on the Durban Platform for Enhanced Action on 6 June 2014 in Bonn, Germany; what the Government's aims are in such talks; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198587","198587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57732","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what mechanisms are in place to allow an investigation into an allegation that an individual Minister may have breached the Ministerial Code of Conduct during their time in office when that Minister is no longer a serving Minister; who is responsible for initiating such an investigation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198573","198573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57733","2014-06-09","Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will attend the global leaders Climate Summit in September 2014 in New York; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198574","198574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57734","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Community Work Placement providers schemes (a) were operating  by 28 April 2014, (b) were operating no later than 2 June 2014 and (c) are yet to commence; for what reasons any providers have breached of the 2 June 2014 commencement deadline; at what capacity the scheme is currently running; and when he estimates that the scheme will be fully operational (i) in Brighton and Hove Local Authority Area and (ii) nationally.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198636","198636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57735","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time taken for decisions on requests for reconsideration of fit for work decisions in relation to applications for employment and support allowance has been since October 2013.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198668","198668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57736","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer to the hon. Member for Rutherglen and Hamilton West of 21 March 2012, Official Report, column 705W on Atos Healthcare, on how many occasions a Jobcentre Plus decision-maker did not follow the advice of an Atos-approved healthcare professional when making a decision on the eligibility for employment and support allowance in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198542","198542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57737","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have successfully appealed refusals of employment and support allowance as part of (a) the periodic reassessment of existing employment and support allowance claimants and (b) the reassessment of those in receipt of incapacity benefit, severe disablement allowance and income support.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198543","198543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57738","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what criteria his Department uses to assess the saleability of new houses when determining the potential for five-year housing supply.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198538","198538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57739","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what account he takes of local referendums on the desirability of specific sites being allocated to new housing.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198539","198539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57740","2014-06-18","Department for Transport","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many vehicles built by Nissan are in the Government car pool.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198961","198961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57741","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual cost to the public purse is of processing applications for free social care in England.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198598","198598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57742","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications for free social care were (a) approved and (b) rejected in England in (i) 2012 and (ii) 2013.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198599","198599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57743","2014-06-09","Department of Health","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate his Department has made of the cost of administering the social care means test in England.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198597","198597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57744","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the new Indian government to reopen investigations on the events in 1984 at the Golden Temple in Amritsar; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198540","198540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57745","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will support an international enquiry into the events at the Golden Temple in Amritsar in 1984.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198541","198541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57746","2014-06-09","Home Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her statement of 30 April 2014, Official Report, column 831, on Stop-and-Search, which police forces have signed up to the revised code on stop-and-search to date.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198635","198635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57747","2014-06-18","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential costs and benefits of bringing forward legislative proposals similar to those in the US Servicemen's Readjustment Act 1944.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198839","198839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57748","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans his Department has to provide assistance to people with cold-related health conditions who are struggling to pay their heating bills.","Biography information for Sir Robert Smith","Sir Robert Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198929","198929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57749","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on support for people in fuel poverty who suffer from cold-related health conditions.","Biography information for Sir Robert Smith","Sir Robert Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198976","198976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57750","2014-06-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information has been provided to his Department by (a) EDF Energy and (b) the Office for Nuclear Regulation on the application by EDF Energy to extend the operating life of the Dungeness B reactor.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198936","198936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57751","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what analysis has been carried out by the Atomic Weapons Establishment at Aldermaston into the effects on (a) human beings, (b) other animals and (c) the wider environment of the use of a nuclear warhead in the UK nuclear arsenal.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198935","198935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57752","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of when the Afghanistan Air Force will be ready to function independently of US and UK support.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199016","199016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57753","2014-06-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of the Afghanistan National Army has deserted in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199017","199017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57754","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what benefits he expects to accrue to the UK economy from the agreement signed in China on 26 May 2014 between the Building Research Establishment and the Shenzhen Municipal Government to set up a training and research and development centre on sustainable building construction in China.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198981","198981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57755","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much (a) military and (b) humanitarian aid the UK provided to the Libyan government in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199015","199015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57756","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of MINURSO in implementing its role in Western Sahara.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199050","199050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57757","2014-06-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of changes in the number of Moroccan troops along the Berm in Western Sahara from the levels specified in the 1991 agreement.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199052","199052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57758","2014-06-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) net and (b) gross administration charges for the national insurance pension scheme were in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199014","199014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57759","2014-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what use his Department has made of the National Wellbeing Index introduced by the Office for National Statistics in formulating policy since the introduction of that Index in 2011; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national wellbeing as defined in that Index since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198862","198862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57760","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what use his Department has made of the National Wellbeing Index introduced by the Office for National Statistics in formulating policy since the introduction of that Index in 2011; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national wellbeing as defined in that Index since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198863","198863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57761","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what (a) subjective and (b) objective measures the Office for National Statistics uses to measure public wellbeing; and whether that Office is considering any changes to those measures.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198857","198857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57762","2014-06-09","HM Treasury","2014-06-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what use his Department has made of the National Wellbeing Index introduced by the Office for National Statistics in formulating policy since the introduction of that Index in 2011; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national wellbeing as defined in that Index since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198873","198873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57763","2014-06-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what use his Department has made of the National Wellbeing Index introduced by the Office for National Statistics in formulating policy since the introduction of that Index in 2011; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national wellbeing as defined in that Index since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198865","198865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57764","2014-06-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-06-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what use his Department has made of the National Wellbeing Index introduced by the Office for National Statistics in formulating policy since the introduction of that Index in 2011; and what policies his Department has introduced to improve national wellbeing as defined in that Index since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198864","198864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57765","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the use in Northern Ireland of prize draws to increase voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198963","198963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57766","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps he is taking to disseminate the lessons learned from the data mining pilots for the introduction of individual electoral  registrations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198972","198972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57767","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with (a) church and community leaders from black and minority ethnic communities and (b) Operation Black Vote on increasing registration levels for voters in those communities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198964","198964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57768","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether monies collected from fixed penalty notices issued for failure to register on the electoral register will be retained by the local authority which issues that notice.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198967","198967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57769","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, when electoral registration officers will be able to impose fixed penalty notices for non-registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198968","198968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57770","2014-06-09","Cabinet Office","2014-06-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of people eligible to be on the most recent (a) census and (b) electoral register who were not recorded.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198969","198969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57771","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to provide that the freeze dates for population size for boundary reviews and the census be in the same year.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198970","198970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57772","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with reference to the Answer of 20 May 2013, Official Report, column 443W, on electoral register, what the results were of his Department's cooperation with data holding organisations on datasets that can be used to ensure completeness and accuracy of the electoral register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199000","199000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57773","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what training has been given to electoral registration officers in the implementation of fixed penalty notices for non-registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198971","198971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57774","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment  he has made of the introduction of individual electoral registration in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 198973","198973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57775","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with reference to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 387W, on electoral register, what estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of gathering and holding information on the proportion of attainers who are registered to vote; and what assessment he has made of the usefulness of such information for improving the introduction of individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199037","199037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57776","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with reference to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, columns 509-10W, on electoral registration, whether his Department provides funding to Bite the Ballot to increase voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199047","199047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/57777","2014-06-09","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-06-04","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with reference to the Answer of 23 April 2012, Official Report, column 623W, on electoral register, what steps he has taken to improve student registration in the run up to individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 199048","199048"
