"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756677","2017-09-06","Cabinet Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to respond to Law Commission Electoral Law: An Interim Report, published in February 2016; and whether the Government plans to implement the Law Commission's recommendations to bring forward legislative proposals for a single Electoral Administration Act.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7725","7725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756678","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions the Government has had with the Council of Europe on the ruling of the European Court of Human Rights that a blanket ban against prisoner voting contravenes Article 3 of Protocol No. 1 of the European Convention on Human Rights.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7704","7704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756679","2017-09-06","Cabinet Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that university governing bodies in England cooperate with electoral registration officers in local councils as required under section 13 of the Higher Education and Research Act 2017; and whether he plans to extend that statutory duty to (a) secondary schools and (b) further education institutions.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7705","7705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756680","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 23 February 2016 to HL6056, what progress the Government has made on implementing new regulations governing the conduct of parish polls; when the Government plans to publish the outcome of the Parish polls: consultation on the government's intentions to modernise parish poll regulations which concluded in 2014; and for what reasons a response to that consultation has not been published.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7727","7727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756681","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions the Government has had with the BBC on broadcasting parliamentary proceedings on the radio.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7716","7716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756682","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that European Social Fund projects for training young people from disadvantaged groups and communities continue after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7720","7720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756683","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when the Government plans to respond to the Public Accounts Committee report of 14 March 2017, National Citizen Service, HC955, Session 2016-17; and what the reason is for the time taken so far to respond to that report.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7717","7717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756684","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when the Government plans to report on its review into full-time youth volunteering; and what the reason is for the time taken to publish that report.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7718","7718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756685","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what her policy is on targeting recruitment of new board members for the National Citizen Service at young people; and when the next recruitment of board members for that service is due to take place.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7719","7719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756686","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether it is the Government's policy to deliver a three year youth policy statement; when she plans to announce her priorities and plans for youth policy; and what the reason is for the time taken for the Government to deliver that statement.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7728","7728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756687","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the role of youth work in combating radicalisation.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7714","7714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756688","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with which Minister of her Department the brief for youth policy, the National Citizen Service and the UK Youth Parliament lies; when the Government plans to publish the terms of reference and timetable for its review of youth policy; and whether the reduction in the number of Ministers in her Department has had an effect on the number of civil servants in her Department.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7715","7715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756689","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been prosecuted for perjury in the family court in each year since 2007, by gender.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7869","7869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756690","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to increase the level of transparency of the Construction Industry Training Board's administration of levy income and grants.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7592","7592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756691","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to create more conservation areas across London.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8261","8261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756692","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average wait time is for personal independence payment appeals to be heard by the Courts and Tribunals Service.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7868","7868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756693","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department plans for UK membership of the CEN and CENELEC committees after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8266","8266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756694","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the UK will continue to mandate the use of the CE mark for goods sold in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8264","8264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756695","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to stop the sale of counterfeit toys online.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8265","8265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756696","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people over retirement age in receipt of disability living allowance have been called in for a review in the last four years.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8165","8165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756697","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people over state retirement age have applied for personal independence payments; and how many of those people are now in receipt of that benefit.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8166","8166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756698","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that contractors working in the construction industry are in possession of all appropriate licenses before being allowed to operate in public areas and walkways.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8262","8262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756699","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to improve health and safety standards and risk assessment processes on contractors working in the construction industry when drawing up construction plans.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8263","8263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756700","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to replace funding from the European Social Fund for employment programmes after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7888","7888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756701","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to undertake a new universal credit satisfaction survey in roll-out areas.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7847","7847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756702","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how his Department monitors claimant commitment obligations placed on disabled people to ensure that they are reasonable obligations.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7857","7857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756703","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the effect has been of changes in the timetable for introducing supported housing funding on the availability of new accommodation.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7867","7867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756704","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that businesses affected by terrorism do not experience unnecessary delays in receiving payments from insurance providers.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7889","7889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756705","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to prevent food poverty and the use of foodbanks.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7602","7602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756706","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the estimated annual cost to the Government is for (a) maintenance and (b) operations of the Severn Crossings after they return to public ownership.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7550","7550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756707","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding will be put in place to stop the spread of TB in cattle after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr  Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7560","7560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756708","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what risk assessment East Sussex Healthcare NHS Trust carried out on perinatal and other maternity-related deaths before removing consultant-led maternity services from that Trust area.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7564","7564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756709","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what risk assessment East Sussex Healthcare NHS Trust carried out on the implications of potentially longer travel time resulting from the move of consultant-led maternity services to Hastings for the health of mothers and pre-born or new-born babies.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7780","7780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756710","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will assess the feasibility of raising the maximum sanction to five years in prison for animal cruelty sentences in England and Wales to align sentences with Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7598","7598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756711","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the 25 Year Environment Plan will include measures to help manage the UK's impact on the environment in other countries through the products it imports.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7829","7829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756712","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of banning the landing of bass by fixed nets on reducing the incidence of accidental catching of those fish.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8441","8441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756713","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to review the acceptable levels of exposure to radiofrequency radiation from mobile telephone base stations.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8421","8421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756714","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Yemen.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8442","8442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756715","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to ensure that local authorities have adequate funds to maintain their local libraries.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7808","7808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756716","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2017 to Question 4449, if the Government will make an assessment of the merits of bringing forward legislative proposals on installing automatic fire suppression systems in all new residential premises, student accommodation and nurse's houses, including buildings under 30 metres.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7807","7807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756717","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with Scottish farming stakeholders on the adequacy of the Common Agricultural Policy's set-aside policy; and how any successor programme will take cognisance of (a) Scottish land topography and (b) the standard farm in Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7814","7814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756718","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with Scottish farming stakeholders on the practicality of the Common Agricultural Policy's three crop policy; and how any successor programme will take cognisance of existing Scottish farm land bio diversity.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7813","7813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756719","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what advice his Department has given the Welsh Government on whether financial guarantees provided by the Welsh Government to the Circuit of Wales project should be considered on-balance sheet expenditure.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7610","7610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756720","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the Consumer Prices Index rate of inflation.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8132","8132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756721","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department made to the Welsh Government on the transfer of functions necessary to procure the next Wales and Borders rail franchise before the end of the existing franchise agreement.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7872","7872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756722","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department received from the Welsh Government on the transfer of functions necessary to procure the next Wales and Borders rail franchise before the end of the existing franchise agreement.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7871","7871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756723","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the Pound to Euro exchange rate.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7690","7690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756724","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the Pound to US Dollar exchange rate.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7691","7691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756725","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the Consumer Price Index rate of inflation.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7692","7692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756726","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many fire fighters have developed cancer in the first 10 years after retirement since 1967.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7823","7823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756727","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a position paper on the future of HM Revenue and Customs after the UK leaves the EU and its role in investigating tax avoidance by multinational corporations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7874","7874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756728","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the salary is of the (a) highest and (b) lowest-paid employee of the Bank of England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7841","7841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756729","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment has been undertaken of the effect of the creation of Heathrow's third runway and the upgrade to the runway at RAF Northolt will have on airspace capacity in West London; and whether Heathrow's third runway creation will reduce the ability to operate flights from RAF Northolt.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7825","7825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756730","2017-09-07","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if the UK will continue to fund the European Commission's Humanitarian Aid and Civil Protection department after the UK leaves the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7875","7875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756731","2017-09-07","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to publish a position paper on the future of British development assistance after the UK leaves the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7876","7876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756732","2017-09-07","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much each Commonwealth country receives from the EU Development Fund; whether the UK will continue to pay into the EU Development Fund after the UK leaves the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7873","7873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756733","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will provide a holiday on employers' national insurance contributions for a full year for (a) those with a disability, (b) those with chronic mental health problems, (c) ex-offenders, (d) those unemployed for a year or more, (e) care leavers and (f) veterans.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7734","7734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756734","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the total cost to (a) the economy, (b) government revenue and (c) public services of unemployment among (i) people with a disability, (ii) people with chronic mental health problems, (iii) ex-offenders, (iv) people who have been unemployed for a year or more, (v) care leavers and (vi) veterans.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7735","7735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756735","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of processes within NHS mental health trusts for monitoring whether patients have been offered NICE-recommended psychological therapies.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7736","7736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756736","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on patient safety of exceeding the average bed occupancy rate recommended by the Royal College of Psychiatrists.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8405","8405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756737","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 1.86 of the Autumn Statement 2014, how much of the £150 million made available for child and adolescent eating disorder services has been allocated to each clinical commissioning group for 2017-18.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8231","8231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756738","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what implications the findings of the research study, Do English mental health services know whether they followed NICE treatment recommendations for depression with patients who killed themselves, published in the scientific journal Psychology and Psychotherapy in July 2017, have on his policy; and what steps he plans to take as a result of its conclusions and recommendations of that report.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8227","8227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756739","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of people who are self-employed who have a disability.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7739","7739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756740","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to provide incentives for employers to employ people from hard-to-reach groups.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7738","7738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756741","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to respond to its consultation on the Work, Health and Disability Green Paper; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8129","8129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756742","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of people with a disability who are (a) employed, (b) inactive in the labour market and (c) unemployed; and what proportion of those people employed in (i) large businesses, (ii) medium-sized businesses and (iii) small businesses have a disability.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7733","7733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756743","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on businesses of inactivity in the labour market among people who have a (a) disability and (b) chronic mental health condition.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7737","7737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756744","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment has been made of the extent to which the UK's immigration rules on adopted children (a) meet obligations under the Hague Adoption Convention and (b) adequately support families with adopted children within the visa system.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7782","7782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756745","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of the £5.48 email receipt charge levied on emails to UK Visas and Immigration from outside the UK will represent a return to the public purse.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7783","7783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756746","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment has been made of the effect of the new visa application email charges on the level of tourism in Summer 2017 in comparison to the last five years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7784","7784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756747","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visa applications have been received since 30 May 2017 from people who cannot use services in the eight languages offered but who would have had services available to them in their languages before 1 June 2017.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7785","7785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756748","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect on access to UK Visas and Immigration's services of its new charges of £5.48 per email received from overseas for certain visa applications.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7774","7774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756749","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will ensure that PhD students will be eligible for 30-hours free childcare.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7551","7551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756750","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) male and (b) female prisoners who have been identified with mental health issues (i) have been subsequently moved to a secure mental health hospital, (ii) are still in the prison where those issues were identified, (iii) have moved prison and (iv) have been moved to a bail hostel in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8137","8137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756751","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what programmes his Department has operated in prisons for drug rehabilitation in each year since 2010 broken down by (a) budget, (b) number of male and female prisoners who used the programme and (c) location of prison.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8130","8130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756752","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent by his Department on drug rehabilitation for (a) men and (b) women in prisons in (i) England and (ii) Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8136","8136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756753","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been allocated to learndirect Ltd from the Adult Education budget between 1 November 2017 and 31 July 2018.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8411","8411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756754","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons learndirect Ltd is being permitted to recruit additional adult education learners in the light of its Grade 4 assessment by Ofsted.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8412","8412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756755","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding from the Adult Education budget was requested by learndirect Ltd for 2017-18.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8409","8409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756756","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department allocated to learndirect Ltd from the Adult Education budget between 1 August and 31 October 2017.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8410","8410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756757","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Government's policy is on the application of the derogation in Article 1 (4) of Regulation (EC) No. 1071/2009 for community transport operators which have a main occupation other than that of road passenger transport operator to operate vehicles under section 19 or 22 permit to parish and town councils.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7836","7836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756758","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of the effect of the level for funding Greater Manchester Police in 2016-17 and 2017-18 on its ability to respond to all reported crimes in Salford and Eccles constituency.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8182","8182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756759","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of any correlation between levels of crime and the number of police in Salford and Eccles constituency.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8181","8181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756760","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the types of incidents police have provided an immediate response to in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18; and whether there has been any change in the ability of the police to respond to crimes such as burglary, shoplifting and anti-social behaviour.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8275","8275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756761","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the adequacy of rehabilitation and support services available to people leaving prison in Greater Manchester for the last two years.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8183","8183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756762","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment assessment appeals were taken to the tribunal stage in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18 to date.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8151","8151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756763","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment assessment decisions were (a) overturned as a result of an appeal tribunal and (b) maintained in (i) 2016-17 and (ii) 2017-18 to date.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8150","8150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756764","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Salford and Eccles constituency had personal independence payment awards reduced or removed in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18 to date as a result of reassessment.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8152","8152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756765","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's paper, Corporate Governance Reform, published on 29 August 2017, whether companies will be required to make a full disclosure of executive bonus payments and how they are paid.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8197","8197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756766","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's paper, Corporate Governance Reform, published on 29 August 2017, whether the publication of pay multiples will apply solely to the CEO of a company.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8198","8198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756767","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's paper, Corporate Governance Reform, published on 29 August 2017, whether annual pay ratio reporting will require the reporting of exact pay and remuneration.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8199","8199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756768","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 42 of the Government's paper Corporate Governance Reform published on 29 August 2017, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to require companies to disclose their corporate governance arrangements.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8176","8176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756769","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's paper Corporate Governance Reform published on 29 August 2017, what plans he has to require companies to accept recommendations from an employee advisory council.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8177","8177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756770","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 20 of the Government's paper Corporate Governance Reform published on 29 August 2017, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to require quoted companies to report the ratio of CEO pay to the average pay of their UK workforce.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8178","8178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756771","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 1.6 of the Government's paper Corporate Governance Reform published on 29 August 2017, how many and what proportion of the respondents that supported an annual binding vote on remuneration were trade unions.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8179","8179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756772","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 1.7 of the Government's paper Corporate Governance Reform published on 29 August 2017, how many and what proportion of the respondents that supported options (iii) and (iv) were trade unions.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8180","8180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756773","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's paper, Corporate Governance Reform, published on 29 August 2017, what representations he has received on the proposal for the Investment Association to maintain a public register of listed companies that experience shareholder opposition to pay awards.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8196","8196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756774","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's paper Corporate Governance Reform published on 29 August 2017, how many meetings he or ministers of his Department had with representative of trade unions during the preparation of that paper.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8172","8172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756775","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government's paper Corporate Governance Reform published on 29 August 2017, for what reason the Financial Conduct Authority will not maintain a register of listed companies that experienced shareholder opposition to pay awards.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8173","8173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756776","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 4 of the Government's paper Corporate Governance Reform published on 29 August 2017, whether he has assessed the potential effect of a designated non-executive director on strengthening the voice of employee influence.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8174","8174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756777","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if it is the Government's policy to bring forward legislative proposals to introduce an energy price cap.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8175","8175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756778","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether legislation is required to implement the Government's proposed cap on household energy prices.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8440","8440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756779","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the performance indicators are which he has agreed with National Savings and Investments for the delivery of tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7777","7777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756780","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many parents have successfully signed up for (a) 30-hours free childcare, (b) tax-free childcare and (c) both 30-hours free childcare and tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7789","7789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756781","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations her Department has received on the Open University's refusal to accept students from Cuba.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7842","7842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756782","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to review the driving test after the UK leaves the EU and is no longer subject to the European Driving Licence Directive.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7805","7805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756783","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to introduce a mandatory element to the driving test on driving safely in the presence of heavy goods vehicles.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7804","7804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756784","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether animal testing is conducted at Porton Down.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7776","7776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756785","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will prohibit animal testing at his Department's facilities.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7866","7866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756786","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the amount of resources from the foreign aid budget that will be allocated to projects in Burma in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018; and if she will list those projects.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8284","8284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756787","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding from the foreign aid budget was allocated to projects in Burma in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016; and if she will list those projects.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8283","8283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756788","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the new business rates appeal process known as check, challenge, appeal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8321","8321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756789","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses appealed their business rates in each of the last seven years in (a) England, (b) each English region and (c) each local authority area.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8322","8322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756790","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses have registered to use the new business rates appeal process since the check, challenge, appeal system was established in (a) England, (b) each English region and (c) each local authority area.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8323","8323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756791","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children have been transferred to the UK under the Dublin III Regulation since January 2017; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8318","8318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756792","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the number of children is who were transferred under the Dublin III Regulation in 2016 by nature of the relative they were reunited with.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8317","8317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756793","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will be responsible for the administration of the 1918 Representation of the People commemoration fund; and if she will publish details on how organisations can apply for grants from that fund.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7590","7590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756794","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of air cadets have completed courses in gliding in each of the last five years; how many air cadets have completed gliding courses in each of the volunteer gliding squadrons since 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7851","7851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756795","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many young people have (a) joined and (b) left the air cadets in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7852","7852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756796","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many instructors qualified to conduct gliding lessons through the Volunteer Gliding Squadrons have been available to offer lessons in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7853","7853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756797","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will impose sanctions on President Maduro and other high-ranking Venezuelan Government officials.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7601","7601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756798","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to increase the small claims limit for road traffic accident-related personal injury claims to £5,000 and to increase the small claims limit for all other personal injury claims to £2,000.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7819","7819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756799","2017-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Military Police investigations into staff at AFC Harrogate there have been in the last 10 years; what the (a) related allegations and (b) outcomes were in each of those investigations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7890","7890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756800","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have applied to join the Army who are aged between 16 and 24 since the commencement of the This is Belonging campaign.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7740","7740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756801","2017-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many instructors have been returned to unit from AFC Harrogate (a) with and (b) without prejudice in the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7891","7891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756802","2017-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many disciplinary investigations into instructors have been conducted at AFC Harrogate in the last 10 years; what the (a) related allegations and (b) outcomes were in each of those investigations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7892","7892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756803","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the This is Belonging campaign by the Army was specifically marketed to 16 to 24-year olds in low socio-economic groups.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7741","7741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756804","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) men and (b) women have applied to join the Army since the commencement of the This is Belonging campaign.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7742","7742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756805","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the cities of Manchester, Sheffield, Birmingham, Belfast and Cardiff were up-weighted in the marketing of the This is Belonging campaign by the Army.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7743","7743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756806","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have applied to join the Army from the lowest three socio-economic groups since the commencement of the This is Belonging campaign.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7744","7744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756807","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people who have applied to join the Army since the commencement of the This is Belonging campaign have achieved five GCSEs with grades C and above.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7745","7745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756808","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people who have applied to join the Army since the commencement of the This is Belonging campaign have completed university degrees.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7747","7747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756809","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people who have applied to join the Army since the commencement of the This is Belonging campaign have completed A-levels.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7746","7746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756810","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to review the period of tie during which valid claims can be made to the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority following the reporting of an incident to the police.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7527","7527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756811","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Serious Further Offence reviews were commenced in respect of offences allegedly committed by offenders who at the time were being supervised by the National Probation Service where the offender's period of supervision followed a prison sentence of 12 months or less in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8141","8141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756812","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the (a) performance and (b) effectiveness of community rehabilitation companies in carrying out their statutory duties in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8400","8400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756813","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any additional funds above the agreed contract for 2016-17 were given to community rehabilitation companies in England and Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8401","8401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756814","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Serious Further Offence reviews were commenced in respect of offences allegedly committed by offenders who at the time were being supervised by community rehabilitation companies where the offender's period of supervision followed a prison sentence of 12 months or less in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8142","8142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756815","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the categories of crime which trigger a Serious Further Offence review have changed in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8186","8186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756816","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many small businesses in the North West can access broadband.","Biography information for Trudy Harrison","Trudy Harrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8153","8153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756817","2017-09-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to promote music education and support the development of future professional musicians in the UK.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7887","7887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756818","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle long hospital stays for patients with complex mental health needs as a result of insufficient community or rehabilitation services.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8200","8200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756819","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress has been made on supporting a joint working group with lenders, valuers and the industry focussing on modern methods of construction; and when the first meeting of that group will be held.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8226","8226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756820","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of crime in Stafford constituency in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7573","7573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756821","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) pieces of unlawful terrorist material have been taken off the internet, (b) hate preachers have been excluded from the UK, (c) organisations have been proscribed in the UK, (d) British citizenships have been revoked and (e) passports removed for terrorism-related reasons since May 2015; and how many arrests the police have made for terrorism-related offences since May 2015.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7580","7580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756822","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken to (a) tackle traffic congestion and (b) improve public transport in Stafford constituency.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7581","7581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756823","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many businesses the Manufacturing Advisory Service has assisted in Stafford constituency since May 2015.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7576","7576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756824","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many new companies were started in Stafford constituency in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7577","7577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756825","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps his Department has taken to support businesses in Stafford constituency.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7575","7575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756826","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to increase the level of access to credit for businesses in Stafford constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7578","7578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756827","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support small and medium-sized businesses in Stafford constituency.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7579","7579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756828","2017-09-06","Department for International Trade","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many businesses in Stafford constituency have received export support from his Department since it was set up.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7574","7574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756829","2017-09-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, who will be the UK counterpart to Peter Sorensen, the European Commission lead on aviation matters in negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7788","7788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756830","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total expenditure was by the NHS on pharmaceutical industry products in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8404","8404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756831","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are on a Diabetes Education and Self Management for Ongoing and Newly Diagnosed programme.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8187","8187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756832","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many eye surgeries as a result of diabetic conditions have been performed by the NHS in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8188","8188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756833","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many amputations as a result of diabetic conditions have been performed by the NHS in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8189","8189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756834","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has spent on drugs and products related to diabetes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8325","8325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756835","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs in Great Britain and Northern Ireland registered to practise there were on 1 July 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8228","8228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756836","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many specialist diabetes nurses there were on 1 July 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8229","8229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756837","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many bariatric procedures were conducted in 2016.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8230","8230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756838","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs applies a de minimis limit for investigating allegations of fraud.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7845","7845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756839","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has undertaken a cost-benefit analysis of allowing GP practices to fund tuition fees for medical students who would join that practice on qualification.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8191","8191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756840","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the efficacy of playing classical music in public spaces to deter anti-social behaviour.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8190","8190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756841","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Child Support Agency applies a de minimis limit for investigating allegations of fraud.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7846","7846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756842","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the forthcoming National Insurance Contributions Bill, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of granting Class 3 national insurance credits to young people engaged in full-time social action programmes.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8437","8437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756843","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the forthcoming National Insurance Contributions Bill, if =he-she- will consult the Youth Full-Time Social Action Review on the potential merits of granting Class 3 national insurance credits to full-time volunteers.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8438","8438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756844","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what provision her Department makes to assist with the living costs of disabled students attending university.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8435","8435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756845","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons interest rates on student loans are set at their present level; and what the potential merits are of lowering those levels.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8436","8436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756846","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many eligibility codes for 30 hours of free childcare were generated before the deadline of 31 August 2017.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8168","8168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756847","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many eligibility codes for 30 hours of free childcare have been validated by providers and local authorities.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8167","8167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756848","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to visit Dewsbury and District Hospital in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8169","8169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756849","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the letter to him from Barnardo's, Victim Support, Liberty, Rape Crisis and the National Working Group of 18 July 2017, if he will review the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority Guidelines to ensure that children who are raped or sexually abused are not refused compensation on the grounds that they consented to that rape or abuse.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7879","7879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756850","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Table 4 of the Annual Statistics of Scientific Procedures on Living Animals, Great Britain, 2016, what the experiments carried out on the 190 cats were.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7633","7633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756851","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Table 2.3 of the Annual Statistics of Scientific Procedures on Living Animals, Great Britain, 2016, how her Department ensures that the colonies from which 1,739 primates used for the first time in experimental procedures in 2016 originate are self-sustaining.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7634","7634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756852","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the primates used in experimental procedures in 2016 were F1, born from wild parents, or F2 greater, born from parents who were also born in captivity; and how she plans to monitor the reduction in F1 primates that should occur if the colonies are truly self-sustaining.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7635","7635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756853","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many primates used in experiments for the first time in 2016 came from Asia or Africa; and what steps the Government is taking to ensure that there is a reduction in the importation of monkeys for research.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7630","7630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756854","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken to reduce the use of monkeys in regulatory testing for human medicines since 2016.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7631","7631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756855","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether hoists are refundable under the Access to Work scheme.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8356","8356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756856","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, why Access to Work claim forms require certification by an employer or support worker.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8357","8357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756857","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how self-employed people can meet the Access to Work certification requirement by an employer or support worker.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8358","8358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756858","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons Access to Work claim handlers make separate payments to customers who have multiple such allowances rather than making a single payment.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8359","8359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756859","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an assessment of (a) the adequacy of and (b) compliance with the fire safety standards of furniture products in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7834","7834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756860","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Government of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region on the imprisonment of three protestors involved in the pro-democracy Umbrella Movement of 2014.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7831","7831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756861","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will update his Department's analysis of 18 April 2016, published in HM Treasury analysis: the long-term economic impact of EU membership and the alternatives, Cm 9250, on the effect of leaving the EU single market and concluding a trade deal with the EU on public sector receipts.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7833","7833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756862","2017-09-06","Cabinet Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7905","7905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756863","2017-09-06","Cabinet Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish details of all (a) meetings and (b) telephone calls that have taken place between the Cabinet Secretary and representatives of the Legatum Institue in the last 18 months.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8423","8423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756864","2017-09-06","Attorney General","2017-09-04","To ask the Attorney General, which EU legislation within the Law Officers' Departments' responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7904","7904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756865","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7921","7921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756866","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7906","7906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756867","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which EU legislation within her Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7909","7909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756868","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the Ugandan authorities and the UK's Ugandan High Commissioner on repression and violence in Northern Uganda.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7584","7584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756869","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7912","7912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756870","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7910","7910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756871","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which EU legislation within her Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7907","7907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756872","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7908","7908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756873","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7913","7913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756874","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which EU legislation within her Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7915","7915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756875","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7917","7917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756876","2017-09-06","Northern Ireland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7918","7918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756877","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to table AS 08 Q of the Quarterly Immigration Statistics, January to March 2017, published on 25 May 2017, how many applications for asylum made during Quarter 1 of 2017 were made by unaccompanied children who arrived in the UK (a) under section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016, (b) through the Dublin III Regulation and (c) by their own initiative.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7830","7830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756878","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which EU legislation within her Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7914","7914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756879","2017-09-06","Wales Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7922","7922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756880","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether red routes in London will be classified as major roads for the purposes of the new National Road Fund.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8448","8448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756881","2017-09-06","Scotland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7919","7919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756882","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7920","7920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756883","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Transport for London Road Network will be eligible for funding from the new National Road Fund.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8422","8422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756884","2017-09-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the EU institutions about funding for Northern Ireland from the EU Peace Programme (a) before and (b) after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7536","7536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756885","2017-09-06","Department for International Trade","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has been made of the cost to the UK of setting up a commercial defence investigatory body to oversee anti-dumping (AD) and anti-subsidy (AS) investigations, follow up complaints by UK industry in line with WTO rules, monitor undertakings and monitor AD and countervailing measures arising out of AS investigations by other countries.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7627","7627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756886","2017-09-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7911","7911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756887","2017-09-06","Department for International Trade","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7916","7916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756888","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on access to non-UK migrant labour in (a) non-seasonal agricultural sectors and (b) the egg industry when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8399","8399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756889","2017-09-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with pharmaceutical companies on potential employment in that sector for qualified persons for pharmacovigilance, marketing authorisation holders and qualified people for batch release after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7565","7565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756890","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate has been made of the level of representation the UK will require at the World Trade Organisation and the cost of that representation once the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7585","7585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756891","2017-09-06","Department for International Trade","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the cost of setting up a department to investigate trade barriers not related to anti-dumping or anti-subsidy investigations in countries that discriminate against UK exports.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7625","7625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756892","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which EU legislation within his Department's responsibilities will (a) be incorporated into UK law through the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill and (b) require to be amended under powers in that Bill.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7903","7903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756893","2017-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether Grenfell Tower was equipped with a functioning wet or dry riser system.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8193","8193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756894","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the practice of bleach enema as a treatment to cure autism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7786","7786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756895","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the practice of bleach enema as a treatment to cure autism.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7787","7787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756896","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 July 2017 to Question 5949, on crimes of violence: acids, how many of the assaults identified involved (a) acid, (b) ammonia, (c) bleach and (d) other substances.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8124","8124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756897","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to update guidance to classify acid as a weapon made for causing injury under section 1 of the Prevention of Crime Act 1953.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8147","8147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756898","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) motorcycles, (b) mopeds and (c) off-road vehicles have been seized by police under section 59 of the Police Reform Act 2002 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8148","8148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756899","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on application of the careful or competent driver standard to specialist police drivers.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8119","8119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756900","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 July 2017 to Question 5949, on crimes of violence: acids, if she will list the 39 police forces in England and Wales which provided figures on acid and corrosive attacks.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8125","8125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756901","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to publish its Missing Persons Strategy.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7781","7781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756902","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to amend the Poisons Act 1972; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8171","8171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756903","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle criminal use of motorcycles, mopeds and scooters.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8121","8121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756904","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with manufacturers and retailers about reducing crime involving motorcycles, mopeds and off-road vehicles.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8120","8120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756905","2017-09-06","Attorney General","2017-09-04","To ask the Attorney General, what plans he has to update guidance issued to prosecutors on charging emergency service drivers with careless or dangerous driving.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8122","8122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756906","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle criminal use of off-road vehicles.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8117","8117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756907","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on the recording of crime involving motorcycles, mopeds, scooters or off-road bikes.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8118","8118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756908","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had since 16 July 2017 with retailers on restriction of sales of acids and other corrosive substances.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8158","8158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756909","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on sentencing and other powers available to the courts to deal with assaults using acid or other corrosive substances.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8159","8159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756910","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what new guidance has been provided to police officers since 16 July 2017 on (a) preventing attacks with acid or other corrosive substances, (b) searching potential perpetrators for harmful substances and (c) responding to victims at the scene of assaults in which such substances have been used.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8232","8232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756911","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken since 16 July 2017 to ensure that appropriate support is provided to victims of acid or corrosive attacks.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8222","8222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756912","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to improving police recording and reporting of offences involving acid or corrosive substances since 16 July 2017.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8223","8223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756913","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made on the strategy for reducing the number and impact of acid attacks announced on 16 July 2017.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8233","8233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756914","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to update Home Office circular 43/2001 on financial assistance to police officers in legal proceedings.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8447","8447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756915","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken since 16 July 2017 to (a) ensure that victim impact statements are completed by the police in every case of assault involving acid or corrosives and (b) encourage the police to prepare community impact assessments showing how such attacks have affected communities.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8219","8219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756916","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what research her Department has commissioned into the motivations for carrying out attacks with acids or corrosive substances.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8220","8220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756917","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many finished episodes were recorded by hospitals in England with an external cause of assault by corrosive substance for hospitals in 2016-17.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8221","8221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756918","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers have been prosecuted for driving offences committed while on duty in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8123","8123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756919","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to regulate pay rises for managers of large companies.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8149","8149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756920","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that children are aware of the dangers of using social media apps.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8126","8126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756921","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who is responsible for recording and responding to unlawful practices relating to the exclusion from school of children with autism.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7843","7843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756922","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the updated 2017-18 qualifications list for (a) ICT and (b) other subjects will be confirmed.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7837","7837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756923","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support farmers and agri-producers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7844","7844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756924","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time was for a personal independence payment appeal to be heard in each of the last five years in each tribunal area.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8402","8402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756925","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to implement recommendation 8 of the Maynard Taskforce.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8353","8353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756926","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what interim support is available for deaf people between the start of a new job and when an Access to Work workplace assessment is carried out.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8350","8350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756927","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment appeals have been made to the Social Security Tribunals by deaf claimants; and how many of those appeals have been successful.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8349","8349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756928","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training health professionals carrying out personal independence payment assessments receive on deafness.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8351","8351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756929","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to introduce a digital application process that is accessible for deaf people claiming personal independence payment.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8352","8352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756930","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure insurance companies do not increase premiums for patients with existing conditions for which the treatment is covered by the European Health Insurance Card.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8216","8216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756931","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the level of personal debt (a) in total, (b) per household and (c) as a proportion of GDP for the latest period available and for each of the five previous financial years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7587","7587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756932","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much money energy companies have spent on assisting low income households in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8214","8214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756933","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many prosecutions the Health and Safety Executive has brought against employers for a failure to manage high temperatures in the workplace in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7586","7586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756934","2017-09-11","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 28 June 2017 to Question 854 on sex and relationship education, if she will provide an update on the engagement process for statutory guidance on relationships and sex education.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8201","8201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756935","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been spent from the public purse in compensation to recipients of tax credits for errors caused by HM Revenue and Customs in the last seven years in (a) the UK and (b) Wansbeck constituency.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7860","7860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756936","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been lost from the public purse as a result of HM Revenue and Customs errors in respect of tax credits in (a) the UK and (b) Wansbeck constituency in the last seven years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7859","7859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756937","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been spent from the public purse by his Department on appeals and tribunals for all welfare benefits in the last seven years; and whether that information is available at parliamentary constituency level.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7858","7858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756938","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Financial Conduct Authority's High-cost credit and review of the high-cost short-term credit price cap Feedback Statement, published on 31 July 2017, whether his Department has a definition for essential household goods.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7824","7824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756939","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of applying a price cap on rent-to-own goods.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7582","7582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756940","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the level of interest rates charged on rent-to-own goods.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7583","7583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756941","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate the Government has made of how much imported pig meat containing hepatitis E has been sold in British supermarkets in each of the last five years; and what steps the Government is taking to reduce the risk of such infection to consumers.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7850","7850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756942","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) patients were issued with fines by the NHS Business Authority as a result of failure to renew an exemption certificate and (b) of those fines were issued to patients with long-term medical conditions.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7802","7802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756943","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to create a lifelong prescription exemption certificate for patients who have long-term medical conditions which will last for life.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7801","7801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756944","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many of the fines issued by the NHS Business Authority in 2016-17 have been paid.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7778","7778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756945","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Government plans to make a decision on the Swansea Tidal Lagoon project.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7773","7773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756946","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has been invited to attend the meeting of a new contact group on Syria at the UN in New York in September 2017.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7893","7893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756947","2017-09-06","Cabinet Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his policy is on extending the length of time during which overseas electors are eligible to vote in UK elections and referendums.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7668","7668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756948","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to bring all homes in England and Wales to at least an Energy Performance Certificate C rating by 2035.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7660","7660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756949","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to publish a response to the public consultation on the Housing White Paper.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7667","7667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756950","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to provide mental health assessment and professional support to people sleeping rough.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7676","7676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756951","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to provide support and appropriate housing to prevent people from sleeping rough after they leave mental health hospitals.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7677","7677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756952","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when she next plans to review the list of sporting events of national interest available to all television viewers.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7678","7678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756953","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had discussions during the summer adjournment of the House with (a) Iranian authorities and (b) EU counterparts on the case of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7666","7666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756954","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Indonesian Government during the Parliamentary summer recess on human rights violations in West Papua.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7689","7689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756955","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the trends in the numbers of political prisoners in West Papua.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8111","8111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756956","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the UN and (b) EU authorities on human rights abuses in Myanmar.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8386","8386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756957","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic engagements there have been between the UK and Myanmar over the parliamentary summer recess; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8387","8387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756958","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer to the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington of 21 April 2017 to Question 71611, on in vitro fertilisation, what response his Department received from NHS England on commissioning fertility services; and what further action his Department has considered taking on that matter.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8439","8439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756959","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress his Department made during the Parliamentary summer recess on production of the 25-year plan for the environment.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7680","7680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756960","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to complete the England Coast Path by 2020.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7681","7681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756961","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the long-term maintenance and management of the England Coast Path.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7682","7682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756962","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish the strategy on the safeguarding of unaccompanied asylum-seeking and refugee children.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7679","7679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756963","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of training of military and security forces in Myanmar by the UK on the promotion of (a) human rights, (b) democracy and (c) the rule of law.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8385","8385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756964","2017-09-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent in Myanmar in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8389","8389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756965","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the effect of business rates on NHS trusts.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8105","8105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756966","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that emotional and mental health support is provided to young people with cancer (a) during and (b) after treatment.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8107","8107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756967","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to provide financial resources to GPs to meet the increase in indemnity costs as a result of the change to the discount rate on personal injury payouts.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8102","8102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756968","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure people with musculoskeletal conditions have timely access to health and care services.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8113","8113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756969","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people with musculoskeletal conditions have timely access to services to support them in work.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8114","8114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756970","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to improve the (a) quality and (b) availability of information on the use of public services by people with arthritis.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8112","8112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756971","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the National Childbirth Trust on its Hidden Half campaign to improve diagnosis and treatment for post-natal mental illness.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7664","7664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756972","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the Ministry of Justice's decision to change the personal injury discount rate on the future costs of indemnity insurance for GPs.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7686","7686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756973","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department held during the Parliamentary summer recess with victims and victims' groups on the contaminated blood inquiry.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7687","7687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756974","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the difference in eligibility to pay non-domestic rates between private and NHS hospitals.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7688","7688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756975","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to introduce access and waiting time standards so that adults with an eating disorder receive NICE guideline-approved treatment within four weeks.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7685","7685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756976","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the capacity of the NHS to meet demand for diagnostic tests for bowel cancer.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7683","7683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756977","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that there is sufficient resource and capacity to meet waiting time standards for colonoscopy and flexible sigmoidoscopy for suspected lower gastrointestinal cancer.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7684","7684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756978","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of people with suspected rheumatoid and early inflammatory arthritis who received diagnosis and management according to the NICE Quality Standard in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8277","8277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756979","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical commissioning groups do not meet NICE guidelines for IVF treatment.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8388","8388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756980","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of the relative cost of housing compared with wages in (a) Oxford and (b) Oxfordshire on the ability of the Probation Service to recruit and retain staff.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7671","7671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756981","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what post-legislative scrutiny his Department has carried out on the effectiveness of the Debt Relief (Developing Countries) Act 2010.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7665","7665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756982","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to provide humanitarian aid to Rohingya refugees fleeing from Rakhine state; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8390","8390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756983","2017-09-06","Northern Ireland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions he has had with the (a) Police Service of Northern Ireland, (b) Department of Justice, Northern Ireland and (c) Public Prosecution Service for Northern Ireland on individuals charged under the Offences Against the Person Act 1981 for purchasing abortion medication for (i) their own use and (ii) use by a third party.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8097","8097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756984","2017-09-06","Northern Ireland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress has been made on the formation of an executive in Northern Ireland since the start of the summer recess; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8110","8110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756985","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from civil liberties campaign groups on the operation of and use of data from CCTV cameras with facial recognition and biometric tracking capabilities.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8278","8278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756986","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people whose information has been recorded by mobile facial recognition software by police forces in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8279","8279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756987","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that expert medical opinions are taken into account as part of the application process for victims of torture seeking asylum.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8103","8103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756988","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police forces do not collect finger prints for break-ins.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8109","8109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756989","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that asylum assessment standards comply with her Department's guidelines.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8104","8104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756990","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of current legislation regulating the use of CCTV cameras with facial recognition and biometric tracking capabilities.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8098","8098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756991","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the Metropolitan Police on the use of mobile facial recognition software.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8099","8099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756992","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward proposals to extend the remit of the Biometrics Commissioner to include oversight of the use of mobile facial recognition software by police forces.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8100","8100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756993","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to support torture victims seeking asylum in the UK.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8106","8106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756994","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued to police forces on the use of mobile facial recognition software.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8101","8101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756995","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what safeguards are in place to ensure that human rights legislation is complied with in respect of detainees at Campsfield House Immigration Removal Centre.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7672","7672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756996","2017-09-06","Women and Equalities","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the timetable is for delivering funding for abortions for Northern Irish women in England; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8096","8096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756997","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to assist young cancer patients to access welfare benefits.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8095","8095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756998","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of claims made by care providers that paying historical minimum wage arrears owed to care workers who have carried out sleep-in shifts would compromise the financial viability of that sector.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7884","7884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756999","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, under what provisions enforcement activity on the payment of sleep-in shifts by social care providers was temporarily suspended until 2 October 2017.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7885","7885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757000","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to give employees of a listed company the right to be represented on the board.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7673","7673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757001","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to require staff representation on company remuneration committees.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7674","7674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757002","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure a secure supply of helium for use in the British science, manufacturing and defence industries.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7669","7669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757003","2017-09-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Government will continue to apply the family reunification Dublin III Regulation when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7675","7675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757004","2017-09-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to the status of EU citizens after the UK has left the EU on the rights of citizens of (a) Ireland, (b) Malta and (c) Cyprus to vote in elections and referendums in the UK.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7883","7883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757005","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Prime Minister on implementing pension transitional protection arrangements for women born in the 1950s.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8093","8093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757006","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with motor neurone disease receive (a) home adaptations, (b) specialised wheelchairs and (c) adapted vehicles.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8094","8094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757007","2017-09-06","Women and Equalities","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the Equality and Human Rights Commission's Fair opportunities for all: A strategy to reduce pay gaps in Britain report, what steps she is taking to tackle gender, ethnicity and disability pay gaps.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7670","7670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757008","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to promote the Access to Work scheme to people with musculoskeletal conditions.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8108","8108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757009","2017-09-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make it his policy to allow EU27 citizens to continue to be able to vote and to stand as candidates in local government elections after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7661","7661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757010","2017-09-06","Cabinet Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to allow EU27 citizens who are awarded settled status to be able to vote in (a) local government, (b) police and crime commissioner, (c) mayoral, (d) London Assembly, (e) National Assembly for Wales, (f) Scottish Parliament, (g) Northern Ireland Assembly and (h) Parliament elections.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7662","7662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757011","2017-09-06","Cabinet Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to allow EU27 citizens who are awarded settled status to be able to vote in local, regional and national referendums.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7663","7663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757012","2017-09-07","Attorney General","2017-09-04","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to his oral contribution of 27 October 2016, Official Report, column 410, whether he plans to look at guidance given by the Crown Prosecution Service to the lawyers who appear before the courts and regularly deal with applications of sexual offences.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8314","8314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757013","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Attorney General's oral contribution of 27 October 2016, Official Report, column 410, whether he plans to review guidance given to judges on what they may say to juries with regard to admissibility of a complainant's sexual history.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8315","8315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757014","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy for UKVI to give applicants a target date for when their visa applications will be processed.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7529","7529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757015","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK EU nationals have received compensation for unlawful detention under Immigration Act powers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8156","8156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757016","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visa application cases have taken over (a) six, (b) nine, (c) 12 and (d) 18 months to be processed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7791","7791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757017","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the DVLA's system for reporting medical conditions.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8267","8267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757018","2017-09-06","Scotland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy and the Scottish Government on tackling the importing of counterfeit electrical goods into Scotland.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8285","8285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757019","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding his Department has allocated to Trading Standards services in (a) Scotland, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) Wales and (d) England to tackle counterfeit electrical goods being imported into the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8286","8286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757020","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with Trading Standards Scotland on tackling counterfeit electrical goods being imported into Scotland.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8287","8287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757021","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many seizures of counterfeit electrical goods have been seized in each port in Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8288","8288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757022","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department is planning a review of benefits available to cancer patients to ensure that benefits are sufficient to meet any additional financial support required.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8268","8268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757023","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to review the eligibility criteria for funeral expenses payments.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8434","8434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757024","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the change to eligibility groups in the pilot scheme introduced by the International Federation for Intellectual Impairment Sport (INAS) on encouraging more people with Down's syndrome and autism to enter the 2017 INAS World Swimming Championships.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8276","8276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757025","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to extend the smoking ban to include NHS hospital premises.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8145","8145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757026","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has for a further round of funding for projects in support of the Prevent Strategy.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7806","7806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757027","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps have been taken to protect under 18 year olds from grooming and inappropriate relationships.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7822","7822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757028","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 207 to Question HL969, when his Department plans to start the public consultation on the regulation of physician associates.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8185","8185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757029","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his written statement of 3 July 2017, HCWS24, whether the Care Quality Commission's local system reviews of health and social care in 12 local authority areas will include an assessment of whether the commissioning of care services is conducted in a manner that ensures that all services are compliant with the national living wage and national minimum wage.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7596","7596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757030","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the 2014-15 Student Income and Expenditure Survey will be published.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7793","7793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757031","2017-09-06","Cabinet Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many international students from (a) another EU country and (b) outside the EU reside in each parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7821","7821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757032","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many international students entered the UK with (a) a child and (b) an adult dependent in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7820","7820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757033","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the letter of 6 April 2017 from Jon Thompson, Chief Executive HM Revenue and Customs, to the right hon. Member for North Norfolk, how many of the care sector employers involved in the 183 cases between 1 February 2015 and 30 September 2016 of non-compliance with the national minimum wage have been named and shamed by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7792","7792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757034","2017-09-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of care sector companies that do not pay the national minimum wage have been named and shamed by his Department since it began publicly identifying non-compliant employers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7790","7790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757035","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 20 of her Department's policy paper Safeguarding the position of EU citizens in the UK and UK nationals in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, how an EU citizen with settled status returning to the UK after a two-year absence could prove strong ties to the UK in order to retain settled status.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7535","7535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757036","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of maintaining current levels of core educational funding for 16 to 18 year olds on (a) educational outcomes and (b) further education provision; and what plans she has for (i) funding and (ii) resourcing further education in the next five years.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8134","8134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757037","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to announce the criteria and timetable for allocating additional undergraduate medical student places.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7567","7567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757038","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to prevent London medical schools from cross-subsidising the education of international students from their Service Increment for Teaching fund allocated to students from the UK and other EU countries.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8133","8133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757039","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of extra UK medical school places that will be made available to international medical students after the removal of the cap on the number of such places.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7815","7815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757040","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when allocating the 1000 additional undergraduate medical student places, what steps he plans to take to ensure that medical schools outside London receive a fair allocation of those places.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7816","7816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757041","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the Service Increment for Teaching funding allocation process is subject to the market forces factor; and what steps he plans to take to ensure that there is not an excessive regional disparity in allocations of that funding between London and non-London medical schools.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7817","7817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757042","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that additional medical student places are fairly allocated to students from (a) the UK and (b) other EU countries.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8135","8135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757043","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2017 to Question 1153, on social services, what steps he is taking to ensure that the consultation into social care will review the views of people who have children with palliative care needs.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8160","8160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757044","2017-09-07","Cabinet Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2017 to Question 1153, on social services, whether the consultation on social care will include children's social care.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8161","8161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757045","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of local authority charges for burial fees for children in (a) Newcastle, (b) the North East and (c) England.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8127","8127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757046","2017-09-07","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to increase the parity of funding of children's hospices and adult hospices.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8162","8162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757047","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the UK will continue to apply the Dublin III Regulation when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8163","8163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757048","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will review the mobility component of disability living allowance to ensure that children under the age of three are eligible.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8128","8128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757049","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people in all regions can access legal aid providers.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7534","7534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757050","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Israeli Government on the removal of citizenship from people living in Bedouin communities in Israel.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8170","8170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757051","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the July 2017 report by Christine Beddoe on separated and unaccompanied minors in Europe, whether the Government plans to create safe travel routes for those minors with a family member in the UK.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8194","8194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757052","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether officials are working with French authorities to ensure that unaccompanied child refugees in France have information about their legal rights and options.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8195","8195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757053","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that security measures undertaken by other governments outside the UK and funded from the public purse operate in conformity with child protection and human rights principles.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8324","8324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757054","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on purchasing temporary sites for free schools; and how much has been spent to date on each such site.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8398","8398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757055","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent on LocatED between 2015 and 2016.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8289","8289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757056","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's total budget was for LocatED in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8290","8290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757057","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish LocatED's annual accounts for 2016-17.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8291","8291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757058","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what target has been set for the number of free schools to be opened by 2020; and what the number is of free schools that have opened that have contributed towards that target.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8292","8292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757059","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish the job titles and salaries of the senior management team of LocatED.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8293","8293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757060","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the criteria was for the recruitment of the Chief Executive Officer of LocatED.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8294","8294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757061","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many candidates (a) applied and (b) were interviewed for the post of Chief Executive Officer of LocatED.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8295","8295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757062","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what performance objectives she has set for LocatED.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8296","8296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757063","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, where the post of Chief Executive Officer of LocatED was advertised.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8297","8297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757064","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to encourage take-up of the Lyme Disease Action e-learning course amongst primary care practitioners.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7566","7566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757065","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the inspection system in schools on the (a) mental health and (b) retention rate of teachers.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8446","8446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757066","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer and other ministerial colleagues on the public sector pay gap for teachers.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8444","8444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757067","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of year 6 SATs on the mental health of 11 year olds in (a) Hull West and Hessle constituency and (b) England.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8445","8445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757068","2017-09-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on claimants of issuing benefits on a monthly rather than weekly basis due to the introduction of universal credit.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7537","7537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757069","2017-09-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether a devolution deal for Yorkshire that included provision for one combined authority and an elected mayor would require primary legislation.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7861","7861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757070","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of VAT which does not accrue to the public purse as a result of the establishment of subsidiary companies by NHS Foundation Trusts; and what the implications for VAT receipts would be in the event that all foundation hospital trusts set up subsidiary companies for facilities management and pharmacy provision.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8140","8140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757071","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of Eunomia's Residual Waste Infrastructure Review, Issue 12, published in July 2017, which concluded that there is overcapacity in the incinerator sector in the UK.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7775","7775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757072","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what provisions there are in the (a) TransPennine and (b) Northern franchise to encourage (i) the operation of trains on Boxing Day and (ii) equalisation of fares across county boundaries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8146","8146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757073","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of restoring the Skipton to Colne rail route.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8138","8138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757074","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has received representations from (a) Stagecoach and (b) Virgin Eastcoast on renegotiating the terms of Virgin East Coast's contract to operate the East Coast mainline; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8139","8139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757075","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many bus journeys operated out of (a) Keighley and (b) Ilkley bus station in each year from 2010.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7862","7862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757076","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many rail passengers used (a) Ilkley, (b) Keighley, (c) Ben Rhydding and (d) Steeton and Silsden stations in each year since 2010.","Biography information for John Grogan","John Grogan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7863","7863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757077","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many of the 233 employers named by the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy for non-compliance with the national minimum wage on 16 August 2017 identified further arrears, not included in the sum of arrears for which they were named, under the self-correction mechanism introduced by HM Revenue and Customs in 2015; what the combined total was of such further, self-corrected arrears; and to how many workers such arrears were owed.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7533","7533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757078","2017-09-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what evidence his Department holds on compliance with Article 12 of the Issue of energy performance certificates of the Evaluation of the Energy Performance of Buildings Directive 2010/31/EU for buildings (a) rented and (b) leased; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7880","7880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757079","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the scheduled opening and closing times of every ticket office along the Brighton Mainline portion of the Govia Thameslink Railway franchise are; whether those opening times have been met in each of the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8467","8467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757080","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the technology required for the introduction of part-time season tickets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8306","8306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757081","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make part-time tickets available on the Govia Thameslink Railway franchise by 1 January 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8307","8307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757082","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will (a) amend the Ticketing and Settlement Agreement to make part-time season tickets a requirement across all railway franchises and (b) make the provision of part-time season tickets a requirement when re-letting railway franchises.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8305","8305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757083","2017-09-07","Department for International Trade","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which countries have received invitations from the Government to the Defence and Security Equipment International Exhibition at the ExCel Centre from 12 to 15 September 2017.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8328","8328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757084","2017-09-07","Department for International Trade","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the Defence and Security Organisation priority markets are for 2017-18.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8329","8329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757085","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to (a) ensure and (b) monitor implementation of Article 10 Financial incentives and market barriers of Evaluation of the Energy Performance of Buildings Directive 2010/31/EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7881","7881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757086","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken since 1 November 2015 to raise awareness amongst public authorities of their statutory duty to notify her where they have reasonable grounds to believe that a person may be a victim of slavery of human trafficking in accordance with the Modern Slavery Act 2015 (Duty to Notify) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8217","8217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757087","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many notifications her Department has received under section 52 of the Modern Slavery Act 2015 relating to slavery or human trafficking of (a) children and (b) adults.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8218","8218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757088","2017-09-06","Department for International Development","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment has been made of the effectiveness of work by the Punjab Curriculum and Textboard Board on the content of textbooks relating to women, LGBT people and people of other faiths and nationalities.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7895","7895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757089","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to require drivers given notices under section 172 of the Road Traffic Act 1998 to provide the required information at a police station or electronically.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7894","7894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757090","2017-09-06","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many premises in Inverclyde constituency are able to receive superfast broadband services through BDUK-supported projects in 2017; and what the amount of funding her Department has made available for such projects in Inverclyde constituency during that year.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8155","8155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757091","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues and (b) the devolved administrations on making cannabis available through pharmaceuticals where use of that drug can be helpful.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8282","8282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757092","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to address railway signal failures caused by periods of very hot weather.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7561","7561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757093","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on works to upgrade the overhead line between Shenfield and London Liverpool Street.","Biography information for Vicky Ford","Vicky Ford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7562","7562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757094","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Youth Justice of 25 April 2017, Official Report, column 992, if the Government will establish an inquiry on the 1984 Cammell Laird strike and the imprisonment of 37 men.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8164","8164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757095","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will provide an update on the Marine and Coastguard Agency investigation on reports of a chemical haze at Birling Gap beach on 27 August 2017.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8443","8443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757096","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much is levied each year in additional business rates due to (a) sprinklers and (b) other fire protection systems being classified as plant and machinery or being otherwise subject to higher rates.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7896","7896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757097","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much is levied in additional business rates on landlords of residential properties as a result of the classification of sprinkler systems as plant and machinery or otherwise so as to attract a higher level of such rates.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7897","7897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757098","2017-09-07","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much is levied in additional business rates as a result of the installation of CCTV attracting a higher level of such rates.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7898","7898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757099","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the geographic and thematic priorities will be for future work supported by the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7530","7530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757100","2017-09-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has raised the increasing restrictions on freedom of expression in Burma with the Government of Burma.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8424","8424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757101","2017-09-06","Department for International Trade","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department plans to align arms export policy with the EU Common Position on Arms Exports when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7599","7599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757102","2017-09-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if his Department will use negotiations with the EU to ensure that the UK retains influence over EU arms exports frameworks.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7600","7600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757103","2017-09-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his Department plans to ensure through negotiations with the EU that the EU will not be able to impose economic sanctions on the UK when it is no longer a member of the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7531","7531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757104","2017-09-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking in negotiations on the UK's exit from the EU to ensure that geographical indications from the UK continue to be recognised in the EU and that systems for such indications remain compatible across the UK and EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7532","7532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757105","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to ensure that unaccompanied children will be able to be reunited with their close family when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7827","7827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757106","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to procure more Class 700 trains.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7628","7628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757107","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference  to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44265, if the Government will respond to the second Independent review of the personal independence payment assessment, published on 30 March 2017.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7629","7629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757108","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employment tribunal claimants (a) paid fees and (b) have had those fees refunded since 2013.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8363","8363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757109","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to increase the time for which an applicant for an employment tribunal can submit a claim to include the time when employment tribunal fees were introduced.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8396","8396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757110","2017-09-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the value of employment tribunal fees received by the Government was since 2013.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8403","8403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757111","2017-09-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his counterpart in Myanmar; and what was discussed at that meeting.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8413","8413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757112","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the results of the evaluation of the National Referral Mechanism pilot will be announced.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8416","8416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757113","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many councils have (a) ended their involvement in the voluntary national transfer scheme to take child refugees and (b) suspended involvement in the Dubs Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8417","8417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757114","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many and what proportion of people in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry South constituency will be covered by the Government's proposals to safeguard customers on the poorest value tariff.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8414","8414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757115","2017-09-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that small and medium-sized enterprises are not adversely affected as a result of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8415","8415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757116","2017-09-07","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2017 to Question 61630, on classroom assistants: average earnings, if she will provide the same salary data for 2016.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8320","8320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757117","2017-09-07","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the rail industry's preparedness for all UK rolling stock to be compliant with the Persons of Reduced Mobility Technical Specification for Interoperability by 31 December 2019.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8319","8319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757118","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people in Easington constituency (a) enrolled in, (b) applied to and (c) dropped out of university in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8463","8463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757119","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how she plans to encourage more working class students who are concerned about the financial burden in Easington constituency to go to university.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8465","8465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757120","2017-09-06","Department for Education","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many university applications have been submitted deferring entry to September 2018.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8466","8466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757121","2017-09-06","Prime Minister","2017-09-04","To ask the Prime Minister, if the Government will transfer responsibility for UK drugs policy from the Home Office to the Department for Health.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7856","7856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757122","2017-09-06","Department for Transport","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 20 April 2017 to Question 70176, what the reasons are for the time taken to publish the road casualty figures for 2016; and what steps he is taking to ensure the timely publication of future datasets.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7828","7828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757123","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the (a) Competition and Markets Authority and (b) Financial Conduct Authority on overdraft fees.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7848","7848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757124","2017-09-06","HM Treasury","2017-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with UK Financial Investments on the charging of unarranged overdraft fees by the Royal Bank of Scotland.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7849","7849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757125","2017-09-06","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Table 2.1 of the Annual Statistics of Scientific Procedures on Living Animals, Great Britain 2016, of the dogs born outside Europe (a) what countries those dogs came from, (b) how those dogs arrived in the UK, (c) how her Department ensured those dogs' welfare during transport and (d) what those dogs were used for when in the UK","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7597","7597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757126","2017-09-07","Home Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the process is for the appointment of the independent Anti-Slavery Commissioner.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8408","8408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757127","2017-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance is given to work capability assessors who deal with claimants who suffer from chronic fluctuating conditions.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8407","8407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757128","2017-09-06","Scotland Office","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the names are of his Department's special advisers; and what the annual employment costs of those advisers are.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7835","7835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757129","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times ambulances on (a) blue light response and (b) non-blue light response had to take an alternative route as a result of traffic disruption on the A583 in July 2017.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7570","7570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757130","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times ambulances attended incidents on the A583 at or outside Cuadrilla Resources' shale gas site on that road in July 2017.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7568","7568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757131","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times ambulances called to attended incidents on the A583 at or outside Cuadrilla Resources' shale gas site in July 2017 transferred patients for further treatment in hospital.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7569","7569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757132","2017-09-06","Department of Health","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what reports his Department has received of incidents of unreasonable behaviour towards North West Ambulance Service staff at or outside Cuadrilla Resources' shale gas site on the A583.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 8131","8131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757133","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what target his Department has set for the length of time between an appeal being lodged with the Immigration and Asylum Tribunal and the hearing date.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7886","7886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757134","2017-09-07","Ministry of Justice","2017-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of appeals lodged with the Immigration and Asylum Tribunal met the target time for a hearing date between 31 July 2016 to 31 July 2017.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 7632","7632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/756184","2017-09-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent discussions his Department has had with the aerospace industry on the negotiations for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900659","900659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757155","2017-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to extend the broadcasting of court proceedings.","Biography information for Mr John Whittingdale","Mr John Whittingdale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900687","900687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757156","2017-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, Whether he or Ministers of his Department have plans to attend the public meeting in Port Talbot on 20 September 2017 on the proposed siting of a prison in Baglan, Port Talbot.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900688","900688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757157","2017-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to reduce violence and self-harm among prisoners.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900677","900677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757158","2017-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, What assessment his Department has made of the appropriate ratio of staff to prisoners in each prison for operating a safe and rehabilitative prison regime.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900683","900683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757159","2017-09-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to use technology to improve the efficiency of the judicial process.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900678","900678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757919","2017-09-06","Wales Office","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for International Trade on ensuring that the Welsh Government is consulted on future trade deals.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900703","900703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757920","2017-09-06","Wales Office","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, when he plans next to meet the First Minister of Wales.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900696","900696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757921","2017-09-06","Wales Office","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for International Trade on ensuring that the Welsh Government is consulted on future trade deals.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900698","900698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/757922","2017-09-06","Wales Office","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for International Trade on ensuring that the Welsh Government is consulted on future trade deals.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900699","900699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758037","2017-09-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on (a) the total number and (b) trends in the number of UK companies choosing to register in Ireland as a result of the UK's decision to leave the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900654","900654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758509","2017-09-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on ensuring future cooperation with the EU on security policy after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900656","900656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/758510","2017-09-07","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-08-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had during negotiations with the EU on a transition period between the UK leaving the EU and the start date of a new trade agreement between the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Mr Pat McFadden","Mr Pat McFadden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900657","900657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754481","2017-09-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government has received the results of any consultation on Civil Service pay levels in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6449","6449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754482","2017-09-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of Government purchasing currently comes from small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6494","6494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754483","2017-09-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of people in Jarrow constituency worked in the public sector in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6673","6673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754484","2017-09-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure people can vote only once in an election.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6701","6701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754485","2017-09-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will seek to repeal the Fixed Terms Parliament Act 2011.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6705","6705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754486","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost of having the HM Revenue and Customs regional hub for Yorkshire in (a) Leeds and (b) Bradford.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6755","6755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754487","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has received (a) representations or (b) reports on an increase in discrimination towards non-UK EU nationals in terms of their access to mortgage financing on account of uncertainty as to the future status of EU citizens; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6828","6828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754488","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the potential occurrence of discrimination in access to mortgages for non-UK EU citizens; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6829","6829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754489","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of staff at HM Revenue and Customs are employed on a sub-contractual basis.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6702","6702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754490","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department's decision not to gold-plate the Payment Services Regulations by increasing transparency in foreign exchange pricing is consistent with the Government's stated approach to gold-plating; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6665","6665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754491","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what distributional analysis his Department has carried out on the pay of public sector workers who are not covered by a pay review body; and if he will place in the Library a copy of that analysis.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6556","6556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754492","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Government response to the consultation on the Payment Services Regulations, what steps his Department will take to (a) bear in mind the disclosure requirements listed in recital 84 of the Payment Services Directive and (b) achieve greater transparency.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6664","6664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754493","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what distributional analysis his Department has carried out on the public sector pay cap; and if he will place in the Library a copy of that analysis.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6553","6553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754494","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the Government's estimates for 2017-18 as set out in the Supply and Appropriations (Main Estimates) 2010 will accommodate any increased pay offer to the Fire and Rescue Services.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6554","6554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754495","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what equality impact assessment his Department has carried out on the pay of public sector workers who are not covered by a pay review body; and if he will place in the Library a copy of that assessment.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6555","6555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754496","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what distributional analysis his Department has carried out on the Government's plan to cut corporation tax to 17 per cent by 2020.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6564","6564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754497","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue was lost to the Exchequer as a result of the reduction of capital gains tax (a) basic rate to 10 per cent and (b) main rate to 20 per cent excluding residential property and carried interest since that reduction was implemented.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6565","6565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754498","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what equality impact assessment his Department has undertaken on the reduction of capital gains tax (a) basic rate to 10 per cent and (b) main rate to 20 per cent excluding on residential property and carried interest.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6770","6770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754499","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Government has put in place to encourage private sector investment in research and development.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6548","6548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754500","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what equality impact assessment his Department has carried out on the provisions of the forthcoming Finance Bill; and if he will place in the Library a copy of the relevant documents when that Bill receives its First Reading.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6549","6549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754501","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what distributional analysis his Department has carried out on the forthcoming Finance Bill; and if he will place in the Library a copy of the relevant documents when that Bill receives First Reading.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6550","6550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754502","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to introduce legislative proposals for the abolition of Class 2s NICS as announced in the 2016 Budget.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6551","6551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754503","2017-09-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will ensure that listed companies publish the ratio of executive pay to the average pay of the broader UK workforce.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6495","6495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754504","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether, and on what date he or officials of his Department have met with representatives of the Government of Saudi Arabia to discuss the scheduled Saudi Aramco IPO in the last 24 months.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6463","6463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754505","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from the financial services sector on whether financial institutions may leave the UK once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6465","6465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754506","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the proposed ending of separate fees for credit and debit card payments will apply to (a) council tax and (b) rent payments to local authorities and housing associations.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6542","6542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754507","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost of plans to modernise the courts system.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6491","6491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754508","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to reduce VAT on hotels and restaurants in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6493","6493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/754509","2017-09-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to introduce measures to tackle tax avoidance and evasion by people through nom-dom status and offshore trusts.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 6461","6461"
