"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32893","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Preston constituency under the age of 25 years old are recipients of housing benefit.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183302","183302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32894","2014-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what specific provisions the UK Government is putting towards the international effort to decommission Syria's chemical weapons.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183306","183306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32895","2014-01-16","Department for International Development","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much UK aid was sent to the Democratic Republic of Congo in (a) 2010, (b) 2011 and (c) 2012; and what estimate she has made of the amount of such aid sent in 2013.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183303","183303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32896","2014-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in Preston who were convicted of (a) sexual assualt, (b) rape, (c) sexual activity with a child under 16, (d) sexual activity with a child under 13 and (e) sexual assault of a female in 2012 received a custodial sentence of less than (i) six months and (ii) four years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183307","183307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32897","2014-01-16","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-14","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what progress his Department has made in the last three years on establishing 200 all-postal primaries.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183304","183304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32898","2014-01-16","HM Treasury","2014-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what taxation options he is considering in relation to e-cigarettes and the forthcoming budget; and what assessment he has made of the revenue implications of those options.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183308","183308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32899","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which local authorities currently share revenue and benefit services.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183309","183309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32900","2014-01-17","Department of Health","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 138W, on Deloitte, whether any third parties possess a copy of the correspondence from Peter Coates to Mike Turley dated 19 January 2010.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183352","183352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32902","2014-01-17","HM Treasury","2014-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the (a) capital and (b) revenue costs of the proposed Garden Bridge in London; and if he will provide a breakdown of those costs.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183357","183357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32903","2014-01-17","HM Treasury","2014-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what public funding has been allocated to the proposed Garden Bridge project in London; and how much private funding has been secured for that purpose.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183358","183358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32904","2014-01-17","Department for Transport","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse was of legal advice on the legal challenge by Pearson Driving Assessments to the award of the theory test contract.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183327","183327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32905","2014-01-16","Scotland Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183256","183256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32906","2014-01-16","Department for Transport","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183257","183257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32907","2014-01-16","HM Treasury","2014-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183258","183258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32908","2014-01-16","Wales Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183259","183259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32909","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183260","183260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32910","2014-01-16","Leader of the House","2014-01-14","To ask the Leader of the House, with what bank his Office's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183253","183253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32911","2014-01-16","Northern Ireland Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with what bank her Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183254","183254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32912","2014-01-16","Cabinet Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with what bank No. 10 Downing Street's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183255","183255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32913","2014-01-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183245","183245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32914","2014-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183246","183246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32915","2014-01-16","Cabinet Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with what bank the Deputy Prime Minister's Office's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183243","183243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32916","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183244","183244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32917","2014-01-16","Northern Ireland Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which Ministers in her Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider was, (b) purpose of the course was and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183231","183231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32918","2014-01-16","Attorney General","2014-01-14","To ask the Attorney General, with what bank the Law Officers' Departments' bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183238","183238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32919","2014-01-16","Cabinet Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183239","183239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32920","2014-01-16","Cabinet Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Ministers in No. 10 Downing Street have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider was, (b) purpose of the course was and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183232","183232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32921","2014-01-16","Home Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with what bank her Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183250","183250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32922","2014-01-16","Department for International Development","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with what bank her Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183251","183251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32923","2014-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183252","183252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32924","2014-01-16","Women and Equalities","2014-01-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with what bank the Government Equalities Office's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183248","183248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32925","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183249","183249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32926","2014-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183247","183247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32927","2014-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider, (b) purpose of the course and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183214","183214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32928","2014-01-16","Attorney General","2014-01-14","To ask the Attorney General, which Ministers in the Law Officers' Departments have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider, (b) purpose of the course and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183215","183215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32929","2014-01-16","Cabinet Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider, (b) purpose of the course and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183216","183216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32930","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider, (b) purpose of the course and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183217","183217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32931","2014-01-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which Ministers in her Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider, (b) purpose of the course and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183218","183218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32932","2014-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider, (b) purpose of the course and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183219","183219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32933","2014-01-16","Cabinet Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Ministers in his Office have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider, (b) purpose of the course and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183220","183220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32934","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider, (b) purpose of the course and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183221","183221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32935","2014-01-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider, (b) purpose of the course and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183222","183222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32936","2014-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider, (b) purpose of the course and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183223","183223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32937","2014-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider, (b) purpose of the course and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183224","183224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32938","2014-01-16","Women and Equalities","2014-01-14","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, which Ministers in the Government Equalities Office have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider was, (b) purpose of the course was and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183225","183225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32939","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider was, (b) purpose of the course was and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183226","183226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32940","2014-01-16","Home Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Ministers in her Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider was, (b) purpose of the course was and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183227","183227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32941","2014-01-16","Department for International Development","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which Ministers in her Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider was, (b) purpose of the course was and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183228","183228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32942","2014-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider was, (b) purpose of the course was and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183229","183229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32943","2014-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183237","183237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32944","2014-01-16","Leader of the House","2014-01-14","To ask the Leader of the House, which Ministers in his Office have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider was, (b) purpose of the course was and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183230","183230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32945","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183240","183240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32946","2014-01-16","Scotland Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider was, (b) purpose of the course was and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183233","183233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32947","2014-01-16","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with what bank her Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183241","183241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32948","2014-01-16","Department for Transport","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider was, (b) purpose of the course was and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183234","183234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32949","2014-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with what bank his Department's bank overdraft is held; and what fees and charges were payable on the core Department's bank overdraft in the last financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183242","183242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32950","2014-01-16","Wales Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider was, (b) purpose of the course was and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183235","183235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32951","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken training courses; and in the case of each such course what the (a) name of the course provider was, (b) purpose of the course was and (c) cost of each session in the course was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183236","183236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32952","2014-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many officials at each grade in his Department have the authority to execute a purchase; what proportion of those officials have professional procurement qualifications; and what the key indicators used in his Department to assess procurement officer's performance are.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183361","183361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32953","2014-01-17","Department of Health","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many officials at each grade in his Department have the authority to execute a purchase; what proportion of those officials have professional procurement qualifications; and what the key indicators used in his Department to assess procurement officer's performance are.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183362","183362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32954","2014-01-17","Department for Education","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many officials at each grade in his Department have the authority to execute a purchase; what proportion of those officials have professional procurement qualifications; and what the key indicators used in his Department to assess procurement officer's performance are.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183363","183363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32955","2014-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many officials at each grade in his Department have the authority to execute a purchase; what proportion of those officials have professional procurement qualifications; and what the key indicators used in his Department to assess procurement officer's performance are.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183364","183364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32956","2014-01-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many officials at each grade in his Department have the authority to execute a purchase; what proportion of those officials have professional procurement qualifications; and what the key indicators used in his Department to assess procurement officer's performance are.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183365","183365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32957","2014-01-22","HM Treasury","2014-01-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will place in the Library a copy of the document referred to in footnote 76 of page 49 of the Autumn Statement 2013, entitled Upstream Insight: UK advances shale gas fiscal incentives, Wood Mackenzie.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183372","183372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32958","2014-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the political stability of Iraq.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183332","183332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32959","2014-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the effect of conflict on civilians in Iraq.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183334","183334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32960","2014-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the effect of conflict on civilians in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183335","183335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32961","2014-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the work of the Iraqi army.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183333","183333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32962","2014-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the number of civilians killed by the Taliban in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183336","183336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32963","2014-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, by what date the Recruiting Partnering Project was originally expected to be fully operational.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183379","183379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32964","2014-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contingency plan his Department put in place in the event of delays and problems with its Recruiting Partnering Project.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183380","183380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32965","2014-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of whether the additional £1 million per month costs incurred by his Department as a result of changes announced to the Recruiting Partnering Project are likely to rise before the problems with that project are resolved.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183373","183373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32966","2014-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason the Army did not implement a contingency plan when it had become clear that there were delays and cost overruns in the Recruiting Partnering Project.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183374","183374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32967","2014-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many army and reserve applications he estimates have been lost as a result of faults in the Recruiting Partnering Project.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183375","183375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32968","2014-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects to take a decision on whether to pay Capita to build its own IT platform as part of the Recruiting Partnering Project.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183376","183376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32969","2014-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish a detailed rationale and criteria for his Department's 2011 decision to accept the Capita bid to run the Recruiting Partnering Project.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183377","183377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32970","2014-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what meetings Ministers and officials in his Department have held with the project team for the Recruiting Partnering Project; and what was discussed at each such meeting.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183378","183378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32971","2014-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Minister in his Department gave authority for the decision for the Recruiting Partnering Project for army recruitment in 2011.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183325","183325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32972","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any benefit claimants have been subject to benefit sanctions while on a training course authorised by his Department.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183177","183177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33612","2014-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of recent changes in burial fees charged by local authorities.","Biography information for Baroness Burt of Solihull","Lorely Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902050","902050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32384","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to disregard income provided to former service personnel in respect of injuries they received while serving in the armed forces when making social security benefit assessments.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182849","182849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32385","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government has considered recommendations for any sites for new towns or cities in Oxfordshire since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182949","182949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32386","2014-01-15","HM Treasury","2014-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will estimate the cost to the economy of the recent flooding in the Oxford area.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182834","182834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32387","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what locations the Government has considered for new towns or cities in the South East since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182950","182950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32388","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025, the Government's construction industrial strategy published in July 2013, what progress has been made on updating CSkills/HSE-funded research into all recognised card schemes in the construction industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182951","182951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32389","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025, the Government's construction industrial strategy published in July 2013, whether a high-level statement of industry's commitment to having young people working on construction sites has been produced.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182952","182952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32390","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025, the Government's construction industrial strategy published in July 2013, what progress has been made on creating a critical mass for the Building Information Modelling programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182953","182953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32391","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025, the Government's construction industrial strategy published in July 2013, whether the first plan for a (a) market-based and (b) technology-based programme for investment in energy low-carbon construction has been produced.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182954","182954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32392","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025, the Government's construction industrial strategy published in July 2013, whether his Department has given consideration to developing a climate change adaptation plan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182955","182955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32393","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025, the Government's construction industrial strategy published in July 2013, what progress has been made on establishing a trade grouping of UK-based contractors.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182956","182956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32394","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025, the Government's construction industrial strategy published in July 2013, what progress has been made on creating an entity to support overseas trade in construction.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182957","182957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32395","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many household fires (a) in total and (b) per capita each fire authority in England dealt with in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182924","182924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32396","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025, the Government's construction industrial strategy published in July 2013, what progress has been made on developing a co-ordinated approach to engaging young people; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182958","182958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32397","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025, the Government's construction industrial strategy published in July 2013, whether TrustMark has been relaunched.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182959","182959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32398","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the share of (a) manufacturing, (b) financial and (c) non-financial services as a proportion of the total UK economy was in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182925","182925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32399","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025, the Government's construction industrial strategy published in July 2013, what progress has been made on identifying local champions to develop regionally-focused pipelines in construction.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182960","182960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32400","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025, the Government's construction industrial strategy published in July 2013, whether a high-level statement of industry's commitment to having young people working on construction sites has been produced.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182961","182961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32401","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Construction 2025, the Government's construction industrial strategy published in July 2013, whether (a) his Department, (b) the Confederation of British Industry and (c) the construction industry has created a demand map for the industry for (i) infrastructure, (ii) Renovation Maintenance Improvement and (iii) new build to 2025.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182962","182962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32402","2014-01-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funds her Department has made available to repair First World War graves in the graveyard of St Mary Magdalene's Church in Hart Village; and if she will make statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182831","182831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32403","2014-01-15","Department for Transport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to introduce legislative proposals to implement EU Directive 2012/36/EU.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182830","182830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32404","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients attending accident and emergency departments were seen in under four hours in the first week of January of each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182818","182818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32405","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the guidance given by his Department to those dealing with claims for employment and support allowance where the claimant is known to be addicted to alcohol or drugs.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182813","182813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32406","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what account is taken of potential health and safety issues when declaring known drug or alcohol addicts as being fit for work; and what liability his Department has for subsequent problems.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182862","182862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32407","2014-01-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the number of people who do not have DAB radio receivers; and what steps she plans to take to assist consumers with the costs of acquiring such receivers before a digital radio switchover takes place.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182817","182817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32408","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many jobseeker's allowance claimants there were at each jobcentre in Birmingham and Solihull in each month between October 2012 and June 2013.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182823","182823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32409","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his Answer of 8 January 2014, Official Report, column 241W, on social security benefits, if he will publish the written guidance provided to staff to help them decide whether a short term benefit advance is appropriate.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182820","182820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32410","2014-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make available the Gloucestershire Growth Plan produced by Gloucestershire Local Enterprise Partnerships to all hon. Members representing that county.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183012","183012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32412","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding will be put in place to support local discretionary welfare provision after 2015.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182969","182969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32413","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is his policy to conduct a review of local discretionary welfare provision in May 2014.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182934","182934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32414","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in (a) the Metropolitan Borough of Wirral, (b) Birkenhead constituency and (c) the UK which have held their tenancy continuously since 1996 have been affected by the implementation of the under-occupancy penalty in social housing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182929","182929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32415","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households containing at least one carer have been affected by the implementation of the under-occupancy charge in social housing in (a) the Metropolitan Borough of Wirral and (b) Birkenhead constituency.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182922","182922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32416","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households that have suffered a bereavement since April 2013 have been affected by the implementation of the under-occupancy charge in social housing in (a) the Metropolitan Borough of Wirral, (b) Birkenhead constituency and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182921","182921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32417","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of any impact the implementation of the under-occupancy penalty in social housing has had on the number of households accumulating rent arrears in (a) the Metropolitan Borough of Wirral, (b)  Birkenhead constituency and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182920","182920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32418","2014-01-15","HM Treasury","2014-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much corporation tax was paid each year for the last five years under the tonnage system by UK-based shipping companies.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182923","182923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32419","2014-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to include Saudi Arabia in forthcoming P5+1 negotiations with Iran.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182964","182964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32420","2014-01-16","Department for Transport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of take-up rate of free pensioner bus passes in each local authority area.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182985","182985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32421","2014-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to opposition forces in Syria to develop governmental structures.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183002","183002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32422","2014-01-16","Department for Transport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost of a single, standard class open rail ticket from Barrow-in-Furness to (a) London and (b) Manchester has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183003","183003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32423","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to bring forward regulations under the Mobile Homes Act 2013 regarding fees payable to a local authority.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183004","183004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32424","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2013, Official Report, columns 87-8W, on telephone services, which organisations receive grant funding from or have contracts with his Department; how many telephone lines each organisation operates with the prefix (a) 0845, (b) 0844 and (c) 0843; how many calls each line has received in the last 12 months; and whether alternative numbers charged at the BT local rate are available in each case.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182930","182930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32425","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the 2014-15 NHS England Clinical Commissioning Group Outcomes Indicator Set (CCG OIS) will be published; and when the consultation on the next iteration of the CCG OIS will open.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182998","182998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32426","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the recent publication of Eurocare 5 statistics on cancer survival rates, what steps his Department is taking to improve early diagnosis to ensure that cancer is identified early in patients.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182996","182996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32427","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the £2.3 million of funding set aside for strategic clinical networks to improve awareness of symptoms has been allocated to assist early diagnosis of cancer.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182995","182995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32428","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many Article 4 directions relating to betting shops issued by each local authority his Department has been notified of in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182999","182999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32429","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many Article 4 directions relating to payday lending shops issued by each local authority his Department has been notified of in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183000","183000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32430","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effects on the number of (a) households and (b) children living in poverty of reductions in council tax benefit.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182979","182979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32431","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many Article 4 directions relating to fast food shops issued by each local authority his Department has been notified of in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183001","183001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32432","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, in how many cases where local authorities have issued Article 4 directions have they been required to pay compensation to those who permitted development rights have been withdrawn or curtailed as a result of the direction since May 2010.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182940","182940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32433","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, in how many cases he has (a) modified and (b) cancelled a local authority Article 4 direction since May 2010.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182939","182939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32434","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 758W, on employment and support allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber, how many people living in the City of York receiving employment and support allowance were moved from the support group to the work-related group; of those how many sought a review of that decision; and of those seeking a review how many were (a) moved back to the support group as a consequence of the review, (b) not moved back to the support group as a consequence of the review and (c) still awaiting the decision on their request for review in October 2012 and each month since then.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183028","183028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32435","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 758W, on jobseeker's allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber and 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 756W, on employment and support allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber, how many people living in the City of York receiving employment and support allowance were moved from the support group to the work-related group; of those how many sought a review of that decision; and of those seeking a review how many were (a) moved back to the support group as a consequence of the review, (b) not moved back to the support group as a consequence of the review and (c) still awaiting the decision on their request for review in October 2012 and each month since then.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183027","183027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32436","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 758W, on jobseeker's allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber and 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 756W, on employment and support allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber, how many people receiving jobseeker's allowance (JSA) in the City of York had their JSA withdrawn as a result of their alleged failure to comply with conditions laid down by his Department in October 2012 and each month since then.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183029","183029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32437","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 758W, on jobseeker's allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber and 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 756W, on employment and support allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber, how many people receiving employment and support allowance in the City of York were moved (a) from the support group to the work-related group and (b) from the work-related group to the support group in each month since October 2012.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183030","183030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32438","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answers of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 758W, on jobseeker's allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber and 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 756W, on employment and support allowance: Yorkshire and the Humber, how many people living in the City of York were receiving (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) employment and support allowance support group and (c) employment and support allowance work-related group in (i) October 2012 and (ii) each month since then.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183031","183031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32439","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether Alan Lewis had any responsibility for finance and governance at the Kings Science Academy in Bradford.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182871","182871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32440","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions his Department has had with Alan Lewis about financial management at the Kings Science Academy in Bradford.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182872","182872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32441","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent progress has been made by Kings Science Academy in the implementation of its improvement plan.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182850","182850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32442","2014-01-16","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many named illegal migrants are currently listed on the e-Borders database.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182842","182842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32443","2014-01-16","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many named illegal migrants are currently listed on the (a) National Operations Database, (b) Case Information Database, (c) National Allegations Database, (d) Migration Refusal Pool, (e) Warnings Index and (f) Watch Lists.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182841","182841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32444","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many inguinal hernia repair procedures were carried out in England (a) in total and (b) on people aged 65 and over in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182844","182844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32445","2014-01-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of reported radiation levels on the boundary of the Fukushima Nuclear Plant in Japan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182843","182843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32446","2014-01-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the review of the performance of Sellafield Nuclear Reprocessing Plant produced by KPMG Chartered Accountants Group for the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182870","182870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32447","2014-01-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the European Commission's ongoing investigation into the proposed nuclear plant at Hinkley Point; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182824","182824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32448","2014-01-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he last met the Chief Executive of the Office for Nuclear Regulation; and for what purpose that meeting took place.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182825","182825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32449","2014-01-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the regulatory priorities in the 2013 Annual Report from the Office for Nuclear Regulation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182888","182888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32450","2014-01-16","Northern Ireland Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress has been made on the introduction of further measures to tackle fuel laundering.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183005","183005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32451","2014-01-16","Northern Ireland Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Minister for Foreign Affairs in the Republic of Ireland on fuel laundering; and what the outcome was of such discussions.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183006","183006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32452","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has paid to private sector companies to develop the universal credit system; and what his projection is for IT spending on the project in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182987","182987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32453","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many private sector developers are being paid a salary rate of more than (a) £50,000 per year and (b) £100,000 per year for their work on developing the IT system for universal credit.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182986","182986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32454","2014-01-17","Department for International Development","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much aid the Government plans to give to Argentina during the current Parliament.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182942","182942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32455","2014-01-17","Department for International Development","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much aid the UK has given to Argentina since May 2010.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182943","182943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32456","2014-01-16","Department for International Development","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 11W, on Palestinians, for what reasons the reports she received concluded that emergency response systems were working adequately.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183013","183013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32457","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the continuing publication by the Office of National Statistics of its annual statistical bulletin on (a) Childhood, Infant and Perinatal Mortality, (b) Unexpected Deaths in Infancy and (c) Gestation Specific Births and Infant Deaths in England and Wales.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182984","182984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32458","2014-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of progress in establishing the independent international enquiry into events at the end of the conflict in Sri Lanka since the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182835","182835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32459","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have won appeals against loss of housing benefit under the Removal of the Spare Room Subsidy on the grounds that their eligible rent should have been determined in accordance with regulations 12 and 13 as set out in paragraph 5 of Schedule 3 to the Housing Benefit and Council Tax Benefit (Consequential Provisions) Regulations 2006 to date.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182836","182836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32460","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department intends to fill its current vacancies for software developers in its digital service and to build universal credit endstate system and other software projects.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182837","182837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32461","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in his Department are working on software for each of the universal credit IT systems currently planned.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182839","182839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32462","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total value is of the contract entered into by Stockdale Riverside College and (a) the Leadership Development Centre and (b) Vision Lifestyle for the employment of apprentices.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182829","182829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32463","2014-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure apprentices employed by (a) the Leadership Development Centre and (b) Vision Lifestyle are paid all outstanding monies owed to them.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182845","182845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32464","2014-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department can take when apprentices are not paid on time by their employer.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182967","182967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32465","2014-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what due diligence process his Department required (a) the Leadership Development Centre and (b) Vision Lifestyle to undertake prior to their acceptance as sub-contractors for Stockton Riverside College to employ apprentices.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182968","182968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32466","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of type 2 diabetes there have been (a) in total, (b) in each region and (c) in each parliamentary constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182989","182989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32467","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to (a) measure and (b) improve the health and wellbeing of the NHS workforce and its supply chain.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182990","182990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32468","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of (a) adults and (b) children with tooth decay in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182991","182991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32469","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the total amount spent by food and drink companies on advertising high fat, salt and sugar products in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182992","182992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32470","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the Government has to update the recommended guideline daily amounts of (a) sugar, (b) fat, (c) salt and (d) calorie intake.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182994","182994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32471","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will assess the potential benefit to traders of free parking in town centres.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182863","182863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32472","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what resources were made available in each of the last five years for rehabilitation of service personnel returning from Afghanistan.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182861","182861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32473","2014-01-15","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on cyber-bullying.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182857","182857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32474","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Northern Ireland service personnel are currently serving outside the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182858","182858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32475","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of people in Upper Bann constituency were employed in the (a) private and (b) public sector  in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182859","182859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32476","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on the health effects of cyber-bullying.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182860","182860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32477","2014-01-15","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the outcomes are of the Care2Work programme to date; how the outcomes are measured; how many people that programme has supported; and how many such people are in work since receiving help.","Biography information for Margot James","Margot James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182983","182983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32478","2014-01-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many people were fined for not holding a television licence in (a) Havering and (b) the UK in 2013.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183032","183032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32479","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that any proposed council tax increases are approved by residents.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183037","183037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32480","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to review the effectiveness of his policy on tackling obesity in England.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183033","183033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32481","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Government's Change4Life campaign to tackle obesity.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183034","183034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32482","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prevent local authorities imposing excessive parking charges and pursuing aggressive parking enforcement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183038","183038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32483","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) children under 13, (b) teenagers aged 13 to 19, (c) adults aged 20 to 65 and (d) adults aged 65 and over are currently classed as obese in England.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183035","183035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32484","2014-01-15","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of recent trends in the level of crime in the London Borough of Havering.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183039","183039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32485","2014-01-15","HM Treasury","2014-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to decrease the tax on bingo to bring it in line with taxation rates applying to other gambling industries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183036","183036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32486","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many houses have been brought back into use in the London Borough of Havering as a result of changes to the underoccupancy penalty.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183040","183040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32487","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to reform existing trades union legislation to prevent public transport unions undertaking excessive numbers of strikes and to provide independent binding arbitration of future disputes on the London Transport Network and other areas.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183041","183041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32488","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish an impact assessment in respect of his Department's decision to cut funding for 18 year olds.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182928","182928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32489","2014-01-15","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many registered childcare places there were in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) Nottinghamshire in (i) 2009, (ii) 2010, (iii) 2011, (iv) 2012 and (v) 2013.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182903","182903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32490","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the per capita spend on mental health services was in each primary care trust in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) Nottinghamshire in each of the last five years; and how those figures compare to the national average in that period.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182902","182902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32491","2014-01-15","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the schools assessed by Ofsted in Nottinghamshire in 2013 were rated as (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requiring improvement and (d) inadequate.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182900","182900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32492","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what change there has been in median gross weekly pay for (a) men and (b) women in Ashfield constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182899","182899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32493","2014-01-15","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many 16 to 18 year olds were not in education, employment or training in (a) England and (b) each local authority area in the East Midlands in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182901","182901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32494","2014-01-15","HM Treasury","2014-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employers have been (a) recorded by HM Revenue and Customs, (b) prosecuted and (c) convicted for failure to pay eligible employees the national minimum wage in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182832","182832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32495","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the Military Aviation Authority to publish its Annual Air Safety Report for 2012-13.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182905","182905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32496","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) established and (b) actual strength was of the (i) regular and (ii) reserve personnel in the (A) Royal Armoured Corps, (B) Household Cavalry Regiment, (C) 1st The Queen's Dragoon Guards, (D) Royal Scots Dragoon Guards, (E) Royal Dragoon Guards, (F) merged unit of the Queen's Own Hussars and the Royal Irish Hussars, (G) merged unit of the 9/12th Royal Lancers and the Queen's Royal Lancers, (H) The King's Royal Hussars, (I) Light Dragoons, (J) Queen's Royal Lancers, (K) 1st Royal Tank Regiment and (L) 2nd Royal Tank Regiment on 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182904","182904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32497","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many aircraft by type will be in inventory of the (a) RAF, (b) Royal Navy and (c) Army Air Corps in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182906","182906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32498","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many operational cruises HMS Astute has undertaken since she was commissioned.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182907","182907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32499","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assets and how many personnel are taking part in Exercise Red Flag; and what his estimate is of the cost to the public purse.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182909","182909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32500","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assets and how many personnel took part in the last five Red Flag exercises.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182910","182910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32501","2014-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on (a) the intervention of US Special Envoy Donald Booth in South Sudan and (b) current preparations for ceasefire negotiations between the South Sudanese government and rebel forces.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182919","182919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32502","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) established and (b) actual strength was of the (i) regular and (ii) reserve personnel in the (A) 2nd Battalion, Duke of Lancaster's Regiment, (B) 1st Battalion, Royal Regiment of Fusiliers, (C) 2nd Battalion, Royal Regiment of Fusiliers, (D) 1st Battalion, Royal Anglian Regiment, (E) 2nd Battalion, Royal Anglian Regiment, (F) 1st Battalion, Yorkshire Regiment, (G) 2nd Battalion, Yorkshire Regiment, (H) 3rd Battalion, Yorkshire Regiment, (I) 1st Battalion, Royal Welsh, (J) 2nd Battalion, Royal Welsh, (K) 1st Battalion, Mercian Regiment, (L) 2nd Battalion, Mercian Regiment, (M) 3rd Battalion, Mercian Regiment, (N) 1st Battalion, Royal Irish Regiment, (O) 2nd Battalion, Parachute Regiment, (P) 3rd Battalion, Parachute Regiment, (Q) 1st Battalion, Royal Gurkha Rifles, (R) 2nd Battalion, Royal Gurkha Rifles, (S) 1st Battalion, The Rifles, (T) 2nd Battalion, The Rifles, (U) 3rd Battalion, The Rifles, (V) 4th Battalion, The Rifles and (W) 5th Battalion, The Rifles on 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182916","182916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32503","2014-01-15","Department for International Development","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the recent influx of refugees from the Central African Republic into Chad on humanitarian efforts in that country; and what aid the Government is providing to humanitarian organisations operating in Chad.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182917","182917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32504","2014-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the impact of the recent mass emigration from the Central African Republic on stability in that country and the wider region.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182918","182918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32505","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions the RC135 Airseeker has flown from RAF Waddington.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182908","182908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32506","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many days (a) last year and (b) this year to date the (i) Chief of the Air Staff, (ii) First Sea Lord and (iii) Chief of the General Staff worked in London.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182911","182911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32507","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) established and (b) actual strength was of the (i) regular and (ii) reserve personnel in the (A) 1st Battalion, Grenadier Guards, (B) 1st Battalion, Coldstream Guards, (C) 1st Battalion, Scots Guards, (D) 1st Battalion, Irish Guards, (E) 1st Battalion, Welsh Guards, (F) 1st Battalion, Duke of Lancaster's Regiment, (G) 1st Battalion, Royal Regiment of Scotland, (H) 2nd Battalion, Royal Regiment of Scotland, (I) 3rd Battalion, Royal Regiment of Scotland, (J) 4th Battalion, Royal Regiment of Scotland, (K) 5th Battalion, Royal Regiment of Scotland, (L) 1st Battalion, Princess of Wales's Royal Regiment and (M) 2nd Battalion, Princess of Wales's Royal Regiment on 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182912","182912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32508","2014-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the conflict in South Sudan.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182913","182913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32509","2014-01-15","Department for International Development","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she has taken to assist the growing number of internally-displaced persons in South Sudan.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182914","182914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32510","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the planned launch and in-service dates are for each remaining submarine in the Astute class.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182980","182980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32511","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the replacement value is of a single UK Trident warhead.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182981","182981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32512","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when work on (a) the Defence Nuclear Safety Regulator's review of the Ministry of Defence nuclear regulatory framework and (b) the Defence Nuclear Safety Regulator's regulatory strategy will be complete; and whether his Department will publish those documents.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182982","182982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32513","2014-01-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK will be represented at the conference on the humanitarian effects of nuclear weapons hosted by the Mexican government at Nayarit on 13 and 14 February 2014.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182993","182993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32514","2014-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent reports of human rights abuses in Mauritania.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182915","182915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32515","2014-01-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department has taken to reduce electrical waste since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182926","182926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32516","2014-01-15","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional funding she is providing to (a) Avon and Somerset Police and (b) Gloucestershire Police to meet the costs of policing the badger cull.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182851","182851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32517","2014-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy that in all contacts with the governments of Arab countries his Department wil raise issues of religous intolerance and promote the Universal Declaration of Human Rights to protect Christians and other religious minorities.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182808","182808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32518","2014-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the UK has made to the government of Sudan on ending its policies that remove Christian missionaries and persecute those who convert to Christianity from Islam.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182809","182809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32519","2014-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of progress on the removal of chemical weapons from Syria.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182810","182810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32520","2014-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will work with UN Security Council members and the UK's allies in the Southern African Development Community to ensure a resolution is passed to mandate a neutralisation of Democratic Forces for the Liberation of Rwanda and the Hutu militia group.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182811","182811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32521","2014-01-15","Department for Transport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what improvements to the UK rail network are required by the Trans-European Conventional Rail Network.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182856","182856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32522","2014-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations the UK has made to governments in the Middle East and Africa on protection of religious groups and eradicating intolerance of Christians.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182855","182855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32523","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much has been paid to Torbay Council for homelessness prevention and in homelessness prevention grants combined in each year since  2010.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182853","182853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32524","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much has been paid in supporting people grants to Torbay Council in each year since  2010.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182854","182854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32525","2014-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to open discussions with Iran on releasing prisoners of conscience and those jailed for promoting Christianity.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182852","182852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32526","2014-01-15","Department for Transport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential benefits and disadvantages of electrifying the rail line between Newbury and Penzance.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182945","182945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32527","2014-01-15","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many hours of overtime were worked by police officers policing the pilot badger cull in (a) Somerset and (b) Gloucestershire.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182946","182946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32528","2014-01-15","Prime Minister","2014-01-13","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will transfer responsibility for policy relating to annuities from the Chancellor of the Exchequer to the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182947","182947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32529","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the capabilities of local enterprise partnerships to deliver large infrastructure projects; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182944","182944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32530","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the 2014-15 and 2015-16 allocations by NHS England to clinical commissioning groups published on 18 December 2013, how much funding per patient has been allocated to each such group.","Biography information for Dr Thérèse  Coffey","Dr Thérèse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182948","182948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32531","2014-01-15","Department for Transport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will review his Department's guidance to local authorities on shared space.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182827","182827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32532","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new dwelling completions per 1,000 housing stock there have been since December 2006 in each local authority area.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182828","182828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32533","2014-01-15","Department for International Development","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's funding has been spent on reducing preventable newborn mortality since 2010.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182826","182826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32534","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on local authorities increasing council tax by five pounds without a referendum in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182812","182812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32535","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average and (b) maximum length of time is that an individual who has been defined as an age dispute case has been held in an immigration removal centre pending release to local authority care in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183008","183008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32536","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average and (b) maximum length of time is that an individual who has been held in an immigration removal centre pending an age assessment in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183009","183009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32537","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many individuals have been detained in immigration removal centres for the purpose of age assessment in the last 12 months for which figures are available; and how many of those individuals were found to be (a) adults and (b) children.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183010","183010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32538","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in (a) the London Borough of Brent and (b) Brent Central constituency are in receipt of local housing allowance for (i) shared accommodation, (ii) one bedroom properties, (iii) two bedroom properties, (iv) three bedroom properties and (v) four bedroom properties.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183007","183007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32539","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will list each item valued at more than £500 of assets impaired as a result of his decision to discontinue the Enquiry Service facilities as set out in his Department's recent annual report and accounts.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182927","182927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32540","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what provision was made in the valuation of the property leased to Kings Science Academy Bradford of its (a) vacancy and letting history and (b) state of repair.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182868","182868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32541","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the valuation of the site of the Kings Science Academy, Bradford included the value of the buildings on the site.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182873","182873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32542","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the provision has been to recover the capital investment made by his Department and the Education Funding Agency in the new premises at Kings Science Academy, Bradford at the end of the lease period.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182874","182874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32543","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether Alan Lewis was present at any discussions of the site of Kings Science Academy, Bradford at meetings of the school's trustees.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182875","182875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32544","2014-01-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the privatisation of the Defence Support Group; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182965","182965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32545","2014-01-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what environmental assessment he has made of the potential effects of fracking on (a) disposal of waste water at the end of the process, (b) local geology and (c) local landscapes.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182833","182833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32546","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether an offer has been made to the Burmese Army of training in establishing mechanisms to investigate and prosecute cases where Burmese Army soldiers are alleged to have committed human rights abuses.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182814","182814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32547","2014-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what legal assistance his Department is providing to Andy Hall who has been accused of criminal defamation in Thailand.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182815","182815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32548","2014-01-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what EU mechanisms for supporting human rights defenders are being applied in the case of Andy Hall.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182816","182816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32549","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks arising from the scale and speed of the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182876","182876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32550","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme of poor design of operational processes.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182877","182877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32551","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the Chilcot inquiry can publicise all the evidence gathered.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182886","182886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32552","2014-01-15","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking in response to the UN Secretary General's call for member states to conduct a wide-ranging and open debate that considers all options on drugs policy.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182884","182884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32553","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance is given to commissioners to ensure that quality of provision is considered in the commissioning of drug and alcohol treatment services; and what arrangements are in place to monitor commissioning processes.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182885","182885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32554","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will remove Sir Jeremy Heywood from his role in deciding which documents should be released to the Chilcot inquiry.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182887","182887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32555","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme of inadequate engagement with trusts.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182878","182878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32556","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme of insufficient testing of operational designs.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182879","182879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32557","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme of lack of resources and preparation.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182880","182880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32558","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of prisoners' (a) proximity to homes and (b) contact with their families on (i) success of resettlement and (ii) reduction in reoffending.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182881","182881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32559","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to improve conditions at Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre since the last unannounced inspection by HM Chief Inspector of Prisons in October 2013.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182883","182883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32560","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what qualifications, experience and expertise are required of those providing treatment for alcohol and drugs misuse to offenders upon release.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182882","182882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32561","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much and what value of his Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182935","182935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32562","2014-01-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much and what value of his Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182936","182936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32563","2014-01-16","Department for International Development","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much and what value of her Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182937","182937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32564","2014-01-16","Department for Transport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much and what value of his Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182938","182938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32565","2014-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much and what value of his Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182941","182941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32566","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to tackle mandatory fuel purchase charges in the UK vehicle rental sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182821","182821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32567","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has made to his European counterparts on the enforcement of domestic and EU regulations against mandatory fuel purchases in the vehicle rental sector.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182822","182822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32568","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many 18 year olds are studying in further education institutions in Warrington; and what proportion of 16 to 18 year olds in further education that figure represents.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182846","182846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32569","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of 18 year olds in further education in Warrington are studying for (a) level 3 qualifications and (b) level 2 courses.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182847","182847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32570","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of 18 year olds in further education in Warrington come from areas of social deprivation.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182848","182848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32571","2014-01-16","Department for International Development","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will place in the Library a copy of the Report by the Parliamentary Ombudsman to the hon. member for Brighton, Pavilion of an investigation into a complaint made by Mr Oloko and her Department's response.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182838","182838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32572","2014-01-16","Department for Transport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what public relations, media or communications organisations, companies or individuals not directly employed by HS2 Ltd or his Department have been contracted to work on High Speed 2; and how much has been paid to them to date.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182869","182869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32573","2014-01-16","Department for Transport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2013, Official Report, column 123W, on High Speed 2, which individuals engaged by HS2 Ltd are still engaged via personal service companies.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182867","182867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32574","2014-01-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which sites in Buckinghamshire and Oxfordshire are being considered for the development of large communities or garden cities.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182966","182966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32575","2014-01-16","Department for Transport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to section 7.10 of the non-technical summary of the London-West Midlands Environmental Statement published in November 2013, how many people are available along the route who could take advantage of preferment for employment.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182963","182963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32576","2014-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on which occasions HM Prison Oakwood has provided tornado-trained staff to other prisons to deal with disturbances since it first opened.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182865","182865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32577","2014-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on which occasions tornado-trained staff have  been used to deal with disturbances in each prison since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182866","182866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32578","2014-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what staff turnover was in each probation trust in England and Wales in each month since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182864","182864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32579","2014-01-16","Department for Transport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department made ahead of the rollout of European Rail Track Management System (ERTMS) signaling across the rail network; what assessment he has made of the cost of introducing ERTMS signalling; and what assessment he has made of the timescale for the rollout of ERTMS signalling.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182840","182840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32580","2014-01-16","HM Treasury","2014-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which Ministers in his Department have undertaken which training courses; and who provided each course at what cost since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182932","182932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32581","2014-01-16","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for each of the last three financial years how much and what proportion of the Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools; and what the value of such contracts was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182931","182931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32582","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for each of the last three financial years how much and what proportion of the Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools; and what the value of such contracts was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182975","182975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32583","2014-01-16","Department for Education","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for each of the last three financial years how much and what proportion of the Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools; and what the value of such contracts was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182976","182976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32584","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for each of the last three financial years how much and what proportion of the Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools; and what the value of such contracts was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182977","182977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32585","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much and what proportion of the Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools in each of the last three financial years; and what the value of such contracts was.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182978","182978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32586","2014-01-15","HM Treasury","2014-01-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the estimated cost to his Department is of (a) internal counsel and legal cost and (b) external counsel and legal costs in the matter of the legal challenge to the remuneration provisions of the EU capital requirements legislation.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182997","182997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32587","2014-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he expects to receive the report by the Independent Expert Panel assessing the badger cull pilots.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182970","182970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32588","2014-01-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department has collected on air quality in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) each region of the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182971","182971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32589","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received raising concerns that junior doctors are put under pressure to work longer than permitted under working time regulations but not to declare it.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182973","182973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32590","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will investigate whether junior doctors are working hours and shifts which could lead to fatigue.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182974","182974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32591","2014-01-16","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will investigate whether junior doctors are in compliance with working time regulations.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182972","182972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32592","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what criteria and procedures were used for the appointment of the incumbent Secretary to the Lord Lieutenant of County Durham.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183025","183025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32593","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the job title and brief job description is of every official in his Department earning over £100,000 per year.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183026","183026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32594","2014-01-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, from which portion of his Department's budget the planned new recruitment drive for the Army will be borne.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183011","183011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32595","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, to what extent vice lord lieutenants are required to be politically neutral; and what guidance on political objectivity is to given to them.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183014","183014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32596","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether vice lord lieutenants are prohibited from making donations to political parties.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183015","183015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32597","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the area of residence is of each of the incumbent deputy lieutenants in County Durham.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183017","183017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32598","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which officials honours were bestowed upon people from County Durham in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183018","183018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32599","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which organisations and individuals received the Queen's Award for Voluntary Service in County Durham in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183019","183019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32600","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which organisations and individuals have received the Queen's Award for Enterprise in County Durham in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183020","183020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32601","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish a detailed breakdown of the costs incurred by the Vice Lord Lieutenant of County Durham in the fulfilment of his duties since his appointment to that role.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183022","183022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32602","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what criteria and procedures were used for the appointment of each of the incumbent deputy lieutenants in County Durham.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183023","183023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32603","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what criteria and procedures were used for the appointment of the incumbent Vice Lord Lieutenant of County Durham.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183024","183024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32604","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish a detailed breakdown of the costs incurred by each of the deputy lord lieutenants of County Durham in the fulfilment of their duties since their appointment to that role.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183021","183021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32605","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish a detailed breakdown of the costs incurred by the Lord Lieutenant of County Durham in the fulfilment of her duties since her appointment to the role.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183016","183016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32606","2014-01-15","Department for Transport","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 506W, on offshore industry, for what reasons the (a) Eurocopter AS332 Super Puma Mk 1 and (b) Eurocopter EC225 Super Puma models do not feature in the table provided; and if he will provide the information requested in relation to these helicopter models.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182819","182819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32607","2014-01-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in each parliamentary constituency in Cornwall have taken up auto-enrolment into a workplace pension to date.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182988","182988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32608","2014-01-15","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of those detained at Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre were the subject of a Rule 35 report in each of the last 12 months; and how many were released from detention as a consequence.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182898","182898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32609","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of those found to be committing benefit fraud and not prosecuted in court in each of the last five years (a) have repaid monies due in full, (b) are actively making repayments, (c) are in arrears with their repayments and (d) have been prosecuted for breaching their agreement to pay.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182897","182897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32610","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in how many cases the Child Support Agency has started committal proceedings in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182896","182896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32611","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the progress of the Child Support Agency in restarting committal proceedings since the end of the moratorium.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182895","182895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32612","2014-01-15","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of those detained in each of the last 12 months at (a) Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre and (b) all immigration detention centres were considered to have been a victim of torture; and how many of those were released from detention as a consequence.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182893","182893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32613","2014-01-15","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of those detained at (a) Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre and (b) all immigration detention centres were diagnosed with post traumatic stress disorder in each of the last 12 months; and how many of those were (i) released from detention as a consequence and (ii) transferred to a hospital under the Mental Health Act 1983.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182894","182894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32614","2014-01-15","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of those detained at (a) Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre and (b) all immigration detention centres were diagnosed with a mental illness in each of the last 12 months; and how many of those were (i) released from detention as a consequence and (ii) transferred to a hospital under the Mental Health Act 1983.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182892","182892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32615","2014-01-15","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average daily cost of detention per person in each of the last three years was at (a) Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre and (b) all immigration detention centres.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182889","182889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32616","2014-01-15","Home Office","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employers and organisations are registered with the Disclosure and Barring Service (DBS); how many such employers and organisations have registered with the DBS Update Service; and how many have requested a certificate check through the Update Service in the last six months.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182890","182890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32617","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made towards recruiting 10 per cent of patients living with dementia to participate in a clinical trial.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182891","182891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32618","2014-01-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the cross-Government working party on statistics for zero-hours contracts has met to date; and when any final report from that body will be published.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182933","182933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32647","2014-01-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to ensure that vulnerable customers do not pay disproportionately high unit costs for gas and electricity.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902008","902008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32661","2014-01-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions he has had with power companies on their preparedness to deal with bad weather events.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 901994","901994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32662","2014-01-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to help consumers reduce their energy bills.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902000","902000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32717","2014-01-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to ensure that solar PV is appropriately sited.","Biography information for Baroness Burt of Solihull","Lorely Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902017","902017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32832","2014-01-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment he has made of proposed levels of investment in electricity generation.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 901996","901996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32901","2014-01-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to improve competition in the wholesale energy market.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902013","902013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32225","2014-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Birmingham, Hall Green constituency have been incorrectly charged an under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182754","182754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32226","2014-01-15","Home Office","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions recommended by police forces using intelligence developed by the Child Exploitation and Online Protection Centre were successful in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182748","182748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32227","2014-01-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many and what proportion of households in England use token prepayment meters.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182765","182765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32228","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what savings he expects to realise as a result of the implementation of the under-occupancy penalty in each year to 2015-16.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182750","182750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32229","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much expenditure his Department has allocated to discretionary housing payments for tenants in the social housing sector in each year to 2015-16.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182751","182751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32230","2014-01-15","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-10","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December 2013, Official Report, column 226W, on pay, if he will publish the names of the six contractors who currently do not pay the London Living Wage to all staff.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182755","182755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32231","2014-01-15","HM Treasury","2014-01-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many new applications for child tax credits were made in (a) Essex and (b) Chelmsford constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182756","182756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32232","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of trends in rent arrears in social housing in (a) Essex and (b) Chelmsford constituency.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182757","182757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32233","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the proportion of private sector letting not available to tenants in receipt of housing benefit in Essex and Chelmsford.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182759","182759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32234","2014-01-14","Home Office","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many houses provided through the COMPASS contracts do not meet contractual standards on quality due to (a) minor and (b) major defects.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182742","182742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32235","2014-01-14","Home Office","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to apply key performance indicators to the COMPASS contract.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182743","182743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32236","2014-01-14","Home Office","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional costs her Department incurred in 2013 in the development of the COMPASS programme above those initially planned for; and what the estimated cost of the programme is over the next seven years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182740","182740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32237","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the total amount of housing benefit wrongly withheld from people under the removal of the spare room subsidy whose eligible rent should have been determined in accordance with regulations 12 and 13 as set out in paragraph 5 of Schedule 3 to the Housing Benefit and Council Tax Benefit (Consequential Provisions) Regulations 2006; and what estimate he has made of the average loss for each household affected.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182766","182766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32238","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure refunds are paid to people who have lost housing benefit under the removal of the spare room subsidy but should not have done so, due to their eligible rent not having been determined in accordance with regulations 12 and 13 as set in paragraph 5 of Schedule 3 to the Housing Benefit and Council Tax Benefit (Consequential Provisions) Regulations 2006.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182769","182769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32239","2014-01-14","Department for Education","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps are being taken by his Department to ensure that (a) vacant Governor places are filled, particularly in rural and coastal areas and (b) such Governors are representative of a wide range of groups, including local employers.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182744","182744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32240","2014-01-14","Department for Education","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the expected implications are for learners and colleges of the proposed reduction in funding for 18 year olds, particularly those learners undertaking level 3 vocational programmes.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182745","182745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32241","2014-01-14","Department for Education","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consultation was undertaken before the recent announcement that funding for 18 year olds will be reduced to 17.5 per cent of that allocated to 16 and 17 year olds.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182746","182746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32242","2014-01-14","Home Office","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 27W, on human trafficking, if she will place in the Library a copy of (a) the Foundation Training Programme and (b) the Competent Authority Training.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182747","182747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32243","2014-01-14","HM Treasury","2014-01-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 157W, on Gangmasters Licensing Authority (GLA), what proportion of notifications of breaches of minimum wage received by the National Minimum Wage Inspectorate from the GLA (a) were investigated and (b) resulted in compensation payments in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12 and (iii) 2012-13.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182752","182752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32244","2014-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 157W, on Gangmasters Licensing Authority, what the number and value of compensation payments through the imposition of compensation orders was in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182753","182753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32245","2014-01-15","Cabinet Office","2014-01-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason his note of 6 December 2013 on implementing the Military Covenant did not include reference to any activity related to the Ministry of Justice.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182764","182764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32246","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 Janaury 2014, Official Report, column 146W, on NHS Institute for Innovation and Improvement, what the (a) name was of each consultant used and (b) value was of each contract for consultancy for the NHS Institute for Innovation and Improvement in the most recent year for which data is obtainable.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182749","182749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32247","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on which occasions HMP Oakwood has called on tornado-trained staff from other prisons to deal with disturbances since first opening.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182760","182760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32248","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions the National Tactical Response Group has been called out to Oakwood Prison since the opening of that prison; on what date each such call-out occurred; and what the nature of the incident was.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182761","182761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32249","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on which occasions the National Tactical Response Group (NTRG) was called out in each month in 2013; and to which prison the NTRG was called out in each such case.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182762","182762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32250","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of persons convicted were given custodial sentences in each year from 2002 to 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182763","182763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32251","2014-01-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the potential effects of the agreement between PostNL and LDC to extend TNT's end-to-end delivery service on Royal Mail.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182741","182741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32252","2014-01-14","Department of Health","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether people born with cleft lip and palate are entitled to cosmetic surgery on the NHS free of charge.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182781","182781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32253","2014-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to impose a statutory duty on Fire and Rescue Services in England to respond to flooding incidents.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182758","182758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32254","2014-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the Court of Appeal's judgment dated 20 December 2013 in relation to dangerous dogs, [2013] EWCA Crim 2396.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182783","182783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32255","2014-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to his Answer of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 729W, on the badger cull, when he plans to publish the requested information on the full costs of the pilot badger culls.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182784","182784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32256","2014-01-15","Department for Transport","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that rail services in West Cumbria will be less affected by adverse weather conditions in future.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182800","182800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32257","2014-01-15","Department for Transport","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Network Rail delay minutes have been caused by adverse weather in Cumbria in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182801","182801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32258","2014-01-15","Department for Transport","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) passenger and (b) freight or non-passenger trains have been cancelled on the Network Rail London North Western route owing to adverse weather in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182802","182802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32259","2014-01-15","Department for Transport","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress he has made on the acquisition of additional rolling stock for the Northern Rail franchise.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182803","182803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32260","2014-01-15","Department for Transport","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the Cumbrian Coast railway line is protected from severe storm damage.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182799","182799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32261","2014-01-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people employed by (a) green organisations and (b) consumer groups were seconded to his Department in each of the last four years; and from which organisation each was seconded.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182788","182788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32262","2014-01-14","Home Office","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what clawback mechanisms are included in the COMPASS contracts; and whether she expects to exercise them.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182785","182785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32263","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many software developers his Department is currently seeking to recruit for its digital service in order to build the universal credit end state system and other software projects; and what contingency plan is in place in case it is unable to fill them all.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182767","182767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32264","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that people who have lost housing benefit under the removal of the spare room subsidy but should not have done so are informed of their actual housing benefit entitlement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182768","182768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32265","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have lost housing benefit under the removal of the spare room subsidy but should not have done so, due to their eligible rent not having been determined in accordance with regulations 12 and 13 as set in paragraph 5 of Schedule 3 to the Housing Benefit and Council Tax Benefit (Consequential Provisions) Regulations 2006; and of those, how many have left their homes.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182770","182770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32266","2014-01-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of his Department's overall procurement spend for each of the previous three financial years was (a) spent on joint procurement exercises with other departments and (b) shared between different organisations within the same department group.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182771","182771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32267","2014-01-15","Department for International Development","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's overall procurement spend for each of the previous three financial years was (a) spent on joint procurement exercises with other departments and (b) shared between different organisations within the same department group.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182772","182772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32268","2014-01-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of his Department's overall procurement spend for each of the previous three financial years was (a) spent on joint procurement exercises with other departments and (b) shared between different organisations within the same department group.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182773","182773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32269","2014-01-15","Department for Transport","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of his Department's overall procurement spend for each of the previous three financial years was (a) spent on joint procurement exercises with other departments and (b) shared between different organisations within the same department group.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182774","182774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32270","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of his Department's overall procurement spend for each of the previous three financial years was (a) spent on joint procurement exercises with other departments and (b) shared between different organisations within the same department group.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182775","182775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32271","2014-01-14","Department for Education","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when schools will receive the new funding for children adopted from care and those under a special guardianship order announced by his Department on 1 October 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182782","182782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32272","2014-01-14","HM Treasury","2014-01-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse has been of registering people for self-assessment tax who now qualify because of changes to child benefit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182787","182787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32273","2014-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to impose a statutory duty on the fire and rescue service to respond to flooding incidents.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182786","182786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32274","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 148W, on NHS: management consultants, where records and details of consultancy contracts are held.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182805","182805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32275","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 149W, on Peters & Peters, in which specific cases Peters & Peters were instructed in 2008, 2009 and 2010; and in respect of the ongoing case from 2005, how much Peters & Peters have been paid for the case.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182806","182806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32276","2014-01-15","Department of Health","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which legal firms his Department instructed in (a) 2008-09 and (b) 2009-10; and what the cost to the public purse was of those instructions.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182804","182804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32277","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to write to the hon. Member for Tooting with a full response to Question (a) 178975, (b) 179774, (c) 180654, (d) 180660, (e) 180670 and (f) 180671.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182807","182807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32278","2014-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people whose previous residence is listed as being in Coventry are currently in prison.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182791","182791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32279","2014-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people whose previous residence is listed as being in the West Midlands are currently in prison.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182792","182792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32280","2014-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average monthly cost of maintaining someone in prison is.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182793","182793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32281","2014-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what evidence his Department has used in formulating its proposals to sell parts of the Probation Service.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182794","182794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32282","2014-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received regarding damage caused by US oil company Chevron-Texaco in Ecuador.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182789","182789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32283","2014-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has discussed the issue of environmental and social damage caused by Chevron-Texaco in Ecuador with his counterparts in the Ecuadorian and US governments.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182790","182790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32284","2014-01-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department holds information on the level of reserves held by each local authority.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182798","182798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32285","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average ratio of prison officers to inmates in prisons in England and Wales was in June (a) 2009, (b) 2010, (c) 2011, (d) 2012 and (e) 2013.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182796","182796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32286","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the staff to prisoner ratio at each prison in England and Wales is.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182797","182797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32287","2014-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of fish stocks in UK and European waters.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182776","182776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32288","2014-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of trawling on fish stocks.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182777","182777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32289","2014-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many UK fishing businesses use trawlers when fishing.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182778","182778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32290","2014-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans the Government has to introduce measures to protect and replenish fish stocks in UK waters.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182779","182779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32291","2014-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which fish species commonly caught in the UK are currently considered at risk.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182780","182780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32292","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the staff to prisoner ratio at HM Prison Oakwood is.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182795","182795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31972","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will impose a maximum waiting period of eight weeks on Atos work capability assessments in Plymouth and Devon.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182540","182540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31973","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of average waiting times for ATOS work capability assessments in Plymouth and Devon; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182737","182737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31974","2014-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he took to ensure involvement by independent non-institutional experts in the Engineering and Physical Sciences Research Council programme supporting radioactive waste research announced on 8 January 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182567","182567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31975","2014-01-13","HM Treasury","2014-01-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs is investigating the off-shoring to the Cayman Islands of profits by UK Power Networks.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182515","182515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31976","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what work has been undertaken as part of the National Strategic Planning review of emergency planning in the evacuation of populations in (a) the three-mile radius detailed emergency planning zone and (b) the wider 30-mile radius zone around nuclear power plants following a serious release of radiation in an accident when roads within both zones are impassable due to heavy snow cover or extensive flooding.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182572","182572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31977","2014-01-13","Department for Education","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral Anwer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 14, on childcare costs, if he will give further details of how the figure of £18 billion was estimated.","Biography information for Mary Macleod","Mary Macleod","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182548","182548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31978","2014-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will fund a western conveyance channel aimed at cutting flooding risk in Oxford.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182568","182568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31979","2014-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of a western conveyance channel on flood prevention in Oxford.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182569","182569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31980","2014-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce flood risk in Oxford.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182570","182570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31981","2014-01-13","Department for Education","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the change in levels of racist bullying in schools was between 2012 and 2013.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182511","182511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31982","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with his colleagues in the Department for Communities and Local Government on the effect of the High Court ruling on housing benefit eligibility for rough sleepers who use night shelters.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182514","182514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31983","2014-01-13","Home Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department has met representatives of the alcohol industry to discuss the issue of minimum alcohol pricing in the last six months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182566","182566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31984","2014-01-13","Department for Transport","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential consequences arising from the proposed electrification of the Wigan to Bolton line for the use of diesel trains and rolling stock on the Northern Franchise operations in the Merseyside and Lancashire area.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182592","182592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31985","2014-01-13","Department for Transport","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the effect on other connected lines would be of electrifying the Wigan to Bolton line.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182600","182600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31986","2014-01-13","Department for Transport","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans for the electrification of the Wigan to Bolton line are currently planned by his Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182713","182713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31987","2014-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the potential cost to the UK cement industry of carbon floor price compensation measures under the EU's draft guidelines on environmental and energy aid for 2014-2020, published on 18 December 2013.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182738","182738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31988","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total spend on employment and support allowance has been in each month of the last five years in (a) Birmingham, Hall Green constituency, (b) Birmingham and (c) England.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182729","182729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31989","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total amount of (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) any other benefits withheld in sanctions was in each month of the last five years in (i) Birmingham, Hall Green constituency, (ii) Birmingham and (iii) England.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182730","182730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31990","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what savings to the public purse have accrued as a result of the under-occupancy penalty in each month since its introduction from (a) Birmingham, Hall Green constituency (b) Birmingham and (c) England.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182733","182733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31991","2014-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what savings to the public purse have accrued from the changes to council tax benefit in each month since April 2013, from (a) Birmingham, Hall Green constituency, (b) Birmingham and (c) England.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182736","182736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31992","2014-01-13","Department for Transport","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of closures on the road network as a result of the construction of High Speed 2; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182545","182545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31993","2014-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made any commitments not to support a UN General Assembly resolution on human rights in Burma in 2014.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182504","182504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31994","2014-01-13","Department for International Development","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many women who have been victims of rapes and sexual violence by Burmese armed forces have received financial assistance from her Department in the last two years.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182505","182505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31995","2014-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what outcomes are expected from training provided to the Burmese Army.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182506","182506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31996","2014-01-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that Burmese Army soldiers receiving training by UK armed forces have not been involved in human rights abuses in the past.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182507","182507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31997","2014-01-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will discuss with Ofcom the finding of its report Trends in Advertising Activity Gambling, published oin November 2013; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182711","182711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31998","2014-01-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to bring into effect sections 23-25 of the Administration of Justice Act 1982.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182564","182564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/31999","2014-01-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will now bring into force the provisions contained in the Easter Act 1928.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182565","182565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32000","2014-01-14","Department for Transport","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Christmas period on the ability of those affected to respond to the High Speed 2 Environmental Statement Consultation.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182617","182617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32001","2014-01-14","Department for Transport","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, by what method those wishing to petition the High Speed 2 Hybrid Bill must raise points in response to the Environmental Statement Consultation.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182618","182618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32002","2014-01-14","Department for Transport","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that those affected by High Speed 2 have enough information to respond to the Environmental Statement Consultation.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182619","182619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32003","2014-01-14","Department for Transport","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the information contained in the High Speed 2 Environmental Statement; and what assessment he has made of the effects of the amount of information within the Environmental Statement Consultation on those wishing to respond.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182620","182620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32004","2014-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2013, Official Report, columns 949-50W, on chancel liability, what recent assessment he has made of the effects of chancel liability.","Biography information for Andrea Leadsom","Andrea Leadsom","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182721","182721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32005","2014-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how his Department will ensure the independent assessment of the (a) humaneness, (b) safety and (c) effectiveness of the two pilot badger culls during the period of the extension of the pilots.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182591","182591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32006","2014-01-13","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-09","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how many school parties visited Parliament from each of the (a) English  regions and (b) other constituent parts of the UK in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182707","182707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32007","2014-01-13","Department for Transport","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department has allocated to programmes to make stations more accessible for people with disabilities; and if he will publish details of each such spending commitment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182714","182714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32008","2014-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2014, Official Report, column 240W, on jobseeker's allowance, how many short-term benefit advances were issued in each month from April to December 2013.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182563","182563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32009","2014-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance has been issued by his Department to decision makers on the awarding of short-term benefit advances.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182550","182550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32010","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the abolition of housing benefit on the Government's child poverty targets.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182712","182712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32011","2014-01-13","Department for Education","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on extending the provision of foster care up to the age of 21 for looked-after children in local authority care.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182571","182571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32012","2014-01-14","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average ratio of prison officers to inmates in prisons in England and Wales was in June 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182604","182604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32013","2014-01-14","Department of Health","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons respiratory health is not represented as a responsibility of any Minister in his Department in the List of Ministerial Responsibilities published in December 2013.","Biography information for Roger Williams","Roger Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182611","182611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32014","2014-01-13","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-09","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will assess any potential effect on (a) credit ratings and (b) jury composition of the implementation of individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182539","182539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32015","2014-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what meetings his Department has held with the Indian government on their assessment of the elections in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182492","182492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32016","2014-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure freedom of movement of opposition leaders in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182493","182493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32017","2014-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the decision not to send UK election observers to monitor the Bangladeshi elections; and what his policy is on sending observers to future such elections.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182495","182495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32018","2014-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the economic and industrial effect of the current instability in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182490","182490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32019","2014-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the legitimacy of the recent elections in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182491","182491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32020","2014-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to facilitate dialogue between opposing political parties in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182494","182494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32021","2014-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent meetings the British High Commissioner in Bangladesh has had with the Bangladeshi government to encourage the stability of that country.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182496","182496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32022","2014-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of housing development has taken place on (a) greenbelt and (b) brownfield land in each of the last 20 years in England; and how many (i) housing units and (ii) hectares of land this figure represents.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182525","182525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32023","2014-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many hectares of land in England have been (a) declassified and (b) classified as greenbelt in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182526","182526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32024","2014-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of the Work Programme in supporting those in long-term unemployment in (a) Essex and (b) Chelmsford constituency.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182606","182606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32025","2014-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of people claiming universal credit in (a) Essex and (b) Chelmsford constituency in April 2014.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182607","182607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32026","2014-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to create more employment opportunities for young people in (a) Essex and (b) Chelmsford constituency.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182608","182608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32027","2014-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) adults and (b) young people have been helped to find employment by Chelmsford Jobcentre Plus in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182609","182609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32028","2014-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Chelmsford constituency and (b) Essex have received personal independence payment since April 2013.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182610","182610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32029","2014-01-13","HM Treasury","2014-01-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of tax relief on (a) pension contributions on the overall level of contributions and (b) income and capital gains from ISAs on the overall level of non-pension savings.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182593","182593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32030","2014-01-13","HM Treasury","2014-01-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on reductions of the (a) lifetime allowance and (b) annual allowance for pension contributions on the overall level of pension saving.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182594","182594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32031","2014-01-14","Department for Education","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many sixth form college corporations have been dissolved in the last 10 years; and in each case for what reason the corporation was dissolved.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182624","182624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32032","2014-01-14","Department of Health","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the per capita expenditure and size of each general practice in Hampshire was in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182557","182557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32033","2014-01-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training on annuities and alternatives to annuities is provided to staff at the Pensions Advisory Service.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182555","182555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32034","2014-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2013, Official Report, columns 478-9W, on flood control, and his oral Answer to the hon. Member for York Central of 9 January 2014, for what reasons the earlier answer shows that his Department's spending on flood protection in England fell from £646 million in 2010-11 to £533 million in 2013-14 when his oral Answer on his Department's spending on flood protection states that he is providing more money for this purpose than any previous Government in the current spending review; how the £2.3 billion figure in his oral Answer relates to the £646 million and £533 million figures in the answer of 15 July 2013; how the figure of £2.3 billion was calculated; over what period the £2.3 billion will be spent; and what the evidential basis is for the statement that the current Government is providing more than any previous Government on flood protection.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182589","182589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32035","2014-01-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many full-time equivalent staff are currently employed in the Environment Agency's offices in (a) York, (b) Leeds, (c) Rotherham and (d) Hull; how many posts will be declared redundant in each office as a result of his decision to reduce the Agency's staff by 1,700 by October 2014; and what the duties are of each of the posts in Yorkshire that are currently being considered for redundancy.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182590","182590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32036","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 17 December 2013, Official Report, column 607W, on energy: company accounts, if he will place in the Library a copy of his instructions to Ofgem on the report on the transparency of financial accounts of the energy companies.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182536","182536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32037","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 31 January 2013, Official Report, column 895W, on energy: Scotland, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of changes in the market share of each of the six biggest energy suppliers in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182538","182538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32038","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Oral Statement of 2 December 2013, Official Report, column 631, on energy bills, what recent discussions he has had with energy suppliers on reductions in bills for customers on fixed-term contracts.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182535","182535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32039","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much onshore wind generation capacity was installed in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182500","182500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32040","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much biomass generation capacity was installed in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182501","182501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32041","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much small-scale hydroelectric generation capacity was installed in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182502","182502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32042","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much tidal generation capacity was installed in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182498","182498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32043","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much large-scale hydroelectric generation capacity was installed in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182503","182503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32044","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much offshore wind generation capacity was installed in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182499","182499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32045","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to Annex A of his Department's Main Estimate 2013-14 entitled Detailed breakdown of Part II table changes from 2012-13, (a) what programmes are supported and (b) how much funding each such programme receives under the sub-headings (i) K Manage our energy legacy responsibility and cost-effectively, (ii) L Nuclear Decommissioning Authority (NDPB), (iii) M Coal Authority (NDPB) and (iv) N Civil Nuclear Police Authority (NDPB).","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182704","182704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32046","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to Annex A of his Department's Main Estimate 2013-14 entitled Detailed breakdown of Part II table changes from 2012-13, (a) what programmes are supported and (b) how much funding each such programme receives under the sub-headings (i) E Deliver the capability DECC needs to achieve its goals, (ii) F NDA and SLC expenditure (NDPB), (iii) G Coal Authority (NDPB), (iv) H Committee on Climate Change (NDPB), (v) I Nuclear Decommissioning Authority Income (CFER) and (vi) J Electricity Market Reform.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182705","182705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32047","2014-01-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much has been raised in each local authority area and in total through the Community Infrastructure Levy (d106) in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182575","182575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32048","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many individuals employed by (a) major UK utility companies, (b) Energy UK and (c) any related energy utility organisation were seconded to his Department in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182547","182547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32049","2014-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many individuals employed by (a) major UK utility companies, (b) Energy UK and (c) any related energy utility organisation were seconded to his Department in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182541","182541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32050","2014-01-13","HM Treasury","2014-01-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many individuals employed by (a) major UK utility companies, (b) Energy UK and (c) any related energy utility organisation were seconded to his Department in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182542","182542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32051","2014-01-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many individuals employed by (a) major UK utility companies, (b) Energy UK and (c) any related energy utility organisation were seconded to his Department in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182543","182543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32052","2014-01-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many individuals employed by (a) major UK utility companies, (b) Energy UK and (c) any related energy utility organisation were seconded to his Department in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182544","182544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32053","2014-01-15","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-09","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what support his Department is giving the Bite the Ballot campaign in advance of National Voter Registration Day.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182726","182726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32054","2014-01-15","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-09","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what work his Department is undertaking to raise awareness of National Voter Registration Day.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182727","182727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32055","2014-01-14","Department of Health","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on limiting the amount of sugar in food and drink.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182558","182558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32056","2014-01-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he raised the issues of (a) the Israeli government's approval of new housing units at the illegal settlements of Ofra and Karnei Shomron and (b) the commitment made by the UK and other EU member states at the Foreign Affairs Council on 14 December 2013 to monitor settlement expansion and its broader implications, and act accordingly with the Israeli Foreign Minister on 7 January 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182519","182519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32057","2014-01-14","Department for Transport","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether a trial of the new managed motorway all lanes running design standard will be conducted before implementation of these schemes.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182724","182724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32058","2014-01-14","Cabinet Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people aged 24 and under in (a) total and (b) each Government office region have been unemployed for over a year in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182556","182556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32059","2014-01-14","Cabinet Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the rate of unemployment among young men of (a) Afro-Caribbean, (b) Bangladeshi and Pakistani, (c) other Asian and (d) other ethnic minority origin.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182716","182716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32060","2014-01-13","Department of Health","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of how clinical commissioning groups in Mid Derbyshire are planning for Parkinson's services in Mid Derbyshire.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182516","182516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32061","2014-01-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure members of the public receive a better service from the Child Support Agency.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182708","182708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32062","2014-01-14","Department for Education","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, columns 19-20, if he will publish a list of the Free Schools approved by Ministers which were amongst the 17 per cent of lowest-scoring against assessment criteria.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182517","182517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32063","2014-01-14","Home Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK registered vehicles were found to be on UK roads illegally because (a) the driver was not insured, (b) the vehicle lacked a valid tax disc and (c) the vehicle lacked a valid MOT by (i) county and (ii) police force area in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182605","182605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32064","2014-01-13","Home Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-human primates by (a) species and (b) country of origin were imported into the UK for the purposes of scientific research in each month of (i) 2012 and (ii) 2013; and how many such non-human primates in each category were (A) wild-caught, (B) F1 generation and (C) captive-bred.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182703","182703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32065","2014-01-14","Department of Health","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times Ministers and officials from his Department have met representatives of The Portman Group since May 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182715","182715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32066","2014-01-14","Department of Health","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the dates, agendas and minutes of any meetings Ministers and officials in his Department have had with representatives of the Portman Group since May 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182623","182623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32067","2014-01-14","Department of Health","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of disinvestment in spinal surgery by NHS trusts on neighbouring hospitals.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182602","182602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32068","2014-01-14","Department of Health","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on health outcomes of patients classified as urgent facing above-average waiting times for spinal surgery; and what steps he is taking to mitigate adverse effects arising from such waiting times.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182603","182603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32069","2014-01-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department is taking to assess the credibility and value-for-money of technologies available for re-use of plutonium in the UK.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182497","182497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32070","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to his Department of the Work Programme has been from June 2011 to date.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182579","182579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32071","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in work who would be claiming out-of-work benefits without the intervention of the Work Programme.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182582","182582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32072","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost of the Work Programme payments for (a) attachment, (b) job outcomes and (c) job sustainment has been from June 2011 to date.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182580","182580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32073","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of savings in out-of-work benefits through the intervention of the Work Programme to date.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182581","182581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32074","2014-01-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many referrals to the Work Programme there were from June 2011 to September 2013; and what the job outcomes are for people classed as (a) JSA 18 to 24, (b) JSA 25+ and (c) JSA early entrant.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182583","182583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32075","2014-01-14","Home Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many bonuses have been awarded to staff of her Department since 1 September 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182612","182612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32076","2014-01-14","Home Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many contracts her Department has awarded to Serco since 1 January 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182613","182613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32077","2014-01-14","Home Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many contracts her Department has awarded to G4S since 1 January 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182614","182614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32078","2014-01-14","Home Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what value of bonuses has been paid to staff of her Department since 1 September 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182615","182615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32079","2014-01-13","Home Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings she has had with the Metropolitan Police since 1 September 2013 to discuss UK citizens returning from Syria.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182597","182597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32080","2014-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many contracts his Department has awarded to SERCO since 1 January 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182596","182596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32081","2014-01-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many contracts have been awarded by his Department to G4S since 1 January 2013.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182595","182595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32082","2014-01-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of Newcastle City Council's application for the removal of deemed consent of To Let boards; and when he intends to announce a final decision on this matter.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182709","182709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/32083","2014-01-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on procedures for scrutinising and enforcing Colombian compliance with human rights clauses in the trade agreement between the EU and Colombia.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 182706","182706"
