"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601946","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic assessment he has made of relations between the Philippines and the UK since the appointment of President Rodrigo Duterte in June 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48768","48768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601947","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many pregnant women have been offered personal birth budgets since February 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48765","48765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601948","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions Ministers of his Department have had with Ministers of the Department for Justice on the investigation of stillbirths and neonatal deaths.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48766","48766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601949","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the NHS plans to publish Sustainability and Transformation Plans in full or summary form.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48767","48767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601950","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress the NHS has made on piloting the recommendations of the National Maternity Review since that review was published in February 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48748","48748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601951","2016-10-19","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has made an assessment of the procedures that Greenwich Clinical Commissioning Group followed when it took its decision to award the contract for musculoskeletal services to Circle Holdings PLC; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48757","48757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601952","2016-10-19","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to alter the terms of reference of the Expert Working Panel Group Inquiry into Primodos.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48751","48751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601953","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Healthier Together programme.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48712","48712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601954","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the status is of the Healthier Together programme in Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48711","48711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601955","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on the Healthier Together programme in Greater Manchester since that programme was introduced.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48714","48714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601956","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the measurable outcomes of the Healthier Together programme.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48713","48713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601957","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take in response to the findings on bullying and harassment in the Care Quality Commission's report on the South East Coast Ambulance Service NHS Foundation Trust, published on 29 September 2016.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48698","48698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601958","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take in response to the findings of the Care Quality Commission's report on the South East Coast Ambulance Service NHS Foundation Trust, published on 29 September 2016, relating to the performance of that Trust.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48699","48699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601959","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that health providers commissioned to give influenza vaccinations to patients at home are also commissioned to provide such vaccinations for eligible carers.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48800","48800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601960","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of his Department's budget for NHS providers' capital was transferred to revenue spending in each year since 2009-10; and what the capital budget and revenue budget was for NHS providers in each of those years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48796","48796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601961","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of the tendering process for the private company that will run the trust which provides support for people affected by contaminated blood; and how many full-time equivalent staff in his Department are involved in that tendering process.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48802","48802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601962","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the tendering process is for the private company that will run the trust which provides support for people affected by contaminated blood; which companies have expressed an interest in that tender; what the size of the initial bids made by those companies has been; and what the timetable is for that tendering process.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48803","48803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601963","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how (a) much funding from the public purse has been allocated to and (b) many full-time equivalent staff were employed by (i) UK Visas and Immigration and (ii) the UK Human Trafficking Centre for their work in relation to the National Referral Mechanism in each of year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48799","48799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601964","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who passed through the National Referral Mechanism categorised as victims of modern slavery and trafficking had no legal right of residence in the UK at the time of their passage and were potentially subject to immigration enforcement action in the event that they had not received a Reasonable Grounds decision in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48804","48804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601965","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how (a) much funding from the public purse has been allocated to and (b) many full-time equivalent staff have been employed by the Independent Anti-Slavery Commissioner in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48798","48798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601966","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who passed through the National Referral Mechanism as victims of modern slavery and trafficking were granted discretionary leave to remain in the UK in order to assist in police investigations and prosecutions in each fiscal year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48797","48797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601967","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Conclusive Grounds decisions reached through the National Referral Mechanism for victims of human trafficking and slavery took longer than 45 days in each year since 2009-10; and what central government funding was provided for decisions that were taken longer than 45 days in each of those years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48795","48795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601968","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Reasonable Grounds decisions reached through the National Referral Mechanism took longer than five days in each year since 2009-10; and whether the decision-making in each of those decisions was by (a) UK Visa and Immigration or (b) the UK Human Trafficking Centre.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48794","48794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601969","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which clinical commissioning groups fund homeopathy treatments; and if he will provide a list of those groups.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48703","48703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601970","2016-10-24","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 37587, what progress the Government has made on consulting local authorities to identified a specified number of children refugees to be resettled in the UK in the next year under subsection (1) of 67 of the Immigration Act of 2016.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48721","48721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601971","2016-10-19","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the possible closure of the Collective Passport Office will have on the ability of pupils from lower income families to afford passports for school trips.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48719","48719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601972","2016-10-24","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 37587, how many child refugees are planned to be resettled in the UK in the next year in accordance with subsection (1) of 67 of the Immigration Act of 2016.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48722","48722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601973","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2016 to Question 42399, what the equivalent data is for the most recent period for which such data exists, broken down by whether the application was made by (a) the police, (b) the National Crime Agency or (c) immigration officers.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48729","48729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601974","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department holds on the average length of time people going through the National Referral Mechanism remain supported by the Salvation Army following a Reasonable Grounds decision, in each fiscal year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48730","48730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601975","2016-10-18","Attorney General","2016-10-14","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions since the passage of the Modern Slavery Act 2015 have adult victims (a) applied for and (b) been granted the statutory defence for crimes they were compelled to commit while being enslaved or trafficked.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48731","48731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601976","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has any plans routinely to collect and publish data on (a) the response times and (b) the number of referrals through the National Referral Mechanism by First Responders.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48732","48732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601977","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings Ministers of her Department have had with social media companies to discuss harmful online content since May 2015.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48743","48743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601978","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on the rules that will apply to foreign students seeking employment after graduating (a) during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU and (b) once the UK has exited the EU.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48745","48745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601979","2016-10-19","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police cautions have been issued for offences under (a) section 127 of the Communications Act 2003 and (b) section 1 of the Malicious Communications Act 1988.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48754","48754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601980","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on issuing visas for overseas academies to participate in research at UK institutions (a) during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU and (b) once the UK has exited the EU.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48746","48746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601981","2016-10-19","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from women's groups on the problems associated with harmful speech on the internet.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48755","48755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601982","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she plans to take to allow universities to attract foreign students (a) during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU and (b) after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48770","48770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601983","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how the proposed changes to university admissions for foreign students will be tailored to different (a) courses offered and (b) educational institutions.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48771","48771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601984","2016-10-19","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Security Industry Authority licence applications were received in each of the last 12 months; and how many such applications were processed within 25 days.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48787","48787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601985","2016-10-19","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken to process a Security Industry Authority licence application has been in the last year.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48786","48786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601986","2016-10-19","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many stakeholders within the Collective Passport Service were consulted about the possible closure of the Collective Passport Office in Durham.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48784","48784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601987","2016-10-19","Home Office","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the effect on the level of immigration of each of the measures announced in her speech to the Conservative Party conference.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48791","48791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601988","2016-10-18","Department for International Development","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of projects that foster co-operation and co-existence have had on the prospects of securing lasting peace between Israelis and Palestinians.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48704","48704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601989","2016-10-18","Department for International Development","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to support projects that foster co-operation and co-existence between Israelis and Palestinians.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48705","48705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601990","2016-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 October 2016 to Question 46577 which foreign jurisdictions have made use of the information and resources to which she refers during the last five years; and how much has been received from such jurisdictions in fees.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48793","48793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601991","2016-10-18","Prime Minister","2016-10-14","To ask the Prime Minister, whether any government Minister was present at her meeting with Rupert Murdoch held in September 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48716","48716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601992","2016-10-18","Department for Transport","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the £55.7 billion cost of the High Speed 2 project also includes the cost for the High Speed 3 project.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48723","48723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601993","2016-10-18","Department for Transport","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the local economy of delays caused by accidents between junctions 12 and 14 of the M56 motorway.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48769","48769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601994","2016-10-19","Department for Transport","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to monitor the environmental effect of flights going to and from London City Airport; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48758","48758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601995","2016-10-19","Department for Transport","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what restrictions are in place controlling flights going to and from London City Airport; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48759","48759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601996","2016-10-18","Department for Transport","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what date his Department holds on the number of incidents involving (a) lorries and (b) buses that related to wheel loss.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48738","48738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601997","2016-10-18","Department for Transport","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding from the public purse his Department has allocated to the garden bridge project; and how many full-time equivalent staff in his Department have been working on that project.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48801","48801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601998","2016-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent steps his Department is taking to reduce the level of child maintenance arrears.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48749","48749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601999","2016-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children living in relative poverty in the UK (a) on the latest date for which figures are available and (b) a year before that date.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48785","48785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602000","2016-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much Disabled Facilities Grant was given to Bradford Council in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48735","48735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602001","2016-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that deafblind people and those with complex needs are able to secure meaningful employment in all professionals contexts.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48697","48697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602002","2016-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which post offices in each constituency have moved to premises shared with private sector organisations; and which organisations each such post office is sharing with.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48700","48700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602003","2016-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which post offices in each constituency have moved from ground floor to first floor premises in the last two years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48701","48701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602004","2016-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether public consultations or surveys were undertaken in the former Department for Energy and Climate Change to ascertain whether people trusted and understood the data-sharing element of the Warm Home Discount Scheme in the run-up to implementing that scheme.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48717","48717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602005","2016-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment of public opinion his Department has made on the construction of nuclear power stations on sites not currently occupied by such stations.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48775","48775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602006","2016-10-18","Department for Transport","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to impose fines on Volkswagen as a result of its manipulation of emissions tests in 2015.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48779","48779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602007","2016-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of accelerating the Small Modular Reactor Competition process.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48780","48780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602008","2016-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what forecast he has made of the date when the Government's Small Modular Reactor Competition (Phase One) will be completed.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48740","48740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602009","2016-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the cost of the Small Modular Reactor Competition (Phase One) to its completion.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48739","48739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602010","2016-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what independent body or bodies he plans will judge phase one of the Small Modular Reactor Competition.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48736","48736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602011","2016-10-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the economic effect of the UK leaving the EU on the steel industry in South Wales.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48741","48741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/602012","2016-10-19","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of adding a five years sunset clause to the proposed Great Repeal Bill governing the expiry of EU legislation which has entered the statute book.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48720","48720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600992","2016-10-18","Cabinet Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, (a) how many former Civil Servants have taken up employment in roles that directly relate to their work for the Government since May 2015 and (b) how many of those Civil Servants are working in the private sector.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48527","48527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600993","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what formal guidance the Government has issued to departments on equality impact assessments.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48607","48607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600994","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many equality impact assessments government departments carried out in each year between 2010 and 2016.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48637","48637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600995","2016-10-17","Cabinet Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the process used by the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments in drawing up its advice on appointments to be taken by former Ministers and former civil servants.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48629","48629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600996","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the Government's policy is on transitional arrangements for financial service providers to minimise disruption to financial markets during and after the process of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Mrs Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48636","48636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600997","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of money lost by UK investors as a result of Providence Bonds and Providence Bonds II being placed in administration in September 2016.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48608","48608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600998","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what communication has taken place between the UK Financial Ombudsman Service, the Bank of England and the Channel Islands Financial Ombudsman in relation to protection for investors in Providence Bonds and Providence Bonds II.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48609","48609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600999","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to increase financial protection for investors within the UK who invest in mini-bonds.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48610","48610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601000","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the level of financial protection available to investors in mini-bonds not covered under the financial services compensation scheme.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48612","48612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601001","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Financial Secretary to the Treasury of 14 September 2016, Official Report, column 914, how many people who had decisions made by Concentrix in relation to their tax credits overturned have received their payments within four working days.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48615","48615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601002","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2016 to Question 44746, how many of those letters were not responded to within 30 days; and what further action was taken against non-respondents from November 2014 to the end of August 2016.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48621","48621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601003","2016-10-18","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much EU Solidarity Fund flood relief funding the Government applied for after the 2015-16 winter storms.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48572","48572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601004","2016-10-18","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects to receive funding awarded by the EU Solidarity Fund.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48573","48573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601005","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the difference between the amount raised from the gift aid small donations scheme and the amount estimated to have been raised from that scheme by the second half of 2016 at its introduction.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48658","48658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601006","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much additional funding has been made available by HM Revenue and Customs to deal with the issues identified with Concentrix's handling of the tax credits checking contract.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48509","48509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601007","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when in the tax credits checking process Concentrix received payment for changing tax credit awards in a way which was initially thought to be correct.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48510","48510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601008","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to re-tender the contract for tax credit checks to another private company after the Concentrix contract ends or return the service to the public sector; and what the cost to the public purse was of the tendering process that awarded Concentrix that contract.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48516","48516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601009","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44815, what the total cost was of processing (a) mandatory reconsiderations and (b) appeals; and whether that cost was borne by (i) Concentrix or (ii) HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48543","48543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601010","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2016 to Question 44746, how many other letters to tax credit claimants were sent out in addition to those stated in that answer, how much, in total, it cost to issue those letters and whether the cost of issuing those letters was borne by (a) Concentrix or (b) HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48540","48540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601011","2016-10-18","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to review his Department's policies in light of the relative gain in strength of the Euro against sterling.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48558","48558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601012","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September 2016 to Question 45416, on Concentrix, (a) what the total cost was of the appeal cases listed in table 2 and (b) whether that cost was borne by (i) Concentrix or (ii) HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48542","48542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601013","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been paid to Concentrix for revising tax credit offers in a way which was initially thought to be correct; and if any of that amount can be subsequently recovered should those decisions be successfully appealed.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48517","48517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601014","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the introduction of the national living wage on the UK's international competitiveness.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48520","48520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601015","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for how long his Department plans that the Lifetime ISA will be on offer.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48523","48523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601016","2016-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an application to the EU Solidarity Fund before December 2016.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48559","48559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601017","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to limit the use of accessible toilets solely for disabled people.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48583","48583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601018","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons the publication of the Bonfield Review, due to be published in March 2016, has been delayed; and when he expects that review to be made available.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48622","48622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601019","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his oral contribution of 10 October 2016, Official Report, column 81, on the Neighbourhood Planning Bill and the Land Registry, for what reasons he has chosen not to privatise the Land Registry.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48623","48623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601020","2016-10-18","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the expression of interest made to his Department by Shepway District Council on proposals for a garden town development near Otterpool in Kent.","Biography information for Damian Collins","Damian Collins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48619","48619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601021","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to improve on the Sport England strategy to develop physical literacy in schools during this current Parliament.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48553","48553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601022","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to take advantage of new technologies such as activity and exercise tracking to improve childrens' fitness and physical literacy in schools.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48554","48554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601023","2016-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to repeal the EU directive on the artist's resale right after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48555","48555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601024","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to maintain discipline in the Army after changing the rules on physical punishment.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48521","48521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601025","2016-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the Marine Accident Investigation Branch report, published on 12 October 2016, on the collision involving the MV Karen fishing boat from Ardglass, County Down in the Irish Sea on 15 April 2016.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48552","48552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601026","2016-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with senior officials in the Royal Navy on the recommendations of the Marine Accident Investigation Branch report on the collision involving the MV Karen fishing boat from Ardglass, County Down in the Irish Sea on 15 April 2016.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48530","48530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601027","2016-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to announce the contract award date for the Defence Business Services corporate services integration and innovation provider contract; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48574","48574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601028","2016-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to pause the issuing of a formal contract notice in the Official Journal of the European Union for the outsourcing of Defence Business Services in light of the implications of the EU referendum result.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48575","48575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601029","2016-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department had with UK steelmakers before the decision was made to use French steel in the construction of Trident successor submarines.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48578","48578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601030","2016-10-18","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department received any bid from steel companies with plants in the UK to supply plate steel for the Successor class of nuclear submarines.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48618","48618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601031","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 14 June 2016 to Question 40132, whether there have been any changes to her Department's plans for the roll out of the National Teaching Service; and when her Department expects to confirm the details of those plans.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48579","48579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601032","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding per head is received for childcare in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber and (d) the UK in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48585","48585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601033","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding per head has been allocated for childcare in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber and (d) the UK in the financial years (i) 2016-17 and (ii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48586","48586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601034","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will review the effect of SATs in primary schools on children's mental health.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48627","48627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601035","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary and (b) secondary school teachers left the profession or took early retirement in each year for which data is available since 2011.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48673","48673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601036","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 26 July 2016 to Question 42842 and with reference to freedom of information requests ref: 2016-0032573 and ref: 2016-0042333, on pupil data sharing with the police and Home Office, on how many people has data been (a) requested and (b) provided in response to requests for information to the National Pupil Database made by the (i) Home Office and (ii) police; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48634","48634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601037","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to hold discussions with parents on the effect on children's mental health of primary school SATs.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48626","48626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601038","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 26 July 2016 to Question 42842 and with reference to freedom of information requests ref: 2016-0032573 and ref: 2016-0042333, on pupil data sharing with the police and Home Office, how many Home Office requests for information to the National Pupil Database for individual personal confidential data that have been granted were for the purposes of immigration control; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48635","48635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601039","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start centres have closed in Nottinghamshire since 2010; and where such centres were located.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48675","48675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601040","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary school children in each academic year have been eligible for the pupil premium in each year since it was introduced; and how much the Government has spent on pupil premium for primary age pupils in each year group in each academic year to date.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48679","48679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601041","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary school pupils in each year group in each (a) region and (b) local authority receive the pupil premium.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48678","48678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601042","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools with sixth forms there are where the proportion of students achieving GCSE A*-C in English and A*-C in mathematics is lower than the national average in each respective subject.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48667","48667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601043","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the compatibility of the policy in Schools that work for everyone, published on 12 September 2016, with the (a) UK's general obligations under the UN Convention on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities: Article 24 to promote disabled pupils' right to mainstream education, (b) Government's Interpretative Declaration commitment to build the capacity of mainstream schools to be inclusive of disabled pupils and (c) General Comment No.4 on Article 24, published on 2 September 2016.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48655","48655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601044","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the amount and proportion of funding for the free childcare entitlement which is currently retained by local authorities to support wider early years work.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48531","48531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601045","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department sought legal advice in advance of redrafting the Building Bulletin 100 guidance relating to sprinkler systems in school buildings; and what assessment her Department made of that advice.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48532","48532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601046","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to retain visa exemptions for PhD-level jobs after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48535","48535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601047","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether prospective EU national students will not be subject to tuition fee increases for the academic years 2018-19 and 2019-20.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48537","48537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601048","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of any correlation between the size of a school sixth form and the grade awarded by Ofsted for its sixth form provision.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48549","48549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601049","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it the Government's policy to ensure that schools are open to pupils from a range of different religious and non-religious backgrounds.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48556","48556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601050","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to retain access to the Erasmus Plus programme after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48539","48539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601051","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to monitor and support the mental health of (a) primary and (b) secondary school pupils.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48601","48601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601052","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the findings of the research on teachers' working hours, published by the Education Policy Institute on 10 October 2016, whether she plans to make an assessment of the findings in that research.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48604","48604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601053","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what provision her Department has put in place for SEND pupils who will not be able to pass selective school admission policies.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48550","48550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601054","2016-10-18","Department for Education","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what role Ofqual has in the setting of the requirements for special needs access to examinations specified by the Joint Council for Qualifications.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48500","48500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601055","2016-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to respond formally to the Soil Association's Save Our Anti-Biotic campaign.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48499","48499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601056","2016-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has spent to date of the £1.25 million committed to the Badger Edge Vaccination Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48504","48504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601057","2016-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to extend badger vaccination schemes in 2017.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48505","48505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601058","2016-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to prevent the small hive beetle from affecting the UK's bee population.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48506","48506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601059","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the number of people who have undertaken (a) training and (b) refresher training approved by her Department on humane shooting of badgers in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48569","48569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601060","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many operators have been licenced to carry out badger culling; and how many such licence applications have been refused since the badger cull began.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48570","48570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601061","2016-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has had discussions with suppliers other than Statens Serum Institut to procure the BCG vaccine.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48557","48557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601062","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the potential environmental benefits of a tax on disposable coffee cups.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48544","48544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601063","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people in (a) the UK and (b) Wiltshire have been prosecuted under sections (a) 1(3), (b) 3(1) and (c) 3(3) of the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 in (i) 2015 and (ii) 2016 to date; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48656","48656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601064","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to review regulations on food and drink packaging after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48653","48653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601065","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what methods are used to deliver her Department's approved training on the humane shooting of badgers.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48654","48654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601066","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to prevent the illegal killing of hen harriers.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48687","48687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601067","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to change its policy on the use of genetically modified organisms in farming after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48641","48641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601068","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the potential UK liability for EU disallowance penalties in relation to late payment by the Rural Payments Agency of Basic Payments in the 2015-16 CAP round.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48628","48628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601069","2016-10-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she estimates that the BCG vaccine will be available to resume the Badger Edge Vaccination Scheme; and what plans her Department has in place to procure BCG for this purpose.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48577","48577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601070","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what resources she has made available to ensure that Article 16 of the Tuberculosis (England) Order 2014 is enforced.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48611","48611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601071","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the press statement issued by the Minister for the Middle East and Africa on 5 October 2016, entitled Minister for the Middle East statement on plans to construct a new settlement in the West Bank, what discussions he has had with the government of Israel on preventing illegal settlement activity in the Palestinian Occupied Territories.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48624","48624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601072","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on demolitions that took place on 9 October 2016 in the community of Khan al-Ahmar in the Palestinian Occupied Territories.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48625","48625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601073","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role the Government plans to take in helping to facilitate a resumed dialogue between Somaliland and Somalia after presidential elections in Somaliland in March 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48669","48669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601074","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what overseas visits he has made since his appointment.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48662","48662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601075","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) his Chinese counterpart and (b) officials from Tibet on human rights in Tibet.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48663","48663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601076","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for the Commonwealth of the recent announcement by the government of the Maldives that the Maldives plans to exit the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48666","48666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601077","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on the economies of Commonwealth states of the UK's decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48664","48664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601078","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary-General of the Commonwealth on the UK's decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48665","48665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601079","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect the closure of the Dadaab refugee camp will have on the stability of Somalia and the East Africa region.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48649","48649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601080","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with key stakeholders in the pharmaceutical sector on the effect of the UK leaving the EU since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48689","48689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601081","2016-10-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the Somaliland government's work on reconciliation between the communities in the Sool and Sanaag regions of Somaliland; and what support the Government is providing in assisting with those efforts.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48526","48526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601082","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, at what (a) ministerial (b) official level the Government will be represented in the next round of the human rights dialogue with the Chinese authorities.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48563","48563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601083","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last raised the detention of the Panchen Lama with the Chinese authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48564","48564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601084","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the (a) Chinese and (b) Indian authorities on the damming of rivers in Tibet and the effect of that action on water supplies to India.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48565","48565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601085","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when a UK (a) Minister and (b) official last visited (i) the area designated by the Chinese government as the Tibetan Autonomous Region and (ii) the areas of Tibet subsumed by the Chinese government into China in the 1960's; what requests for such visits are outstanding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48566","48566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601086","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to review the level of limited diplomatic representations of the UK in Central America.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48519","48519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601087","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to require clinical commission groups to start collecting data on the number of children who have been abused and need therapeutic support.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48541","48541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601088","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) on how many occasions during the most recent negotiation period Ministers and officials of his Department met with representatives from the Pharmaceutical Services Negotiating Committee and (b) when he plans to announce a funding package for community pharmacy for 2016-17.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48605","48605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601089","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of the reduction in the number of community pharmacies in England of (a) five, (b) 10, (c) 25 per cent on the number of patients (i) seeking a GP appointment and (ii) attending accident and emergency units.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48606","48606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601090","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the diagnosis of stroke in children.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48595","48595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601091","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training is provided to NHS clinicians on diagnosing childhood stroke.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48596","48596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601092","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the lifelong support available to survivors of childhood stroke.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48597","48597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601093","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what engagement his Department has had with the families of childhood stroke survivors.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48598","48598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601094","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what activities have been undertaken by (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department to promote the benefits of children having the MMR vaccine since 2011.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48581","48581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601095","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he will publish the evidence he has concerning B12.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48594","48594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601096","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on the availability of injectable B12 over the counter.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48593","48593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601097","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the new 28-day diagnosis standard for all cancers on the urgent and non-urgent two-week waits for breast cancer referrals.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48508","48508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601098","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of implementing the recommendations contained in NICE's evaluation consultation document, Asfotase alfa for treating paediatric-onset hypophosphatasia, published on 22 September 2016, on the outcomes of people living with that disease.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48514","48514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601099","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with NHS England the decision to put treatment for (a) Waldenström's macroglobulinaemia and (b) other diseases on hold after the recent High Court decision on HIV pre-exposure prophylaxis.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48515","48515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601100","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with key stakeholders in the pharmaceutical sector on the effect of the UK leaving the EU since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48692","48692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601101","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of recommending newly created synthetic alcohols as safer and healthier alternatives to regular drinking when such alcohols reach the market.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48651","48651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601102","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to introduce (a) plain packaging for and (b) graphic warnings on alcohol sold in supermarkets.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48652","48652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601103","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential benefits of repealing provisions in UK law derived from the EU Tobacco Directive on to e-cigarettes in order to incentivise safer and healthier alternatives to conventional tobacco.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48685","48685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601104","2016-10-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has plans to bring forward legislative proposals to prohibit advertisements for fast food on television before the watershed.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48640","48640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601105","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications of devolution for the future of health services in the Liverpool City Region.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48630","48630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601106","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the number of (a) hospital and (b) community care service doctors working in the NHS by nationality.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48632","48632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601107","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 23 March 2016 to Question 31153, how many NHS organisations have now adopted the national whistleblowing policy and what progress has been made in developing a support scheme to secure work for NHS employees who have made protected disclosures.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48590","48590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601108","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to advice published by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention on the effect of varicella vaccination on shingles, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policy on mandatory varicella vaccination of the findings of that report.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48617","48617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601109","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will undertake a consultation with patients, staff and the public on the proposed closure of congenital heart services at Royal Brompton Hospital.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48616","48616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601110","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many scrap metal dealers have had their scrap metal licences revoked for not displaying a copy of their licence (a) at each site identified in the licence and (b) on any vehicle that was being used in the course of the dealer's business in each year since 2013.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48633","48633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601111","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for (a) personal, (b) project and (c) establishment licences for scientific research on animals have been granted in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48631","48631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601112","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what projection she has made of future demand for the Knowledge of Life in the UK test.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48672","48672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601113","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications her Department has received from (a) children in Europe who potentially qualify for resettlement to the UK under the Dublin III convention and (b) children currently in Europe who potentially qualify for resettlement to the UK under section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016 who do not have a family member in the UK since 2 July 2016; and what the (i) date and (ii) outcome of those applications were.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48680","48680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601114","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Written Statement WS114 of 21 July 2016, what new arrangements she plans to put in place at Tinsley House to safeguard and promote the welfare of children who previously have been detained in Cedars.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48681","48681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601115","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children were detained for immigration purposes at ports in the UK in each of the last three years; and how many such children were unaccompanied.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48682","48682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601116","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many families detained at Cedars Pre-Departure Accommodation were (a) removed from the country and (b) released into the community in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48683","48683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601117","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of applications for personal licences, project licences and establishment licences to carry out scientific research on animals have been (a) approved and (b) rejected in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48642","48642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601118","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK test centres for the Knowledge of Life in the UK were operating in each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48671","48671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601119","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons gender-based violence has been included in the Adults at Risk guidelines to caseworkers under the category mental health conditions.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48643","48643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601120","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what monitoring processes are in place to oversee the new Adults at Risk guidelines.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48644","48644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601121","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to monitor or re-evaluate the mechanisms in place under the new Adults at Risk guidelines.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48645","48645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601122","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what consultation process took place before the implementation of the new Adults at Risk guidelines.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48646","48646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601123","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the new Adults at Risk guidelines on the number of Rule 35 (3) reports.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48647","48647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601124","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Rule 35 (1), Rule 35 (2) and Rule 35 (3) reports were submitted in the (a) first, (b) second and (c) third quarters of 2016.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48648","48648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601125","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the implications for its policies of the number of successful prosecutions for forced marriage.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48534","48534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601126","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of climate change on the number of climate refugees coming to the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48533","48533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601127","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will request that the Migration Advisory Committee undertake a cost-benefit analysis of the economic contribution that net student migration makes to the UK economy.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48536","48536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601128","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to restrict or remove EU and EEA nationals' entitlement to access social housing after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48538","48538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601129","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many warrants have been issued authorising entry in accordance with section 16(5) of the Scrap Metal Dealers Act 2013 in each year since that Act came into force.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48546","48546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601130","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many scrap metal (a) site and (b) collectors licences have been (i) renewed and (ii) revoked in each year since 2013 in each local authority.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48547","48547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601131","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many scrap metal (a) site and (b) collectors licences have been issued in each year since 2013.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48548","48548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601133","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many scrap metal (a) sites and (b) collectors licences have been modified because of a change of trading name in each year since 2013.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48592","48592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601134","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will provide information on the (a) number and (b) nationalities of people on the flight from London on 7 September 2016 that was part of Operation Nexus; from which London airport that flight departed; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48551","48551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601135","2016-10-18","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to review the efficacy of sections 103 and 104 of the Anti-Social Behaviour, Crime and Policing Act 2014.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48561","48561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601136","2016-10-18","Department for Transport","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure effective working between the Maritime and Coastguard Agency and local Fire and Rescue services on appropriate access to flight and winch training.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48503","48503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601137","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications to UK Visas and Immigration (UKVI) have been refunded by UKVI; and how much has been allocated for such refunds in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48494","48494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601138","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on securing renewable energy in developing countries in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48496","48496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601139","2016-10-18","Department for International Development","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of withdrawing overseas development assistance funding to countries in which the death penalty is applied.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48525","48525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601140","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 46228, what (a) targets and (b) mechanisms are in place to ensure that funding allocated to the Energy Africa campaign has reached the number of beneficiaries for which that campaign is intended.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48507","48507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601141","2016-10-18","Department for International Development","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she plans to publish an updated list of her Department's priority countries.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48524","48524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601142","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that UK aid for Turkey to help address the effects of the conflict in Syria is being used for its intended purposes.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48571","48571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601143","2016-10-18","Department for International Development","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the humanitarian effect of the closure of the Dadaab camp on Somali refugees in that region.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48670","48670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601144","2016-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans the Government has to include the key entitlements for victims and witnesses set out in her Department's Code of Practice for Victims of Crime, published in October 2015, in primary legislation.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48620","48620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601145","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2016 to Question 41032, whether the families of the victims of the 61 prisoners convicted of murder released on Christmas Day 2015 were informed of the offender's temporary release.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48562","48562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601146","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer on 12 October 2016 to Question 41032, what the average release period was for those offenders broken down by category of offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48567","48567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601147","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 October 2016 to Question 41032, from which prisons the 61 prisoners convicted of murder were released from on temporary licence for Christmas Day 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48568","48568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601148","2016-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions her Department has had with the Judicial Office on permitting district judges to sit as presiding judges at the Muslim Arbitration Tribunal.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48560","48560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601149","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many serving prisoners were not in prison accommodation overnight on New Year's Eve 2015; what offences were committed by each such offender; and how many such offences were in which category of violent offences against the person.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48582","48582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601150","2016-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to improve the safety of prison staff at work.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48599","48599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601151","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what convictions have been secured against people for not displaying a copy of their scrap metal licence (a) at each site identified in the licence and (b) on any vehicle that was being used in the course of the dealer's business in each year since 2013.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48591","48591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601152","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, to list the local authorities which have (a) conducted or are conducting inquiries into baby ashes and cremation regulations and (b) had discussions with the Government on conducting potential inquiries.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48511","48511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601153","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) charged and (b) convicted for accepting cash payment for scrap metal under section 6 of the Scrap Metal Dealers Act 2013 in each year since that Act came into force.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48545","48545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601154","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who the attendees were of meetings of the National Cremation Working Group; the positions they hold; and the organisations they represent.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48512","48512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601155","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the range of civil and criminal powers that are available to financial services regulators to investigate and protect investors who have entrusted funds to regulated firms in the financial services sector.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48522","48522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601156","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when her Department intends to publish a consultation on the personal injury reforms announced by the Chancellor of the Exchequer in the 2015 Autumn Statement; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48497","48497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601157","2016-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans she has to re-open Wellingborough Prison.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48501","48501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601158","2016-10-18","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans are in place to improve security at Wellingborough Prison to prevent travellers encroaching on the site.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48502","48502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601159","2016-10-17","Prime Minister","2016-10-13","To ask the Prime Minister, if she will publish minutes of her meeting with Rupert Murdoch in September 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48659","48659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601160","2016-10-17","Prime Minister","2016-10-13","To ask the Prime Minister, on what date agreement was reached that she would meet Rupert Murdoch during her visit to New York in September 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48660","48660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601161","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on transport infrastructure projects in Chippenham constituency in each year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48684","48684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601162","2016-10-18","Department for Transport","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the delay repay scheme to begin operating on the (a) Greater Anglia franchise and (b) West Anglia route.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48688","48688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601163","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the planned timetable is for the recruitment of a new chief executive for HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48639","48639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601164","2016-10-18","Department for Transport","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department holds data on the level of motor vehicle ownership in (a) England and (b) Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48600","48600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601165","2016-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the level of work allowance for universal credit will be for people (a) with and (b) without a housing element included in their universal credit in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48603","48603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601166","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the second table on page five of his Department's document, Personal Independence Payment: Official Statistics, if he will provide the data on reconsideration outcomes by (a) category or disabling condition, (b) sub-group and (c) disability in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48513","48513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601167","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's document, Personal Independence Payment: Detailed medical condition, July 2016 caseload, if he will provide the same subcategories of data broken down by the size of the award in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48492","48492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601168","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will provide an update on the roll-out of personal independence payment re-assessments for the HU postcode area.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48493","48493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601169","2016-10-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of (a) Atos and (b) Capita personal independence payment assessments have been carried out in the applicant's home in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48495","48495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601170","2016-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) former miners and (b) widows of former miners are in receipt of the mineworker's pension in (i) the UK, (ii) the East Midlands and (iii) Ashfield constituency.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48674","48674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601171","2016-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the oral Answer of 13 September 2016, Official Report, column 764, when he plans to meet the hon. Member for Ashfield to discuss the mineworker's pension scheme.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48676","48676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601172","2016-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much the Government has received from the mineworker's pension scheme since 1994.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48677","48677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601173","2016-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2016 to Question 47675, if he will publish the recommendations made by his Department's internal process reviews into the deaths of social security claimants since 2014.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48668","48668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601174","2016-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2016 to Question 42974, when the written responses from external stakeholders on child maintenance service charges will be made available.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48576","48576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601175","2016-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many families in the North East received child maintenance through the (a) Child Support Agency and (b) Child Maintenance Service in 2015-16; and how many of those families were (i) single-parent families, (ii) low-income families, (iii) survivors of domestic violence and (iv) workless households.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48694","48694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601176","2016-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to review the efficiency and cost-effectiveness of the Child Maintenance Service for families which use that service.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48695","48695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601177","2016-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of moving the Child Support Agency to the Child Maintenance Service on (a) single-parent families, (b) low-income families, (c) survivors of domestic violence and (d) workless households.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48696","48696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601178","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make assessments of projected installed generating capacity for non-domestic solar panel installations in each of the next five years, based on the (a) current rate of £8 per kilowatt and (b) Valuation Office Agency proposal for up to £61 per kilowatt.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48587","48587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601179","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people were employed in the solar energy sector in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber, (d) England and (e) the UK in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48588","48588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601180","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will provide the email address for people to contact his Department with examples of the effect the UK leaving the EU is having on universities and academia and place in the Library copies of the emails received.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48589","48589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601181","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people switching from cigarettes to e-cigarettes in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48580","48580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601182","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the cost to the public purse was of bringing on stream reserve coal-fired power stations to meet demand on 13 September 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48498","48498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601183","2016-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the outcome of the discussions that are due to take place between the Government and the Post Office on a funding package from 2018 onwards will be subject to parliamentary scrutiny.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48529","48529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601184","2016-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to make a decision on the timetable for the construction of Hinkley Point C.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48528","48528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601185","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has a scientific advisor on the team which is leading on negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48584","48584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601186","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with key stakeholders in the automotive industry on the effect of the UK leaving the EU since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48638","48638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601187","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he plans to take to strengthen Wales' international business links.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48661","48661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601188","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will assess the merits of negotiating changes to US import tariffs on British beer after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48657","48657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601189","2016-10-18","Department for International Trade","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with key stakeholders in the pharmaceutical sector on the effect of the UK leaving the EU since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48690","48690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601190","2016-10-18","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with key stakeholders in the pharmaceutical sector on the effect of the UK leaving the EU since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48691","48691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601191","2016-10-18","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with key stakeholders in the automotive industry on the effect of the UK leaving the EU since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48693","48693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601192","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential economic effect of the withdrawal of EU funding on the South Wales metro project.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48650","48650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601193","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will assess the merits of establishing a negotiating bloc with other financial centres to conclude an extra-EU deal on financial services' tariff-free access to the single market.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48686","48686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601194","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of extracting the UK from EU shared payment liabilities once the UK exits the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48613","48613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601195","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of extracting the UK from EU shared contingent liabilities and loan guarantees once the UK exits the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48614","48614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601196","2016-10-17","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how his Department plans to seek the opinion of British companies in the consideration of the domestication of EU regulations after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48518","48518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/601197","2016-10-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he plans to take to safeguard the provisions of the EU Working Time Directive once Article 50 has been triggered.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48602","48602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600536","2016-10-17","Attorney General","2016-10-12","To ask the Attorney General, whether he has any plans to review the categories of offences which are capable of referral to the Court of Appeal on the grounds of leniency.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48243","48243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600537","2016-10-17","Cabinet Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what checks are made to ensure that a person is eligible to vote when they register to vote online.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48390","48390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600538","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether any conditions were imposed on Sir Richard Paniguian's appointment to the board of Raytheon Systems.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48445","48445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600539","2016-10-17","Cabinet Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many former ministers since May 2015 (a) have taken up employment in roles which directly relate to positions they held in Government and (b) are working in the private sector.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48446","48446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600540","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of (a) the amount of money wrongly withheld from benefit claimants due to errors made by Concentrix and (b) the average length of time that payments were mistakenly withheld.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48377","48377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600541","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have had their tax credits stopped and subsequently reinstated by Concentrix due to incorrect information held on claimants cohabiting.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48378","48378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600542","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations the UK Government has made to the World Health Organisation on proposals to change tax rates for e-cigarettes.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48448","48448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600543","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many financial institutions offer ISAs; and what the total value is of monetary assets in ISAs.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48418","48418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600544","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with counterparts in the Bahamas on improving tax transparency since the leak of internal files from the company register in that country.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48428","48428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600545","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the value of assets that will be put into Lifetime ISAs in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48457","48457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600546","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to reduce inheritance tax avoidance.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48317","48317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600547","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of the annual UK tax revenue was paid by employees of mining companies listed on the London Stock Exchange in each year since 1995.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48354","48354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600548","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of the annual UK tax revenue was paid by mining companies listed on the London Stock Exchange in each year since 1990.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48353","48353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600549","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to reduce the rate of VAT on motorcycle safety clothing.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48332","48332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600550","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of GDP the UK mining industry contributed in (a) 1995, (b) 2005 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48357","48357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600551","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment has been made of the performance of Concentrix in resolving complaints regarding how they have dealt with tax credit claims.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48360","48360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600552","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the UK economy of the recent fall in the value of sterling against the US dollar.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48371","48371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600553","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claimants in (a) England, (b) the North East, (c) Redcar and Cleveland and (d) Middlesbrough have had a tax credit claimed stopped and subsequently reinstated by Concentrix in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48379","48379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600554","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the UK's annual financial contribution to the World Health Organisation is.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48368","48368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600555","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children that will be living in families affected by the limitation to two children of (a) the child element of child tax credit and (b) child additions within universal credit in (i) 2017-18 and (ii) 2020-21.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48389","48389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600556","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what reduction in entitlement he expects for the average family affected by the limitation to two children of the child element of child tax credit in 2017-18.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48228","48228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600557","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to investigate reports of misconduct by the Global Restructuring Group of the Royal Bank of Scotland relating to small business finance in dash for cash claims made against that bank since 2008.","Biography information for Jo Churchill","Jo Churchill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48268","48268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600558","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many financial institutions offer the (a) flexible ISA, (b) help to buy ISA and (c) innovative finance ISA.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48278","48278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600559","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value of assets is in pounds sterling in (a) the flexible ISA, (b) the help to buy ISA and (c) the innovative finance ISA.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48277","48277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600560","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions officials of his Department have had with local enterprise partnerships on future funding from the Government for new projects after the projects that are funded by European Structural and Investment Funds are completed.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48281","48281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600561","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Statement of 13 August 2016 on EU funding beyond the date the UK leaves the EU, what estimate he has made of the cost to the Government of funding the completion of projects previously funded by European structural and investment funds.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48283","48283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600562","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the loss of revenue to the Treasury as a result of (a) bogus self-employment and (b) workers being paid under the Construction Industry Scheme.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48295","48295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600563","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to prevent false self-employment in the construction industry.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48296","48296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600564","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that potential remedies for people affected by the collapse of the Connaught Income Services 1 Fund are not ruled unattainable as a result of the time taken by the Financial Conduct Authority to conclude its investigation into that matter.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48464","48464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600565","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will take steps to ensure that consumers are aware that Lifetime ISA savings are from tax income whereas auto enrolment-contributions are from untaxed contributions.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48452","48452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600567","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, (a) how many interventions Ministers of his Department have made to suspend or halt the adoption of local plans since 2010, (b) the grounds on which any such interventions have been made and (c) the names of the councils subject to such interventions.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48491","48491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600568","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects the review by Dame Louise Casey into opportunity and integration in isolated communities to be published.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48218","48218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600569","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the announcement by the then Prime Minister of 20 July 2015, when he expects the Cohesive Communities Programme to be launched.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48219","48219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600570","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support London boroughs in areas where the number of rogue private landlords is increasing.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48319","48319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600571","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what date the nine Dorset councils and Dorset LEP submitted their application for the creation of a combined authority; when he expects to be able to give his decision on that application; and what the earliest date is on which a combined authority could start work.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48308","48308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600572","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to set minimum periods for the review of local plans to enable established green belt boundaries to operate without the prospect of change for longer periods.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48309","48309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600573","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to finalise the tenant eligibility criteria, start date and funding for the extension of right to buy to housing association tenants.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48310","48310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600574","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of reductions in local government budgets on the level of provision of housing for people affected by domestic violence.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48321","48321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600575","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will consider the merits of extending the criteria of the Troubled Families programme to include families affected by alcohol and other substance addictions.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48342","48342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600576","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what contingency plans his Department had in place before the EU Referendum for loss of European Investment Bank finance for affordable homes; and if he will place a copy of such plans in the Library.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48344","48344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600577","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to ensure that any shortfall in European Investment Bank finance for affordable homes as a result of the UK leaving the EU will be met by the UK Government.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48343","48343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600578","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK's vote to leave the EU on future funding for housing from the European Investment Bank.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48421","48421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600579","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to work with community groups and charities to encourage victims of (a) forced marriage and (b) domestic violence to seek help and advice.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48459","48459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600580","2016-10-17","HM Treasury","2016-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the European Investment Bank on future funding for affordable housing.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48410","48410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600581","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with housing associations and other organisations who benefit from funding from the European Investment Bank on the level of future funding that will be required to build affordable homes.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48411","48411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600582","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2016 to Question 43519, what plans he has to ensure that local authorities with the highest proportions of attendance allowance cases in payment are able to provide the same level of attendance allowance funding under the structure proposed in his Department's consultation, Self-sufficient local government: 100 per cent business rate retention.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48441","48441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600583","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that more homes are accessible for disabled people.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48443","48443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600584","2016-10-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if the connectivity and communications of simple internet-connected devices such as cameras, televisions and domestic appliances is regulated by Ofcom.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48306","48306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600585","2016-10-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps to develop an industry standard to ensure the security of simple internet-connected devices such as cameras, televisions and domestic appliances.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48307","48307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600586","2016-10-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to provide each London borough council with the necessary provisions to ensure that all residents can access superfast broadband.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48314","48314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600587","2016-10-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the manufacturer liability for simple internet-connected devices such as cameras, televisions and domestic appliances in the event such a device is hijacked in a cyber attack; and how consumers can obtain compensation from the manufacturer in the event of such an attack.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48305","48305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600588","2016-10-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the cyber security of simple internet-connected devices such as cameras, televisions and domestic appliances; and what steps she is taking to ensure those devices cannot be hijacked for distributed denial of service and other cyber attacks.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48303","48303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600589","2016-10-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress the Government has made on increasing funding for greyhound welfare from gambling operators since publication of the Government response to the Second Report of the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs Committee, Session 2015-16, on Greyhound welfare, HC 478.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48466","48466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600590","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel were dishonourably discharged on the grounds of their sexual orientation from the (a) Royal Navy excluding the Royal Marines, (b) Royal Marines, (c) Army and (d) Royal Air Force in each year from 1986 to 2000.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48288","48288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600591","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel who were dishonourably discharged from the (a) Royal Navy excluding the Royal Marines, (b) Royal Marines, (c) Army and (d) Royal Air Force in each year from 1986 to 2000 have since had that dishonourable discharge reviewed and amended.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48290","48290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600592","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department made of whether British steel could be used in the construction of the pressure hulls for the Trident Successor programme.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48291","48291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600593","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what meetings his Department has had and on what dates with Sir Richard Paniguan in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48276","48276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600594","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average annual charge for water is for Ministry of Defence water bill customers.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48232","48232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600595","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to how many customers his Department provides water.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48233","48233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600596","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department paid (a) Severn Trent and (b) other third parties for issuing water bill charges in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48234","48234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600597","2016-10-17","Department for International Trade","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many (a) companies and (b) organisations currently hold strategic export control licences.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48220","48220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600598","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons he has not made a counter-Daesh quarterly update to the House since May 2016; and when he next plans to provide such an update.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48375","48375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600599","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which (a) medicinal and (b) non-medicinal products have been approved for use by armed forces service personnel to aid them in staying alert.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48333","48333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600600","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the cost to the public purse of current and planned procurement contracts of a fall in the value of sterling.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48369","48369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600601","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which current and planned defence procurement projects have costs which are currency sensitive.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48370","48370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600602","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, (a) how many times and (b) in relation to which projects the Revise or Confirm Offer procedure has been invoked in Scotland by his Department's procurement function in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48415","48415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600603","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times the Revise or Confirm Offer procedure has been invoked by his Department's procurement function in the last 12 months against firms based (a) outside and (b) within the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48414","48414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600604","2016-10-17","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the operation of the Revise or Confirm Offer procedure in defence procurement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48416","48416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600605","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions she has had with the Department for Communities and Local Government on the proposal by Sir Martin Narey in his review of children's homes that local planning authorities include clear statements in their local plans about the level of housing need for children in children's homes.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48433","48433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600606","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on children's safety of changes to Building Bulletin 100 guidance relating to sprinkler systems in school buildings.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48391","48391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600607","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the independent review of children's residential care by Sir Martin Narey, published in July 2016, when she plans to set up the Residential Care Leadership Board recommended in that review.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48434","48434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600608","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the independent review of children's residential care by Sir Martin Narey, published in July 2016, whether she plans a fundamental review of fostering recommended in that review.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48435","48435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600609","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which schools are designated as teaching schools.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48439","48439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600610","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the key performance targets are for Regional School Commissioners from October 2016.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48383","48383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600611","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how an apprenticeship standard will be created when there are fewer than the required ten employers to set up a trailblazer group in a specialised occupation; and what role the Institute for Apprenticeships' sectoral groups will play in that process from April 2017.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48449","48449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600612","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on the development of regional commissioning of children's home placements for looked after children.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48386","48386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600613","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to address mental health issues in children potentially caused by pressure at school.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48352","48352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600614","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what distributional analysis her Department has conducted of changes to the early years funding formula; and what analysis her Department has made of which local authorities' funding will (a) increase and (b) decrease as a result of those changes.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48364","48364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600615","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will discuss with her counterparts in the devolved institutions ways to ensure that young people across the UK receive a similar level of assistance in accessing apprenticeships.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48361","48361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600616","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of disadvantaged two year-olds take up the free 15 hours of early education in each type of setting; and what evidence her Department has gathered on the effect of that offer on the developmental gap between disadvantaged two year-olds and their peers and (b) the comparative effect of that early education being delivered in each type of early years setting.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48367","48367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600617","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which local authorities allocate additional quality supplements to childcare and early education providers.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48365","48365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600618","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which local authorities offer more than 15 hours' free early education to three and four year-olds in (a) maintained nursery schools and nursery classes and (b) private, voluntary and independent childcare settings.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48366","48366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600619","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the value is of outstanding student loan debts owed by graduates who have moved overseas since 2006.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48221","48221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600620","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of teachers in English schools are (a) British nationals and (b) non-British EU nationals.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48229","48229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600621","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to answer named day Questions 43736, 43737 and 43738, tabled on 20 July 2016 by the right hon. Member for East Ham, on the Bright Tribe Multi-Academy Trust.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48230","48230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600622","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what date the Education Funding Agency purchased the former East Ham Police Station.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48231","48231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600623","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will undertake an impact assessment on the compatibility of the Schools that Work for Everyone green paper consultation document with section 149 of the Equality Act 2010 on public sector equality duty.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48273","48273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600624","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has held with (a) fire services, (b) the Fire Brigades Union and (c) other organisations on its current consultation on Building Bulletin 100 guidance.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48274","48274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600625","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) nursery schools, (b) primary, middle, secondary, all-through and special schools, (c) pupil referral units and short-stay schools, (d) faith schools, (e) independent schools, (f) academies, chains and free schools and (g) sixth-form colleges are designated as teaching schools.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48450","48450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600626","2016-10-17","Department for Education","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools currently designated as teaching schools were rated (a) good, (b) requires improvement, (c) inadequate and (d) special measures at their most recent Ofsted inspection.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48451","48451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600627","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of applications to the Farming Recovery Fund have been paid to farmers affected by flooding since December 2015.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48465","48465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600628","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the (a) availability and (b) affordability of contents insurance for renters in at-risk flood areas.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48461","48461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600629","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to put mechanisms in place to maintain the UK's air quality (a) targets and (b) levels after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48267","48267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600630","2016-10-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the environmental impact of the oil spill in the North Sea from the BP Clair platform in early October 2016; what steps his Department has taken to ensure the effects of that incident are minimised; and whether he plans to seek a penalty from BP for any damage that results from that incident.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48240","48240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600631","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what dates Ministers and officials in her Department met with (a) representatives from the British pork industry and (b) her EU counterparts to discuss the MRSA superbug strain.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48350","48350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600632","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment the Government has made of the public health danger posed by the use of antibiotics for agricultural purposes.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48312","48312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600633","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to minimise the use of antibiotics in livestock management.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48313","48313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600634","2016-10-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which recommendations from the report of the independent farming regulation task force on better regulation in farming and food businesses have been implemented since that report was published in May 2011.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48384","48384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600635","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the treatment of the Tatar minority in occupied Crimea.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48447","48447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600636","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support a peace process in Colombia.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48477","48477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600637","2016-10-17","Women and Equalities","2016-10-12","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that same-sex marriages are recognised in all British Overseas Territories; and what recent (a) meetings and (b) correspondence she has had on that issue.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48323","48323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600638","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the UN Human Rights Council on protecting children in Yemen.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48362","48362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600639","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what integrated processes between services in the UK have been organised to receive Syrian child refugees from Calais.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48244","48244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600640","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many local authorites have offered to receive and house Syrian child refugees.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48245","48245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600641","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress has been made on reaching an agreement on receiving children to the UK from the Calais camps.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48246","48246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600642","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the (a) extent, (b) effectiveness and (c) sources of financing of PKK terrorism in Turkey; and what support the Government has offered to the government of Turkey to help tackle such terrorism.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48259","48259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600643","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what integrated processes between the UK and other countries have been organised to receive Syrian child refugees.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48265","48265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600644","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48294","48294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600645","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the viability of operating a no-fly zone within Syria.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48292","48292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600646","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the determination by the European Court of Human Rights and the UN Special Rapporteur on Torture and Other Cruel, Inhuman and Degrading Treatment or Punishment that detention on death row represents a form of torture.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48224","48224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600647","2016-10-17","Department for Transport","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the travel industry of continuing threat-level warnings in relation to travel to Sharm el-Sheikh in Egypt.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48227","48227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600648","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the humanitarian situation in Yemen following the air strike on a funeral hall in Sana'a on 8 October 2016.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48431","48431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600649","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is planning to take in respect of Russia as a result of the findings of the independent MH17 Joint Investigation Team.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48456","48456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600650","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to develop (a) diplomatic and (b) trading relationships with Japan since the referendum on exiting the EU.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48442","48442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600651","2016-10-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his policy differs between countries on his Department's intervention in the judicial and legal affairs in cases abroad involving British nationals.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48473","48473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600652","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of local authorities that have undertaken an equality impact assessment before making changes to their budget for public health.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48487","48487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600653","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ring-fence public health spending in 2018-19.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48488","48488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600654","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent meetings he has had with (a) Ministers and (b) officials of the Department for Communities and Local Government on multipurpose hubs for community health and wellbeing in (i) England, (ii) Wiltshire and (iii) Dorset.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48216","48216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600655","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent per head on GP services in (a) Enfield Clinical Commissioning Group area, (b) Barnet Clinical Commissioning Group area, (c) Haringey Clinical Commissioning Group area and (d) on average by all Clinical Commissioning Group areas across Greater London in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48212","48212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600656","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average waiting times for treatment in the accident and emergency departments of (a) the Royal Free London NHS Foundation Trust and (b) North Middlesex University Hospital NHS Trust for each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48213","48213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600657","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the effect on the number of community pharmacies of proposed changes to pharmacy funding.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48286","48286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600658","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of organ donors.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48299","48299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600659","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on the implications of possible relocation of the European Medicines Agency outside the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48279","48279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600660","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice his Department gives to clinical commissioning groups on how to respond in circumstances where a private provider of patient transport services has its ambulances seized by bailiffs; and on how many occasions such a seizure has taken place.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48242","48242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600661","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many foreign-born EU nationals are employed in the NHS in (a) the UK, (b) England and (c) London both in gross terms and as a proportion of the total NHS workforce.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48264","48264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600662","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the evidential basis is for his Department to support an indoor ban on e-cigarettes and other reduced harm products on the grounds of such a ban improving public health in the UK.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48250","48250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600663","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings he has had in the last 12 months with representatives from the British Medical Association, the General Medical Council and the Royal College of Nursing on reducing the need for temporary and agency staff in NHS England.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48255","48255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600664","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the proposal tabled for the forthcoming World Health Organisation Framework Convention on Tobacco Control Conference of the Parties to ban or restrict the sale of certain e-cigarette flavours to responsible adults.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48248","48248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600665","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Prime Minister of 12 October 2016,  Official Report, column 300, when he expects the relative per capita underfunding for (a) Nene Clinical Commissioning Group (CCG) and (b) Corby CCG against the national picture to have been corrected.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48260","48260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600666","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what evidential basis his Department has to support a prohibition on claims of the effectiveness of e-cigarettes and other reduced harm products as smoking cessation aids on the grounds of such prohibition improving public health in the UK.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48249","48249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600667","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Prime Minister of 12 October 2016, Official Report, column 300, if he will set out the annual funding for (a) Nene Clinical Commissioning Group (CCG) and (b) Corby CCG in each of the last five years and for each future year where forecasts of funding have been made.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48261","48261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600668","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent agency and temporary health workers were employed in (a) NHS England, (b) each English region and (c) Bradford Teaching Hospital Foundation Trust  in 2015-16.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48251","48251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600669","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total expenditure on full-time equivalent agency and temporary staff costs was in (a) NHS England, (b) each English region and (c) Bradford Teaching Hospital Foundation Trust in 2015-16.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48252","48252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600670","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to reduce the number of babies born in the back of an ambulance in England.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48258","48258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600671","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to meet representatives from the British Medical Association to discuss his Department's plans to increase medical school places.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48253","48253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600672","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Home Office and the Department for Exiting the European Union on ensuring job security for EU nationals employed in NHS England.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48254","48254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600673","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of pharmacies located in pharmacy clusters are within each decile of deprivation in the English indices of deprivation for 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48257","48257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600674","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure improvement in cancer treatment in those areas identified in the Macmillan Cancer Support survey, published in October 2016, as requiring such improvement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48256","48256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600675","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, how the Government's committed spend of up to £300 million per year to improve cancer diagnostics was allocated in 2015-16.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48238","48238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600676","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total financial deficit for the NHS in England was at the end of June 2016.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48376","48376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600677","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is putting in place to protect women accessing abortion clinics (a) in London and (b) elsewhere against protestors.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48322","48322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600678","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) Public Health England and (b) other national bodies address the growing extent and costs of alcohol abuse.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48341","48341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600679","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that access to contraception is not restricted on the basis of age.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48432","48432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600680","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of potential reductions in the level of pharmacy funding on waiting times for NHS prescriptions.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48429","48429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600681","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of reductions in pharmacy funding on the availability of essential medicines.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48430","48430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600682","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 40071, how many NHS Protect staff there were by the job title and role, including press and public relations staff, in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48458","48458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600683","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions since the Care Quality Commission's (CQC) new powers in relation to the fit and proper person test came into force the CQC has received concerns raised by a third party about whether a director meets the fit and proper person standards; and on how many such occasions (a) the CQC passed on those concerns and (b) the director in question denied consent to the CQC to pass on those concerns.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48408","48408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600684","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions since the Care Quality Commission's (CQC) new powers in relation to the fit and proper person test came into force the CQC has assessed the directors of (a) NHS and (b) private providers as not being fit and proper persons after an inspection.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48409","48409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600685","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) previous NHS directors and (b) previous private provider directors the Care Quality Commission (CQC) has on record as not being fit and proper persons to act as directors since the new responsibilities of the CQC and NHS trusts came into force in 2014; and how the CQC ensures that individual providers are aware of the people on this list when making a decision to hire directors.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48406","48406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600686","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions since the Care Quality Commission's (CQC) new powers in relation to the fit and proper person test came into force the CQC has rejected an application to register a provider because of concerns about whether the registered manager is a fit and proper person.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48407","48407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600687","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many reports entered into NHS Protect's Fraud Information Reporting System Toolkit have been turned into cases in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48400","48400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600688","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding NHS Improvement has received for the 2016-17 financial year; how many staff that body employs; and how much funding each of the organisations that body has superseded received in each of the preceding five financial years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48405","48405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600689","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many providers NHS Protect has quality assessed against fraud, bribery and corruption standards in each year since 2009-10; and how many such providers NHS Protect has found to be performing below those standards in each such year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48401","48401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600690","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 1.104 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, whether the Government carried out an equality impact assessment of the policy to make savings in local authority public health spending.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48424","48424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600691","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 1.104 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on women of savings in local authority public health spending.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48425","48425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600692","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the information in answers to Questions (a) 11426 on 15 October 2015, (b) 11427 on 15 October 2015, (c) 11428 on 15 October 2015 and (d) 40070 on 13 June 2016 contain data from before the 2011-12 financial year when NHS Protect was set up.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48392","48392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600693","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many pharmacies are now clustered.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48436","48436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600694","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the cost to the NHS of missed GP appointments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Mr Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48444","48444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600695","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much money was (a) restrained and (b) confiscated by (i) NHS Protect and (ii) local counter-fraud specialists as a result of the discovery of wrongdoing within the NHS in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48394","48394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600696","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many registered private providers the Care Quality Commission has placed under special measures in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48395","48395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600697","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to Table 1 on page 5 of the NHS Protect document, Payroll fraud: guidance for prevention, detection and investigation, published in June 2015, if he will provide that information for each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48393","48393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600698","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many accredited training sessions and (b) how much free paralegal advice NHS Protect has provided to staff throughout the NHS in each year since 2010-11; and how many staff in NHS Protect were employed to carry out those activities in each such year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48396","48396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600699","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which NHS bodies have Local Counter-Fraud Specialists (LCFSs); and (a) how much funding each LCFS received, (b) how many investigations each LCFS carried out and (c) in how many such investigations wrongdoing was found in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48397","48397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600700","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether and by how much the (a) funding and (b) staffing of (i) the Care Quality Commission and (ii) NHS providers has increased as a result of the new requirement to apply a fit and proper person test to NHS directors since October 2014.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48402","48402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600701","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will list the Regional and Specialist teams within NHS Protect; how many investigations have been carried out by each of those teams in each year since 2009-10; and how many such investigations in each area led to a finding of wrongdoing in each such year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48398","48398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600702","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many directors were employed by NHS (a) trusts and (b) foundation trusts at the start of the 2014-15 financial year; and of those directors, how many no longer held posts in each type of trust by the start of the (i) 2015-16 and (ii) 2016-17 financial years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48403","48403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600703","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many reports of (a) expenses claims, (b) payroll and (c) other fraud NHS Protect have received from each region through the Fraud and Corruption Reporting Line in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48399","48399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600704","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) private and (b) NHS providers were registered with the Care Quality Commission (CQC) in each year since 2009-10; and how many (i) routine and (ii) risk-based inspections the CQC carried out of each type of provider in each such year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48404","48404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600705","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 1.2.3.2 of Schedule 2 to the Compass contract for the accommodation of asylum seekers, if she will publish a copy of the contractor's arrangements for ensuring that its staff, volunteers and sub-contractors who are likely to have direct contact with service users are subject to criminal records bureau and disclose checks prior to any such contracts for each such contractor in Great Britain and Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48385","48385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600706","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding her Department is providing for costs associated with (a) health services and (b) civil legal advice and assistance in Scotland for expenditure consequential on dispersing asylum seekers to Scotland.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48426","48426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600707","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to resettle the unaccompanied child refugees in Calais entitled to be in the UK.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48478","48478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600708","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what provision her Department makes for asylum seekers who require documents from their country of origin to normalise their immigration status.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48324","48324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600709","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of investigations conducted into allegations by service users that they have suffered abuse or harassment from Compass asylum accommodation contractor or sub-contractor staff; in what year each such investigation was carried out; and what the outcome of each such investigation was.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48325","48325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600710","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 1.2.3.2 of Schedule 2 to the Compass contract for accommodation for asylum seekers in the Midlands and East of England, what arrangements are in place to ensure that all contractor staff and sub-contractors who are likely to have contact with service users are subject to criminal records bureau and disclosure checks prior to working on that contract; who is responsible for applying such checks; and what the pass rate was for any such checks in 2015-16.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48326","48326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600711","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 1.2.3.2 of Schedule 2 to the Compass contract for accommodation for asylum seekers in the North-West Region, what arrangements are in place to ensure that all contractor staff and sub-contractors who are likely to have contact with service users are subject to criminal records bureau and disclosure checks prior to working on that contract; who is responsible for applying such checks; and what the pass rate was for any such checks in 2015-16.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48327","48327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600712","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the time taken to issue work permits for foreign workers.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48315","48315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600713","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) police officers and (b) police community support officers have been assaulted in each constabulary in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48334","48334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600714","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many days of police time were lost in sick leave as a result of assaults on police officers in each constabulary in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48335","48335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600715","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the delays in the processing of Disclosure and Barring service checks.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48316","48316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600716","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that family members who report paedophilia to the police are treated as victims instead of witnesses.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48320","48320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600717","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 1.2.3.2 of Schedule 2 to the Compass contract for accommodation for asylum seekers in London and the South-East Region, what arrangements are in place to ensure that all contractor staff and sub-contractors who are likely to have contact with service users are subject to a criminal records bureau and disclosure checks prior to working under that contract; who is responsible for applying such checks; and what the pass rate was for any such checks in 2015-16.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48329","48329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600718","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 1.2.3.2 of Schedule 2 to the Compass contract for accommodation for asylum seekers in Wales and South-West, what arrangements are in place to ensure that all contractor staff and sub-contractors who are likely to have contact with service users are subject to a criminal records bureau and disclosure checks prior to working under that contract; who is responsible for applying such checks; and what the pass rate was for any such checks in 2015-16.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48328","48328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600719","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 1.2.3.2 of Schedule 2 to the Compass contract for accommodation for asylum seekers in Scotland and Northern Ireland, what arrangements are in place to ensure that all contractor staff and sub-contractors who are likely to have contact with service users are subject to criminal records bureau and disclosure checks prior to working under that contract; who is responsible for applying such checks; and what the pass rate was for any such checks in 2015-16.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48330","48330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600720","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 1.2.3.2 of Schedule 2 to the Compass contract for accommodation for asylum seekers in the North-East, Yorkshire and Humber region, what arrangements are in place to ensure that all contractor staff and sub-contractors who are likely to have contact with service users are subject to criminal records bureau and disclosure checks prior to working under that contract; who is responsible for applying such checks; and what the pass rate was for any such checks in 2015-16.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48331","48331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600721","2016-10-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish further information on the proposed Controlling Migration Fund; what the criteria for that Fund will be; and when that Fund will come into operation.","Biography information for Matt Warman","Matt Warman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48355","48355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600722","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which local authorities have signed up to COMPASS for the provision of asylum accommodation.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48241","48241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600723","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign-born EU nationals are employed by her Department and its agencies.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48263","48263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600724","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much has been spent from the public purse on (a) police officers and (b) Crown Prosecution Service training in respect of (i) stalking and (ii) coercive control offences in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48297","48297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600725","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were (a) charged, (b) prosecuted and (c) convicted of stalking under Section 4a of the Protection from Harassment Act in (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15; and what the average sentence was for such offences in each such year.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48460","48460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600726","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum cases have been referred to the Case Assurance and Audit Unit that related to asylum seekers in the City of Cambridge in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48484","48484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600727","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what expenditure her Department made and what funding it provided to the Scottish Government in 2015-16 for the provision to dispersed asylum seekers in Scotland of (a) health services and (b) civil legal advice and assistance and civil legal aid.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48462","48462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600728","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum cases are being processed by her Department in the City of Cambridge.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48485","48485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600729","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to work with the Crown Prosecution Service, other Government departments and the police to improve the prosecution rate for the use of knives in Southwark.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48486","48486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600730","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what work her Department undertakes with (a) refuges and (b) women's support groups on forced marriage.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48463","48463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600731","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in refugee camps in Greece.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48474","48474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600732","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will list the refugee camps which are currently receiving aid from her Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48475","48475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600733","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent meetings she has had with (a) Ministers and (b) officials of the Department for International Trade on the effect on developing countries of EU food tariffs.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48215","48215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600734","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the potential pressure on its foreign aid budget from requirements for humanitarian aid within Syria and neighbouring countries.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48293","48293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600735","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's budget is planned to be allocated to projects administered by other Departments in 2017-18.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48287","48287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600736","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of assistance funding to Afghanistan, announced by her Department on 2 October 2016, she estimates will be spent by Departments other than her own in each year to 2019-20.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48289","48289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600737","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the implications of her Department's policies of the conclusions contained in the 2016 UNESCO GEM report on global education.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48282","48282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600738","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the report by UNESCO, entitled Global Education Monitoring Report 2016; and what steps at (a) bilateral and (b) multilateral level her Department plans to take as a result of that report.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48247","48247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600739","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that the humanitarian response in Haiti reflects the needs of older people affected by Hurricane Matthew.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48351","48351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600740","2016-10-17","Home Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in the refugee camps in France.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48479","48479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600741","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in the refugee camps in Italy.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48480","48480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600742","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in the refugee camps in Serbia and Montenegro.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48481","48481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600743","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Jordan.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48482","48482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600744","2016-10-17","Department for International Development","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Lebanon.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48483","48483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600745","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate her Department has made of the number of ex-offenders who (a) left prison with no fixed address and (b) became homeless after leaving prison in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48419","48419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600746","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department plans to take in response to the HM Inspectorate of Probation and HM Inspectorate of Prisons report on an Inspection of Through the Gate Resettlement Services for Short-Term Prisoners, published in October 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48423","48423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600747","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44395, where in the Tribunals and Gender Recognition Statistics Quarterly if the number of special educational needs and disability tribunals for each year is published.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48437","48437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600748","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support her Department provides to people who leave prison in London without having somewhere to live.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48318","48318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600749","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what average length of sentence has been given to people prosecuted under section (a) 89(1) and (b) 89(2) of the Police Act 1996 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48337","48337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600750","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been (a) charged and (b) prosecuted under section (i) 89(1) and (ii) 89(2) of the Police Act 1996 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48336","48336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600751","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is her policy to retain the measures in the EU Directive on the rights of victims of crime in UK law after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48266","48266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600752","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what rehabilitation programmes are provided for people serving prison sentences of 12 months or less.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48269","48269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600753","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department plans to undertake a full review of sentencing guidelines.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48270","48270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600754","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she plans that a review of Through the Gate provision for offenders serving 12 months or less will begin; and when she plans to present the findings of that review.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48271","48271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600755","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons are facilitating the Government's Through the Gate provision for offenders serving 12 months or less.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48272","48272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600756","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans she has for her Department to (a) acknowledge and (b) celebrate Anti-Slavery Day 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48235","48235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600757","2016-10-17","Attorney General","2016-10-12","To ask the Attorney General, what assessments he has made of the implications of the power of the (a) CPS to take over and drop private prosecutions and (b) courts to award costs against a person who initiated an unsuccessful private prosecution for the effective and equitable working of the justice system.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48298","48298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600758","2016-10-17","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment she has made of the efficacy of her Department's communication with the public regarding minor penalty offences.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48472","48472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600759","2016-10-17","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent meetings he has had with Ministers of the Northern Ireland Executive on the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48226","48226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600760","2016-10-17","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what support his Department is giving to Co-operation Ireland's Challenging Attitudes, Changing Horizons programme.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48236","48236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600761","2016-10-17","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what provision will be made under proposals to introduce electronic voter registration in Northern Ireland for people (a) living in rural areas not well served by broadband access and (b) in older age groups less inclined to use online technology.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48359","48359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600762","2016-10-17","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent progress he has made on agreeing a timetable with political parties in Northern Ireland for full transparency of donations to such parties; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48413","48413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600763","2016-10-17","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate he has made of the potential cost to the public purse of introducing online voter registration in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48412","48412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/600764","2016-10-17","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what equality impact assessment his Department has undertaken on the measures that will be contained in the Representation of the People (Electronic Communications and Amendment) (NI) Regulations 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 48417","48417"
