"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524741","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what decisions have been taken on the distribution of the funding that was announced in the General Practice Forward View.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40392","40392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524742","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many junior doctors were employed by the NHS in (a) West Yorkshire and (b) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40398","40398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524743","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether meeting notes, correspondence and plans produced by the Sustainability and Transformation Plan footprint leadership teams are included within the remit of clinical commissioning groups in their capacity as public authorities for the purposes of the Freedom of Information Act 2000; and if he will place in the Library a list of contacts for each footprint area.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40404","40404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524744","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2016 to Question 39429, if he will publish a copy of all communications his Department has had with the Vote Leave Campaign on its use of the NHS logo.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40405","40405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524745","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received from Sustainability and Transformation Plan leadership teams on the deadline for delivery of Sustainability and Transformation Plans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40377","40377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524746","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who holds responsibility for (a) funding, (b) commissioning and (c) regulating the training of healthcare professionals to fit intra-uterine methods of contraception.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40351","40351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524747","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits to mental health patients of treatments offered by Care Farms.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40410","40410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524748","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of drop-in sexual health clinics in (a) Liverpool, Wavetree constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) England operational in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40411","40411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524749","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the mechanisms in place to pursue complaints against private company owners providing dental services in the event that the dentist who carried out the procedure leaves the country.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40379","40379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524750","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of making the Mobetron mobile device for the delivery of radiotherapy available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40347","40347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524751","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the mechanisms in place for patients to pursue complaints against dentists who leave the country before the General Dental Council can investigate.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40380","40380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524752","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department takes to ensure that healthcare professionals are trained to fit intra-uterine methods of contraception.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40339","40339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524753","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to increase the number of healthcare professionals in (a) primary and (b) community care trained to fit intra-uterine methods of contraception.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40338","40338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524754","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with (a) local education and training boards, (b) Public Health England and (c) Health Education England on the training of healthcare professionals to fit intra-uterine methods of contraception.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40337","40337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524755","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many students on (a) nursing, (b) midwifery and (c) Allied Health Professional courses benefitted from the NHS Bursary maternity award in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40275","40275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524756","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many students on (a) nursing, (b) midwifery and (c) Allied Health Professional courses successfully returned to their studies after benefitting from the NHS Bursary maternity award in the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40276","40276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524757","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS in England has spent on prescribing (a) paracetamol and (b) Viagra in the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40273","40273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524758","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to make (a) Nivolumab and (b) other immuno-oncology treatments for lung cancer available on the NHS.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40281","40281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524759","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the time taken for NICE appraisal processes for the provision of Nivolumab on the treatment of NHS patients with non-small cell lung cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40282","40282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524760","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38720, if his Department will make an assessment of the likely effect on the free services currently being offered by community pharmacies of planned changes to funding.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40371","40371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524761","2016-06-27","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2016 to Question 39429, on NHS logos, what the cost to his Department has been of legal advice on the use of the NHS logo by the Vote Leave Campaign; and what plans he has to apply for injunctive proceedings related to the use of that logo.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40368","40368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524762","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications for brain tumour research were made to the National Institute for Health Research in the last 24 months; and how many of those applications were successful.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40315","40315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524763","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effectiveness in delivering medicines savings in the community of the not-dispensed scheme for community pharmacies proposed by the Pharmaceutical Services Negotiating Committee.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40320","40320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524764","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effectiveness in delivering medicines savings in the community of the therapeutic substitution service for community pharmacies proposed by the Pharmaceutical Services Negotiating Committee.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40321","40321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524765","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 9 May 2016 to Question 36231, when he expects the liver disease framework to be published.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40333","40333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524766","2016-06-15","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children in England have been detained in immigration removal centres in each year since 2015; how many of those children so detained have been deported; and how many children are still in detention.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40318","40318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524767","2016-06-15","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from (a) Burma, (b) Afghanistan and (c) Syria are held in immigration removal centres in England.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40312","40312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524768","2016-06-15","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding the Government has allocated to tackle domestic violence in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40313","40313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524769","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that asylum caseworkers are trained to assess the claims of people who are seeking asylum on the grounds of persecution relating to religion or belief.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40359","40359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524770","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications to her policies of the findings of the All-Party Parliamentary Group on International Freedom of Religion or Belief's report entitled, Fleeing Persecution: Asylum Claims in the UK on Religious Freedom Grounds, published in June 2016; and what plans she has to implement the recommendations of that report.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40369","40369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524771","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her most recent estimate is of the number of UK citizens who have travelled to fight with Daesh in Syria and Iraq; and how many such persons have since returned to the UK.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40358","40358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524772","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to improve the training and support caseworkers receive on asylum claims in the UK on grounds of religious persecution.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40387","40387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524773","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to implement the recommendations of the report by the All-Party Parliamentary Group for International Freedom of Religion or Belief, entitled Fleeing Prosecution: Asylum claims in the UK on Religious Freedom Grounds.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40386","40386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524774","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on the number of police call-outs of reductions in staffing in (a) mental health units, (b) hospitals and (c) social care services.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40429","40429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524775","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the request of the hon. Member for Inverness, Nairn, Badenoch and Strathspey for an urgent meeting on behalf of his constituents as requested by that hon. Member on 30 May 2016.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40406","40406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524776","2016-06-27","Home Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of provision of frontline police officers to ensure public safety; what steps she is taking to monitor that provision; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40430","40430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524777","2016-06-27","Department for International Development","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to address demolitions by Israel of Palestinian homes and other structures in the West Bank.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40391","40391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524778","2016-06-15","Department for International Development","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the findings of the report of the International Development Committee, UK implementation of the Sustainable Development Goals, HC103, published on 8 June 2016, on the need for a cross-government approach in order to achieve the Sustainable Development Goals, what recent discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on those goals.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40327","40327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524779","2016-06-15","Department for International Development","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the implications are for the Government's policy on using Overseas Development Funding aid through the EU Emergency Trust Fund for Africa to send Eritreans in the EU back to Eritrea of the recommendation by the Commission established by the UN Human Rights Council to refer that country to the International Criminal Court.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40328","40328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524780","2016-06-15","Department for International Development","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the implications for her policies are of the report from the Committee on Development of the European Parliament on the New Alliance for Food Security and Nutrition (NAFSN), published on 3 May 2016, on the Government's support for the NAFSN.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40329","40329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524781","2016-06-15","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many female offenders received an immediate sentence of (a) less than six months and (b) six months or more in each police force area in Wales in each of the last six years; and what the offence group was for such offenders.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40350","40350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524782","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate he has made of the number of EU nationals in prisons in England and Wales in (a) the latest period for which figures are available and (b) each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40280","40280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524783","2016-06-27","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, for what reasons the Government did not extend the European Union Referendum (Voter Registration) Regulations 2016 to Northern Ireland to enable late registration by any method; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40440","40440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524784","2016-06-15","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the level of threat in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) Great Britain from dissident republican groups.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40455","40455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524786","2016-06-27","Prime Minister","2016-06-13","To ask the Prime Minister, by how long his train from London was delayed when attending a meeting with parliamentary colleagues and others at Haywards Heath on 13 June 2016; what alternative arrangements were made for his travel; and what the cost to the public purse was of those arrangements.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40443","40443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524787","2016-06-27","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2016-06-13","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Electoral Commission's staff handbook.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40388","40388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524788","2016-06-27","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2016-06-13","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what guidance the Electoral Commission has given to its staff on political impartiality.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40389","40389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524789","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Transport of 11 May 2016, Official Report, HC Deb, column 692, when officials began working on the proposals to implement the 15-minute threshold for rail journey compensation; from what date he expects that customers will be able claim compensation under that threshold; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40383","40383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524790","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will release a copy of the modelling analysis referred to in the GTR Remedial Plan, published on 12 February 2016, on the combined impact of the infrastructure restrictions at London Bridge, the diversion of Thameslink services and the increased use of London Victoria as a terminus on the punctuality and reliability of the network.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40384","40384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524791","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects part-time season tickets to be available to all rail passengers.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40385","40385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524792","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Prime Minister's Oral Answer Prime Minister of 8 June 2016, Official Report, column 1189, on airport expansion, whether the term summer includes the September sitting of the House.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40390","40390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524793","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received from Calderdale Council on the construction of a new rail station at Elland.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40375","40375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524794","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received from Calderdale Council on the construction of a new rail station at Hipperholme.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40376","40376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524795","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 39089, on railway signals, and with reference to Network Rail's press release of 29 May 2014, entitled Britain's rail revolution quickens pace as first contracts for new traffic management technology are awarded, what the reason is for the difference in the values for Network Rail's traffic management first deployment contract.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40374","40374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524796","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 39089, on railway signals, what the scope of work covered by the installation programme is for the (a) Wales and (b) Romford Rail Operating Centre.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40373","40373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524797","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place in the Library a copy of the training syllabus, training manuals and associated materials on training for Highways England traffic officers for moving vehicles from live lanes to emergency refuge areas.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40409","40409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524798","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discretion is available to local authorities to grant blue badges to disabled people who are in receipt of the enhanced mobility rate of personal independence payment other than through the moving around criteria; and what steps he has taken to monitor local authorities in their exercise of that discretion.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40296","40296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524799","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission an impact assessment of the potential effects of the provisions of his Department's Blue Badge Scheme Local Authority Guidance (England), published in October 2014, on people with autism, mental ill health and learning disabilities.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40294","40294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524800","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of local authorities that charge to issue blue badges to disabled people.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40295","40295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524801","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Southeastern train operating company meets its Public Performance Measure targets.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40286","40286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524802","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2016 to Question 37807 and with reference to the Answer of 29 October 2015 to Question 12850, on Thameslink railway line: rolling stock, for what reasons the introduction of Class 700 trains has been delayed.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40367","40367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524803","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of Clause 21 of the Bus Services Bill on the ability of local authorities in England to acquire a shareholding in existing bus companies.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40365","40365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524804","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2016 to Question 39527, on bus services, what consultation he undertook on the role of municipal bus companies on the proposals in Clause 21 of the Bus Services Bill; and what research he has commissioned on the potential effects of that clause on (a) passengers and (b) the bus services market.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40366","40366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524805","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in pedestrian fatalities between 2013 and 2014.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40290","40290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524806","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the most recent meeting of the (a) Cycling Stakeholder Forum and (b) Cycling Safety Sub-Group was held.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40291","40291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524807","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received about plans to redevelop Cardiff Central railway station.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40292","40292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524808","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2016 to Question 39519, what the whole life cost of the East Coast Main Line Intercity Express fleet is; and how much of that cost will be met by funding from his Department.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40361","40361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524809","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2016 to Question 39519, how much was provided to which projects under funding for (a) Highways England capital expenditure, (b) major transport schemes in local authorities and (c) other rail enhancements.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40360","40360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524810","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 39159, what the figures for his Department's spending on cycling programmes in each year to 2021 are in real terms.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40300","40300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524811","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 39160, what the figures for his Department's spending on walking programmes in each year to 2021 are in real terms.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40301","40301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524812","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the timeliness of bus services across England and Wales in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40303","40303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524813","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the punctuality of railway services across England and Wales in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40304","40304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524814","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 37789, how much investment there has been in rolling stock by (a) private operators and (b) his Department in each year since 1994.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40308","40308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524815","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with (a) East Anglia franchise bidders on rolling stock and (b) rolling stock companies on the East Anglia franchise.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40309","40309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524816","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring before the House legislative proposals on requiring bus companies to instal audio-visual technology to aid visually impaired passengers.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40319","40319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524817","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to assess the potential cost of relocating the Lakeside Energy from Waste Facility in the event of a decision being made to permit the construction of the North West Runway at Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40330","40330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524818","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 37807, on Thameslink railway line: rolling stock, whether he expects the Class 700 Thameslink rolling stock to come into revenue-earning service in 2016.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40331","40331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524819","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 18 April 2016 to Question 33921, on Thameslink railway line: rolling stock, what measures have been put in place relating to evacuation safety risk; and whether his Department has received any other representations on safety relating to Class 700 trains.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40332","40332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524820","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average waiting time is for a driving test appointment (a) in England, (b) at the Halifax test centre and (c) at the Huddersfield test centre.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40334","40334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524821","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's policy is on maintaining an intercity standard train service between (a) Norwich and London, (b) Ipswich and London, (c) Colchester and London and (d) Chelmsford and London.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40322","40322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524822","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether train operators are required in selecting new rolling stock to make an assessment of the effect of such selection on UK industry and the wider UK economy.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40323","40323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524823","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's policy is on taking account of the benefits of contracts to the UK economy in determining future rolling stock orders.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40324","40324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524824","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much revenue Govia Thameslink Railway has paid to the Government since taking up its franchise in 2014.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40444","40444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524825","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the provision of overtime payments to train staff employed by Govia Thameslink Railway.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40445","40445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524826","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that drivers are aware of the need to take care when driving past or near horses and their riders.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40448","40448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524827","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much profit Govia Thameslink Railway  was expected to make over the lifetime of its franchise according to the original business case; and how much profit that company has made since the start of that franchise.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40447","40447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524828","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, (a) on what dates and (b) by what margins Govia Thameslink Railway has been in breach of the terms of its franchise agreement since the start of that franchise in 2014.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40446","40446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524829","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to support women and men who want to remain in employment after reaching state pension age.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40431","40431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524830","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of British nationals claiming pensions who live outside the UK and the European Economic Area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40305","40305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524831","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of British nationals claiming pensions who live outside the UK and in the European Economic Area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40306","40306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524832","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease qualified for attendance allowance in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40288","40288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524833","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people transferred from disability living allowance to personal independence payments in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40289","40289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524834","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been awarded the enhanced rate mobility component of personal independence payment in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40287","40287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524835","2016-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department collects on the (a) cost of tribunal hearings for sanctioned jobseeker's allowance claimants and (b) costs of tribunals for other benefits.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40297","40297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524836","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects Capita to respond to the right hon. Member for Delyn in relation to correspondence dated 1 February, 14 April and 10 June 2016 relating to Mrs M. of Flint.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40348","40348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524837","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what service standard he expects of Capita for response times for correspondence from hon. Members relating to personal independence payments.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40349","40349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524418","2016-06-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if the Government will retain the Apprenticeship Grant for Employers in 2017-18.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40204","40204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524419","2016-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will make an assessment of the effect of the withdrawal of funding from the UK Commission for Employment and Skills on the Government's analysis of skills shortages in the North East.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40241","40241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524420","2016-06-14","Cabinet Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the remit of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 to cover Ombudsman Services provided by the Ombudsman Services Company.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40236","40236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524421","2016-06-14","Cabinet Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what revenue the Government has received from the sale of government-owned assets in the Newcastle upon Tyne local authority area between 2010 and 2016.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40238","40238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524422","2016-06-14","Cabinet Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans the Government has to sell government-owned assets in the Newcastle upon Tyne local authority area.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40239","40239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524423","2016-06-15","HM Treasury","2016-06-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many national infrastructure projects have been established in Scotland since 1997.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40215","40215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524424","2016-06-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to exempt the viewing of sporting events in which nations of the UK are participating from the obligation to pay the TV Licence.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40211","40211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524425","2016-06-15","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if the Government will review the mechanism by which service personnel are awarded payment in the event of life-changing injuries during their time in the armed forces to take greater account of the effect of those injuries on those people.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40214","40214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524426","2016-06-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what account he took of the pattern of complaints relating to terms and conditions made through the service complaints procedures in reforming the pay structure for the armed forces.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40216","40216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524427","2016-06-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to take account of the levels of satisfaction with pay reported in the Regular Armed Forces Continuous Attitude Survey in his setting of pay policy for the armed forces.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40217","40217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524428","2016-06-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the UK's liaison officer to Eurocorps was withdrawn.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40232","40232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524429","2016-06-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what interim milestones he has set for the armed forces to improve their response time to complaints to the target level of 90 per cent closed within 24 weeks.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40240","40240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524430","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has developed proposals that enable academies to be re-brokered with a new sponsor or multi academy trust on the initiative of parents of children in those academies.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40259","40259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524431","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to adjust the pupil premium funding for schools to take account of the additional responsibilities proposed in the Children and Social Work Bill in its current form.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40243","40243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524432","2016-06-14","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement on (a) academy chains and (b) the ability of US or European companies to establish academy chains in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40237","40237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524433","2016-06-14","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many agency staff were contracted to cover classes in primary and secondary schools in England and Wales in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40235","40235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524434","2016-06-14","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans the Government has to increase the number of teachers in training.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40234","40234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524435","2016-06-14","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 38739, whether her Department has made an estimate of the number of children who were receiving School Action or School Action Plus who subsequently would not be expected to meet the criteria for an Education, Health and Care plan.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40221","40221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524436","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on taking account of the effect on demand for school places of immigration (a) in general and (b) from nationals from other EEA countries.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40249","40249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524437","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what research her Department has (a) undertaken and (b) commissioned on the effect of immigration on demand for school places; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40250","40250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524438","2016-06-14","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of the existing 15 hours of free childcare that is provided by nurseries that are (a) private, (b) voluntary and (c) independent.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40248","40248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524439","2016-06-14","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to improve teacher retention.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40263","40263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524440","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from (a) local authorities and (b) other bodies on pressures on school places due to immigration from (i) EU and (ii) non-EU countries.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40251","40251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524441","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the average cost to the public purse of an additional (a) school place and (b) classroom in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40252","40252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524442","2016-06-14","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding for children and young people with special educational needs was allocated to East Sussex local authority area through the dedicated schools grant in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40269","40269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524443","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is her policy that local stakeholders will be able to express views on proposals to require a school to convert to academy status.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40256","40256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524444","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department takes to vet directors of multi-academy trusts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40257","40257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524445","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to ensure that multi-academy trusts are accountable to the parents of students in those academies.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40258","40258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524446","2016-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much progress her Department expects to make towards eliminating fuel poverty by the end of this Parliament.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40206","40206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524447","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential health benefits of increasing the temperature below which cold weather payments are made.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40207","40207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524448","2016-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 8th June 2016 to Question 39232, how many agency workers were employed by her Department in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40209","40209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524449","2016-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 39039, how many of the 193 off-payroll contingent staff employed by her Department since May 2015 were paid through limited companies; and what the total amount paid through limited companies was in that period.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40210","40210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524450","2016-06-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment she has made of the effect on the UK offshore oil and gas industry workforce of the withdrawal of the Super Puma airframes from commercial operation.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40203","40203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524451","2016-06-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the date and title is of all reports that have been provided by Her Majesty's Inspectorate of Constabulary into the Civil Nuclear Constabulary in each of the last five years; and if she will place those reports in the Library.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40228","40228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524452","2016-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the date and title is of all reports and assessments produced by her Department relating to the Civil Nuclear Constabulary in each of the last three years; and if she will place those reports in the Library.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40253","40253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524453","2016-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what fitness testing is carried out for Civil Nuclear Constabulary officers on active service; how many officers were tested in each of the last two years; and what the results of those tests were.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40254","40254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524454","2016-06-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much her Department spent on agency workers in financial year 2015-16; and how much was paid to each agency used in that year.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40255","40255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524455","2016-06-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has made an assessment of the implications for her Department's policies of the findings of the University of Dundee study on the use of clothianidin, imidacloprid and thiamethoxam neonicotinoid  pesticides, published on 28 April 2016.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40264","40264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524456","2016-06-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy not to recognise any future Dalai Lama where that person has been selected by the Chinese government.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40268","40268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524457","2016-06-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that the proposed EU-Canada trade agreement is not implemented until it has been fully scrutinised by national parliaments.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40225","40225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524458","2016-06-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 26 April 2016 to Question 35542, on Asia: climate change, if he will draw to the attention of the Department for Energy and Climate Change the report to which he refers in that Answer.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40245","40245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524459","2016-06-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Chinese counterpart for the release of Tashi Wangchuk.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40229","40229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524460","2016-06-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of delivery of arms by Russia to Fiji.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40219","40219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524461","2016-06-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK offered support to Saudi Arabia for the process of that country being elected to the UN Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40220","40220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524462","2016-06-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Chinese counterpart on releasing the Tibetan blogger Druklo.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40200","40200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524463","2016-06-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Chinese government on the detention and charging of Tibetan education advocate Tashi Wangchuk; and what response he has received to those representations.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40201","40201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524464","2016-06-15","Department of Health","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 38977, how the figure of 10,000 new nursing, midwifery and allied health training places by 2020 was calculated.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40208","40208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524465","2016-06-14","Department of Health","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the final decisions on the Pharmacy Integration Fund.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40226","40226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524466","2016-06-14","Department of Health","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve uptake of cervical screening among all age groups.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40222","40222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524467","2016-06-14","Department of Health","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support Cervical Screening Awareness Week.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40223","40223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524468","2016-06-14","Department of Health","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has made an assessment of how the uptake rate for cervical screening in England compares to that in the rest of Europe.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40224","40224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524469","2016-06-14","Home Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2016 to Question 39000, how many interviews with people making accusations of child abuse have been carried out by Operation Pallial under the Achieving Best Evidence guidance with a social worker present.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40261","40261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524470","2016-06-14","Home Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 June 2016 to Question 39000, how many of the eight people convicted as a result of Operation Pallial investigations had previous convictions for sexual offences.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40262","40262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524471","2016-06-15","Home Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of police community support officers in England and Wales were BME in each year from 2005 to 2015.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40212","40212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524472","2016-06-15","Home Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on access to higher education for people who have been granted humanitarian protection.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40213","40213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524473","2016-06-14","Department for International Development","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the operational readiness of St Helena Airport; and when she expects commercial operations at that airport to commence.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40233","40233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524474","2016-06-14","Department for International Development","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the weekly cost of the deferment of the opening of St Helena Airport.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40230","40230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524475","2016-06-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how the wishes of victims of a crime perpetrated by a foreign national offender are taken into account when considering whether to deport that offender to a foreign prison.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40202","40202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524476","2016-06-14","Scotland Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on steps to prevent consumers purchasing counterfeit electrical goods that are being sold in Scotland.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40265","40265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524477","2016-06-14","Scotland Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the number of counterfeit electrical goods sold in Scotland in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40267","40267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524478","2016-06-14","Scotland Office","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills on steps to prevent counterfeit electrical goods from being sold in Scotland.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40266","40266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524479","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will re-assess the business case for the Hoo Green to Bamfurlong spur of the second phase of High Speed 2 to take account of the decision to place the train depot at Crewe rather than Golborne.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40242","40242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524480","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38478, what the current average time taken is to process driving licence renewal applications for people over 70 years old where medical investigations are required.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40260","40260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524481","2016-06-15","Department for Transport","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 9.2.7 of the report by Lord Heseltine, Tees Valley: opportunity unlimited, published in June 2016, if he will make it his policy to provide a new strategic road Tees crossing.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40244","40244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524482","2016-06-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications there were for personal independence payments in the latest year for which figures are available; what proportion of those applications were rejected; and what proportion of unsuccessful applications were subsequently granted on appeal.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40246","40246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524483","2016-06-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to publish the findings of its forthcoming review on personal independence payments.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40247","40247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524484","2016-06-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many mandatory reconsiderations of jobseekers' allowance sanctions there have been in each of the last five years; and what the total cost was of processing such reconsiderations in each of those years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40205","40205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524485","2016-06-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the value was of the cash commission paid to companies for clients' completion of the Work Programme in each year from 2011 to 2016.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40231","40231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524486","2016-06-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the long-term effect on incomes of households with children affected by the planned replacement of widowed parent's allowance by bereavement allowance.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40218","40218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524487","2016-06-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many winter fuel payments were delayed by administrative problems in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40227","40227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524189","2016-06-14","Attorney General","2016-06-09","To ask the Attorney General, how and why the Crown Prosecution Service (CPS) joined the Metropolitan Police in announcing that retired police sergeant Gurpal Virdi was charged with misconduct in public office and with indecent assault on a person under 16 years; what publicity the CPS recorded as resulting at the time; when the memorandum of a conviction proved 1 April 1987 for offences on 7 November 1986 of a defendant born on 5 September 1970 with informant or complainant recorded as PC Markwick came to the attention of the CPS; what steps were taken to put right the effect of the wrong statement; when those steps were taken; and what the results of those steps were.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40180","40180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524190","2016-06-14","Attorney General","2016-06-09","To ask the Attorney General, what the cost is to the Crown Prosecution Service of obtaining a transcript of the Southwark Crown Court trial of charges against Gurpal Virdi.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40181","40181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524191","2016-06-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of apprentices in the Tees Valley area (a) went on to work full-time with the employer with which they trained and (b) were subsequently unemployed in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40117","40117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524192","2016-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential effect on (a) businesses and (b) the local community in Paisley of the decision to close the Post Office branch and replace it with a franchise.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40139","40139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524193","2016-06-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on (a) businesses and (b) local communities in Scotland of the decision to allow the closure of Post Office branches in Scotland and their replacement by franchises.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40136","40136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524194","2016-06-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether there is a mechanism equivalent to the Cross-Council Funding Agreement to ensure fair peer review and transparency for research proposals crossing the border between the Engineering and Physical Sciences Research Council and the UK Space Agency.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40096","40096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524195","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on the public purse of privatising the Land Registry while maintaining ownership of the Land Register.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40115","40115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524196","2016-06-14","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what contingency plans the Cabinet Office has in place in the event of a high-volume of users causing a slow-down or failure of the gov.uk website.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40105","40105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524197","2016-06-14","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the socio-demographic characteristics of users visiting the gov.uk website.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40097","40097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524198","2016-06-14","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the customer satisfaction ratings were for the gov.uk website related to (a) content accuracy, (b) ability to find information, (c) proportion of users who found the website search tool good or very good and (d) proportion of users who got everything or most of what they wanted when visiting the website since 2012.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40094","40094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524199","2016-06-14","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what contingency plans his Department has in place in the event of a failure of all or part of the gov.uk website.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40091","40091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524200","2016-06-14","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the annual running cost of the gov.uk website was in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40092","40092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524201","2016-06-14","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that those non-UK citizens who are not eligible to vote are not able to vote in the EU referendum.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40157","40157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524202","2016-06-14","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will request that the Electoral Commission investigate the extent to which the electoral roll prepared for the EU referendum on 23 June 2016 contains citizens of EU countries who are not eligible to vote.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40158","40158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524203","2016-06-13","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the proportion of people aged (a) 16 to 24, (b) 25 to 44, (c) 45 to 54, (d) 55 to 64, (e) 65 to 74 and (f) 75 years and older who have the (i) evidence and (ii) technology needed to verify their identity online.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40125","40125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524204","2016-06-13","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2016 to Question 39272, what proportion of the cohort of Civil Service Fast Streamers who joined in April 2013 have already undertaken a regional placement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40168","40168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524205","2016-06-13","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will request that the Electoral Commission investigate the extent to which the electoral roll prepared for the referendum on the UK's membership of the EU 2016 includes citizens of EU countries who are not eligible to vote.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40169","40169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524206","2016-06-13","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that non-UK citizens who are not eligible to vote are not able to vote in the referendum on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40170","40170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524207","2016-06-14","HM Treasury","2016-06-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the level of accuracy of the credit records held by credit reporting agencies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40182","40182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524208","2016-06-14","HM Treasury","2016-06-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when Ministers or senior officials of his Department last met with credit ratings agencies to discuss the accuracy of the credit record histories of UK nationals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40183","40183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524209","2016-06-14","HM Treasury","2016-06-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to require regular audits of the accuracy of records held by credit ratings agencies on UK nationals' credit history; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40184","40184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524210","2016-06-14","HM Treasury","2016-06-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many fines have been levied on credit rating agencies (a) in total and (b) for inaccurate reports of individuals' credit records; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40185","40185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524211","2016-06-14","HM Treasury","2016-06-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to require the Financial Conduct Authority to require credit rating agencies to improve their reporting of an individual's credit record; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40186","40186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524212","2016-06-14","HM Treasury","2016-06-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to provide any funding for a further assessment of the Redcar SSI site as recommended in the independent report, Tees Valley: opportunity unlimited, published on 7 June 2016.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40128","40128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524213","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 24 May 2016 to Question 37689, if he will indicate where in that document details are provided on the (a) potential effect on the triple lock pension policy and (b) value of state pensions for people who retire before 6 April 2016 of a potential reduction in economic growth in the event of the UK voting to leave the EU.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40148","40148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524214","2016-06-14","HM Treasury","2016-06-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the Government's response to the discussion paper on options for supporting English regional airports from the potential impacts of air passenger duty devolution, published in July 2015.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40093","40093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524215","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of (a) local authority and (b) housing association homes in each English local authority area have not met the decent homes standard in each year since 2001.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40126","40126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524216","2016-06-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will provide additional resources to the Tees Valley Combined Authority and Local Enterprise Partnership to assist them in the key role envisioned for them in the independent report, Tees Valley: opportunity unlimited, published on 7 June 2016.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40129","40129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524217","2016-06-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications were made by developers for housebuilding on green belt land in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40163","40163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524218","2016-06-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many houses were built on green belt land in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40156","40156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524219","2016-06-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) unsuccessful and (b) successful applications there were for planning permission for residential homes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40166","40166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524220","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many applications there were by developers for housebuilding on brownfield sites in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40176","40176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524221","2016-06-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 6 June 2016, Official Report, column 825, what the source is for the comments attributed to the Leader of Hull City Council.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40188","40188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524222","2016-06-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what timetable he has set for commencing the second stage of the Leveson Inquiry.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40192","40192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524223","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the budget is of the Mk4A upgrade programme.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40193","40193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524224","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the goal is of the Mk4A upgrade programme.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40194","40194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524225","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Mk4A upgrade is expected to increase the yield of the warhead.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40195","40195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524226","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when work on the Mk4A upgrade programme began.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40196","40196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524227","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Mk4A upgrade is planned to come into service.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40197","40197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524228","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what forecast he has made of by how long the Mk4A upgrade programme will extend the operational life of the current warhead.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40198","40198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524229","2016-06-14","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to increase war pensions for veterans to correspond with the state pension triple lock.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40108","40108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524230","2016-06-13","Department for International Development","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Fallujah.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40109","40109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524231","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent report he has received on seizing Saudi weapons from Syrian rebel forces.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40110","40110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524232","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) regular service personnel, (b) reservists and (c) civilian staff were employed by his Department in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40111","40111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524233","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance his Department is providing to the Iraqi armed forces to help reclaim the city of Fallujah from Daesh.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40112","40112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524234","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department provides (a) at home and (b) in schools for children who have special educational needs and disabilities.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40174","40174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524235","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support apprenticeship providers to take on people who have special educational needs and disabilities.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40175","40175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524236","2016-06-14","Department for Education","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy that any children who would have been entitled to free school meals under the previous system retain that entitlement under the new eligibility criteria under universal credit.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40165","40165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524237","2016-06-14","Department for Education","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will (a) establish an additional National Teaching Service (NTS) pilot in Teesside and (b) give priority to the Tees Valley in the NTS national roll-out in response to the recommendation in Lord Heseltine's report, Tees Valley: opportunity unlimited to prioritise the Tees Valley for national roll-out of the NTS.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40132","40132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524238","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 37443, what guidance her Department provides to admission authorities on how consultations should be advertised.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40146","40146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524239","2016-06-14","Department for Education","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the additional cost relative to the previous system of additional entitlements to free school meals created by new eligibility criteria under universal credit.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40159","40159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524240","2016-06-14","Department for Education","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when new eligibility criteria for free school meals under universal credit will be (a) published and (b) implemented.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40160","40160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524241","2016-06-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans she has to extend consumer protections to customers of district heating schemes.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40167","40167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524242","2016-06-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she plans to respond to the letter of 3 June 2016, from offshore wind companies to EU energy ministers in the June EU Energy Council.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40104","40104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524243","2016-06-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she expects the Bonfield Review of consumer advice, protection standards and enforcement for energy efficiency and renewable energy to be published.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40173","40173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524244","2016-06-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2016 to Question 38502, what estimate she has made of her Department's (a) core total evidence spend and (b) core research and development spend in each of the next five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40177","40177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524245","2016-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assurances she has received from Natural England that the system of wildlife licences provides adequate protection for red squirrel species.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40113","40113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524246","2016-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 May 2016 to Question 35884, on Bees: Pesticides, if she will make it her policy to exercise her powers to lift the temporary ban on neonicotinoids in the future; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40149","40149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524247","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the cost was of operating the British Embassy in Ankara and the Consulate-General in Istanbul in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40144","40144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524248","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on the civil war in Yemen of arms sold by the UK to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40150","40150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524249","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answers of 27 April 2016 to Questions 34797 and 34798, what assessment he has made of the implications for the UK's role in Israeli-Palestinian peace negotiations of UK funding being used by UN-funded non-governmental organisations to commemorate Palestinian terrorists.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40140","40140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524250","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many people are part of the team working on projects to improve Turkey's prospects of joining the EU based at the British Embassy in Ankara; and what the total cost of that team was in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40141","40141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524251","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings the team working on projects to improve Turkey's prospects of joining the EU, based at the British Embassy in Ankara, have had with representatives of the Turkish government in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40142","40142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524252","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to NHS England's consultation on a proposed method to support investment decisions in specialised commissioning, launched on 12 April 2016, if NHS England will issue a consultation on arrangements for commissioning treatments recommended through NICE's highly specialised technology programme.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40102","40102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524253","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans NICE has to consult on its methodology for carrying out evidence reviews and impact analyses to support NHS England's specialised commissioning process.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40103","40103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524254","2016-06-14","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times the list of conditions eligible for a medical exemption certificate has been reviewed since its introduction.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40106","40106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524255","2016-06-14","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to review the list of medical conditions eligible for a medical exemption certificate.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40107","40107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524256","2016-06-14","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) standard and (b) higher rate for NHS-funded nursing care is for 2016-17.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40116","40116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524257","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the mental health services budget is for people living in Tottenham.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40121","40121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524258","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made in implementing recommendation three of the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, published in February 2016, on local multi-agency suicide prevention plans in Tottenham constituency.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40122","40122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524259","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 10 of NHS England's Strategic Framework for Specialised Services board paper, published in May 2016, what plans his Department has to issue directions to NICE regarding the adoption of its guidance by NHS England for treatments recommended through (a) the technology appraisal programme and (b) the highly specialised treatment evaluation programme.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40123","40123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524260","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 10 of NHS England's Strategic Framework for Specialised Services board paper, published in May 2016, what plans NHS England has to trial alternative reimbursement models for drugs and devices.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40124","40124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524261","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the capping of payments to NHS agency staff on levels of patient safety.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40143","40143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524262","2016-06-14","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are resident in the areas covered by each clinical commissioning group in England; and how many births were recorded in each such area in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40133","40133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524263","2016-06-14","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what resources his Department has allocated to assessing the counter-proposal to the Government's plans for community pharmacy published by the Pharmaceutical Services Negotiating Committee in April 2016.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40161","40161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524264","2016-06-14","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to respond to the counter-proposal to the Government's plans for community pharmacy published by the Pharmaceutical Services Negotiating Committee in April 2016.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40162","40162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524265","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will instruct officials of his Department to continue to work with the manufacturers of Nivolumab on ensuring that patients with non-squamous non-small cell lung cancer can access that drug through the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40151","40151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524266","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of hospital shifts that have not been filled as a result of the introduction of caps to the number of NHS agency staff since (a) November 2015, (b) February 2016 and (c) April 2016.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40190","40190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524267","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of staff who have returned to permanent NHS jobs as a result of the introduction of caps on the number of NHS agency staff.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40191","40191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524268","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to NHS England's announcement, NHS England backs general practice with a multi-billion transformation plan, published on 21 April 2016, what formula his Department plans to use to determine the allocation of the 2.4 billion a year funding.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40153","40153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524269","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to NHS England's announcement, NHS England backs general practice with a multi-billion transformation plan, published on 21 April 2016, how much of the 2.4 billion a year funding will be allocated to GPs in (a) Tottenham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Haringey.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40154","40154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524270","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the primary care budget is for people living in Tottenham constituency.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40152","40152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524271","2016-06-14","Department of Health","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2016 to Question 37125, whether his Department has any plans to collect data on the number of student nurses that have already studied for a degree before entering nurse training.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40189","40189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524272","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers who were granted refugee status were not provided with a (a) biometric residence permit and (b) National Insurance number by her Department before their 28-day asylum support ceased in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40155","40155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524273","2016-06-14","Home Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the Metropolitan Police is of obtaining a transcript of the Southwark Crown Court trial of charges against Gumpal Viladi.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40178","40178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524274","2016-06-14","Home Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Metropolitan Police have provided her with a copy of the memorandum of a conviction/order entered in the Register of Lambeth East Juvenile Court that records the proving on 1 April 1987 of offences or complaints by PC Markwick by a defendant aged over 16 on 7 November 1986.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40179","40179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524275","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will provide additional funding for transfer cases related to the Dublin Regulation where further evidence of family links is needed for asylum to be granted.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40147","40147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524276","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, to how many unaccompanied child refugees her Department has granted permission to join family in the UK; and what the countries of origin were of such children.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40127","40127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524277","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied child refugees have been reunited with relatives in the UK since the announcement, Unaccompanied asylum-seeking children to be resettled from Europe, on 4 May 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40120","40120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524278","2016-06-14","Home Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugees currently housed in the refugee camp in Calais are unaccompanied children; and what steps are being taken to ensure that the asylum applications of those children are prioritised.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40095","40095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524279","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications for the Government's policy on asylum of the report by the All-Party Parliamentary Group for International Freedom of Religion or Belief, entitled Asylum report: inadequate assessment of religion-based claims, published in June 2016.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40100","40100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524280","2016-06-14","Home Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugees currently housed in the refugee camp in Calais have immediate family members already resident in the UK; and what steps are being taken to reunite those families.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40098","40098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524281","2016-06-13","Department for International Development","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that its support for education in its target countries reaches (a) girls and (b) other marginalised groups.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40172","40172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524282","2016-06-13","Leader of the House","2016-06-09","To ask the Leader of the House, what estimate he has made of the potential cost of providing simultaneous and written translation in Welsh Grand Committees for bilingual proceedings.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40145","40145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524283","2016-06-14","Scotland Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much funding the Government provided to Citizens Advice Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40187","40187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524284","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which organisation (a) was responsible and (b) carried out the modelling on punctuality and reliability of the combined impact of the infrastructure restrictions at London Bridge, the diversion of Thameslink services and the increased use of London Victoria as a terminus; how much that modelling cost; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40199","40199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524285","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the redacted Govia Thameslink Railway remedial plan, dated 12 February 2016, was not made publicly available until 26 May 2016.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40171","40171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524286","2016-06-14","Department for Transport","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many full-time equivalent officials of his Department are working on the invitation to tender for the West Midlands rail franchise; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40164","40164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524287","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to decide which stations will be affected by Network Rail's decision to defer Access to All works from Control Period 5 into Control Period 6; and how the outcome of that decision will be published.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40118","40118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524288","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department has received on the recommendation of Sir Peter Hendy's report published in November 2015, on replanning of Network Rail's Investment Programme to defer Access to All works from Control Period 5 to Control Period 6.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40119","40119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524289","2016-06-27","Department for Transport","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects work to commence on providing disabled access to all platforms at Lichfield Trent Valley railway station in response to his Department's review of the Access for all programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40101","40101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524290","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what additional funding his Department plans to make available for walking and cycling initiatives as a result of the cycling and walking investment strategy.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40114","40114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524291","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the number of starts in Scotland on the Work Choice programme in each of the last three financial years for which such information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40135","40135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524292","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what research his Department has undertaken on the potential merits of implementing a universal basic income.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40099","40099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524293","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the number of referrals for individuals in Scotland to the Work Choice programme in each of the last three financial years for which such information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40138","40138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524294","2016-06-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 37474, how many full-time equivalent officials of his Department are responsible for any debt collection activity that the CMS system is undertaking to ensure that former Child Support Agency child maintenance arrears are received.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40130","40130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524295","2016-06-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 27 May 2016 to Question 37474, on children: maintenance, what specific areas of case closure require less effort than earlier analysis suggested.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40131","40131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524296","2016-06-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the level of income that the Health and Safety Executive will receive from commercial sources in each year up to 2019-20.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40134","40134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524297","2016-06-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the number of job outcomes in Scotland for the Work Choice programme in each of the last three financial years for which such information is available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40137","40137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524785","2016-06-15","Prime Minister","2016-06-09","To ask the Prime Minister, how many former interpreters for UK armed forces in Afghanistan have applied to settle in the UK; and how many such applications have been successful.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905427","905427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525192","2016-06-15","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential effectiveness of the agreements reached at the Anti-Corruption Summit in May 2016 in tackling corruption.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905422","905422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525193","2016-06-15","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect of the National Citizen Service on life chances.","Biography information for Huw Merriman","Huw Merriman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905420","905420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/525194","2016-06-15","Cabinet Office","2016-06-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to amend provisions of the Representation of the People Act 1983 relating to the franchise.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 905417","905417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523832","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016, HCWS30, whether his Department carried out an equality effect assessment on the effect on the public of the decision to centralise policy functions in his Department's London office.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39894","39894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523833","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which bodies have made representations to the Government on the inclusion of administration costs, travel and wages in the funding for the Digital Apprenticeship System; and what proportion of bodies making such representations were in favour of the Government's proposals.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39941","39941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523834","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether a provider would need to achieve an Excellent rating in (a) one, (b) two or (c) three of the Teaching Quality, Learning Environment and Student Outcomes and Learning Gain categories in order to achieve an overall Excellent rating under the Teaching Excellence framework.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39919","39919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523836","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, by when he expects the findings from the Insolvency Service investigation into BHS to be published.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39931","39931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523837","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in which month the Pye Tait Review of retentions in the construction industry will be published.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39981","39981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523839","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what resources his Department has allocated to the Regulatory Delivery Directorate for enforcement of part G of the Building Regulations 2010 in domestic properties.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40034","40034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523840","2016-06-13","Cabinet Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings Ministers of his Department had to discuss tax evasion and avoidance between (a) 5 April 2016 and 5 May 2016 and (b) 6 May 2016 and 6 June 2016.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39936","39936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523841","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings Ministers of his Department had to discuss tax evasion and avoidance between (a) 5 April 2016 and 5 May 2016 and (b) 6 May 2016 and 6 June 2016.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39934","39934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523842","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government's anti-poverty objectives in (a) Malawi, (b) Ghana and (c) Nepal are being taken into account when negotiating tax treaties with those countries.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39928","39928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523843","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the distributional effect of the exclusion from National Insurance contributions of property, dividends, pensions and other forms of non-employment income.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39914","39914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523844","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representation there will be on the board of the Institute for Apprenticeships from (a) business, (b) charities and (c) trades unions.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39895","39895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523845","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the funding caps for apprenticeship standards and frameworks will be in the new levy system.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39896","39896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523846","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which body will have the responsibility for conducting reviews of the funding caps on apprenticeship standards and frameworks.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39899","39899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523847","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how frequently the funding caps on apprenticeship standards and frameworks will be reviewed.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39900","39900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523848","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 June 2016 to Question 905207, what definition of the digital economy is used by (a) his Department, (b) the Office of National Statistics and (c) other government bodies.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39901","39901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523849","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to prevent regulated financial intermediaries from promoting products in the unregulated sector by implying that victims of misselling or fraud will have recourse to the protections offered by regulation.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39907","39907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523850","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Department for International Development had any role in the current negotiations of tax treaties with (a) Malawi, (b) Lesotho, (c) Ghana and (d) Nepal.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39976","39976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523852","2016-06-13","HM Treasury","2016-06-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what role the new money guidance body will play in coordinating financial capability initiatives.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40051","40051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523858","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Local Government Association on the effect of charges on local authorities of changes to funding over the next five years announced in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39883","39883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523860","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Northern Ireland Executive on steps to support first-time buyers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39884","39884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523862","2016-06-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Northern Ireland Executive on reducing the number of people sleeping rough in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39886","39886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523867","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons TV Licensing is not included in the Tell Us Once service.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39908","39908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523869","2016-06-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to ensure that landmarks in the stewardship of English Heritage fly the Union flag in place of the organisation's house flag.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39881","39881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523871","2016-06-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the amount charged to the deceased by TV Licensing in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39915","39915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523873","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will develop plans to include TV Licensing in the Tell Us Once service.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39920","39920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523875","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of each type of vehicle procured as part of urgent operational requirements for (a) Operation Herrick and (b) Operation Telic have been returned to the UK.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39947","39947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523877","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Jackal and (b) Foxhound patrol vehicles were in use by the Army in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39948","39948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523880","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many merchant seafarers employed by the Royal Fleet Auxiliary have retired in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39970","39970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523882","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to implement recommendation 15 of the Department for Transport's Maritime Growth Study, published in September 2015, on improving links between the Royal Navy and the wider UK maritime sector.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39966","39966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523885","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 May 2016 to Question 38217, on his Department's BME pay gap, where the information about this is held; and what estimate he has made of the cost of providing the information.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39973","39973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523887","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his Ministerial colleagues on the potential effect of the recommendations of the Maritime Growth Study, published in September 2015, on the future supply of UK-domiciled merchant seafarers to the Royal Fleet Auxiliary.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39967","39967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523889","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Type 26 frigate will be able to operate across the full range of climatic conditions in which the Royal Navy operates.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39921","39921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523891","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has considered purchasing the AeroVironment Blackwing miniature tube-launched drone.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39911","39911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523893","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has met representatives of AeroVironment to discuss the Blackwing miniature tube-launched drone.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39912","39912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523896","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made in the provision of helicopter evacuation capability for members of the armed forces injured in combat zones since 2004.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39913","39913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523898","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing a British field hospital for Kurdish Peshmerga; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39942","39942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523902","2016-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to extend the operational life of the Type 23 frigate.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39922","39922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523903","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a Board of Inquiry was held following the deaths of the recruits at Deepcut barracks between 1995 and 2002; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39923","39923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523904","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will write to the Chief Constables of Surrey and Devon  and Cornwall Police Forces to request that they place in the public domain their reports into the deaths at Deepcut barracks between 1995 and 2002; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39924","39924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523905","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the library the evidence provided by the Royal Military Police to the (a) Surrey Police and (b) Devon and Cornwall Police inquiries into deaths at Deepcut barracks between 1995 and 2002; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39925","39925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523906","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps have been taken by his Department as a result of the recommendations of the Review by Sir Nicholas Blake QC of the circumstances surrounding the deaths of four soldiers at Princess Royal Barracks, Deepcut between 1999 and 2002, published in 2006, relating to statements detailed in the Appendix to that review by civilian staff and recruits of (a) sexual harassment, (b) sexual assault and (c) bullying at that base; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39926","39926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523907","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State, House of Lords Official Report, 27 April 2016, Column 1229, how many independent service police investigations have been carried out on allegations of civilian casualties during operations against Daesh in Iraq and Syria in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39927","39927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523908","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Royal Fleet Auxiliary's (a) operational and (b) crew costs were in each year from 2008-09 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39902","39902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523909","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many merchant seafarers were employed by the Royal Fleet Auxiliary in each year from 2008-09 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39903","39903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523910","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many merchant seafarers employed by the Royal Fleet Auxiliary took voluntary redundancy in each year from 2008-09 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39904","39904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523912","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will assess the effect of the use of Lariam on the quality of performance of military personnel on operations.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39872","39872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523913","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the factors underlying decisions to leave the armed forces early; and what he is doing to address the most significant factors behind such decisions.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39979","39979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523914","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the Royal Fleet Auxiliary's future requirement for (a) officer cadets and (b) ratings.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39969","39969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523915","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on morale among members of the armed forces of the transition from Pay 2000 to the new Pay 16 pay structure.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39957","39957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523916","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what health and safety assessment his Department has conducted on military personnel or contractors loading or unloading equipment from his Department's vessels onto the pier head at Ascension Island.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39958","39958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523917","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Royal Navy assets on global maritime patrol are used to maximum effect in combatting illegal, unregulated and unreported fishing.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39959","39959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523919","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average cost is to the (a) Royal Navy and (b) Royal Fleet Auxiliary of training (i) an officer cadet and (ii) a rating.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39968","39968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523920","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether HMS Lancaster is in a state of extended readiness.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40031","40031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523921","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department established the Nuclear Warhead Capability Sustainment Programme at the Atomic Weapons Establishment (AWE); who has been appointed as Senior Responsible Owner for that programme; who the key stakeholders for that programme are; how many scientists from the US national nuclear weapons laboratories are seconded to work on that programme; how many AWE scientists have visited the US national nuclear weapons laboratories as part of that programme; what that projected full cost of that programme is; how many scientists are working on that programme; how much has been spent on that programme to date; and what estimate he has made of the cost of that programme to completion.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39995","39995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523922","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether HMS Dauntless is being used as a harbour training and accommodation ship.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40030","40030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523923","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will provide field surgical teams for the Peshmerga Regional Government.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40008","40008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523924","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how old the (a) women and (b) men in the army were who told the Sexual Harassment Report 2015 survey that they had been a victim of a sexual assault in the previous 12 months.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39983","39983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523926","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of staff at the Army Foundation College Harrogate who have direct contact with children have yet to be cleared by the Disclosure and Barring Service.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39984","39984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523927","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what methods are used to immobilise fissile material removed from dismantled nuclear warheads withdrawn from operational service; what that cost is of that immobilisation programme; and where that process is carried out.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39994","39994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523928","2016-06-15","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to publish post-occupancy evaluations of primary and secondary schools built under wave 1 of the Priority Schools Building Programme.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40035","40035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523929","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of schools in England have access to a defibrillator; and if she will make an assessment of how that proportion compares to the equivalent proportions in each other constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39992","39992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523930","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to increase the proportion of schools with access to a defibrillator.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39991","39991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523931","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidelines her Department issues on inset days at schools in England.","Biography information for Steve Brine","Steve Brine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39982","39982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523932","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress her Department has made on creating a 10 million fund for small schools to secure expert support and advice on converting to academy status.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40029","40029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523933","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much notice her Department gave schools of the changes to primary school SATs tests in 2016.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40046","40046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523934","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many investigations her Department is currently carrying out into unregistered schools in England; and what steps her Department is taking to monitor such schools.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40028","40028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523935","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will review her Department's decision not to publish a Children's Home Data Pack for the year ending 31 March 2015.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39998","39998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523936","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 13 April 2016 to Question 32732, when she plans to publish a response to the consultation into out-of-school education settings.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39876","39876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523938","2016-06-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households in each (a) region of and (b) parliamentary constituency in the UK received the Energy Company Obligation (i) between 2010 and 2015 and (ii) since May 2015.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39898","39898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523940","2016-06-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of potential steps to reduce greenhouse gas emissions associated with domestic hot water production.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40033","40033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523941","2016-06-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will publish a plan setting out how all government departments plan to contribute to reducing the UK's carbon emissions.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39977","39977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523942","2016-06-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 8 March 2007 to Question 125573 and paragraph 1.21 of the National Audit Office's report, HC360, 1995-96, what the reasons are for the difference in the figures given in those documents for the Government's guarantee of the Mineworker's Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40047","40047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523944","2016-06-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the total (a) energy consumption and (b) amount of greenhouse gas emitted by domestic properties for heating water in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40032","40032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523946","2016-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to support fishing any stocks at a higher level than the maximum sustainable yield level in the forthcoming negotiations on the multi-annual plan to manage North Sea fish stocks.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40038","40038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523947","2016-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many whales, dolphins and other aquatic mammals have been beached on British shores in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39933","39933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523948","2016-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what technical assistance her Department has offered to the government of the Pitcairn Islands to help ensure that its draft biosecurity legislation meets best practice.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39960","39960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523950","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Canadian counterpart on steps to secure the release of foreign hostages held by Muslim extremists in the Philippines.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39891","39891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523951","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2016 to Question 29803, what representations his Department made to the government of China at the annual UK-China Human Rights Dialogue held in April on accusations of the harvesting of organs in that country.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39875","39875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523952","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received representations to support the candidacy of Argentine Foreign Minister Susanna Malcorra for the position of UN Secretary General; what assessment he has made of the potential effect on UK sovereignty over the Falkland Islands of such an appointment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39873","39873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523953","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress his Department has made on supporting the establishment of marine protected areas in the high seas.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39961","39961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523954","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which departmental budget is supporting the Government's blue belt policy to protect marine biodiversity in the UK Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39962","39962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523955","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what medical assistance the UK provides to the Peshmerga in the Kurdistan region.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39943","39943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523957","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department plans to publish a strategy for its blue belt policy to protect marine biodiversity in British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40037","40037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523958","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has extended to the British Overseas Territories of St Helena, Ascension and Tristan da Cunha the (a) International Convention on Civil Liability for Oil Pollution Damage 1969, (b) 1992 Protocol to the International Convention on the Establishment of an International Fund for Compensation for Oil Pollution Damage, (c) 2010 Protocol to the International Convention on Liability and Compensation for Damage in Connection with the Carriage of Hazardous and Noxious Substances by Sea, (d) International Convention on Civil Liability for Bunker Oil Pollution Damage 2001, (e) International Convention on Oil Pollution Preparedness, Response and Co-operation 1990 and (f) 1997 Protocol to the International Convention for the Prevention of Pollution from Ships 1973.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40036","40036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523959","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will support the provision of specialist treatment at the Queen Elizabeth Hospital Birmingham for seriously injured Peshmerga from the Kurdistan region in Iraq.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40012","40012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523961","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role the Government is playing in UN discussions on improving mechanisms for casualty recording.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40001","40001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523962","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Burundi on (a) ending political violence and unrest and (b) alleged extra-judicial killings, torture, lack of freedom of expression and other human rights abuses in that country.","Biography information for Joanna Cherry","Joanna  Cherry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40003","40003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523963","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how  much the NHS spent on treating people with medical conditions caused by botox injections in the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40023","40023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523964","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the most expensive drugs bought from pharmaceutical companies by the NHS were in the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40024","40024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523965","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the average price paid by the NHS for prescription drugs in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40025","40025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523966","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the amount paid by the NHS to pharmaceutical companies for prescription drugs in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40026","40026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523967","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on interpreters in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39980","39980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523968","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to increase the provision of respite and replacement care for carers in England.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40019","40019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523969","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to develop a cross-departmental strategy to provide more support to carers in England.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40020","40020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523970","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the proportion of each Sustainability and Transformation Plan area's total place-based target allocation was calculated.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39975","39975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523971","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the largest financial contracts between the NHS and pharmaceutical  companies were in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40017","40017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523972","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate NHS England has made of the projected savings from the introduction of dose banding of chemotherapy drugs without affecting quality of care.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40000","40000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523973","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of access to stroke rehabilitation services in areas that are socio-economically deprived.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40014","40014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523975","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the budget for NHS Protect was in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40070","40070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523976","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost of rough sleeping to the NHS.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40058","40058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523977","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on GP services of increasing medical indemnity costs for GPs.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39917","39917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523978","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the divergence between the below-average incidence of testicular cancer amongst men living in the most deprived areas and the above-average number of deaths amongst that cohort when diagnosed with testicular cancer.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39918","39918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523979","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 3 May 2016 to Question 35936, on blood: contamination, when he plans to publish a formal response to the public consultation.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39880","39880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523980","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 15 April 2016 to Question 33132, when he plans to publish details of NHS support funding for community pharmacies under the Pharmacy Access Scheme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39879","39879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523981","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment NHS England has made of variation in aseptic services and the delivery of high quality infusional chemotherapy to cancer patients.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39964","39964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523982","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage NHS England and the Medicines and Healthcare Products Regulatory Agency to collaborate to ensure aseptic capacity is managed to a commonly high standard, is reimbursed at a sustainable level and supports further investment to meet growing demand in the NHS.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39963","39963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523983","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment NHS England has made of the capacity in the NHS to meet the demand for aseptic services.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39965","39965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523984","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of first year students enrolled onto undergraduate-level nursing degrees in England are studying part-time.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39949","39949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523985","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many recommendations of the report of the public inquiry into Mid Staffordshire NHS Foundation Trust have not been implemented.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39932","39932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523986","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve early diagnosis and treatment of testicular cancer amongst men living in the most deprived areas.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39945","39945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523987","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the diagnosis and treatment of cytomegalovirus in infants and children.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39930","39930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523988","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department last reported on what progress has been made implementing the recommendations of the report of the public inquiry into Mid Staffordshire NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39938","39938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523989","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to promote integrated care in the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39885","39885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523990","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people under the age of 18 have died after receiving the HPV vaccination in the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39887","39887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523991","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing on the NHS laser-guided shoes to people with Parkinson's disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39888","39888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523992","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to improve end-of-life care over the next five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39889","39889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523993","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Royal College of Nursing on the effect of boredom on obesity.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39890","39890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523994","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 12 April 2016 to Question 32505, where the updated guidance on dealing with family reunion applications referred to in that Answer can be found.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39877","39877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523995","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to monitor the effect of the introduction of the Psychoactive Substances Act 2016.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39937","39937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523996","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were prevented from travelling to the UK by the authority to carry scheme in each month of its operation.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39971","39971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523997","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was spent on e-borders before April 2006; and how much has been spent on e-borders and its successor programmes since April 2006.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39972","39972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523998","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full-time equivalent officials in her Department are responsible for identifying, verifying and processing potential Dublin Regulation transfer cases.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39897","39897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523999","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to introduce compulsory advanced notification for (a) commercial and (b) pleasure craft of arrival in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40057","40057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524000","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of applications for visitor visas from each country were accepted in the most recent year for which records are available.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39999","39999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524001","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to tackle smuggling and trafficking at British ports.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40050","40050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524002","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied asylum seeking children were denied permanent asylum having applied as an adult in 2015.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39996","39996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524003","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department issues to police forces on the provision of photographic evidence, where available, to people who have committed road traffic offences.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39974","39974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524004","2016-06-13","House of Commons Commission","2016-06-08","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what the budget was for the out-of-hours taxi service for armed police officers working in the House in each of the last five years; and on how many occasions that service was used in each of those years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40018","40018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524005","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress his Department has made on returning to political negotiations to end the conflict in Yemen; and what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK's support for the Saudi-led coalition on achieving this aim.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40002","40002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524006","2016-06-13","Department for International Development","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the funding commitments her Department have made to contribute to the UN sustainable development goals; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39989","39989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524007","2016-06-13","Department for International Development","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what contribution her Department has made to the UN Sustainable Development Goals in the last six months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39990","39990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524008","2016-06-13","Department for International Development","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of total EU member states' aid the UK aid funding represents.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39951","39951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524009","2016-06-13","Department for International Development","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with the devolved administrations on her Department's priorities.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39952","39952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524010","2016-06-13","Department for International Development","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with her US counterpart on levels of corruption in states in receipt of international aid.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39954","39954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524011","2016-06-13","Department for International Development","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether UK aid for the Ethiopian government is conditional upon that government addressing human rights concerns.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39893","39893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524012","2016-06-13","Department for International Development","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that UK aid for the conflict in Yemen benefits its intended recipients; and what proportion of the 85 million of aid for Yemen committed in the last year has been used to support children.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39874","39874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524013","2016-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many fines of what total monetary value were written off by HM Courts Service in Staffordshire in each year since 2011-12.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39882","39882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524014","2016-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times he has visited Wales in his official capacity since the last UK general election.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39905","39905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524015","2016-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times Ministers in his Department have visited Wales in an official capacity since the last UK general election.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39906","39906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524016","2016-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many men have (a) been charged with and (b) served a prison sentence for non-violent crimes in the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40021","40021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524017","2016-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women have (a) been charged with and (b) served a prison sentence for non-violent crimes in the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40022","40022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524018","2016-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to undertake a review of the sentencing guidelines for traffic offences.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40049","40049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524019","2016-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate he has made of the number of lawyers trained in supporting people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40055","40055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524021","2016-06-13","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate she has made of cost to the Electoral Office for Northern Ireland of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39955","39955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524022","2016-06-13","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions she has had with the Police Service of Northern Ireland on financial resources and increasing levels of recruitment.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39953","39953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524023","2016-06-13","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Chief Electoral Officer on proposed industrial action by electoral office staff in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39950","39950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524024","2016-06-13","Northern Ireland Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the efficiency and effectiveness of the Electoral Office for Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39956","39956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524025","2016-06-13","Prime Minister","2016-06-08","To ask the Prime Minister, how many meetings he had to discuss tax evasion and avoidance between (a) 5 April 2016 and 5 May 2016 and (b) 6 May 2016 and 6 June 2016.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39935","39935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524026","2016-06-13","Prime Minister","2016-06-08","To ask the Prime Minister, when he plans to reply to the letter of 27 April 2016 from the hon. Member for Redcar and the hon. Member for Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland on the All Party Parliamentary Group on Steel.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39939","39939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524027","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what further steps the Government plans to take to reduce the incidence of drownings of refugees and migrants in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39929","39929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524028","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make representations to Ryanair on the cost of amending boarding passes and other travel documents.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39892","39892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524029","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of the inclusion of the Northallerton to Teesport line in the rail electrification scheme.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39946","39946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524030","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the evidence given by the Minister of State for Transport to the EU Internal Market Sub-Committee on 18 April 2016, what the (a) purpose, (b) membership and (c) date of the last meeting of the new forum the Government has established is.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39940","39940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524031","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he agreed to a variation of the franchise contract with Govia Thameslink Railway in respect of Southern Railway; and what consultation took place with hon. Members before he agreed that variation.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40027","40027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524032","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of transport projects delivered from the Local Growth Fund have been dedicated to walking to date.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39978","39978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524033","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many coastguard search and rescue helicopters are available for operations in Scotland.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40005","40005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524034","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the coastguard response time was to the incident off Portobello in Edinburgh in the early hours of 15 May 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40006","40006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524035","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which coastguard stations cover the Firth of Forth.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40007","40007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524036","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how his Department measures the performance of the coastguard.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40004","40004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524037","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the coastguard search and rescue capability for the Firth of Forth is.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40009","40009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524038","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the amount spent by his Department on audio-visual systems intended for buses in the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39985","39985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524039","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received from local transport authorities on the implementation of audio-visual systems on public transport in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39986","39986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524040","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what coastguard personnel responded to the incident off Portobello beach in Edinburgh in the early hours of 15 May 2016.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40010","40010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524041","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average response time is for coastguard personnel on emergency callouts; and what the longest response times were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40011","40011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524042","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of existing public transport infrastructure for people with sight and hearing loss; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39988","39988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524043","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many coastguard rescue (a) employees and (b) volunteers cover Scotland.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40013","40013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524044","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 26 April 2016 to Question 34503, if he will release a summary or redacted version of risk assessments carried out by the Cross-Government Working Group on RPAS.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40015","40015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524045","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 12 April 2016 to Question 32352, whether the memorandum of understanding between the Home Office, the Civil Aviation Authority and the police has been agreed.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40016","40016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524046","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to engage with the European Aviation Safety Authority task force assessing the risk of collision between drones and aircraft.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39997","39997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524047","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on transport infrastructure projects in Thornbury and Yate constituency in each year from 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40048","40048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524048","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 15 of his Department's Cycle Delivery Plan, published in October 2014, what progress has been made on his Department's review of road traffic law.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40053","40053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524049","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which bus operators his Department has (a) met and (b) otherwise engaged with during the last six months on the Bus Services Bill.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40054","40054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524050","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department has received from the new Mayor of London on working together to deliver his manifesto commitment to freeze transport fares.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40052","40052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524051","2016-06-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average cost was of a tribunal hearing for a benefits claimant who had been sanctioned for not complying with work search requirements in the last 12 months; how many such tribunals there were in each of the past five years; and what the total cost was of those tribunals in each of the past five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39944","39944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524052","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the affordability of the child support system for people who are self-employed.","Biography information for Joanna Cherry","Joanna  Cherry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39916","39916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524053","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of children likely to be affected by the planned replacement of widowed parent's allowance by bereavement allowance.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39909","39909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524054","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the annual saving which would be generated by the planned replacement of widowed parent's allowance by bereavement allowance.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39910","39910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524055","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 4 May 2016 to Question 35935, when he plans to publish the report of the review into the supported housing sector.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39878","39878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524056","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to involve providers in the review of supported housing.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40069","40069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524057","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Stafford constituency are in receipt of the New Enterprise Allowance.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39993","39993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524058","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has had with stakeholders on the terms of reference of the forthcoming review on personal independence payments.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39987","39987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524060","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department plans to collect data on Government funding allocated to brain tumour research.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40068","40068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524061","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent progress has been made on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership negotiations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40086","40086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524062","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answers of 25 May 2016 and 31 March 2016 to Questions 37757 and 31997, if he will publish data on referrals made by the Pay and Work Rights Helpline in 2014-15.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40084","40084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524063","2016-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what powers environmental health officers have to assess excessive noise from residential and commercial properties on a street level.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40087","40087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524064","2016-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to enable environmental health officers to assess excessive noise in a neighbourhood on a daily basis.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40088","40088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524065","2016-06-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what measures are in place for environmental health officers to arrange a second observation of excessive noise in a property where a household frequently changes occupancy.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40089","40089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524066","2016-06-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of naval vessels and aircraft routinely conduct monitoring and reporting of maritime activity (a) in the presence of vessels engaged in fishing and (b) otherwise when they are operating in or transiting through the Exclusive Economic Zone of British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40044","40044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524067","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Lord Heseltine's report, Tees Valley: Opportunity unlimited, published on 7 June 2016, what assessment her Department has made of the feasibility of a University Technical College or Institute of Technology in the Tees Valley area.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40065","40065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524068","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children (a) in total and (b) per 10,000 children are in care in each local authority in England.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40074","40074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524069","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many residential children's homes with capacities of (a) fewer than six and (b) six or more residents operate in England.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40075","40075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524070","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many residential children's homes have (a) closed and (b) opened in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40076","40076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524071","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to publish the findings from areas piloting 30 hours of free childcare.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40077","40077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524072","2016-06-13","Department for Education","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authority children's services departments have been visited by the Chief Social Worker for Children since she took up that post.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40078","40078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524073","2016-06-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department has taken to support the Teesside Carbon Capture Storage Collective since the announcement of the reduction in government funds in that sector.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40079","40079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524074","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that Government aid to the fishing sector on St Helena supports pole and line fishing methods.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40039","40039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524075","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on establishing a fully-protected marine reserve in the waters of Ascension Island.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40040","40040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524076","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether all government vessels are checked by rodent detection dogs before visiting locations where rodents have been eradicated in South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40041","40041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524077","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many rodent reintroduction incidents have occurred on South Georgia since the commencement of the rodent eradication project.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40042","40042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524078","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the next review of the South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands Marine Protected Area is planned to take place.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40045","40045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524080","2016-06-13","Cabinet Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 6 June 2016 to Question 38408, what the budget of the European Fast Stream was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40073","40073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524081","2016-06-13","Department for International Development","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the feasibility of air drops of humanitarian aid in Syria; and what her Department's strategy is for ensuring humanitarian aid is delivered to Syria after the passing of the UN deadline on 1 June 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40083","40083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524082","2016-06-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he has made on negotiations with the Libyan government on plans to tackle human trafficking and smuggling.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40090","40090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524083","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve awareness and education of cytomegalovirus among parents and children.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40080","40080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524084","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 28 April 2016 to Question 35252, how many staff in NHS trusts were (a) off-payroll in 2013-14 and (b) paid off-payroll in NHS foundation trusts in 2012-13.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40085","40085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524085","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff have been employed by NHS Protect in each of the last eight years; and how many such people were employed as investigators.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40071","40071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524086","2016-06-13","Department of Health","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff were paid off-payroll in each agency for which his Department is responsible in each of the last  three financial years for which information is available.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40072","40072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524087","2016-06-13","Department for International Development","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to include best practice biosecurity and waste management requirement clauses in its next contract for the Pitcairn Island supply ship.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40043","40043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524088","2016-06-13","Prime Minister","2016-06-08","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to the oral Answer of 8 June 2016, Official Report, which treaty changes (a) protect the UK from ever closer union and (b) provides protection for the UK's currency; and on what date he plans those treaty changes to be made.","Biography information for Richard Drax","Richard Drax","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40082","40082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524089","2016-06-13","Department for Transport","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of transport projects delivered from the Local Growth Fund have been dedicated to cycling to date.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40056","40056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524090","2016-06-13","Home Office","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many penalty charges have been issued for motorway middle lane offences since the legislation governing those charges came into force.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40081","40081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524091","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's Employment and Support Allowance: Work Capability Assessment Outcomes Made on Paper Evidence, published on 19 November 2012, if he will publish the figures for tables 1, 2 and 3 for the financial years 2102-13, 2013-14, 2014-15 and 2015-16.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40066","40066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524092","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average cost to the public purse was of processing a mandatory reconsideration of a (a) universal credit and (b) jobseeker's allowance sanction in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40067","40067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/524093","2016-06-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-06-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance he has issued to supported housing providers about funding following the absorption of housing benefit into universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 40064","40064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523363","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Post Office has spent on settlement agreements and redundancy payments for Crown Office staff since January 2010.","Biography information for Mhairi Black","Mhairi Black","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39588","39588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523364","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many former Crown post offices which have been franchised have (a) closed and (b) relocated since January 2010.","Biography information for Mhairi Black","Mhairi Black","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39589","39589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523365","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Post Office has spent on refurbishing the premises of the Crown Post Office in Paisley since January 2010.","Biography information for Mhairi Black","Mhairi Black","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39590","39590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523366","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016, on BIS consultation, HCWS30, what assessment his Department has made of the relative level of difficulty in redeploying (a) London-based and (b) non-London-based staff to address urgent priorities.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39598","39598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523367","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016, on BIS consultation, HCWS30, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of split-site working and recruiting on a flexible location basis for policy officials.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39599","39599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523368","2016-06-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Written Statement of 26 May 2016, HCWS30, how many roles there are (a) at and (b) below Senior Civil Service level based in the Sheffield office at St Paul's Place.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39618","39618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/523369","2016-06-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-06-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to (a) improve the transparency of car hire firms and (b) ensure people hiring cars are not incorrectly charged for damage to such cars.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 39638","39638"
