"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086750","2019-03-14","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 228749 on Driving: Autism, what estimate he has made of the number of drivers with autism affected by the guidance on the DVLA website between 15 February and 4 March.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230831","230831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086751","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the total amount is of compensation paid from the public purse to sub-postmasters who have left the network under Post Office Ltd's network transformation programme.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230832","230832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086752","2019-03-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the Sri Lankan Government's progress towards meeting the objectives set by the UN Human Rights Council in resolutions 30/1 and 34.1 on promoting reconciliation, accountability and human rights in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230918","230918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086753","2019-03-14","Attorney General","2019-03-11","To ask the Attorney General, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230833","230833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086754","2019-03-14","Wales Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230834","230834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086755","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many sub-postmasters have conditionally resigned from the Post Office Network but are not able to leave because an alternative cannot be found which would allow them to receive the government-funded leavers payment.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230835","230835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086756","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post offices (a) retailers operate and (b) each retailer operates.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230836","230836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086757","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the decision-making authority of Planning Inspectorate for the development of the AQUIND interconnector on the effectiveness of local democracy.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230919","230919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086758","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the evidential basis was for the decision to provide the Planning Inspectorate with decision-making powers for the development of the AQUIND interconnector.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230920","230920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086759","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether an interconnector development has taken place as a result of a decision by the Planning Inspectorate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230921","230921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086760","2019-03-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many temporary sub-postmasters are currently operating branches in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales, (c) Northern Ireland, and (d) each region of England.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230837","230837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086761","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to allow students to study British Sign Language at school.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230726","230726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086762","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the National Genomic Strategy will be launched; and what opportunities there will be for stakeholder involvement in that strategy's development.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230838","230838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086763","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how his goal to sequence five million genomes will be realised; and what steps his Department will take to ensure that participants reflect the demographic make-up of the population.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230839","230839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086764","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to ensure that the upcoming Pubs Code review includes a full public consultation.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230840","230840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086765","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether consumers will have the opportunity to share their views as part of the review into the Pubs Code.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230841","230841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086766","2019-03-14","Wales Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what plans his Department has for participation in Earth Hour on 30 March 2019.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230656","230656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086767","2019-03-14","Wales Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the Minister for the Cabinet Office on increasing electoral registration and voter turnout in Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230657","230657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086768","2019-03-14","Wales Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department has spent on external consultants in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230658","230658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086769","2019-03-14","Wales Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of statistical datasets collected or collated by his Department are made publicly available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230659","230659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086770","2019-03-13","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2019 to Question 226656 on Railways: Passengers, what corresponding increases in capacity in the form of (a) new rolling stock and (b) infrastructure enhancements have been provided by the rail industry in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230842","230842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086771","2019-03-13","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what carbon budget his Department has set for this year and each of the next (a) five, (b) 10 and (c) 15 years.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230843","230843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086772","2019-03-13","Department for Transport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the capacity of the rail freight industry to support the construction of High Speed Two.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230844","230844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086773","2019-03-14","Department for International Trade","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 229270 on Exports: Advertising, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the Exporting is Great campaign working with (a) private sector partners, and (b) a network of exporters to promote exporting.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230922","230922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086774","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) more parents are able to access a place at their preferred school and (b) permanently excluded children are able to access places at alternative mainstream schools.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230923","230923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086775","2019-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of youth services and social services on reducing youth violence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230924","230924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086776","2019-03-13","Department for International Trade","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 229270 on Exports: Advertising, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the Music Exporting Growth Scheme.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230925","230925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086777","2019-03-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to provide additional funding and support to youth services and projects engaging with young people at risk of violence.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230926","230926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086778","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimates his Department has made of the reduction of frontline police officers in each year since 2015 in (a) Lambeth and Southwark BCU, (b) London and (c) England.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230927","230927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086779","2019-03-14","Home Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans his Department has to (a) increase frontline police numbers and (b) ensure police have sufficient resources to tackle knife crime and other forms of violent crime.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230928","230928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086780","2019-03-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of student residences which have been identified as having aluminium composite material cladding that is unlikely to meet the limited combustibility requirements set out in Building Regulations guidance; and what steps he is taking to ensure all student residences meet the requirements of that guidance.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230845","230845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086781","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has in place for people to claim legacy benefits who have not been given access to universal credit in (a) full and (b) live service areas.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230846","230846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086782","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has spent in restoring British endangered species in each if the last three years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230847","230847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086783","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many national nature reserves are (a) at risk of deteriorating and (b) deteriorating.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230848","230848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086784","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure NHS Resolution's claims management system has an injury code specific to invasive Group B Streptococcus (GBS) infection to improve the quality of data collection on GBS clinical negligence cases.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230607","230607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086785","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many wildlife licence applications Natural England has completed within the 30-day time frame in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230849","230849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086786","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many SSSI enforcement actions have Natural England undertaken in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230850","230850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086787","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make invasive Group B Streptococcus infection a notifiable disease.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230615","230615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086788","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he will enable Liverpool CCG to award General Medical Contracts rather than continue with Alternative Provider Medical Services Contracts to ensure the continuation of GP services currently being provided by Primary Care Connect in the Garston and Halewood Constituency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230660","230660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086789","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer to 11 March to Question 228713 on Nuclear Reactors, what direct funding is available for a feasibility and development project for (a) tidal and (b) wave energy projects.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230851","230851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086790","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his policy of not allowing GP services provided via Alternative Provider Medical Services Contracts to be provided using other contractual models such as General Medical Services Contracts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230661","230661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086791","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2019 to Question 228711, what funding has been spent to date on the strategy for small modular nuclear reactors; and what funding has been contractually committed.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230929","230929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086792","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to amend (a) the statutory Code of Practice for the Welfare of Dogs and Code of Practice for the Welfare of Cats in relation to invisible fencing containment systems and (b) the Animal Welfare Act 2006 to ban the use of hand-held remote controlled e-collar devices.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230930","230930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086793","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what research his Department has commissioned on the effect on GP services in deprived communities of continuing to provide GP services through Alternative Provider Medical Services Contracts when the operators of such contracts hand them back; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230662","230662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086794","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to review the policy of General Medical Services Contracts not being able to provide GP services when Alternative Provider Medical Contracts fail.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230663","230663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086795","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, from which of his Department's budgets the Selective School Expansion Fund will be funded.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230852","230852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086796","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has allocated any funding for free schools to other policy areas in the past 12 months.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230853","230853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086797","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has revised the draft Animal Welfare (Sentencing and Recognition of Sentience) Bill since his Department closed the consultation on 26 October 2018; and when he plans to lay the Bill before Parliament.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230931","230931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086798","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has diverted any funds that had been allocated to the improvement and expansion of alternative provision to other policy areas in the past 12 months.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230854","230854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086799","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to (a) change the maximum penalty for offences under section 32(1) of the Animal Welfare Act 2006 and (b) make it easier to prosecute attacks on service animals.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230932","230932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086800","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what legislative steps he plans to take to introduce compulsory milk contracts between producers and purchasers.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230933","230933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086801","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Farm Animal Welfare Committee has completed its review of standards for animal welfare during transport.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230934","230934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086802","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to ban third party sales of puppies and kittens.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230935","230935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086803","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to find those responsible for the blood products that were imported from the US during the 1970s and 1980s which were contaminated and consequently caused people in the UK to be infected with HIV and Hepatitis.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230936","230936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086804","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which head teachers he met on (a) 7 March 2019 (b) 8 March 2019 and (c) 9 March 2019.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230937","230937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086805","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to seek an exemption for those travelling to the EU with a guide dog in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal and is treated as an unlisted or third country for the purposes of travelling with a pet.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230727","230727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086806","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what occasions since he took office he has met with representatives of the National Association of Head Teachers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230855","230855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086807","2019-03-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department plans to take to respond to concerns raised by representatives of the solar industry on the proposed Smart Export Guarantee scheme.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230631","230631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1086808","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, to which Commonwealth states the Government is providing assistance on changes to LGBT law.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230938","230938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088082","2019-03-14","Women and Equalities","2019-03-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to help women return to the labour market after taking a career break to fulfil caring responsibilities.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909790","909790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1088615","2019-03-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-11","Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, What steps the Government is taking to ensure that the welfare system works for women.","Biography information for Alex Burghart","Alex Burghart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909797","909797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084380","2019-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on security and democracy of the appointment of unelected governors who are members of the AKP in towns and cities in Turkey with predominant Kurdish populations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230020","230020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084381","2019-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure a free and fair election in Turkey.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230021","230021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084382","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the validity of the findings of the Council of Europe Venice Commission Opinion on Constitutional Arrangements and Separation of Powers and the Independence of the Judiciary and Law Enforcement in Malta.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230022","230022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084383","2019-03-12","Treasury","2019-03-08","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the relationship between reductions in funding for children’s services and associated costs for (a) schools, (b) the police and (c) the NHS.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230050","230050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084384","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the correlation between funding for children’s services between 2010-11 and 2017-18 and the number of (a) referrals to children’s services, (b) referrals to children's services within 12 months, (c) children in need, (d) child protection enquiries, (e) child protection plans and (f) looked after children over that period.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230051","230051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084385","2019-03-12","Department for International Trade","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government will take to exempt the NHS and other public services from future trade deals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230026","230026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084386","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2019 to Question 225494 on European Research Council and Marie Curie Fellowships, if will he publish the independent advice from Sir Adrian Smith.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230082","230082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084387","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the  August 2017 Life sciences: industrial strategy report, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the process of translating academic discovery into industry drug development in (a) immunology, (b) genomics and (c) other areas where the UK is world-leading.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230083","230083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084388","2019-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2019 to Question 221547, on Voting Rights; EU Nationals,which EU member states have yet to confirm reciprocal voting rights for UK citizens residing in their respective state in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230023","230023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084389","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of UK citizens that have been offered diplomatic protection by the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230027","230027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084390","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Burkina Faso; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230028","230028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084391","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of life expectancy in (a) Coventry South, (b) Coventry and (c) the West Midlands since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230029","230029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084392","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the number of students from disadvantaged backgrounds studying for degree-level apprenticeships.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230030","230030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084393","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with (a) universities and (b) police forces on the safety of universities from terrorist activity.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230031","230031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084394","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he will report to Parliament annually on the operation of the Voluntary Scheme for Branded Medicines Pricing and Access; and whether such reporting will extend to the operation of the statutory pricing scheme.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230052","230052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084395","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress has been made on increasing NHS uptake of innovations prioritised by the Accelerated Access Collaborative; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230053","230053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084396","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether, as a result of the 2019 Voluntary Scheme for Branded Medicines Pricing and Access, he has plans to review the role and scope of the Accelerated Access Collaborative.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230054","230054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084397","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans are in place with respect to section 3.54 of the 2019 Voluntary Scheme for Branded Medicines Pricing and Access on UK data infrastructure.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230055","230055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084398","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that payments under the 2019 Voluntary Scheme for Branded Medicines Pricing and Access are used to increase access to medicines that are recognised by NICE as (a) cost and (b) clinically effective.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230056","230056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084399","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of increasing the state pension age on access to benefits; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230024","230024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084400","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224488 on European University Institute, whether he has sought legal advice on his assessment that in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal, the UK’s membership of the EUIC will automatically cease on 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230057","230057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084401","2019-03-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2018 to Question 153188 on Common Travel Area, what further areas of reciprocal rights will be included within the Common Travel area in addition to the six areas listed in that Answer.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230084","230084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084402","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224488 on European University Institute, whether he has consulted the European University Institute on the status of UK membership of the European University Institute Convention following the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230085","230085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084403","2019-03-13","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2018 to Question 153188 on Common Travel Area, for what reason the reciprocal voting rights for Irish citizens do not cover referendums; and what assessment she has made of the implications of that for Irish citizens in Northern Ireland in relation to any border poll conducted under schedule 1 of the Northern Ireland Act 1998.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230086","230086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084404","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department's White Paper on The UK’s future skills-based immigration system, Cm 9722, how the  proposed future introduction of Electronic Travel Authorisation for EU nationals set out in that White Paper will operate within local journeys in the Common Travel Area and local journeys over the Irish land border.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230087","230087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084405","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many job seeker's allowance claimants in Bradford East were subjected to sanctions in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230088","230088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084406","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many job seeker's allowance claimants in Bradford East who were subjected to sanctions in each year from 2010 successfully overturned the sanction decision.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230089","230089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084407","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children in households affected by the two-child limit on welfare payments are in (a) Bradford East and (b) West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230090","230090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084408","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many successful appeals there have been against decisions on (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment claims in Bradford East in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230091","230091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084409","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many successful mandatory reconsiderations against decisions there were for (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment claimants in Bradford East in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230092","230092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084410","2019-03-12","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department has plans to allow self-employed migrants to enter the UK under the proposed future skills-based immigration system.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230058","230058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084411","2019-03-12","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect on the construction industry of only allowing skilled visas for roles at RQF Level 3 or above; and if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of reducing that requirement to RQF Level 2.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230059","230059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084412","2019-03-12","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposals in the Immigration White Paper on the construction industry.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230060","230060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084413","2019-03-12","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what engagement he has had with representatives of the construction industry on the Immigration White Paper.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230061","230061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084414","2019-03-12","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to tackle forced labour in the construction industry.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230062","230062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084415","2019-03-12","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that any future changes to immigration policy do not lead to a rise in forced labour.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230063","230063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084416","2019-03-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Government guidance entitled Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by her Department Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after failing the tax compliance questions in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230093","230093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084417","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after failing the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230094","230094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084418","2019-03-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after failing the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230095","230095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084419","2019-03-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after failing the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230096","230096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084420","2019-03-13","Department for Transport","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the guidance entitled, Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after failing the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230097","230097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084421","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many meetings he had with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230034","230034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084422","2019-03-12","Cabinet Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings he held with his Department's Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230035","230035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084423","2019-03-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230036","230036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084424","2019-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230037","230037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084425","2019-03-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230038","230038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084426","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230039","230039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084427","2019-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230040","230040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084428","2019-03-12","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230041","230041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084429","2019-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230042","230042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084430","2019-03-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230043","230043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084431","2019-03-12","Treasury","2019-03-08","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230044","230044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084432","2019-03-12","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230045","230045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084433","2019-03-12","Department for International Development","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many meetings she held with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230046","230046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084434","2019-03-12","Department for International Trade","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230047","230047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084435","2019-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230048","230048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084436","2019-03-12","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many meetings she held with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230049","230049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084437","2019-03-12","Prime Minister","2019-03-08","To ask the Prime Minister, how many meetings she held with her Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230064","230064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084438","2019-03-12","Scotland Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230065","230065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084439","2019-03-12","Department for Transport","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230066","230066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084440","2019-03-12","Wales Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many meetings he held with his Department’s Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 December 2018 and 28 February 2019.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230067","230067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084441","2019-03-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 7 February 2019 to Question 215122 on Foreign and Commonwealth Office: Official Hospitality, for what purpose his Department organised the (a) Patient Safety Conference Reception and the (b) St David's Day Reception.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230068","230068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084442","2019-03-13","Cabinet Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has for publication of Conflict, Security and Stability Fund programme summaries up to the end of July 2019.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230069","230069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084443","2019-03-12","Department for Transport","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2019 to Question 226511, whether London Overground has submitted proposals to close ticket offices at any of its stations.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230025","230025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084444","2019-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in Indonesia on the proposed early release of Abu Bashir.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230070","230070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084445","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had with Ofsted on how effective management of pupil exclusions can be strengthened in the new inspection framework for schools.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230098","230098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084446","2019-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in South Sudan of sexual violence committed by that country's armed and security forces against displaced persons.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230071","230071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084447","2019-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Egyptian counterpart on their cooperation with the Italian investigation into the murder of former Cambridge University student, Guilio Regeni.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230072","230072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084448","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school efficiency advisers have been (a) employed and (b) deployed by his Department since 2017.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230032","230032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084449","2019-03-13","Department for Education","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many school efficiency advisers have been deployed in each region since 2017.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230033","230033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084450","2019-03-13","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times he has visited immigration detention centres since his appointment as Secretary of State for the Home Department; and which immigration detention centres he has so visited.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230099","230099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084451","2019-03-12","Scotland Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 26 April 2018 to Question 136969 on Scotland Office: Freedom of Information, if he will publish the findings of his Department's review of its practices on publication of Freedom of Information responses.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230100","230100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084452","2019-03-12","Scotland Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the cost to the public purse was of his Department's communications team in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230101","230101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084453","2019-03-12","Scotland Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much money his Department has spent on social media advertising in each month since August 2018.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230102","230102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084454","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data the Government collects on the number of bleeds people with severe haemophilia have each year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230073","230073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084455","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer 1 February 2019 to Question 209777 on Personal Independence Payment, what the medical conditions were of personal independence payment claimants who applied under normal rules and died after registering but prior to her Department making a decision on their claim.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230074","230074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084456","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2019 to Question 209777 on Personal Independence Payment, after how many days on average the 5,290 claimants who applied for personal Independence payment under special rules for terminally ill people died after registering but prior to her Department making a decision.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230075","230075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084457","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2019 to Question 209778 on Personal Independence Payment, how many of the 7,990 personal independence payment claimants who died within six months of their claim being registered and had their claim disallowed applied under normal rules; what conditions such claimants had; and what reasons were given for their claims being disallowed.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230076","230076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084458","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2019 to Question 209778 on Personal Independence Payment, how many of the 7,990 personal independence payment claimants who died within six months of their claim being registered and had their claim disallowed applied under special rules for terminal illness; what conditions such claimants had; and what reasons were given for their claim being disallowed.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230077","230077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084459","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer on 1 February 2019 to Question 209780 on Personal Independence Payment, how many personal independence payment claimants who died within three months of their initial application being disallowed applied under normal rules; and what conditions those claimants had.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230078","230078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084460","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2019 to Question 209780 on Personal Independence Payment, how many personal independence payment claimants who died within three months of their initial application being disallowed had made previous claims that were refused.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230079","230079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084461","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2019 to Question 209781 on Personal Independence Payment, what the recorded reasons for claimants being disallowed at initial decision under normal rules.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230080","230080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084462","2019-03-12","Department for Transport","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of trains have run without second member of staff for (a) all and (b) part of the service on GTR Southern Railway services in (a) 2016, (b) 2017 and (c) 2018.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230103","230103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084463","2019-03-12","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 211250, on Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence against Women and Domestic Violence, what new protective tools have been introduced.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230104","230104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084464","2019-03-12","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 211250,  on the Council of Europe Convention on Preventing and Combating Violence against Women and Domestic Violence, if he will publish the guidance and support for frontline professionals.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230105","230105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084465","2019-03-12","Home Office","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which criterion the Government does not meet in order to ratify Istanbul Convention.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230106","230106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084466","2019-03-12","Department for International Trade","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) the NHS and (b) other public services will be excluded from future trade deals.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230107","230107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1084467","2019-03-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many Linear Accelerator machines NHS England purchased as a result of the £130 million funding allocated to the Linear Accelerator programme in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18  and (c) 2018-19; and how many machines it plans to purchase in (i) 2019-20 and (ii) 2020-21 as a result of that programme.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230081","230081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083513","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether it is his Department's policy to fund the cost of replacing faulty composite fire doors in all public and private sector high rise buildings.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229620","229620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083514","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the extent of financial pressure on social landlords caused by the pursuit of property disrepair claims.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229621","229621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083515","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will ensure that the rough sleeping statistics published by his Department comply with the code of practice for official statistics.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229622","229622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083516","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that pupils are (a) taught the history of and (b) well informed about the holocaust.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229716","229716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083517","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure the full allocation of the Community Housing Fund is allocated.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229623","229623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083518","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received representations on the sharing by the United States Administration of the draft proposals in its Middle East Peace Plan with (a) Egypt, (b) Jordan and (c) the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229652","229652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083519","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for food imports from the US of the United States - European Union Negotiations: Summary of Specific Negotiating Objectives, published by the Office of the United States Trade representative in February 2019.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229717","229717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083520","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent violent protests and Israeli military exercises on stability in the region of the Gaza border.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229653","229653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083521","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Cuban counterpart on the legalisation of same-sex marriage in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229654","229654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083522","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons his Department decided to increase the cap on the amount of funding between February and May 2016 for the Garden Bridge Trust that could be used for pre-construction activity.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229718","229718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083523","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS rollout of lung cancer scanning programmes, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of smoking cessation methods.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229719","229719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083524","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has (a) had discussions with the Charity Commission and (b) received representations on the appropriateness of the Garden Bridge Trust chair meeting the Charity Commission chair in 2013 to seek his advice on how to register the trust as a charity.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229720","229720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083525","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to widen access to blood glucose monitoring technology for diabetes patients.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229721","229721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083526","2019-03-14","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 224488, what the evidential basis is the statement in that answer that the UK’s EU membership is inextricably linked to its current membership of the European University Institute Convention and that the UK’s membership of the EUIC will automatically cease on 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229722","229722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083527","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to implement Part 4 of the Education and Skills Act 2008 in order to require registration and inspection of independent alternative education providers that provide part-time education for at least 12.5 hours a week.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229723","229723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083528","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that the UK is able to end the live export of animals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229590","229590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083529","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Defence on animal welfare standards at the Defence Science and Technology Laboratory at Porton Down.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229724","229724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083530","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure the Industrial Strategy supports BAME-owned businesses.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229655","229655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083531","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support BAME-run businesses.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229656","229656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083532","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to encourage entrepreneurship in BAME communities.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229657","229657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083533","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy,  what steps he is taking to ensure that business start-up support schemes funded by his Department are engaging with BAME communities.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229658","229658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083534","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the default measure of housing supply derived under the standardised methodology can be bypassed where a Local Plan has been submitted under the transitional arrangements which meets its objectively assessed need; whether increased weight can be attributed to the emerging plan in respect of a five-year housing land supply; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229725","229725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083535","2019-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) men and (b) women have (i) been imprisoned for less than six months and (ii) been imprisoned for less than six months and reoffended within a year of release in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229726","229726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083536","2019-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of implementing a presumption against the use of custodial sentences of less than six months for non-violent crimes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229727","229727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083537","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has in place to ensure that UK carbon emissions continue to fall year on year.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229728","229728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083538","2019-03-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has in place to ensure that the proportion of renewable resources in the UK's energy mix continues to increase year on year.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229729","229729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083539","2019-03-12","Department for International Development","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has in place to support (a) countries increasingly affected by extreme weather linked to climate change and (b) refugees displaced by the effects of climate change.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229730","229730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083540","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had with international counterparts to promote a global co-ordinated approach on tackling climate change.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229731","229731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083541","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Iranian counterpart on reports that crowds chanted death to Theresa May and called for the destruction of Israel and America during a rally to mark the 40th anniversary of the Islamic revolution.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229659","229659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083542","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 5.16 of Budget 2018, what proportion of the £410 million for adult and children's social care will be allocated to children’s social care.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229732","229732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083543","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking in advance of the Spending Review to ensure that children’s services departments are adequately funded.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229733","229733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083544","2019-03-12","Cabinet Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff at the National Cyber Security Centre are categorised as (a) supplier resource and (b) contingent labour.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229624","229624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083545","2019-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Government of Malta on establishing a public inquiry to determine what the Maltese authorities (a) knew and (b) ought to have known of the real and immediate risk to the life of journalist Daphne Caruana Galizia.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229596","229596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083546","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 106036, how many of the sites considered for the UK Holocaust Memorial were first brought to the attention of the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation (a) before 7 September 2015, (b) between 7 September and 30 October 2015 inclusive and (c) after 30 October 2015.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229625","229625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083547","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2018 to Question 203298, on what date the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation made the decision that (a) Millbank Tower should no longer be considered as a possible site for the Holocaust Learning Centre and (b) the preferred site for the Learning Centre was Victoria Tower Gardens.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229626","229626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083548","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much public money has been spent by the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation to date; what assessment he has made of the financial accountability of that Foundation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229627","229627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083549","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2018 to Question 203303, for what reasons Royal Parks was not involved in the selection of the design for the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre in Victoria Tower Gardens.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229628","229628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083550","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2018 to Question 203301, on what date (a) the Government and (b) the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation decided that the constraints on locating the Holocaust Learning Centre in Victoria Tower Gardens could be overcome and that the proposed location should be confirmed.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229629","229629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083551","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2018 to Question 203301, what new information available between 14 September 2016 and 24 October 2017 underlay the Government’s conclusion that the (a) technical, (b) financial, (c) planning and (d) other constraints on locating the Holocaust Learning Centre in Victoria Tower Gardens could be overcome.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229630","229630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083552","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2018 to Question 203301, what criteria the Government used to determine whether the constraints on co-locating the Holocaust Learning Centre with the Memorial in Victoria Tower Gardens could be overcome.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229631","229631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083553","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what undertakings the Government has given the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation on the availability of land in Victoria Tower Gardens for the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre; how much land those undertakings cover; and on what dates those undertakings were given.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229632","229632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083554","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on what date (a) the Government and (b) the UK Holocaust Memorial Foundation were first informed about the potential application of section 8 (1) of the London County Council (Improvements) Act 1900 to the proposed location of the Holocaust Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229633","229633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083555","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to reverse the decline in the number of secondary school students taking GCSE language courses.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229597","229597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083556","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the study published in the journal Biological Conservation entitled Worldwide decline of the entomofauna: A review of its drivers, what steps his Department will take to reverse the decline of the insect population.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229598","229598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083557","2019-03-12","Department for Transport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 13 February 2019 to Questions 218813 and 218814, what the timescale is for the delivery of a Southern Rail Link to Heathrow; and when he plans to set out further opportunities for market involvement in that project.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229599","229599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083558","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 13 February 2019 to Questions 218813 and 218814, what estimate his Department has made of the journey times to Heathrow Airport from stations in the London Borough of Sutton after the opening of a Southern Rail Link.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229600","229600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083559","2019-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many use of force incidents occurred during the escorting of detained children to and from (a) young offender institutions, (b) secure training centres and (c) secure children’s homes in each of the last five years; and what proportion of these involved the use of (i) Minimising and Managing Physical Restraint (MMPR) and (ii) non-MMPR techniques.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229734","229734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083560","2019-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest level of Minimising and Managing Physical Restraint (MMPR) technique, low, medium, high or pain-inducing, was for each MMPR use of force incident during the escort of detained children to and from (a) young offender institutions, (b) secure training centres and (c) secure children’s homes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229735","229735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083561","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether a record is kept of restraint for good order and discipline during detained children’s escort to and from (a) young offender institutions, (b) secure training centres and (c) secure children’s homes.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229736","229736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083562","2019-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many complaints on the use of force by custody escort staff have been made by, or on behalf of, detained children escorted to and from (a) young offender institutions, (b) secure training centres and (c) secure children’s homes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229737","229737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083563","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase awareness of different forms of contraception among students in secondary schools.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229604","229604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083564","2019-03-12","Cabinet Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of efforts to secure UK elections from outside interference in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229605","229605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083565","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate he has made of the proportion of UK electricity demand which will be supplied by non-nuclear renewable sources in (a) 2020, (b) 2030 and (c) 2040.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229606","229606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083566","2019-03-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve levels of patient satisfaction with the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229607","229607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083567","2019-03-11","Cabinet Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229738","229738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083568","2019-03-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229739","229739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083569","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229740","229740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083570","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229741","229741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083571","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229742","229742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083572","2019-03-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229743","229743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083573","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the total number of schools in England that have metal- or knife-detecting technology.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229608","229608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083574","2019-03-11","Department for International Development","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many consultations by her Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229744","229744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083575","2019-03-11","Department for International Trade","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229745","229745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083576","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229746","229746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083577","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many consultations by her Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229747","229747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083578","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229748","229748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083579","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229749","229749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083580","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229750","229750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083581","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229751","229751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083582","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions his Department has had with local authorities on the use of public spaces protection orders to target homeless people.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229609","229609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083583","2019-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229752","229752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083584","2019-03-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229753","229753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083585","2019-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229754","229754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083586","2019-03-12","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many consultations by her Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229755","229755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083587","2019-03-11","Leader of the House","2019-03-07","To ask the Leader of the House, how many consultations by her Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229756","229756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083588","2019-03-11","Scotland Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many consultations by his Department (a) are open, (b) are closed awaiting a Government response and (c) have been initiated since 2016.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229757","229757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083589","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 211713 on Universal Credit; when the (a) minutes of the meeting between the Social Security Advisory Committee and officials in her Department and (b) joint report will be published.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229758","229758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083590","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the managed migration pilot phase will include sufficient numbers of claimants who are deemed to be vulnerable to allow for the collection of meaningful data on how vulnerable claimants can be safely migrated.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229759","229759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083591","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans are in place to evaluate the managed migration pilot phase; whether that evaluation will be an independent evaluation; and whether her Department plans to publish an evaluation report.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229760","229760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083592","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government is taking steps to ensure that claimants in the managed migration pilot who are deemed to be vulnerable are not put at risk due to their benefits stopping.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229761","229761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083593","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of companies who have transferred the apprenticeship levy in London.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229660","229660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083594","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the potential merits of using existing data to pre-populate Universal Credit applications for people who are (a) terminally ill and (b) in the support group; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229762","229762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083595","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to increase consumer awareness of the potential advantages and disadvantages of investing in cryptoassets.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229610","229610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083596","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of rules regulating the installation and operation of digital signage in residential areas and the effect of light pollution from these signs on local residents.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229634","229634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083597","2019-03-12","Cabinet Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to ensure that the minutes of all quarterly Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman meetings are displayed clearly on their website.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229763","229763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083598","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has held with his Ukrainian counterparts on potential foreign interference in that country's forthcoming presidential election.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229611","229611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083599","2019-03-12","Cabinet Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to ensure that stakeholders of the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman who raise questions on the Ombudsman's service charter receive a response.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229764","229764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083600","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how long it takes for the proceeds of serious crime to be administered to communities through (a) the safer communities fund and (b) other grant applications.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229765","229765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083601","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants have moved to Universal Credit from legacy benefits to date.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229635","229635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083602","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an estimate of the number of people who will move to universal credit from legacy benefits each month from March 2019 to July 2020 apart from people moved as part of the managed migration pilot.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229636","229636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083603","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of claimants who will move to universal credit from legacy benefits (a) in total and (b) through managed migration.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229637","229637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083604","2019-03-11","Attorney General","2019-03-07","To ask the Attorney General, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on weight given to victim statements under the unduly lenient sentencing scheme.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229766","229766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083605","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent estimate his Department has made of the total net economic effect of foreign tourists visiting (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229612","229612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083606","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to improve access to high speed broadband for small rural businesses.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229767","229767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083607","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made on developing proposals for national tenant representation following his Green Paper on social housing.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229638","229638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083608","2019-03-11","Women and Equalities","2019-03-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the legislation on sexual harassment in the workplace.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229613","229613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083609","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of (a) a maximum level of funding for the administration and (b) guidance on the pay structure of charitable organisations to ensure that an adequate level of funding is allocated to their charitable causes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229768","229768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083610","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 36 of his social housing Green Paper, if he will publish a summary of the responses to his question on whether there is a need for a stronger representation for residents at a national level.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229639","229639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083611","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions,pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2019 to Question 223219 on Personal Independence Payment: Epilepsy, how many people with epilepsy who were in receipt of disability living allowance but did not receive an award as a result of a reassessment for personal independence payment have chosen to appeal that decision through (a) mandatory reconsideration and (b) a tribunal.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229769","229769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083612","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on short stay visitor visas for EEA nationals wishing to visit the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229770","229770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083613","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans for a national tenant-led consultation with tenants on how to set up a national tenant body.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229640","229640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083614","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Green Paper on social housing, what plans he has to rebalance the relationship between landlords and residents in the social housing sector.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229641","229641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083615","2019-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many warning signs and injuries occurred during the restraint of detained children being escorted to and from (a) young offender institutions, (b) secure training centres and (c) secure children’s homes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229771","229771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083616","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the current shortfall in the number of occupational health professionals.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229772","229772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083617","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the recycling rates in Nottinghamshire in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229773","229773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083618","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the reduction in Category M prices and the single activity fee on the financial sustainability of community pharmacies.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229774","229774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083619","2019-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he had with his Emirati counterpart during his visit to Abu Dhabi on 3 March 2019.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229661","229661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083620","2019-03-12","Department for Transport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what financial and other support he plans to allocate to the Newcastle-under-Lyme constituency to build the required infrastructure identified in the area local cycling and walking infrastructure plan.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229662","229662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083621","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Timpson report on exclusions was completed; and when he plans to publish that review.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229592","229592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083622","2019-03-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his letter of 24 October 2018 to the hon. Member for East Worthing and Shoreham, when he plans to make a decision on the call-in of the New Monks Farm planning application in Lancing West Sussex.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229593","229593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083623","2019-03-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the guidance entitled Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after failing the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229775","229775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083624","2019-03-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the guidance entitled Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after failing the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229776","229776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083625","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the guidance entitled Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after failing the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229777","229777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083626","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many veterans in receipt of a war pension are claiming employment support allowance as part of their universal credit claim.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229663","229663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083627","2019-03-12","Department for International Trade","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the guidance entitled Procurement policy note 03/14: promoting tax compliance, how many suppliers were allocated contracts by his Department as a result of complying with (a) one and (b) more than one of the mitigating circumstances after failing the tax compliance questions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229778","229778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083628","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many veterans in receipt of (a) an armed forces compensation scheme guaranteed income payment and (b) the war pension scheme unemployability supplement have undertaken a work capability assessment to prove their entitlement to the housing element of universal credit in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Mrs Helen Grant","Mrs Helen Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229664","229664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083629","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many high street banks offer Islamic mortgage services.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229779","229779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083630","2019-03-12","Department for International Trade","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what his Department’s policy is on the inclusion of private provision of NHS Services in future trade negotiations with other countries in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229780","229780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083631","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of universal credit claimants have been able to verify their identity successfully online; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229601","229601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083632","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken is for a universal credit claim to be verified manually when the claimant is not able to verify their identity online.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229614","229614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083633","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many companies in London have transferred support for apprenticeships arising from their apprenticeship levy payments to other employers to date.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229615","229615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083634","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total number and proportion of universal credit claimants who have applied for advance payments is in each of the past five years; and what number and proportion of such applications have been approved.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229665","229665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083635","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the process is for her Department when it considers an application for an advance payment for universal credit.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229666","229666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083636","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how long it takes on average to process an advance payment application for universal credit.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229667","229667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083637","2019-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in the German Government on reports of UK residents who allegedly collaborated with the Nazi regime during the second world war receiving pensions under the war victims' legislation of that country.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229781","229781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083638","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the environmental effect of oil exploration operations in Poole Bay.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229591","229591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083639","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of care leavers aged 22-25 years old had contact with a personal adviser in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229782","229782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083640","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many care leavers aged 19-25 years there are by local authority in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229783","229783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083641","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many care leavers aged 19-21 years old have had contact with a personal adviser in each local authority area in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229784","229784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083642","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many care leavers aged 22-25 years old have had contact with a personal adviser in each local authority area in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229785","229785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083643","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many care leavers aged 22-25 years old there are in the Dorset County Council area.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229786","229786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083644","2019-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the conclusions of the Prospect report The State of Natural England 2018-2019.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229787","229787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083645","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many care leavers aged 22-25 years old there are in the Poole Council area.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229788","229788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083646","2019-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the reduction of Natural England’s budget on biodiversity and habitat conservation.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229789","229789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083647","2019-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what increased duties and responsibilities Natural England will take on after the UK leaves the European Union.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229790","229790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083648","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made on establishing the new National Stability Forum for Children’s Social Care; how the members of that Forum were selected; and what the terms of reference are for that Forum.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229791","229791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083649","2019-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many licences Natural England has issued for activities which may disturb or kill European protected species in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229792","229792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083650","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how the National Stability Forum for Children’s Social Care is working to engage stakeholders across the sector; how that Forum has promoted effective practice and delivery; and whether that Forum has presented any recommendations for taking a national policy approach to improving looked-after children’s outcomes.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229793","229793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083651","2019-03-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress Natural England has made on the National Trail; and what the completion date is for that project.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229794","229794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083652","2019-03-11","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2019-03-07","To ask The  Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, if the Committee will undertake a survey of hon. Members on the (a) cost and (b) resources allocated by hon. Members to responding to e-mails from (i) 38 Degrees and (ii) other campaigning organisations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229668","229668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083653","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect on patient care of reforms to dermatology services at Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS Foundation Trust; and what plans his Department has to improve the effectiveness and availability of dermatology services throughout the UK.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229669","229669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083654","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients with (a) psoriasis, (b) atopic dermatitis and (c) hidradenitis suppurativa were seen by a dermatologist in 2018 in (i) Northern Lincolnshire and Goole NHS Foundation Trust and (ii) nationally.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229670","229670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083655","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timeframe is for Getting It Right First Time units to visit (a) Northern Lincolnshire and (b) Goole NHS Trust in relation to (i) gastroenterology and (ii) dermatology.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229671","229671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083656","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the savings accrued to the public purse by North Lincolnshire Care Commissioning Group as a result of the implementation of Yorkshire and Humber AHSN’s improved faecal calprotectin pathway for diagnosis of Inflammatory Bowel Disease; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229672","229672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083657","2019-03-12","Department for Transport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many male direct entrants at Grade 7 level in his Department started on a higher salary level than the Grade 7 minimum in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017 and (d) 2018.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229673","229673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083658","2019-03-12","Department for Transport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many male direct entrants at Grade 7 level in his Department started on a higher salary level than the Grade 7 minimum in 2019.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229674","229674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083659","2019-03-12","Department for Transport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many men promoted from senior executive officer level to grade seven in his Department started on a higher salary than the grade seven minimum from 1 January 2015 to date.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229675","229675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083660","2019-03-12","Cabinet Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people died as a result of issues related to homelessness in Bethnal Green and Bow in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229795","229795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083661","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether offences of shop theft of goods worth £200 or less are classified summary-only crimes since the introduction of the Anti-Social Behaviour, Crime and Policing Act 2014.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229676","229676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083662","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recorded incidences there have been of (a) violence with injury crimes and (b) robberies from business properties in each year since 2012 by police force area.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229677","229677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083663","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recorded incidences there were of robberies from business properties where the theft was valued at under £200 in each year since 2012.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229678","229678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083664","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recorded incidences there were of robberies from business properties where the value of theft was valued at over £200 in each year since 2012.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229679","229679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083665","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recorded incidences of online fraud there were where the value of theft was under £200 in each year since 2012.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229680","229680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083666","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recorded incidences of online fraud there were where the value of theft was greater than £200 in each year since 2012.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229681","229681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083667","2019-03-12","Cabinet Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2019 to Question 228168 on Brexit, when his Department will publish the full recent costs of physical advertising in relation to the UK's withdrawal from the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229796","229796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083668","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Iraqi counterpart on the judicial process for the trial of non-combative civilians living in Daesh-controlled areas in that country, and the sentences handed down to those people.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229682","229682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083669","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his US counterpart on the absence of a meeting between President Trump and representatives of the Iraqi government during the US President's recent visit to that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229683","229683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083670","2019-03-11","Department for International Development","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has allocated to  support internally displaced persons in (a) Rubkan camp and (b) Northern Syria.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229602","229602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083671","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on Iraq’s (a) economy and (b) energy supply of that country's compliance with US sanctions against Iran.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229684","229684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083672","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what protection UK and Allied forces can provide to internally displaced persons in (a) Rubkan camp and (b) northern Syria.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229603","229603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083673","2019-03-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the UK will (a) work with and (b) provide funding to Eurostat after the implementation period or in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229797","229797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083674","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2019 to Question 210057, for each available year, what the (a) mean and (b) median waiting time is for complaints (i) which are not resolved within eight weeks of being accepted, (ii) which are not settled within 15 weeks of the investigation commencing and (iii) where an ICE report is not issued within 20 weeks of the investigation commencing.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229798","229798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083675","2019-03-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2019 to Question 217031 on Independent Case Examiner, what the (a) mean and (b) median waiting time is for complainants who are not informed within four weeks of whether their complaint has been accepted for investigation in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229799","229799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083676","2019-03-11","Cabinet Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government will take to ensure that UK statistics remain cross-comparable with Eurostat in the event (a) of the UK leaving the EU without a deal and (b) that the UK otherwise ceases collaboration with Eurostat.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229800","229800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083677","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post offices are temporarily closed in (a) Scotland, (b) England, (c) Wales, and (d) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229801","229801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083678","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) main, (b) local, (c) community, and (d) outreach post offices are temporarily closed in (i) Scotland, (ii) England, (iii) Wales, and (iv) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229802","229802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083679","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many sub-postmasters have resigned since the start of the Post Office Ltd's network transformation programme.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229803","229803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083680","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to de-escalate tensions between the Kurdistan Regional Government and the Iraqi authorities to reduce the risk of any further outbreak of violence in that region.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229685","229685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083681","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on the clearance of explosive devices from roads and towns in previously Daesh-held areas of Iraq; and how many civilians have so far been able to return to their homes as a result of that work.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229686","229686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083682","2019-03-11","Department for International Development","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how the Government's programmes to increase humanitarian relief and disease prevention in Yemen will be delivered in Houthi-controlled areas.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229687","229687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083683","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the £4.5 million of arms exports to Saudi Arabia authorised between July and September last year were intended for use in the war in Yemen.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229688","229688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083684","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Saudi Arabian and Emirati counterparts on their reported recruitment and deployment of children from Sudan to take part in ground combat operations in the conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229689","229689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083685","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children from Sudan that have been recruited by Saudi Arabian and Emirati forces and deployed in combat operations in the conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229690","229690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083686","2019-03-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients have been prescribed cannabis-based products for medicinal use; and how many were (a) private prescriptions and (b) prescriptions funded by NHS or NHS Scottish.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229804","229804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083687","2019-03-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many medical practitioners are registered to prescribe cannabis-based products for medicinal use; how many of those practitioners (a) operate private practices and (b) are NHS or NHS Scotland employees; and if he will list the (i) Trusts and (ii) Health boards at which each of those NHS and NHS Scotland employee works.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229805","229805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083688","2019-03-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of medical practitioners that have had applications to be on the Specialist Register of the General Medical Council (a) approved, (b) rejected and (c) where a decision pending in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229806","229806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083689","2019-03-12","Treasury","2019-03-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2019 to Question 226209, whether HMRC will provide assistance to people affected by disguised remuneration debt who experienced loss of residence prior to HMRC confirming their policy not to force the sale of a main residence in January 2019.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229807","229807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083690","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 12.3 of the Explanatory Memorandum to The Electricity and Gas (Market Integrity and Transparency) (Amendment) (EU Exit) Regulations 2019 instrument, from what budget the funding will be drawn to pay the estimated £1.9m capital costs for a domestic REMIT reporting system.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229808","229808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083691","2019-03-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 12.3 of the Explanatory Memorandum to The Electricity and Gas (Market Integrity and Transparency) (Amendment) (EU Exit) Regulations 2019 instrument, what payment mechanism will be used for Ofgem to recover the estimated operational costs of £500k per annum to operate a new domestic REMIT system.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229809","229809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083692","2019-03-11","Department for International Development","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has held discussions with Palestinian officials on recent reports that the Palestinian Authority will reduce the salaries of its public sector workers but continue paying salaries for the families of martyrs, wounded or prisoners.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229691","229691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083693","2019-03-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference paragraph 12.3 of the Explanatory Memorandum to The Electricity and Gas (Market Integrity and Transparency) (Amendment) (EU Exit) Regulations 2019 instrument, what the anticipated timescales are for establishing the registration and reporting requirements set out in that instrument.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229810","229810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083694","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the telecommunications equipment reportedly used by Saudi Arabian and Emirati forces to direct the operations of Sudanese child soldiers deployed in combat operations in the conflict in Yemen was (a) supplied by UK companies and (b) authorised for export by the UK government.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229692","229692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083695","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made at the United Nations on the potential merits of the creation of a UN Special Rapporteur with responsibility for monitoring the protection of journalists and press freedom.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229693","229693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083696","2019-03-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2019 to Question 227413 on Tomography: Inhealthcare, what the timescale was for the procurement process for PET-CT scanning services in 2017-18.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229811","229811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083697","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in Myanmar on the continued incarceration of Reuters journalists Wa Lone and Kyaw Soe Oo; and what response he has received as a result of those representations.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229694","229694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083698","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Government plans to follow the actions of US State Department and refuse visa applications to five individuals accused of involvement in significant corruption of the election process in the Democratic Republic of Congo; and what other steps he plans to take in respect of those individuals.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229695","229695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083699","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many registered intermediaries there (a) are and (b) are estimated to be in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229642","229642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083700","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of requiring registered intermediaries to have an enhanced DBS check given their access to vulnerable witnesses.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229643","229643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083701","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to dispel rape myths and stereotypes from juries in line with the commitment in the Sexual Violence against Children and Vulnerable People National Group Progress Report and Action Plan 2015.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229644","229644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083702","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken (a) to monitor and (b) improve compliance with the Under 10s Protocol since it was reissued.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229645","229645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083703","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many barristers have received the advocacy and the vulnerable training.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229646","229646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083704","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young witnesses have provided evidence from a non-court live link site in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229647","229647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083705","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to help ensure that visually impaired young people can access learning materials adapted to their particular reading need.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229616","229616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083706","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of how many non-court sites where vulnerable witnesses may provide evidence (a) are operational and (b) will be operational in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229648","229648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083707","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he plans to have with Cabinet colleagues on ensuring that the upcoming spending review provides funding is adequately weighted towards special needs provision.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229617","229617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083708","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the pilot for non-court remote link sites for Section 28 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999 is planned to commence.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229649","229649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083709","2019-03-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2019 to Question 227413 on Tomography: Inhealthcare, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the procurement process for PET-CT scanning services in England.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229812","229812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083710","2019-03-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings (a) the chair of the Charity Commission and (b) other staff of the Charity Commission held with the Garden Bridge Trust after its registration as a charity.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229813","229813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083711","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of looked after children in children’s homes inside and outside the borough who were reported missing by a) duration of missing incident and (b) age of child at the start of missing incident and (c) went missing more than once during the year for each year since 2015.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229650","229650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083712","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children placed in children’s homes (a) inside the local authority responsible and (b) outside the local authority responsible were reported missing in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229651","229651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083713","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of assessment and management of chronic pain by (a) general practitioners, (b) nurses and (c) pharmacists.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229696","229696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083714","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that general practitioners, nurses and pharmacists are competent in the routine assessment and management of chronic pain.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229697","229697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083715","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To asks the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the implementation of all of the pilots for first contact physiotherapy practitioners; and when the outcomes of those pilots will be reported.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229698","229698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083716","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the increase in the number of physiotherapists that will be working in primary care networks over the next three years; and what steps his Department is taking to achieve that increase.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229699","229699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083717","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people judged to be entitled to the higher rate of disabled living allowance for life have been granted the standard rate when assessed for migration to personal independence payment.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229618","229618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083718","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many TB tests on pigs have returned a negative result after a primary inconclusive test result in England in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229700","229700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083719","2019-03-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average time taken is from the date of a first sample to a final test result in TB tests on pigs in England for each year since 2013.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229701","229701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083720","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons registered nurses employed by nursing and care homes are not able to administer medication by injection or change dressings for patients who are self-funding where continuing healthcare funding is not in place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229702","229702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083721","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidelines he has issued to clinical commissioning groups to ensure that they accept and process without delay applications received from clinicians for fast-track continuing healthcare funding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229703","229703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083722","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-resident parents are in maintenance arrears through the Child Maintenance Service; and what amount of money is outstanding in such arrears in Lanark and Hamilton East constituency.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229814","229814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083723","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many fast-track applications for continuing healthcare funding have been rejected by each clinical commissioning group in the last twelve months for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229704","229704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083724","2019-03-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2019 to Question 227413 on Tomography: Inhealthcare, for what reasons the procurement process for PET-CT scanning was not subject to public consultation.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229815","229815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083725","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to publish a formal response to the Access to Cash review, published on 6 March 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229816","229816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083726","2019-03-12","Department for Education","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of companies who have transferred the apprenticeship levy in London.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229817","229817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083727","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to reduce length of time it takes for a claimant to receive their first universal credit payment after the claimant’s first assessment period has ended.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229705","229705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083728","2019-03-12","Women and Equalities","2019-03-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the implications for Government policies of the conclusions of the report from the Women's Budget Group, Triple Whammy: The impact of local government cuts on women, published on 7 March 2019 which found that changes to local authority funding disproportionately affects women.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229706","229706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083729","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps his Department has taken to help protect women human rights defenders around the world from (a) death threats, (b) attacks, (c) defamation campaigns, (d) judicial harassment and (e)  criminalisation of their work.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229707","229707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083730","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the report on the situation if women human rights defenders, published by the UN Special Rapporteur on the situation of Human Rights Defenders in January 2019, if his Department will take further steps to (a) protect women human rights defenders who are at risk and (b) help ensure a safe and enabling working environment for women human rights defenders.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229708","229708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083731","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to develop a cross-governmental approach to support and help protect women human rights defenders.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229709","229709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083732","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that female journalists are consulted on the UK's media freedom campaign; and what steps his Department is taking to promote that campaign at the London conference on media freedom in July 2019.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229710","229710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083733","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to (a) develop protection mechanisms and (b) provide emergency protection funds for female journalists at risk.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229711","229711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083734","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in Saudi Arabia on the case of Abbas al-Hassan and his co-defendants and the Government's opposition to their execution since the beginning of 2019.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229712","229712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083735","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received any assurances from the Government of Saudi Arabia that Abbas al-Hassan and his co-defendants will not be executed.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229713","229713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083736","2019-03-12","Department for Transport","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the LNER Azuma trains will be ready to travel north of York.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229714","229714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083737","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken in days has been from arrest to sentence for persistant young offenders in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229715","229715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083738","2019-03-12","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the RAF targeteers working in the Saudi Combined Air Operations Centre are on loan or on secondment to the Saudi Arabian armed forces.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229818","229818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083739","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timescale is for a second round of the Diabetes Transformation Fund; and how areas in need will be able to bid for that funding as part of the NHS Long-Term plan.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229819","229819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083740","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to ensure the continued availability of the Beta Blocker Metoprolol for people who are prescribed this medicine on the NHS.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229619","229619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083741","2019-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to NATO on the Turkish Government's procurement of the Russian S-400 Missile Defence System.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229594","229594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083742","2019-03-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Turkish Government on their purchase of the Russian S-400 Missile Defence System.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229595","229595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083743","2019-03-12","Treasury","2019-03-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2019 to Question 226145, how much the (a) High Net Worth Unit and (b) Affluent teams collected separately in taxation in each year from 2009-10 until their merger.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229820","229820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083744","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of flood prevention schemes in small conurbations in Oxfordshire.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229821","229821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083745","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Environment Agency is receiving adequate funding to prevent flooding in smaller conurbations in Oxfordshire.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229822","229822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1083746","2019-03-11","Department for International Trade","2019-03-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to protect the (a) NHS and (b) other public services in the negotiation of trade agreements after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229823","229823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1081885","2019-03-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to stimulate increased lending from high street banks to small and medium-sized house builders in England.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228146","228146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082375","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what diplomatic steps he has taken to promote the correct usage and proper functioning of Interpol red notices among his foreign counterparts.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 228770","228770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082454","2019-03-06","Northern Ireland Office","2019-03-06","What steps she is taking to seek the restoration of power-sharing devolved government in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909559","909559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082455","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve quality and choice in higher education.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909698","909698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082527","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the NHS has for the future of Royston Hospital; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229074","229074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082528","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many of the traders identified by HMRC as being intra-EU only traders have had an EORI number issued; and how many of those EORI numbers been issued since the start of the Government's day one no deal business readiness campaign.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229087","229087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082529","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the oral contribution of the Housing Minister on 21 February 2019, Official Report, col 648WH, if he will place in the Library a copy of the letter from the Housing Minister to the hon. Member for Oldham West and Royton on housing targets.","Biography information for Tony Lloyd","Tony Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229103","229103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082530","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the operating cost per unit of Nimrod aircraft in each financial year until their withdrawal from service in 2011.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229135","229135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082531","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the local environment of sheep farming.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229199","229199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082532","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that large technology companies are complying with regulations on personal data.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229088","229088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082533","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Example Case Study in Chapter 8 of his Department’s White Paper, the UK’s future skills-based immigration system, Cm 9722, what estimate his Department has made of the number of UK citizens living elsewhere in the European Union with a partner from the European Economic Area who would be required to meet the Minimum Income Requirement should they decide to continue their family life in the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229136","229136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082534","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in the most recent month for which data is available, in what proportion of universal credit assessments for working claimants was income data taken from (a) RTI data provided by HMRC and (b) claimants' payslips.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229075","229075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082535","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what his plans are for a review of whether it should be a criminal offence to trespass in the course of establishing an encampment; what the timetable is for such a review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229076","229076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082536","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his letter to Conservative Members of Parliament dated 7 February 2019, what plans he has to strengthen policy on intentional unauthorised development; what the timetable is for the delivery of those plans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229077","229077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082537","2019-03-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 28 February 2019 to Question 225613, on Parental Leave: Childbirth, whether his Department plans to say more about next steps by 30 April 2019.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229200","229200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082538","2019-03-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will undertake an economic impact assessment on the potential merits of extending the national living wage to employees under the age of 25.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229201","229201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082539","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support his Department is providing to Credit Unions to improve their governance policies.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229202","229202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082540","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, which of his Ministers have met with officials from Santander bank in the last two years; and on what dates those meetings took place.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229203","229203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082541","2019-03-11","Department for International Trade","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will commit to excluding the NHS and other public services from future trade deals.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229137","229137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082542","2019-03-11","Department for International Trade","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many applications for (a) Standard Individual Export Licences, (b) Open Individual Export Licences and (c) Open Individual Trade Control Export Licences for exports to Saudi Arabia were referred to Ministers by the Export Control Joint Unit and its predecessor the Export Control Organisation in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229204","229204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082543","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he will take in the forthcoming workforce implementation plan to ensure that there are sufficient staff in the NHS to diagnose and treat cancer..","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229138","229138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082544","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much capital funding his Department will spend on (a) creating new school places and (b) investing in existing school buildings in each of the next five fiscal years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229139","229139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082545","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department will spend on providing free childcare to (a) two-year-olds and (b) three and four-year-olds in each of the next five fiscal years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229140","229140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082546","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when travellers from Australia, Canada, Japan, New Zealand and the United States will be able to use eGates at UK ports.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229205","229205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082547","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department will spend on (a) the childcare element of the working tax credit and (b) the childcare element of Universal Credit in each of the next five fiscal years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229141","229141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082548","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, at which ports will travellers from Australia, Canada, Japan, New Zealand and the United States be able to use eGates.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229206","229206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082549","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Intelligence and Security Committee’s report on Detainee Mistreatment and Rendition, published in June 2018, what role British personnel played in interrogations at Abu Ghraib while the prison was under the control of the United States Administration.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229207","229207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082550","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether British personnel stationed at Abu Ghraib (a) made an assessment of and (b) produced a report on the conditions in which prisoners at that facility (i) lived and (ii) were treated; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229208","229208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082551","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2019 to Question 223830, if he will make an estimate of the cost of finding out what proportion of universal credit claimants have not been in receipt of any benefits in the 180 days following a sanction decision.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229104","229104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082552","2019-03-11","Department for International Development","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the £100 million budget for landmine clearance is being spent on clearing landmines in Syria; and whether that budget also provides for the clearance of other devices such as improvised explosive devices.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229209","229209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082553","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that every young person with vision impairment has access to the same learning materials as their sighted peers.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229142","229142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082554","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February to Question 216193 on Special Educational Needs: Visual Impairment, what powers have been awarded to the Office of Qualifications and Examinations Regulation to follow up with awarding organisations when mistakes in adapted past papers and national tests for young people with a visual impairment are reported.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229143","229143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082555","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 4 March 2019 to Question 225566 on Public Works Loan Board, what the purpose was of each loan since 2010; and if his Department will include that information as part of the monthly loans report.","Biography information for Chris Philp","Chris Philp","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229210","229210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082556","2019-03-11","Cabinet Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate the Government has made of the cost to the public purse of advertising the EU Withdrawal Agreement on social media (a) up to the present day and (b) until 29 March 2019.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229211","229211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082557","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of eligible adults who have received (a) abdominal aortic aneurysm, (b) bowel, (c) breast and (d) cervical screening in (i) Lambeth CCG (ii) Southwark CCG and (iii) England in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229212","229212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082558","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the National Audit Office report entitled Investigation into the management of Health Screening, published 1 February 2019, what steps his Department is taking to ensure NHS screening laboratories are sufficiently staffed.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229213","229213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082559","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will allocate funding for Transport for Greater Manchester to implement its Local Cycling and Walking Infrastructure Plan.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229214","229214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082560","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to ensure more students are allocated places at their preferred schools.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229215","229215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082561","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to (a) increase school funding and (b) support secondary schools to reduce debts.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229216","229216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082562","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent progress his Department has made in its review of student finance; and when he plans to report on that review to the House.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229217","229217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082563","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason gender is a mandatory field on funding applications to the Education and Skills Funding Agency; and whether he plans to make an assessment of the adequacy of that agency's funding application form.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229144","229144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082564","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the results of the consultation on mandating calorie labelling in the out-of-home sector will be published.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229218","229218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082565","2019-03-11","Women and Equalities","2019-03-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the Government portal for gender pay gap reporting contains accurate and up to date information.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229105","229105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082566","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the budget was of each of his Department's (a) non-ministerial departments, (b) executive agencies, (c) executive non-departmental public bodies, (d) advisory non-departmental public bodies and (e) other agencies in the most recent financial year for which records are available.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229145","229145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082567","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total amount was that HMRC have paid out as a result of lost tribunal cases in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229219","229219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082568","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the definition of extremism used by OFCOM is aligned with the definition used by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229146","229146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082569","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2019 to Question 227110 on Buildings: Insulation, when the BS 8414 test will take place; and whether combustible insulation behind that cladding will be tested.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229147","229147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082570","2019-03-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) nusinersen/Spinraza and (b) other life-saving drugs are made available for people with spinal muscular atrophy.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229106","229106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082571","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has written to people who will be affected by the changes to pension credit entitlement which come into force on 15 May 2019 to inform them that they will no longer be entitled to claim pension credit if their partner is not of state pension age.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229220","229220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082572","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she has taken to publicise the changes to pension credit entitlement which come into force on 15 May 2019 to (a) couples who will no longer receive that entitlement because one partner is not of state pension age and (b) other people.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229221","229221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082573","2019-03-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the revised completion date of the courts reform programme on (a) the cost of the programme and (b) the predicted date when the cumulative benefits of the programme are expected to be greater than the cumulative costs.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229148","229148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082574","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department is using for projected rates of dementia in the technical review of local authorities’ needs and resources.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229089","229089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082575","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding allocated to councils for respite care has been accessed to date; and what steps his Department is taking to encourage carers to make use of that support.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229090","229090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082576","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government plans to introduce a requirement for social care workers in England to be registered.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229091","229091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082577","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department is planning on introducing a requirement for social care workers to register with Care Quality Commission.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229092","229092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082578","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2019 to Question 217589 on Buildings: Insulation, for what reasons his Department has decided to use a bespoke test methodology.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229149","229149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082579","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2019 to Question 227111 on Buildings: Insulation, when his Department plans to announce the results of the call for evidence to form the basis for a technical review of Approved Document B (Fire Safety).","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229150","229150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082580","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the speech by the Children and Families Minister announcing new early years funding, of 28 February 2019, whether additional funding for maintained nurseries will be funded from new revenue from HM Treasury.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229151","229151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082581","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2018 to Question 202313 on the UK Shared Prosperity Fund, what the timetable is for the public consultation on the design of the UK Shared Prosperity Fund; and when he plans to publish that consultation document.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229152","229152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082582","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to respond to the letter of 5 February 2019 from the hon. Member for Croydon North on fire safety and cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229153","229153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082583","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to encourage emergency services to promote the Herbert Protocol for people living with dementia in their local areas.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229093","229093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082584","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how the £100 million investment in the Government's Rough Sleeping Strategy will be spent; over what timescale that money will be spend; and how much of that funding will be allocated to local authorities.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229222","229222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082585","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the Rough Sleeping and Homelessness Reduction Ministerial Taskforce last met; and what plans there are for future meetings.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229223","229223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082586","2019-03-11","Department for International Development","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support humanitarian relief in Afghanistan in response to the recent floods.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229079","229079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082587","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effect of the Local Housing Allowance freeze on levels of rough sleeping.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229224","229224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082589","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on which projects his Department will spend funding from (a) capital departmental expenditure limits and (b) capital annually managed expenditure in each fiscal year from 2018-19 to 2020-21.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229154","229154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082590","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 20 February 2019 to Question 222001, when Public Health England plans to undertake an independent academic review of heated tobacco products.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229155","229155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082591","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of 16 to 18 year olds in full-time education studying foreign language courses in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229081","229081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082592","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department maintains an ongoing dialogue with the Vice-President of Zimbabwe; and what representations his Department has made to the Vice-President of Zimbabwe on the January 2019 violence in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229107","229107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082593","2019-03-11","Department for International Development","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has made an assessment of the difficulties that women in Zimbabwe face in obtaining sanitary products in that country; and whether he is taking steps to tackle that humanitarian need.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229108","229108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082595","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, where the funding will come from for the proposed expansion of the UK’s diplomatic network; over what period that expansion will take place; and whether that funding will be taken from elsewhere in his departmental budget.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229109","229109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082596","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to expand the membership of the Equal Rights Coalition among (a) African, (b) Asian and (c) other countries during the Government’s term as co-chair of that coalition in 2019-20.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229110","229110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082597","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Russian counterpart on the continued detention of Oyub Titiev.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229111","229111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082598","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will guarantee that President Bolsonaro of Brazil will not be accorded the honour of a state visit to the UK during his term in office because of his record of hate speech against members of the LGBT community.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229112","229112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082599","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he will formally invite Cuba to join the Equal Rights Coalition during the Government’s term as co-chair of the coalition, in light of the recent progress the Cuban Government has made on LGBT rights.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229113","229113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082600","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his international counterparts for the rights of indigenous peoples to be embedded into the proposed International Treaty on Human Rights and Transnational Corporations.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229114","229114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082601","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the continued mass detention and mistreatment of Uyghur Muslims in western China.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229115","229115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082602","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Bahraini counterpart on the recent upholding of the convictions against relatives of the wife of Mr Sayed Alwadaei, the Director of Advocacy of the London-based Bahrain Institute for Rights and Democracy.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229116","229116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082603","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Bahraini counterpart on the case of the human rights activist Nabeel Rajab.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229117","229117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082604","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to appoint two new non-executive members to the board of HS2 Ltd; what steps he has taken to improve gender balance on that board; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229156","229156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082605","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Saudi Arabian counterpart on the continued detention and threatened execution of women’s rights activist, Israa al-Ghomgham.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229118","229118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082606","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Saudi Arabian counterpart on the continued detention and threatened execution of Abbas al-Hassan and eleven other individuals threatened with execution for exercising their rights to freedom of religion.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229119","229119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082607","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate his Department has made of gender-based pay inequality in the education sector.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229082","229082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082608","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Emirati counterpart on the recent upholding of the conviction and ten-year sentence against human rights activist Ahmed Mansoor.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229120","229120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082609","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many human rights activists his Department estimates are currently in detention in Egypt; and what representations he has made to his Egyptian counterpart on this issue.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229121","229121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082610","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Bangladeshi counterparts since the recent elections in that country to ensure that the Bangladeshi Government remains committed to repatriations of Rohingya refugees to Myanmar on a voluntary basis.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229122","229122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082611","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the safety of (a) British embassy staff and (b) other British nationals resident in Venezuela.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229157","229157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082612","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterparts on the United Nations Security Council on the formal designation of Masood Azhar as a global terrorist.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229158","229158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082613","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of the farming industry on the food standards element of a future trade deal with the US.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229083","229083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082614","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the conclusions of Independent Age into the performance of care homes across England that a third of local authorities experienced care home ratings falling.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229123","229123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082615","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to reverse the decision to remove nurse bursaries.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229225","229225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082616","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of falling usage of cash in retail transactions on the economic sustainability of high streets.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229084","229084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082617","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has issued to health professionals that prescribe Selective Serotonin Reuptake Inhibitors on advice to patients on the potential for (a) erectile dysfunction and (b) other side effects after patients have stopped taking that medication.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229085","229085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082618","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations he has made to his counterpart in the US Administration on the unlawful exhumation and removal of historical British military sites in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229159","229159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082619","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many notices were issued by the Fundraising Regulator against charities in the last year.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229160","229160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082620","2019-03-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts on the future of EU citizens in Iraq and Syria who had previously lived in territory controlled by Daesh.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229094","229094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082621","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of revenue to the Exchequer as a result of measures to tackle tax evasion and avoidance introduced in 2010.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229161","229161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082622","2019-03-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the funding allocated to the Charity Commission.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229162","229162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082623","2019-03-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 04 March 2019 to Question 226128 on Employment and Support Allowance: Arrears, whether it remains her Department policy that 50 per cent of Presenting Officers attend tribunals.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229226","229226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082624","2019-03-11","Treasury","2019-03-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to help prevent UK businesses from avoiding paying tax through profit fragmentation.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229163","229163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082625","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on strategies to protect transport hubs throughout the UK against terrorist activity.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229095","229095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082626","2019-03-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps his Department has taken to support local authorities' preparations for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229164","229164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082627","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of physiotherapists that will be working in primary care in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229096","229096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082628","2019-03-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people living with chronic pain receive support from physiotherapists to help them stay in employment.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229097","229097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082629","2019-03-11","Attorney General","2019-03-06","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of prosecutions for child sexual abuse involved the CPS accepting a defendant's guilty plea to lesser charges in 2017.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229165","229165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082630","2019-03-11","Attorney General","2019-03-06","To ask the Attorney General, in how many cases prosecuted under sections (a) 5 to 9, (b) 16 and (c) 25 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 the CPS accepted a defendant's guilty plea to lesser charges in 2017.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229166","229166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082631","2019-03-11","Department for International Development","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress her Department has made on implementing its Youth Agenda, published in April 2016.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229167","229167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082632","2019-03-11","Department for International Development","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is planning to take to implement her Department's Youth Agenda, published in April 2016.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229168","229168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082633","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether EU citizens will be able to enter the UK with an EEA National identity card under current terms after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229227","229227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082634","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of schools in England that have reduced their school day opening hours in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229228","229228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082635","2019-03-11","Department for Education","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of schools that have asked parents to donate towards activities that are part of the national curriculum in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229229","229229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082636","2019-03-11","Home Office","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the number of (a) British children and (b) children who are eligible for British citizenship currently with rebel groups in Syria.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229230","229230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082637","2019-03-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department has spent on external consultants for work relating to the UK leaving the EU in each year since 2016.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229231","229231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082638","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what training courses the Maritime and Coastguard Agency has provided to Royal Navy personnel on HMS Collingwood since 2008.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229169","229169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082639","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is his policy to facilitate the training of Royal Navy personnel for employment in the merchant navy.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229170","229170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082640","2019-03-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Navy personnel have obtained qualifications to work in the UK merchant navy in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229171","229171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1082641","2019-03-11","Department for Transport","2019-03-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding the Maritime and Coastguard Agency has allocated to merchant navy seafarer training courses for Royal Navy personnel on HMS Collingwood (a) in each year since 2010-11 and (b) to date in 2018-19.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229172","229172"
