"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943863","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether steps are being taken to improve the uptake of structured diabetes education in the (a) NHS Kernow CCG area and (b) throughout England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165622","165622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943864","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what models for the reimbursement of providers of digital health solutions he is assessing in order to increase the availability of such solutions.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165623","165623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943865","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to introduce in the forthcoming alcohol strategy a new national minimum standard of support for families affected by alcohol as called for by the Alcohol and Families Alliance.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165532","165532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943866","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether plans are in place to (a) enhance and (b) expand the NHS Apps Library; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165624","165624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943867","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to include in the forthcoming alcohol strategy provisions as called for by the Alcohol and Families Alliance whereby carers of people with an alcohol problem are adequately informed about carers’ rights and benefits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165533","165533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943868","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether guidance is available to GPs to enable them effectively to direct patients to the NHS Apps Library; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165625","165625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943869","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to increase the use of digital coaching and support for people to manage long term conditions such as diabetes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165626","165626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943870","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recourse to complaint freeholders have who pay into a common management scheme that is badly managed.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165534","165534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943871","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he has made an assessment of the potential merits of the conclusions the report, Skin gambling: teenage Britain’s secret habit, published by Parent Zone in June 2018 of the assessment he has made of the findings of the June 2018; and what discussions he has had with the Gambling Commission on underage skin gambling.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165590","165590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943872","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he is taking steps to ensure a consistent standard of video surveillance systems and readers so that all CCTV recordings are accessible (a) to the police and security services and (b) during criminal trials; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165556","165556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943873","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with (a) Vertex and (b) NHS England on access to Orkambi on the NHS.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165702","165702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943874","2018-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many small and medium-sized businesses in Nottinghamshire have received support under each business support scheme operated by his Department since 2015.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165703","165703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943875","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consultations his Department has held with teachers on the forthcoming T Levels qualifications.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165704","165704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943876","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many unstaffed open libraries that use technology to enable visitors to enter there are in each English region.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165499","165499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943877","2018-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the number of women who take between 39 and 52 weeks maternity leave in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165500","165500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943878","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to introduce a video link between locations in Wakefield and the magistrates' court in Leeds.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165519","165519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943879","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many successful judicial review cases relating to section 322(5) of the Immigration Rules there were in 2017; and how many such cases have yet to be decided.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165706","165706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943880","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of compensation paid to EU nationals (a) detained in and (b) deported from the UK in each month between May 2016 and May 2017.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165707","165707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943881","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 10 May 2018 to Question 136120 on UK Visas and Immigration: Management, how many individuals are assigned to the dedicated taskforce; how many of the 50 senior caseworkers will be in new positions; and what the timeframe is for the conclusion of his Department's review.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165708","165708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943882","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average cost was of processing (a) a child's citizenship application, (b) an adult's citizenship application; and how many applications for children's citizenship his Department received in 2017.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165709","165709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943883","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to publish his Department's consultation on landing cards.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165710","165710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943884","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to conduct a public consultation on his Department's hostile environment policies.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165711","165711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943885","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of progress in preparations for avoiding the introduction of Operation Stack on the M20; if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165436","165436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943886","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the answer of 17 July 2018 to Question 161987 on Veterinary Medicine, how many veterinary surgeons from (a) non-UK EU and (b) non-EU member states employed by organisations contracted to deliver veterinary services in abattoirs on behalf of the by Food Standards Agency, have left that employment since 23 June 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165449","165449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943887","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he is providing guidance to head teachers and school leaders on salary levels for the forthcoming academic year in the absence of the publication of the 2018 School Teachers' Review Body report; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165686","165686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943888","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what (a) financial and (b) other support his Department plans to provide for (i) home adjustments and (ii) maintenance in relation to the homes of old people.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165450","165450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943889","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish his response to the recommendations in the 2018 report of the School Teachers' Review Body before the summer recess.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165696","165696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943890","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral contribution of the then Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs of 20 February 2018, Official Report, column 5, whether it is his Department's policy to explore the possibility of a new fixed link between Great Britain and France.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165618","165618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943891","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 6 March 2018 and 8 March 2018 to Questions 130582 and 130801 on France: Foreign relations, what progress has been made in establishing the committee of wise people to explore future UK-French collaboration.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165619","165619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943892","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many allegations of (a) sexual assault and (b) rape were referred to the Royal Military Police by the (i) Army, (ii) Navy and (iii) RAF in each of the preceding three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165502","165502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943893","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many allegations of (a) sexual assault and (b) rape referred to the Service Prosecution Authority related to service personnel in the (i) Army, (ii) Navy and (iii) RAF in each of the preceding three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165503","165503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943894","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many convictions there were for (a) sexual assault and (b) rape by service personnel in the (i) Army, (ii) Navy and (iii) RAF in each of the preceding three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165504","165504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943895","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish his response to the recommendations in the 2018 report of the School Teachers' Review Body.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165477","165477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943896","2018-07-23","Department for International Trade","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made on the UK’s ability to agree free trade deals while maintaining a common rulebook for all goods with the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165478","165478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943897","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what provision her Department makes for people who when making a benefit application are unable to respond with bank documentation and other relevant paperwork within the requested 10 days.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165608","165608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943898","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made trends in the number of super bugs becoming resistant to antibiotics.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165573","165573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943899","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many National Citizen Service graduates were eligible for free school meals (a) in England and (b) by local authority in the 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165593","165593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943900","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure the mental well-being of young people waiting for their GCSE results.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165574","165574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943901","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to support young people who wish to take more vocational GCSEs.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165575","165575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943902","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to publish the draft Law of Property Bill announced in the 2016 Queen's Speech; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165514","165514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943903","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the Northern Rail compensation scheme.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165576","165576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943904","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to Question 161582 asked by the hon. Member for Dwyfor Meirionnydd on 6 July 2018, when he plans to provide a substantive response to that Question.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165669","165669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943905","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it is the Government's policy to support the drafting of a resolution at the UN Security Council to refer the situation in Northern Rakhine State, Myanmar, to the International Criminal Court so that allegations of atrocities can be impartially investigated.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165613","165613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943906","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that young people from poor backgrounds have access to (a) opera and (b) other such live performances.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165577","165577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943907","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on what date his Department plans to publish the social housing Green Paper.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165680","165680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943908","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on significant numbers of people being detained by the Chinese authorities in re-education camps in the Xinjiang Uyghur Autonomous Region; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165671","165671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943909","2018-07-23","Cabinet Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government has an agreed definition of joint spending in relation to campaign spending for elections and referendums.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165620","165620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943910","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of universal credit have had a deduction from the standard allowance (a) at the 40 per cent and (b) above the 40 per cent level.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165701","165701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943911","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2018 to Question 153838, how many children classified as in scope for the 16-18 maths progress measure were from (a) disadvantaged and (b) non-disadvantaged backgrounds in 2016-17 by each prior attainment grade.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165578","165578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943912","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2018 to Question 153840, how many children classified as in scope for the 16-18 maths progress measure from (a) disadvantaged and (b) non-disadvantaged backgrounds made positive progress in maths in 2016-17 by each prior attainment grade.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165579","165579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943913","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2018 to Question 153838, how many students in scope for the 16-18 maths progress measure from (a) disadvantaged and (b) non-disadvantaged backgrounds did not enter an approved maths qualification in 2016-17 by each prior attainment grade.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165580","165580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943914","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2018 to Question 153842, how many children classified as in scope for the 16-18 English progress measure were from (a) disadvantaged and (b) non-disadvantaged backgrounds in 2016-17 by each prior attainment grade.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165581","165581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943915","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2018 to Question 153843, how many students in scope for the 16-18 English progress measure from (a) disadvantaged and (b) non-disadvantaged backgrounds did not enter an approved English qualification in 2016-17 by each prior attainment grade.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165582","165582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943916","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2018 to Question 153844, how many children classified as in scope for the 16-18 English progress measure from (a) disadvantaged and (b) non-disadvantaged backgrounds made positive progress in English in 2016-17 by each prior attainment grade.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165583","165583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943917","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the financial sustainability of childcare providers in the (a) private, (b) voluntary and (c) independent early education sector.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165661","165661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943918","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2018 to Question 153841, how many children classified as in scope for the 16-18 maths progress measure from (a) disadvantaged and (b) non-disadvantaged backgrounds achieved a grade 4 in maths by the end of 16-18 study in 2016-17 by each prior attainment grade.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165584","165584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943919","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what types of goods will be excluded from the proposed Facilitated Customs Arrangement with the EU.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165517","165517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943920","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2018 to Question 153845, how many children classified as in scope for the 16-18 English progress measure from (a) disadvantaged and (b) non-disadvantaged backgrounds achieved a grade 4 in English by the end of 16-18 study in 2016-17 by each prior attainment grade.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165585","165585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943921","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of teachers teaching maths (a) are qualified maths teachers and (b) hold a relevant post A level qualification for each type of 16-19 provider.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165586","165586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943922","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of teachers teaching English (a) are specialist English teachers and (b) hold a relevant post A level qualification for each type of 16-19 provider.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165587","165587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943923","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children from (a) disadvantaged and (b) non-disadvantaged backgrounds were exempt from the 16-18 maths progress measure because they are recorded as having (i) special educational needs and (ii) overseas qualifications equivalent to a GCSE grade C.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165588","165588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943924","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of current levels of funding for the 30-hours free childcare policy.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165662","165662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943925","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children from (a) disadvantaged and (b) non-disadvantaged backgrounds were exempt from the 16-18 English progress measure because they are recorded as having (i) special educational needs and (ii) overseas qualifications equivalent to a GCSE grade C.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165589","165589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943926","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of a review of legislation on imitation firearms which do not fall under the definition of Section 57(1) of the Firearms Act 1968.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165644","165644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943927","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to help increase rates of (a) recruitment and (b) retention in the childcare profession.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165663","165663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943928","2018-07-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the White Paper, The Future Relationship Between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what remaining frictions there will be for (a) exporters and (b) importers.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165518","165518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943929","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Chinese Government on people being detained by the Chinese authorities in re-education camps.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165672","165672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943930","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for Leave to Remove were in each year since 2004; and how many of those applications were made by parents intending to return to a country in the EEA.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165657","165657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943931","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of children (a) removed from and (b) allowed to remain in the jurisdiction of England and Wales under Leave to Remove applications in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165658","165658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943932","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of CAFCASS reports that were requested for Leave to Remove applications in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165659","165659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943933","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of Hague Convention on Child Abduction cases in England and Wales in each year since 2004; how many children were ordered to remain in England and Wales as a result of those cases; and how many children were allowed to leave the country as a result of those cases.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165660","165660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943934","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to introduce legislative proposals to extend the maximum sentence for causing death by dangerous driving.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165603","165603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943935","2018-07-23","Department for International Development","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2018 to Question 141795, on Palestinians: Overseas Aid, which the auditing body was that was charged with carrying out the independent financial audit.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165443","165443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943936","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate he has made of the number of children who have an autism diagnosis who are home schooled.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165666","165666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943937","2018-07-23","Department for International Development","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department’s Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions her Department has had with the PA on the decision by official Palestinian Authority TV to honour Habbes Bayyoud, Muhammad Nawarah, and Jawad Abu Qara, who murdered two Israeli reserve soldiers in October 2000 in an episode of Giants of Endurance, a programme screened on official PA TV on 16 June 2018.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165444","165444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943938","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the (a) effectiveness of Applied Behaviour Analysis in relation to autistic students and (b) effect of that analysis on the mental wellbeing of those students.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165667","165667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943939","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her statement of 7 June 2018, Official Report, column 19WS, when those claimants who were in receipt of severe disability premium and have moved on to universal credit will begin receiving the ongoing payment; and how those claimants will be informed of their entitlement to that payment.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165508","165508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943940","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her statement of 7 June 2018, Official Report, column 19WS, how the additional payment will be calculated; and whether that payment will be made as a lump sum to claimants.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165509","165509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943941","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the draft Universal Credit (Transitional Provisions) (Managed Migration) Amendment Regulations 2018, how the value of the transitional payment was calculated.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165510","165510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943942","2018-07-23","Department for International Development","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 11 May 2018 to Question 141671, whether the Palestinian Authority has made decision on whether to provide payments to Palestinian prisoners in Israeli jails directly.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165445","165445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943943","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the draft Universal Credit (Transitional Provisions) (Managed Migration) Amendment Regulations 2018, for what reasons universal credit claimants with limited capability for work and work related activity will receive a transitional payment of £80 per month; and what assessment he has made of the value of this payment in comparison to changes in those claimants' income as a result of transitioning to universal credit.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165511","165511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943944","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost per year of paying the London Living Wage to (a) his Department's cleaners working under the OCS contract, (b) all cleaners employed directly or indirectly by his Department and (c) everyone employed by his Department.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165656","165656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943945","2018-07-23","Attorney General","2018-07-18","To ask the Attorney General, how many sentences imposed for causing death by dangerous driving his Department has considered under the unduly lenient sentence scheme in each of the last five years; on how many occasions in each of the last five years he has referred such sentences to the Court of Appeal; and how many of those sentences have been extended by the Court of Appeal as the original sentence imposed fell outside the range of sentences that could reasonably have been imposed in the circumstances of the case.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165604","165604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943946","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many buildings leased or owned by HMRC are currently not occupied; and if he will publish a list of those buildings with the (a) dates since when those buildings have not been occupied and (b) rental and other charges paid on those buildings during those periods in which they have not been occupied.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165438","165438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943947","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps HMRC have taken to work collaboratively with initiatives under the One Public Estate programme in West Sussex to accrue savings to the public purse.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165439","165439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943948","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children who are eligible for 30 hours free childcare in Hove constituency.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165664","165664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943949","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of changes in the level of costs to (a) car auctions and (b) other industries for debit card transaction charges as a result of the Interchange Fee Regulation.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165440","165440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943950","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authorities have provided business rate relief to private, voluntary and independent childcare providers.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165665","165665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943951","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many people used the Fundraising Preference Service in the last 12 months; and what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of that service.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165594","165594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943952","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many registered social workers with a background in (a) child protection and (b) children’s residential care are employed in the (i) Youth Custody Service and (ii) Youth Custody Service Placement Team.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165596","165596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943953","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list the names of advisers contracted to assist the development of secure schools and the (a) qualifications and (b) professional backgrounds of those advisers.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165597","165597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943954","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many registered social workers with a background in (a) child protection and (b) children’s residential care are employed in the Youth Justice Board.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165598","165598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943955","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list the Youth Justice Board publications concerned with safeguarding children in the secure estate commissioned and published in the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165599","165599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943956","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to prepare young people for future jobs in the creative industries in the light of the decrease in the number of students taking GCSEs in arts subjects since 2014.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165538","165538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943957","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to prepare young people for future jobs in the engineering sector in light of the decrease in the number of students taking GCSE Design and Technology since 2014.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165539","165539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943958","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education,  what steps he is taking to prepare young people for future jobs in the digital industries in light of the decrease in the number of students taking GCSEs in computing and ICT since 2017.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165540","165540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943959","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment has been made of the effect of (a) changes in mortgage interest tax relief for private landlords and (b) the end of the wear and tear tax allowance since the inception of those measures in April 2017.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165446","165446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943960","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions have taken place for offences under the Immigration Act 2014 since the inception of Right to Rent measures in February 2016.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165447","165447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943961","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which non-executive appointments have been made to his Department's public bodies from April 2018 to March 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165505","165505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943962","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timetable is for a forensic water investigation in prison service properties as set out in the Crown Commercial Service’s agreement.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165545","165545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943963","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the financial sustainability of childcare providers in the private, voluntary and independent early education sector.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165520","165520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943964","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that water companies do not charge clients for surface water drainage that does not go into the sewer network.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165546","165546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943965","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2018 to Questions 161189, 161190 and 161191 on employment: disability, how her Department is evaluating the success of the Disability Confident scheme if job outcomes attributable to the scheme are not recorded.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165609","165609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943966","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2018 to Question 161192 on disabled Students' Allowance, what statistics on the uptake of disabled students' allowance his Department records; and whether the uptake of that allowance has decreased since the introduction of the £200 contribution for computer equipment.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165610","165610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943967","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking in response to the Civil Aviation Authority's 2018 report that London Gatwick, London Stansted, Birmingham and Manchester airports are not sufficiently accessible to disabled passengers.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165611","165611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943968","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government is planning to create alternative grass-roots funding programmes for creative SMEs if the UK does not participate in EU funded programmes after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165612","165612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943969","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, on what date the Grenfell Tower Memorial Commission was established.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165506","165506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943970","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial support his Department provides to the Spring Consortium; and what the set up costs were of that Consortium.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165600","165600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943971","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what financial support Partners in Practice has provided to each local authority to assist the setting up of Trust models or Community Interest Companies with regard to local authority children's services departments.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165601","165601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943972","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the long-term value of innovation projects in respect of local authority children's services departments.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165602","165602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943973","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of water security for farmers and growers as a result of the closure of the European Agricultural Fund's Water Resource Management grant.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165713","165713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943974","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the interim recommendations of the Independent Medicines and Medical Devices Safety Review into surgical mesh, if he will clarify the conditions that should be met ahead of the resumption of mesh procedures used to treat stress urinary incontinence.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165673","165673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943975","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the three-day strike by cleaners at Guy's Cancer Centre on the provision of services at that centre.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165521","165521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943976","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to page 10 of the 2016-17 Annual Report of the Conflict Stability and Security Fund, what the extent of third party monitoring was of the counter-extremism support provided in Pakistan through that fund.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165463","165463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943977","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any funding for counter-extremism purposes in Pakistan through the Conflict Stability and Security Fund was allocated to the Inter-Services Intelligence.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165464","165464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943978","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which organisations received a portion of the £64 million that was spent in Syria through the Conflict Stability and Security Fund.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165465","165465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943979","2018-07-23","Cabinet Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish the report by Sir Alex Allan on the Windrush report and the advice given to the Rt Hon Member for Hastings and Rye.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165487","165487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943980","2018-07-23","Cabinet Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to publish the Windrush report commissioned by Sir Alex Allan in an unredacted form.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165488","165488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943981","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the findings of the Nuffield Trust report entitled The NHS at 70: How good is the NHS? that the UK is a below-average performer on preventing deaths from strokes, cancer and heart attacks.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165678","165678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943982","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 163204 on Wetlands: Conservation, what duties are placed on local authorities to assess the effect of a proposed development on the listed features of a Ramsar site.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165697","165697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943983","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 163204 on Wetlands: Conservation, whether local authorities are required to consider alternative solutions when determining a planning proposal with potential damaging effects on a Ramsar site.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165698","165698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943984","2018-07-23","Cabinet Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which third party organisations were successful in the tenders for the 48 contracts issued under the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund Framework in 2016-2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165466","165466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943985","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference page 15 of the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund annual report for 2016-2017, which organisations received funding from the Deployed Military Assistance Pool for the purpose of counter-Daesh activities.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165467","165467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943986","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to enable local authorities to enforce routeing conditions and legal agreements for heavy goods vehicles that are part of planning permissions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165699","165699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943987","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the report, Preparing for a drier future, England’s water infrastructure needs, published by the National Infrastructure Commission in April 2018, and the recent hosepipe ban in the North West, what steps he is taking to ensure that water companies to reduce the volume of mains water lost to leaks.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165557","165557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943988","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that the delivery of technical assistance to Bahrain is conditional on that country upholding human rights.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165677","165677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943989","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK Border Force officers were employed at (a) Heathrow, (b) Gatwick, (c) Stansted and (d) Luton airports in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165473","165473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943990","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many days were lost to sick leave by UK Border Force officers at (a) Heathrow, (b) Gatwick, (c) Stansted and (d) Luton airports in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165474","165474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943991","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK Border Force officers were (a) recruited, (b) dismissed and (c) retired at (i) Heathrow, (ii) Gatwick, (iii) Stansted and (iv) Luton airports in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165475","165475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943992","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the introduction of a database to log pets' (a) microchip numbers, (b) owners details and (c) date of entry into the UK.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165547","165547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943993","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if will develop a tracking system to trace all the movements of animals transported (a) from EU member states to the UK and (b) from the UK to EU member states after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165548","165548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943994","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is his Department's policy to continue to share information with European countries in the event of a disease outbreak after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165549","165549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943995","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the free movement provision on equines under the Tripartite Agreement with France and Ireland is planned to continue after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165550","165550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943996","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visitor visa applications were received by UK Visas and Immigration in each of the last five years by country; and what proportion of those applications were refused by country.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165627","165627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943997","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will introduce specific requirements to ensure the welfare of dogs and cats transported to the UK under the Pets Transport Scheme after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165551","165551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943998","2018-07-23","Department for International Trade","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether it is his policy that the importation ban on cat and dog fur will be retained after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165552","165552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943999","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle variations in radiology reporting timescales.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165695","165695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944000","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is his Department's policy to continue to implement and enforce equine identification after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165553","165553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944001","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the continuation of the agreements for the approval of veterinary medicinal products from European countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165554","165554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944002","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of the General Dental Council; and what steps he is taking to hold that body to account.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165705","165705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944003","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-18","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will consider in its definition of single-use plastics the effect of disposable nappies on the residual waste stream that goes to landfill.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165480","165480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944004","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2018 to Question 163564, how many (a) women and (b) men by age group were detained under only section 135 of the Mental Health Act 1983 in 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165595","165595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944005","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to support the use of reusable nappies and their effect on removing plastics from the residual waste stream.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165481","165481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944006","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cessations of bus services his Department or Traffic Commissioners have been notified of in each of the last five ears, and where in the UK these these been.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165527","165527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944007","2018-07-23","Cabinet Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to hold consultation and negotiations with Prospect, the Public and Commercial Services Union and the FDA on the Pay Remit Guidance for civil servants.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165687","165687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944008","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Hong Kong Special Administration Region Government on their plans to prohibit the continued operation of the Hong Kong National Party.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165501","165501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944009","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, from what date the tolls on the Severn Bridges are planned to be removed.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165515","165515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944010","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has commissioned research on the effect of court closures on (a) non-attendances of defendants and (a) staff morale.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165529","165529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944011","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that geographic accessibility to courts does not become a barrier to access to justice as a result of the courts closure programme.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165530","165530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944012","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure magistrates courts are adequately staffed with magistrates.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165531","165531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944013","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2018 to Question 158773, whether his Department consults aviation and consumer stakeholders in its reviews of the Service Level Agreements (SLAs) on UK Border Force performance.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165605","165605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944014","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make it his policy to ensure that UK Border Force service standards are raised and expected waiting times lowered as a result of airport spending on ePassport gate technology to improve throughflow of passengers at the border.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165606","165606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944015","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether UK Border Force plans to improve its service to non-EEA passengers on their arrival in the UK in order to attract trade and investment from those countries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165607","165607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944016","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 162497 on Patrol Vessels, and with reference to his Department's policy of not classifying offshore patrol vessels as warships for shipbuilding purposes, as outlined in the Answer of 9 July 2018 to Question 160710, whether possible future Royal Navy orders for offshore patrol vessels will be subject to international competition.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165493","165493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944017","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on the Israeli Government's policy of restricting access to the Occupied Palestinian Territories for international visitors; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165688","165688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944018","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many family court cases (a) one and (b) both defendants were without legal representation in Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165516","165516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944019","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the Israeli Government's refusal to grant residency permits and visas to foreign nationals who have made their home and livelihood in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165689","165689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944020","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on ensuring access to (a) Gaza and (b) Occupied Palestinian Territories for international visitors.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165690","165690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944021","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 162497 on Patrol Vessels, and with reference to his Department's policy of not classifying offshore patrol vessels as warships for shipbuilding purposes, as outlined in the Answer of 9 July 2018 to Question 160710, whether he has a remit to exempt future orders of Royal Navy and Royal Fleet Auxiliary ships from international competition under Article 346 of the Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165494","165494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944022","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of changes in the level of funding to Merseyside Fire and Rescue Authority on its ability to respond effectively to emergencies.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165691","165691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944023","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for (a) work resuming on the new Royal Liverpool Hospital and (b) the hospital opening.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165692","165692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944024","2018-07-23","Department for International Development","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when her Department will set out its policy on the UN-backed  International Finance Facility for Education; and if the Government will make i t its policy to provide a financial guarantee to that facility.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165693","165693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944025","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the increase in management apprenticeship starts since May 2017 on the takeup of apprenticeships at other levels.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165469","165469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944026","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will increase the length of time for responses to Ofqual’s T Level consultation.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165470","165470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944027","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the decrease in the number of mature students applying to university in 2018-19.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165471","165471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944028","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps is he taking to help reduce the numbers of 16-24 year olds not in education, employment or training.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165472","165472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944029","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times (a) Government Ministers and (b) Government representatives have met representatives of the Royal Liverpool and Broadgreen University Hospitals Trust to discuss the new Royal Liverpool Hospital construction since 15th January 2018; and if he will list those meetings.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165694","165694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944030","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what considerations were made by his Department prior to removing payments for the limited capability for work element of universal credit for applications made after 3 April 2017.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165633","165633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944031","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what consideration was given to the size of social housing waiting lists in local authorities when determining the methodology used to determine the eligibility of local authorities to bid for the Additional Housing Revenue Account Borrowing Programme.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165682","165682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944032","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of local authorities that are (a) eligible and (b) ineligible to bid for the Additional Housing Revenue Account Borrowing Programme have a Housing Revenue Account.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165683","165683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944033","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who applied for universal credit on or after 3 April 2017 have been granted the limited capability for work element.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165634","165634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944034","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the Government plans to publish the consultation on providing greater flexibility for local authority use of right to buy receipts.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165684","165684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944035","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been awarded the Limited Capability for Work Related Activity for universal credit in each month in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165635","165635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944036","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on the number of personal independence payments who have had their mobility car removed following a period of more than 28 days in hospital.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165636","165636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944037","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment claimants claiming under terminal illness rules have had their payments stopped because of a stay of more than 28 days in a hospital.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165637","165637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944038","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reasons social rents from local authority stockholding councils were not included in the figures used to determine average social rents in the local authority area where council rents form a part of the social housing stock for the purpose of determining local authorities' eligibility to bid for the additional housing revenue account borrowing programme.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165685","165685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944039","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) students and (b) students eligible for free school meals studied GCSE drama in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165482","165482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944040","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) students and (b) students eligible for free school meals studied A level drama in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165483","165483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944041","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students by ethnic group studied GCSE drama in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165484","165484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944042","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students by ethnic group studied A level drama in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165485","165485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944043","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 July 2018 to Question 163026, for what reasons more time is required to provide the information requested on the strength of the Army's (a) 1st Division, (b) 3rd Division and (c) Force Troops Command.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165495","165495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944044","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the status is of negotiations between his Department and Boeing over a possible contract to replace its six RAF E-3D Sentry airborne early warning aircraft with a fleet of Boeing E-7 Wedgetail aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165496","165496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944045","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department is assessing the feasibility of fitting the Australian CEAFAR radar on future British warships.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165497","165497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944046","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been paid in (a) compensation payments to customers and (b) penalty payments to his Department by  Govia Thameslink Railway in relation to its rail franchises in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165441","165441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944047","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which elements of RAF squadrons and groups will form the proposed reformation of the Number 11 Group RAF.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165498","165498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944048","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of (a) GSCE level and (b) A-level students were eligible for free school meals in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165486","165486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944049","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on community wellbeing of putting in place detailed statutory responsibilities for the maintenance of public parks by local authorities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165560","165560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944050","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people claiming asylum in Scotland have had to wait longer than the Government’s six-month target for a decision on their claims in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lesley Laird","Lesley Laird","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165700","165700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944051","2018-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 162553, which Department will provide funding for the proposed £3-5 billion domestic satellite navigation system; and whether that funding will be taken from money that has already been allocated in the Budget.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165561","165561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944052","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to make an announcement on the roll-out of HPV vaccination for boys.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165437","165437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944053","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will allow large employees to pass a greater proportion of their Apprenticeship Levy vouchers on to their supply chain subcontractors.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165562","165562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944054","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on ensuring that UK farmers are not compromised by tariffs on future exports of agricultural produce to the EU.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165535","165535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944055","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for water company  debt equity structure, interest payments and dividends of Qfwat recommendations on company borrowing for PR19.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165563","165563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944056","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will make an assessment of the potential merits of providing financial incentives for small businesses taking on T Levels work-placement students.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165564","165564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944057","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues ensuring that farm productivity will not be affected by changes in the availability of non-UK EU labour when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165536","165536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944058","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the oral evidence given before the Environment, Food and Rural Affairs Committee on 20 December 2017, what steps he has taken to ensure the maintenance of high food production standards for (a) domestic and (b) imported food after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165537","165537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944059","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his representative supported the publication of a joint communique at the June OECD Ministerial Meeting.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165565","165565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944060","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the commercial sustainability of childcare providers in the (a) private, (b) volunteering and (c) independent early education sector.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165629","165629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944061","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the validity of  reports of (a) human rights violations, (b) increased restraints on media and trade unions and (c) imprisonment of human rights campaigners by the state of Cambodia.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165679","165679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944062","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has estimated the number of hate crimes reported on university property in the 2016-17 academic year.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165616","165616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944063","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will pause the imposition of NHS benefit eligibility check (BECs) prescription penalty charge notices on disabled and unwell people who have been mistakenly awarded contribution-based employment and support allowance instead of income-based employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165570","165570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944064","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 2.15 of the National Audit Office report, Investigation into Errors in Employment and Support Allowance, HC 837, published on 19 March 2018, if she will extend the scope of the exercise to review the benefit entitlements of people who were mistakenly awarded contribution-based employment and support allowance instead of income-based employment and support allowance to include lost entitlement to free school meals and NHS prescription charges.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165571","165571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944065","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 15 March 2018, HCWS549 on employment and support allowance, how many claimants have been sent an ESA3 change of circumstances form; how many claimants have returned that form; how many claimants have had their claim reassessed; and how many claimants have received backdated payments.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165572","165572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944066","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time taken was for young migrants on limited leave to remain to achieve settled status in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165522","165522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944067","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department is taking steps to reduce the length of time required for settled status for young migrants on limited leave to remain.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165523","165523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944068","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of levels of Government funding for the 30 hours free childcare policy.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165630","165630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944069","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has made any assessment of recent trends in growth of the independent video game development sector.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165617","165617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944070","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on which local authorities have provided business rate relief to private, volunteering and independent childcare providers.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165631","165631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944071","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, at what rate the immigration health surcharge has been set in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165524","165524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944072","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the decision of the Israeli Government not to attend the adoption of its recent Universal Periodic Review report at the UN Human Rights Council; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165453","165453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944073","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the Government of Israel to act upon the three recommendations that the UK made to that country at its recent Universal Periodic Review at the UN Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165454","165454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944074","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many migrants have been refused limited leave to remain, having previously been granted it for one or more years in each of the last 10 reporting years.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165525","165525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944075","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure adherence to UN Security Council Resolution 2286 and the protection of medical facilities and personnel in the context of the occupied Palestinian territory.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165455","165455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944076","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to improve the recruitment and retention of childcare professionals.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165632","165632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944077","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what emergency measures his Department has put in place whose application for asylum seekers for asylum support and whose application has been affected by ATLAS IT failures to ensure that such asylum seekers are not left destitute.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165712","165712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944078","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps is he taking to obtain a full response from the Government of Israel that the investigation into that country’s use of force against demonstrators in Gaza includes an independent element; and what steps he is taking to promote accountability for potential violations of international law should a suitable independent element not be found.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165456","165456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944079","2018-07-23","Department for International Development","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to extend long-term assistance to Gaza’s health system in order to address the needs of patients with complex limb injuries who require specialist treatment and rehabilitation.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165457","165457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944080","2018-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received from the Big Four accountancy firms on their potential break-up.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165526","165526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944081","2018-07-23","Department for International Trade","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his US counterparts on the imposition of tariffs on steel and aluminium imports.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165512","165512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944082","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the revised Memorandum of Understanding between his Department, the Home Office and NHS Digital on the sharing of health data for immigration purposes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165558","165558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944083","2018-07-23","Department for International Trade","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many working visits he has had with his US counterparts since 24 July 2017.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165513","165513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944084","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he has made on consulting with interested parties on the proposed revision of the revised Memorandum of Understanding between his Department, the Home Office and NHS Digital on the sharing of health data for immigration purposes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165559","165559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944085","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 May 2018 to Question 136964, whether his Department holds a record of local authorities that have undertaken a corporate peer challenge from the Local Government Association since 2011.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165507","165507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944086","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will hold discussions with the Ministry of Ayurveda, Yoga and Naturopathy, Unani, Siddha and Homoeopathy in India on those therapies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165462","165462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944087","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will undertake a review of defined areas in regulatory animal testing that includes the use of second species and multiple routes of administering substances with the aim of identifying and eliminating avoidable tests.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165555","165555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944088","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of violence in Jalalabad, Afghanistan as a result of the attack on 1 July 2018 in that city that targeted and killed members of the Hindu and Sikh communities.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165566","165566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944089","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department plans to provide assistance to the Afghan Government to bring to justice the perpetrators of the attack on 1 July 2018 that targeted and killed prominent members of that country's Hindu and Sikh communities, including Awtar Singh Khals, the only Sikh parliamentary candidate.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165567","165567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944090","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the compliance with international law of the proposals by the Assam State Government to remove Indian citizenship from Muslims in that state who cannot provide proof that they were resident in that country before 1971.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165568","165568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/944091","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his counterpart in the Indian Government to ensure that Muslims resident in the state of Assam are not (a) stripped of citizenship and (b) deported after that Government completes its update of the National Register of Citizens.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165569","165569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942835","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations were made to the Turkish Government on BBC reports that four HDP members were shot and killed in Suruc during an election campaign visit by AKP deputy Ibrahim Halil Yıldız on 14 June 2018.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165073","165073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942836","2018-07-19","Department for International Development","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she has taken to ensure that the UK's future trading arrangements align with the African Continental Free Trade Area.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165005","165005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942837","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to raise awareness of the effect on the public purse of non-attendance for hospital appointments.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164895","164895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942838","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the money accrued to the public purse of cross-border manufacturing processes between (a) Great Britain and Northern Ireland and (b) the Irish Republic.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164896","164896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942839","2018-07-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what interim arrangements are in place to ensure that the interests of Northern Ireland are fully represented on the BBC Board in the absence of Northern Ireland executive.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164897","164897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942840","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of setting targets for increased public procurement from Commonwealth nations after the UK withdraws from the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165006","165006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942841","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women born in the 1950s and affected by the changes in state pension age in Coventry (a) are entitled to the full state pension, (b) do not have the required number of qualifying years for a full state pension and (c) were contracted out.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164849","164849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942842","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the provision of specialised nursing care for people with secondary breast cancer in Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164850","164850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942843","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on armed forces veterans of the removal NHS England funding for the Combat Stress programme.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165133","165133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942844","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of recent changes in the tender for the crown marketplace purchasing platform upon the Government’s ability to achieve its target to tender 35 per cent of Government spending to UK-based SMEs.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165007","165007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942845","2018-07-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussion he has had with his EU counterparts on the future status of UK citizens working in EU (a) institutions, (b) bodies and (c) agencies after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164898","164898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942846","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the NHS of treating alchohol-related conditions; and what steps he is taking to reduce that cost.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165018","165018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942847","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve co-operation throughout the health sector to improve research on brain tumours.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165019","165019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942848","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the Government plans to assess the (a) value for money and (b) use of the allocation of new government funds for brain tumour research.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165020","165020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942849","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether any official restrictions have been placed on the ability of officials working on policy relating to the UK leaving the EU in DEFRA agencies to conduct official discussions with (a) port authorities, (b) major retailers, and (c) haulage firms.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165041","165041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942850","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information his Department holds on disciplinary actions that have been taken against police in relation to alleged police mishandling of fox hunting prosecutions since 2005.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165134","165134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942851","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received information from his Israeli counterpart on the cause of death of the Palestinian medic Razan Al Najjar.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165179","165179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942852","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to (a) amend and (b) defer the process for awarding the Southeastern rail franchise as a result of the decision not to introduce in full a new rail timetable in December 2018.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165034","165034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942853","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many full-time equivalent staff are employed in his Department's housing directorate; and how many staff of his Department outside of that directorate work on (a) housing and (b) planning related to housing.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164865","164865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942854","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2018 to Question 125886 on Social Rented Housing: Consultation Papers, whether he plans to publish a Social Housing Green Paper before the 2018 summer recess.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164866","164866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942855","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the roll-out of cycle superhighways throughout London on the level of traffic congestion.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165045","165045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942856","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received from (a) road users and (b) other organisations on the effect of cycle superhighways throughout London on the level of traffic congestion.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165046","165046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942857","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the UK will adhere to the emissions standards for (a) cars, (b) vans and (c) heavy duty vehicles set out in recent EU proposed frameworks after the UK has left the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165035","165035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942858","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to take steps to discourage the purchase of high-emission (a) sports utility and (b) other such vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165036","165036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942859","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of tax-free childcare on employer engagement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165013","165013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942860","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 163137, on Child Tax Credit and Universal Credit, on how many occasions have claimants been refused an exception to the two child limit for (a) child tax credits and (b) universal credit as a result of (i) not meeting the conditions and (ii) not providing sufficient evidence to support their request.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165050","165050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942861","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average length of time has been for filling vacancies in HMRC's National Minimum Wage Compliance Unit in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165074","165074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942862","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the staffing complement is of HMRC's National Minimum Wage Compliance Unit; and how many of those staff posts were unfilled as of 17 July 2018.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165075","165075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942863","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the most recent estimate is of the gender pay gap within HMRC.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165076","165076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942864","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to assist households facing financial difficulties as a result of benefit sanctions.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165077","165077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942865","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has set a target for the amount of revenue to be generated from its estate rationalisation programme.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164964","164964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942866","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the effect is of a claimant refusing a job with a prospective employer where the terms and conditions on offer include a zero hours contract on that claimant's continued receipt of benefits.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165078","165078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942867","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to assist households facing financial difficulties as a result of errors or delays in the roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165079","165079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942868","2018-07-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on NATO's two per cent GDP spending target.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165114","165114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942869","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Child Support Agency (a) arrears-only and (b) arrears cases involving a current liability for a child are open in Glasgow South West constituency.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165080","165080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942870","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) parents with care and (b) non-resident parents with a Child Support Agency case there were in Glasgow South West constituency in the latest period for which figures were available.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165081","165081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942871","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with disabilities in Glasgow South West constituency had a deduction made from their benefits due to the removal of the spare room subsidy in the latest period for which figures were available.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165082","165082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942872","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are employed to investigate tax evasion in the HMRC's Customs Wealthy Team Unit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165083","165083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942873","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of appeals to the Tribunals Service in (a) Glasgow South West constituency, (b) Glasgow, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK for (i) personal independence payments, (ii) employment and support allowance, (iii) income support, (iv) jobseekers allowance and (v) tax credits were successful in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165084","165084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942874","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many officials of her Department at each grade have undergone more than 12 hours of training on universal credit; and what estimate she has made of the number of officials at each grade who will have undertaken such training on the completion of the full roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165085","165085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942875","2018-07-19","Scotland Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what meetings he or officials of his Department have had with (a) the Scottish Trades Union Congress and (b) individual affiliated trades unions since 1 January 2018.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165086","165086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942876","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employees of her Department are employed to investigate benefit fraud; what the estimated cost to the public purse is of such fraud; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165087","165087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942877","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse was of providing free television licences to people over the age of 75 for qualifying residents in (a) Glasgow South West constituency, (b) Glasgow City Local Authority Area and (c) Scotland in 2017-18.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165088","165088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942878","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the longest number of days is a universal credit claimant in Glasgow South West has had to wait before receiving their initial payment.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165089","165089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942879","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with housing associations in (a) Glasgow South West constituency and (b) Glasgow on access to information by those associations from the Landlord Portal for universal credit claimants; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165090","165090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942880","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will take steps to ensure that UK residents are not charged the rate applied to non-UK residents over and above network charges to access his Department's spousal visa helpline.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165091","165091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942881","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 23 May 2018 to Question 136078, what further discussions he has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues and (b) Ofcom on access by third party telephone providers to Government helplines which are advertised as free to customers but for which customers find themselves charged by that third party provider; and if he will take steps to prohibit such access by third party telephone providers who so charge.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165092","165092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942882","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure that members of the public who wish to participate in the Independent Inquiry into Contaminated Blood are entitled to, and receive access to, legal representation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165093","165093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942883","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2018 to Question 159060 on the systematic reviews on the diagnosis, treatment, transmission and prevention of Lyme disease, if his Department will publish a response to those reviews identifying which of the recommendations of those reviews the Government is taking forward; what steps the Government is taking to implement those recommendations; and what the timetable is for the implementation of those recommendations.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165063","165063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942884","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of claimants of disability living allowance with multiple sclerosis received the higher rate of mobility support as a result of being unable or virtually unable to walk because of a physical disability in the 12 months before the roll-out of personal independence payment.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165119","165119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942885","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people with multiple sclerosis are no longer eligible for the higher rate of mobility support as a result of the transition from disability living allowance to personal independence payment since the roll-out of personal independence payment.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165120","165120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942886","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of claimants have received each length of personal independence payment award since its introduction.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165121","165121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942887","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the award of the East Midlands franchise.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165098","165098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942888","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what length of franchise he plans to award to the successful bidder for the East Midlands franchise.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165099","165099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942889","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the award of the South Eastern franchise.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165100","165100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942890","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which bidders to date remain under consideration for the South Eastern franchise.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165101","165101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942891","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 162595 on Heathrow Airport, what statutory mechanisms are in place to ensure that unfunded Public Service Obligations to Heathrow Airport will be binding on both the Heathrow Airport and airlines.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165102","165102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942892","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish his Department’s analysis of feedback from the roadshows for tenants on the development of the Social Housing Green Paper.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165103","165103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942893","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2018 to Question 132937 on Aviation, what definition his Department uses for (a) licensed and (b) certificated aerodromes.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165067","165067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942894","2018-07-23","Scotland Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he plans to visit a food bank in August 2018.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165153","165153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942895","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to extend and enhance diplomatic relationships with Eritrea as a result of the recent agreement between Eritrea and Ethiopia.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164834","164834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942896","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 13 of his Department's Clean Air Strategy 2018, whether his Department has identified the reason for increased agricultural fertiliser use since 2015; and what steps his Department is taking to reverse the associated 3.2% rise in ammonia emissions.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164915","164915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942897","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 64 of the Clean Air Strategy, when he plans to publish the national code of good agricultural practice.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164916","164916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942898","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 64 of the Clean Air Strategy, what steps his Department plans to take to support farmers to make investments in farm infrastructure and equipment that will reduce emissions; and what the timeframe is for the introduction of that support.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164917","164917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942899","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 64 of his Clean Air Strategy 2018, whether he plans to include in his forthcoming agriculture Bill funding for targeted action to protect habitats affected by ammonia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164918","164918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942900","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 64 of the Clean Air Strategy, what funding his Department plans to allocate to tackle the effect of ammonia from agriculture on natural habitats; and what the timeframe is for the allocation of that funding.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164919","164919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942901","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with referenced to page 64 of the Clean Air Strategy which independent experts he plans to comprise the board that will make recommendations on the maximum limits of fertiliser application.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164920","164920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942902","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to seek to permit UK food to continue to be classed under EU country of origin labelling after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164921","164921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942903","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect on food (a) prices and (b) availability of UK food products ceasing to fall under EU country of origin labelling after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164922","164922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942904","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government is seeking continued access to the European Union Reference Laboratory for Alternatives to Animal Testing after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164923","164923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942905","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will bring forward in the forthcoming agriculture Bill provisions to (a) support farmers who practise agroforestry and (b) enable farmers to take up agroforestry.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164924","164924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942906","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidelines his Department has issued to (a) private and (b) state-run prisons on the (i) treatment and (ii) accommodation of prisoners with a diagnosis of dementia.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164958","164958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942907","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of prisoners were released from each prison on a Friday in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164888","164888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942908","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people released from each prison in each year since 2010 were subsequently recalled back into custody (a) within 12 months and (b) within a week.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164889","164889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942909","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been held on remand in prison for more than six months in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164890","164890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942910","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has made an assessment of the effect on people on remand of the reduction under universal credit in the period for which they can claim housing benefit from 12 to six months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164891","164891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942911","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what analysis his Department has commissioned (a) within and (b) outside of his Department on the effect of gambling advertising on (i) the general population (ii) people under the age of 18.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164909","164909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942912","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to restrict online gambling-style games targeted at people under the age of 18.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164910","164910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942913","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to restrict credit card betting.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164911","164911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942914","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to empower local authorities to prevent developers from building on greenbelt land when allocated brownfield sites with existing planning permissions granted have not been developed in that local authority area.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164879","164879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942915","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support local authorities in Wirral which have a shortage of brownfield sites with exemptions under the proposals for the National Plan.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164880","164880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942916","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many homes have been built on brownfield sites in Wirral in each calendar year since 1 January 2011.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164881","164881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942917","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that all brownfield sites are prioritised for development in (a) Wirral and (b) Merseyside.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164882","164882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942918","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will commission research into the relative health and longevity of people who have been taking statins for 10 years compared as against people with similar characteristics who have not taken statins.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164925","164925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942919","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Community Protection Notices have been issued for littering in England in each year since the enactment of the Anti-social Behaviour, Crime and Policing Act 2014.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164926","164926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942920","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 51 of the Government's 2017 Litter Strategy, what progress his Department has made on working with HM Prison and Probation Service to involve fly tipping offenders in clearing fly tipped waste.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164927","164927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942921","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government consulted (a) the Saharawi people and (b) the local population in drawing up its amendment to the EU-Morocco Trade Agreement.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165152","165152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942922","2018-07-19","Women and Equalities","2018-07-17","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to enforce sanctions for companies that fail to report their gender pay gap.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165139","165139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942923","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect on parental (a) employment and (b) productivity of the (i) Tax-Free childcare and (ii) 30-hours free childcare scheme.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165140","165140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942924","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the introduction of the Childcare Choices website has had on trends in the level of parents accessing available childcare options.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165141","165141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942925","2018-07-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish a breakdown of what the money spent pursuant to the the target of 2 per cent of GDP to be spent on defence has been spent on in the last five years; and how much and what proportion of that money was spent on pensions.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165142","165142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942926","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress the Cryptoassets Taskforce is making on its work programme.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165143","165143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942927","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the timeframe is for the first publication from the Cryptoassets Taskforce.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165144","165144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942928","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to extend the provisions of the Money Laundering Regulations 2017 to include the conduct of letting agencies.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165145","165145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942929","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to bring forward legislative proposals for the regulation of (a) unprofessional, (b) unqualified and (c) unethical agents in the property market to tackle money laundering in the property sector.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165146","165146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942930","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on improving levels of compliance with and supervision of the 2017 Money Laundering Regulations of changing HMRC’s policy of not making public the fines incurred from lack of compliance with those regulations of 2017; and if he will take step so to change that policy.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165147","165147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942931","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what quantifiable contribution the monies generated by Air Passenger Duty have made to improving the UK’s environmental commitments.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165148","165148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942932","2018-07-19","Department for International Development","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent estimate she has made of the number of internally displaced persons within Rakhine State, Burma.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164835","164835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942933","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what advice his Department provides to local authorities on setting the criteria of who should be admitted into urgent social or foster care.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165021","165021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942934","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the US Administration on development plans to tackle the humanitarian situation in Gaza.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164836","164836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942935","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Palestinian Authority on development plans to tackle the humanitarian situation in Gaza.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164837","164837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942936","2018-07-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to verify the integrity of information held by Companies House.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165051","165051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942937","2018-07-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies have been found to have registered at Companies House using inaccurate information in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165052","165052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942938","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans HMRC has for staff recruitment in relation to (a) numbers, (b) timing and (c) locations for different possible scenarios for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165155","165155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942939","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans HMRC has to consult with (a) businesses and (b) the accountancy profession on the implications of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165156","165156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942940","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2018 to Question 154717 on Mental Health Services: Armed Forces, how much of the £6.4 million allocated to the NHS England for bespoke veterans' mental health services was spent in South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165022","165022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942941","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 57 of the Government's Litter strategy, published in April 2017, the number of partnerships Highways England has entered into with local authorities in relation to co-operation in tackling roadside litter.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164928","164928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942942","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the Government response to the publication of the Department of Health and Social Care Task and Finish Working Group report into brain tumour research is planned to be published.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165124","165124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942943","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the recommendations of the Department of Health and Social Care Task and Finish Working Group report on brain tumour research, published in February 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165125","165125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942944","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government has plans to take the recommendations of the Department of Health and Social Care Task and Finish Working Group report on brain tumour research, published in February 2018, into consideration when allocating budgets for brain tumour research; and what plans he has to allocate money for brain tumour research.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165126","165126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942945","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2018 to Question 156480, on Social Security Benefits: Scotland, how many claimants the total value of outstanding benefit overpayment in Scotland is attributable to.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165149","165149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942946","2018-07-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the quality of (a) footpaths and (b) cycle-paths in rural areas throughout England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165023","165023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942947","2018-07-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of people who (a) have received and (b) will receive support through the Housing First scheme in (i) the West Midlands, (ii) Birmingham and (iii) Birmingham Northfield constituency.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164838","164838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942948","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 June 2018 to Question 155294 on Special Educational Needs: Inspections, if his Department will encourage Ofsted and HM Chief Inspector to include criteria more tailored to special schools in the new framework in September 2019 including (a) (i) parent and (ii) pupil satisfaction and (b) lower attendance expectations for poorly children.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165024","165024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942949","2018-07-23","Cabinet Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the contractors hired to deliver Conflict, Stability and Security Fund projects in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018 and; and what the value was of those contracts.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165135","165135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942950","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are being taken to introduce targets for early intervention for people with eating disorders.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165025","165025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942951","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which countries were allocated funding from the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018; and what the value was of those allocations.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165136","165136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942952","2018-07-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will list the housing associations with properties within (a) Birmingham Northfield constituency and (b) Birmingham who are eligible for the Voluntary Right to Buy Midlands pilot scheme for housing association tenants; and how many tenants he estimates will take part in that scheme in both of those areas.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164839","164839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942953","2018-07-23","Cabinet Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much Overseas Development Assistance was allocated to the Conflict, Stabilisation and Security Fund in (a) 2017 and (b) 2018 to date.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165137","165137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942954","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many FTE civil servants worked on the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017; and from which Government department those officials were sourced.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165138","165138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942955","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the availability and waiting times for therapeutic services for mental health conditions in (a) the UK and (b) Birmingham.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164840","164840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942956","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish his Department's civil society strategy.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165028","165028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942957","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much Big Lottery Fund spending was distributed per capita in each local authority region in the last year for which data are available.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165029","165029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942958","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of hosting the visit of President Trump to the UK.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165161","165161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942959","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure there are adequate levels of support in schools for LGBT+ pupils.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164841","164841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942960","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether there will be a Barnett consequential for the Scottish budget as a result of the additional funding provided for Computing Science in education in England.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164979","164979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942961","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has made an assessment of the key skills that the UK work force will need over the next (a) 10 and (b) 20 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164892","164892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942962","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average cost of processing a gift aid claim on charitable donations was in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165030","165030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942963","2018-07-23","Cabinet Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants received voluntary redundancy under the 2016 terms of the Civil Service Compensation Scheme before those terms were quashed by judicial review and the 2010 terms were reinstated.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165180","165180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942964","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he is taking steps to increase the availability of pastoral support in primary and secondary schools; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164842","164842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942965","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish the access and disability assessments for the premises used by the (a) Independent Assessment Services and (b) Centre for Health and Disability Assessments to carry out health assessments for people living in the Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164981","164981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942966","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 12 July to Question 161536, whether the Government plans to provide additional (a) staff and (b) resources to respond to a potential increase in the number of claims going to trial in the small claims track as a result of proposed changes to the small claims limit.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164965","164965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942967","2018-07-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with officials of the devolved administration in Northern Ireland on the (a) shortage of carbon dioxide supplies and (b) effects of that shortage on the agri-food industry in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164899","164899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942968","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on the proposed revision of Regulation 1071/2009 on exemptions for community transport providers operating for non-commercial purposes.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164900","164900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942969","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Department of Health in Northern Ireland on tackling obesity among young people.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164901","164901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942970","2018-07-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the economic value of the events industry to tourism in (a) London and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164941","164941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942971","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the work programme is of the UK Special Envoy on Freedom of Religion or Belief.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164902","164902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942972","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of overpaid benefits in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165042","165042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942973","2018-07-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what (a) financial and (b) other support his Department provides to the UK events and exhibitions industry.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164942","164942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942974","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases of underpaid benefits have occurred in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165043","165043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942975","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Colombian counterpart on freedom of religion and upholding human rights in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164903","164903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942976","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total cost of underpaid benefits has been to the public purse in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165044","165044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942977","2018-07-19","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the Government has spent on preparing Northern Ireland Executive departments for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164904","164904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942978","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much LIBOR funding he has yet to allocate.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165031","165031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942979","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has estimated the cost to the insurance industry of an increase in claims tried using the small claims track as a result of proposed changes to the small claims limit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164966","164966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942980","2018-07-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many civil servants his Department has employed in each month since July 2016.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164980","164980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942981","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on which occasions he or Ministers of his Department have met the manufacturers of Aptimil in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165053","165053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942982","2018-07-23","Attorney General","2018-07-17","To ask the Attorney General, if he will seek the release of money from the National Fund in order to set up a fund for good causes.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165032","165032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942983","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on which occasions he or Ministers of his Department have met the manufacturers of SMA infant formula in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165054","165054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942984","2018-07-19","Attorney General","2018-07-17","To ask the Attorney General, what progress he has made in his application to the High Court to release the money held by the National Fund.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165033","165033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942985","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on which occasions he or Ministers of his Department have met the manufacturers of Hipp infant formula in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165055","165055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942986","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on which occasions he or Ministers of his Department have met the manufacturers of Nutramigen infant formula in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165056","165056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942987","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on which occasions he or Ministers of his Department have met the manufacturers of Cow and Gate infant formula in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165057","165057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942988","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on which occasions he or Ministers of his Department have met the manufacturers of Nannycare infant formula in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165058","165058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942989","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise restrictions on freedom of religion or belief in (a) Xinjiang Uyghur Autonomous Region and (b) other parts of China at the next UK-China Human Rights Dialogue; and whether a date for that next dialogue has been confirmed.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165154","165154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942990","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on which occasions he or Ministers of his Department have met the manufacturers of Kendamil infant formula in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165059","165059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942991","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to publish the National DNA Database Strategy Board Annual Report for 2017-2018.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164861","164861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942992","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on which occasions he or Ministers of his Department have met representatives of the British Specialist Nutrition Association in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165060","165060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942993","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the budget for short-term supported housing.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164862","164862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942994","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to fund short-term supported housing through the benefits system.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164863","164863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942995","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on which occasions he or Ministers of his Department have met the manufacturers of infant formula in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165061","165061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942996","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the safety of infant formula.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165062","165062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942997","2018-07-19","Department for International Development","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant the Answer of 10 July 2018 to Answer 160363 on Gaza: Disaster Relief, whether difficulties with permits and access were experienced when the Emergency Medical Team was deployed to Gaza in 2014.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165174","165174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942998","2018-07-19","Department for International Development","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential (a) immediate and (b) long-term effect of the UK-MED specialist rehabilitation team cell on people injured by lower limb gunshot wounds in Gaza.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165175","165175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/942999","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of progress in reducing mortality rates for lung disease over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164975","164975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943000","2018-07-19","Department for International Development","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2018 to Question 160362 on Disaster Relief, for what reasons the UK Emergency Medical Team was not deployed to Gaza.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165176","165176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943001","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money his Department spent from the public purse on Care Commissioning Groups obtaining transparency orders in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164864","164864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943002","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the equity of access to treatment of (a) physical and (b) mental health services in England.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164868","164868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943003","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to reduce the incidence of suicide over the next five years.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164869","164869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943004","2018-07-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many (i) parks and green spaces and (ii) local authorities have been awarded his Department’s Green Flag Award in (a) the North East, (b) the North West, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber, (d) the East Midlands, (e) the West Midlands, (f) the East of England, (g) Greater London (h) the South Eas, and (i) the South West.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164883","164883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943005","2018-07-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of socio-economic status on the incidence of lung disease.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164976","164976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943006","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on that country's decision to reduce the fishing area off the coast of Gaza from six to three nautical miles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164843","164843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943007","2018-07-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 34 of Chapter 4 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, Cm. 9593, published on 12 July 2018, what actions the Joint Committee will be empowered to take in the event of significant divergences between the interpretation of agreements by the courts of the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164929","164929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943008","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether there is a timetable in place for the removal of all combustible cladding from privately owned high-rise buildings; and what sanctions there will be for private owners of such buildings who refuse to remove dangerous cladding.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165127","165127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943009","2018-07-23","Department for International Development","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions her Department has had with the PA on the PA Minister of Culture declaring March 16 as National Reading Day out of loyalty to the Martyrs.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164827","164827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943010","2018-07-23","Department for International Development","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with the PA on the commemoration on Official PA TV on 20 April 2018 of the death of Abu Jihad who was responsible for the murder of 125 Israelis and his declaration that with our skulls we are paving the path to certain victory.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164828","164828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943011","2018-07-23","Department for International Development","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 8641, and with reference to her Department's Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Authority (PA), what discussions her Department has had with the PA on the honouring of Latifa Abu Hmeid by PA officials as a crown on all of our heads on 17 June 2018 as a result of her son, Islam Abu Hmeid, having murdered Israeli soldier Ronen Lyubarsk.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164829","164829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943012","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2018 to Question 161195, whether the Government has made representations to the Government of Pakistan on the murder of Mr Muhammed Shoban on the 25 June 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164848","164848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943013","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the legislation regulating the release of helium-filled balloons and sky lanterns.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164844","164844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943014","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has had and with whom on the number of children who are at risk of experiencing hunger during school summer holidays in 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164845","164845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943015","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his Department's guidance on the practice of second post-mortems in accounting for recent technological advances.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164846","164846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943016","2018-07-23","Department for International Development","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 15 May 2018 to Question 141795, on Palestinians: Overseas Aid, what the terms of engagement are for that independent financial audit.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164830","164830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943017","2018-07-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what engagement she has had with (a) the gambling industry and (b) Gamblers Anonymous on the reduction in maximum stake on Fixed Odds Betting Terminals.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165150","165150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943018","2018-07-23","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department plans to give local authorities increased powers to protect the public from gambling-related harms.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164912","164912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943019","2018-07-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the total cost of contributing to the EU agencies the Government will seek participation in after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165004","165004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943020","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of passengers have waited longer than the Border Force service standard target time at UK (a) ports and (b) airports in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164990","164990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943021","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will consider applications for optometrists within the sub-category of High Value/Inward Investment in respect of Certificate of Sponsorship allocations under the Tier 2 Visa guidelines.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165097","165097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943022","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate he has made of the number of passengers cleared within Border Force service standards at UK (a) ports and (b) airports in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164991","164991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943023","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Border Force officers there were in (a) 2012 and (b) as of 17 July 2018.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164992","164992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943024","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK Border Force staff were employed at each UK (a) port and (b) airport in (i) 2012 and (ii) May 2018.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164993","164993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943025","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in Border Force officers numbers on their effectiveness since 2012.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164994","164994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943026","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the UK Border Force budget was in (a) 2012 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164995","164995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943027","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that UK Border Force is adequately prepared for new customs checks and controls when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164996","164996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943028","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on ensuring that UK Border Force is adequately prepared for new customs checks and controls when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164997","164997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943029","2018-07-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 June 2018 to Question 155938 whether he has decided on a date for when the next steps will be set out.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165177","165177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943030","2018-07-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 April 2018 to Question HL6839, what assessments the Government has since made of the ability of Bahraini human rights defender, Sayed Ahmed Alwadaei, to continue his work given the recent threats and reprisals facing his imprisoned mother-in-law, Hajer Mansoor Hassan.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165178","165178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943031","2018-07-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of granting anonymity to female and male victims of image-based sexual abuse.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164967","164967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943032","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2018 to Question 163103 on Prisoners, whether he has made an assessment of the possible effect on levels of poverty on projected prison population numbers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165017","165017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943033","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to help establish an independent inquiry into the violence in Gaza on 14 May.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165130","165130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943034","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many male prisoners whose security category is D (eligible for open prisons) are awaiting transfer to an open prison in Category (a) B and (b) C Prisons in England and Wales.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165122","165122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943035","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many female prisoners whose security category is D (eligible for open prisons) are awaiting transfer to an open prison in Category (a) B and (b) C Prisons in England and Wales.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165123","165123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943036","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the 5,145 potential victims referred into the National Referral Mechanism in 2017 were placed in safe house accommodation.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164859","164859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943037","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the 5,145 potential victims referred into the National Referral Mechanism in 2017 received no outreach or safe house support.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164860","164860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943038","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what remedial steps the Government plans to take to tackle the declining uptake of apprenticeships since May 2017.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165131","165131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943039","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps are being taken to ensure that the graduation rate of the Family Drug and Alcohol Court is maintained beyond September 2018.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164968","164968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943040","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, to make an assessment of the potential merits of banning the use of electrical water bath systems for the stunning of poultry after the UK has left the European Union.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164984","164984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943041","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the number of suicides recorded by the Coroners Office in each district in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164982","164982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943042","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the closure of the Family Drug and Alcohol Court on rates of substance abuse by people who would otherwise have gone through that Court.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164969","164969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943043","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many deaths attributed to the use of recreational drugs have been recorded by the Coroners Office in each district over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164983","164983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943044","2018-07-19","Cabinet Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 11 2018 to Question 160693, how many public sector construction contracts formerly held by Carillion have not yet been re-brokered to new companies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164867","164867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943045","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the estimated £90 million savings between 2017 and 2023 from decommissioning CSA computer systems are planned to be used; and what proportion of those savings are planned to be reinvested in the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164824","164824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943046","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to make it an offence to purchase component parts of ammunition with the intent to manufacture.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165104","165104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943047","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Child Maintenance Compliance and Arrears Strategy, published on 12 July 2018, what the time limit is for a parent setting up a payment method at the point of application before a Deduction from Earnings Order is set up.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164825","164825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943048","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Child Maintenance Compliance and Arrears Strategy, published on 12 July 2018, when the trial to refer low debt cases to external contractors under the Child Maintenance Service is planned to (a) commence and (b) end; and when she plans to report the findings from that trial.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164826","164826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943049","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the total cost to police forces in England and Wales of policing the state visit by President Donald Trump in July 2018.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165105","165105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943050","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to ban the importation of foie gras after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164985","164985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943051","2018-07-23","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department plans to work with the voluntary sector to improve knowledge and understanding around (a) HIV and (b) other blood-borne viruses among (i) police and (ii) fire services in England and Wales.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165027","165027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943052","2018-07-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of children in the secure estate were from BAME backgrounds in the last 18 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165113","165113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943053","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) boys and (b) girls with a diagnosis of autism were refused CAMHS treatment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165115","165115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943054","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children with a diagnosis of autism from each ethnic background were refused CAMS treatment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165116","165116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943055","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to reintroduce rabies blood testing with an extended wait period before entering the UK after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164986","164986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943056","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of educational attainment of female students with autism at (a) primary school and (b) secondary school level.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165117","165117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943057","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) schoolboys and (b) schoolgirls with autism as their primary educational special need received a (i) permanent and (ii) fixed period exclusion in (A) Dulwich and West Norwood constituency, (B) London, and (C) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165118","165118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943058","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it remains his Department's policy to maintain the conditions of the EU Pet Travel Scheme after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164987","164987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943059","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require (a) dogs and (b) cats to be treated for ticks before entering the UK after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164988","164988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943060","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2018 to Question 159567 on Severn Tunnel: Closures, whether his Department holds information on the costs of the engineering work during the temporary closure of the Severn Tunnel in 2018.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164974","164974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943061","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will made an assessment of the potential merits of reducing the timeframe for the treatment of tapeworm before entry into the UK from 120 hours to 48 hours after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164989","164989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943062","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of (a) employment support allowance and (b) personal independence payment have been sanctioned for abusive behaviour during a work capability assessment in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165107","165107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943063","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what definition his Department uses for abusive behaviour in relation to a sanction of a claimant for (a) employment support allowance and (b) personal independence payment.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165108","165108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943064","2018-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to support the proposal for a Transparent and Predictable Working Conditions Directive.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165047","165047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943065","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much money Great Western Railway has been fined for not meeting performance targets in each of the last eight years for which data is available.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165048","165048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943066","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons her Department uses shared care bands when calculating reductions to child maintenance payments; and what her Department's rationale was in deciding what those bands should be.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165064","165064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943067","2018-07-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how he has allocated spending from the rough sleeping prevention fund in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165160","165160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943068","2018-07-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons her Department is mandating paying parents to continue paying maintenance under the Child Maintenance Service when they have shared care for their child for more than 50 per cent of the year.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165065","165065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943069","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of claimants of (a) employment support allowance and (b) personal independence payment that were refused an assessment as a result of abusive behaviour that did not subsequently complete an application.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165109","165109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943070","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment support allowance and personal independence payment claimants have been denied home visits by the Centre for Health and Disability Assessments because of previous abusive behaviour in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165110","165110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943071","2018-07-23","Ministry of Defence","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) drug and (b) alcohol testing rules are for RAF pilots.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164893","164893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943072","2018-07-23","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what rules are in place for the testing of (a) drugs and (b) alcohol consumption by commercial pilots.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164894","164894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943073","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate his Department has made of the length of time the Windrush taskforce will require to determine whether affected individuals should receive compensation.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165111","165111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943074","2018-07-23","Cabinet Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that survivors of abusive and violent relationships and their new partners can register to vote without being traced by their ex-partner.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165066","165066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943075","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 16b on page 17 of the white paper, The Future Relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, cm. 9593, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) financial cost and (b) potential job losses resulting from the Government's policy to require refunding of tariffs on four per cent of UK goods trade.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165181","165181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943076","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made any assessment of the disruption caused by recent timetable changes implemented by Govia Thameslink Railways to students during the exam season in (a) London and (b) Lewisham Deptford constituency.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165112","165112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943077","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the document The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, page 49, paragraph 162, what preparations are being made to create an enforcement system to prevent the wrongful payment of tariffs; and how much the Government has allocated to fund those preparations.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165182","165182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943078","2018-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 44, paragraph 139 of the White Paper, The future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union cm. 9593, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the timely completion of the interconnectors to Belgium, Norway and Denmark; and what the estimated completion date is of each of those interconnectors.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165183","165183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943079","2018-07-23","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 16b on page 17 of the white paper, The Future Relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union, cm. 9593, what conversations he has had with international broadcasters who hold UK bases on the security of jobs and investment after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165184","165184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943080","2018-07-23","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 26 April 2018 to Question 136964, when he plans to provide a substantive answer to the question asked by the Hon. Member for Denton and Reddish on the delivery of the peer challenge programme; and what the reason is for the time taken in providing that substantive response.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164940","164940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943081","2018-07-19","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding the Government has provided to maintained nursery schools in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164884","164884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943082","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the benefits of (a) Crossrail and (b) High Speed 2 are for North East England.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164885","164885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943083","2018-07-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential for an increase in food bank use during the school summer holidays in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) England.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164886","164886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943084","2018-07-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to reduce fuel poverty in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) England.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164887","164887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943085","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many qualified teachers left the state-funded sector in (a) St Helens and (b) the North West in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165070","165070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943086","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report entitled Rebuilding My Body: Breast reconstruction in England, published by Breast Cancer Now on 18 June 2018, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the conclusions and recommendations of that report.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165014","165014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943087","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many qualified teachers joined the state-funded sector in (a) St Helens and (b) the North West in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165071","165071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943088","2018-07-23","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will commission a new national mastectomy and breast reconstruction audit.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165015","165015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943089","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the wastage rate was of qualified teachers in the state-funded sector in (a) St Helens and (b) the North West in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165072","165072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943090","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on the human rights situation in Xinjiang.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164913","164913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943091","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dogs have been imported into the UK via the Pet Travel Scheme in each year since its introduction.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164961","164961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943092","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dogs have been imported using the Balai Directive in each year since its introduction; and if he will publish the number of dogs imported from each country of origin for each of those same years.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164962","164962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943093","2018-07-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with Haiti officials on the political situation in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164914","164914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943094","2018-07-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many puppies were seized at the ports of (a) Dover and (b) Folkestone and placed in quarantine under the Puppy Pilot scheme in each month between 1 December 2017 and 30 June 2018.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164963","164963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943095","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s Early Years Social Mobility Peer Review Programme, published in April 2018, when he plans to publish further information on the design of the programme.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165128","165128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943096","2018-07-23","Department for Education","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department’s Early Years Social Mobility Peer Review Programme, published in April 2018, which early outcomes for disadvantaged children were considered as part of the selection process for peer reviewers.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165129","165129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943097","2018-07-23","Treasury","2018-07-17","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the number of parents applying for tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165016","165016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943098","2018-07-23","Department for International Development","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the availability of education for women and girls in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164959","164959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943099","2018-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the Government’s response to the Taylor Report consultations.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165049","165049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943100","2018-07-23","Department for International Development","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to publish the first quarterly update and progress report on her Department's People for Peaceful Change project in the occupied Palestinian territories before the House rises for summer recess.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164847","164847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943101","2018-07-19","Home Office","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the effectiveness of ePassport gates in accelerating the border process at UK airports, and (b) potential steps to increase usage of those gates.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164998","164998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943102","2018-07-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to respond to the report of the Law Commission entitled Consumer Prepayments on Retailer Insolvency, HC 543, published on 13 July 2016.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164960","164960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943103","2018-07-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to his oral contribution of 12 July 2018, on EU: Future Relationship White Paper Column 1158, Official Report, column 1158, what the timetable is for the publication of the (a) withdrawal agreement and (b) implementation bill.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165026","165026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943104","2018-07-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason the Government's panel on the future of the High Street (a) does not have a representative of workers in the industry and (b) includes only a Conservative Councillor.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164851","164851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/943105","2018-07-19","Department for Transport","2018-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the UK’s continued membership of the European Railways Agency notwithstanding the terms of the future relationship between the United Kingdom and the European Union.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165037","165037"
