"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50644","2014-05-15","Department for Transport","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether officials in his Department consulted with their counterparts in the Northern Ireland Executive before publishing the draft Traffic Signs Regulations and General Directions 2015 proposals.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198484","198484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50645","2014-05-19","Department for International Development","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many children in the six northern states of Nigeria have been educated through projects backed by her Department since 2008.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198495","198495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50646","2014-05-19","Department for International Development","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much has been spent on the Girls' Education Project in Nigeria since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198496","198496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50647","2014-05-19","Department for International Development","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how often she has spoken with her Nigerian counterparts on the Girls' Education Project in Nigeria in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198497","198497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50648","2014-05-19","Department for International Development","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many children have been educated through the Girls' Education Project in Nigeria to date.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198498","198498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50649","2014-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that a bilingual registered duty lawyer is available at all times in Crown courts in Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198486","198486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50650","2014-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of new employment and support allowance claimants do not have a work capability assessment.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198485","198485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50651","2014-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representation he has made to his Iranian counterpart on the destruction of an historically important Bahá'i cemetery in that country.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198500","198500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50652","2014-05-15","Department for Education","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in how many and what proportion of mainstream secondary schools (a) 10 per cent or fewer, (b) more than 25 per cent and (c) more than 50 per cent of pupils obtained the EBac at GCSE Key Stage 4 in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Skidmore","Chris Skidmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198493","198493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50653","2014-05-19","HM Treasury","2014-05-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the taxpayer of the NHS delivering a guarantee for all patients to have a consultation with their GP within 48 hours of seeking a consultation.","Biography information for Dr Phillip Lee","Dr Phillip Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198479","198479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50654","2014-05-19","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the first Service Complaints Ombudsman to take up his or her duties.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198488","198488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50655","2014-05-15","Department of Health","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department spent on (a) research into treatment and (b) medication for fibromyalgia in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198469","198469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50656","2014-05-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reduction he expects in the Cayman Islands government budget and on the Cayman Islands government provision of funds this year and next to the Cayman Turtle Farm; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198481","198481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50657","2014-05-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether hehas received the World Society for the Protection of Animals' recent report The Cayman Turtle Farm: A Continued Case for Change.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198482","198482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50658","2014-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of levels of compliance by Iranian businesses with financial sanctions imposed by the UK.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198472","198472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50659","2014-05-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he expects to publish the British Geological Survey's assessment of the hydrocarbon resources in the Weald area.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198470","198470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50660","2014-05-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many officials from his Department were involved in the final stages of drafting the IPCC Summary for policy makers of (a) Working Group I and (b) Working Group II.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198471","198471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50501","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, when electoral registration officers will be able to impose fixed penalty notices for non-registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198456","198456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50502","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 387W, on the electoral register, what estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of holding information on the proportion of attainers who are registered to vote; and what assessment he has made of the usefulness of this information in improving the introduction of individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198461","198461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50503","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with reference to the Answer of 24 January 2012, Official Report, column 203W, on the electoral register, what assessment he has made of his Department's performance in making the public aware of individual electoral registration; and how he measures that performance .","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198465","198465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50504","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2014, Official Report, columns 509-10W, on electoral registration, whether his Department provides funding to Bite the Ballot to increase voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198466","198466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50505","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what lessons he has learned from the Northern Irish experience of introducing individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198467","198467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50506","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 20 May 2013, Official Report, column 443W, on the electoral register, what the results were of his Department's cooperation with private sector credit reference agencies on datasets that can be used to ensure completeness and accuracy of the electoral register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198468","198468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50507","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2014, Official Report, column 971W, on the Electoral Administration Act 2013, whether non-individual electoral registration entries will be included on the register by the time of the freeze date for the next boundary review on 1 December 2015.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198462","198462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50508","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with reference to the Answer of 23 April 2012, Official Report, column 623W, on the electoral register, what steps he has taken to improve student registration in the run up to individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198463","198463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50509","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to provide that the freeze dates for population size for boundary reviews and the census be in the same year.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198459","198459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50510","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with reference to the Answer of 10 January 2012, Official Report, column 223W, on the electoral register, what progress has been made on better helping home movers to get on the electoral register in the right place.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198441","198441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50511","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what training has been given to electoral registration officers in the implementation of fixed penalty notices for non-registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198457","198457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50512","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, with reference to the Answer of 8 November 2011, Official Report, column 283W, on the electoral register, if he will make it his policy to collect information on the number of fixed penalty notices issued for non-registration in the run up to the introduction of individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198442","198442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50513","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps he is taking to disseminate the lessons learned from the data mining pilots for the introduction of individual electoral registrations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198458","198458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50514","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the use in Northern Ireland of prize draws to increase voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198443","198443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50515","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with (a) church and community leaders from black and minority ethnic communities and (b) Operation Black Vote on increasing registration levels for voters in those communities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198444","198444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50516","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether monies collected from fixed penalty notices issued for failure to register on the electoral register will be retained by the local authority which issues that notice.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198455","198455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50517","2014-05-14","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what estimate he has made of the number and proportion of people eligible to be on the (a) most recent census and (b) most recent electoral register who were not recorded.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198460","198460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50518","2014-05-14","Cabinet Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the electoral registration rates were in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) the rest of the UK in each of the three years after the introduction of individual electoral registration in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198464","198464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50519","2014-05-15","Department for Transport","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people are employed on a (a) full-time and (b) part-time basis at the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency (DVLA) in Swansea; and how many people will be employed there after the redeployment of all DVLA Northern Ireland-related work at the end of 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198428","198428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50520","2014-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that women who have been in employment are aware of their pension entitlement.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198429","198429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50521","2014-05-15","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of complaints relating to the quality and outcome of laser eye treatment in the private sector between 2010 and 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198426","198426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50522","2014-05-15","HM Treasury","2014-05-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many estates were liable for inheritance tax in 2012; and if he will estimate the number of estates likely to be so affected in 2017 should current regulations remain in place.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198427","198427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50523","2014-05-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of the UK squirrel population that will be made up of (a) red and (b) grey squirrels by the end of 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198425","198425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50524","2014-05-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 7 May 2014, Official Report, columns 162-3W, on new businesses: Wales, which businesses have received support from the Government's Start Up Loan Scheme in the Vale of Glamorgan; and how much has been lent to each.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198380","198380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50525","2014-05-15","Department for Education","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding his Department has provided through the Family Fund to support access to short breaks and respite provision for children, young people and their families experiencing all types of disadvantage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198434","198434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50526","2014-05-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what organisations have been funded by his Department to support access to short breaks and respite provision for children, young people and parents in service families and the families of injured servicemen in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198432","198432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50527","2014-05-15","Women and Equalities","2014-05-12","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what organisations have been funded by the Government Equalities Office to support access to short breaks and respite provision for children, young people and their families experiencing all types of disadvantage in each of the last five years; and how much each such organisation received.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198435","198435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50528","2014-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what organisations have been funded by the Youth Justice Board to support access to short breaks and respite provision for children, young people and their families experiencing all types of disadvantage in each of the last five years; and how much each such organisation received.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198433","198433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50529","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2014, Official Report, column 355W, on medical records databases, for what reason NHS England did not finalise the remedial action to be taken for breach of contract before the original planned start date for extra extraction under care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198419","198419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50530","2014-05-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number of zero-hours contracts in the UK which bar any additional employment.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198378","198378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50531","2014-05-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on the number of zero-hours contracts in the UK which bar any additional employment.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198379","198379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50532","2014-05-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance he has issued to local government on improving digital skills.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198424","198424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50533","2014-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has received about the case of David Flórez, spokesperson for the Patriotic March in Colombia.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198438","198438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50534","2014-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Colombian counterpart about charges brought against leading members of the Patriotic March.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198439","198439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50535","2014-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contributions the UK made to the OSCE in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198411","198411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50536","2014-05-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he was first made aware of allegations of inappropriate activity in National Grid's mains replacement contract with Balfour Beatty.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198365","198365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50537","2014-05-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to investigate allegations of bullying, mis-reporting, fraud and corruption at National Grid in relation to the main replacement contract with Balfour Beatty.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198375","198375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50538","2014-05-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on what dates since February 2012 he met (a) Ofgem, (b) the National Grid and (c) distribution network operators to discuss fraud in the regulated networks sector.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198376","198376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50539","2014-05-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many fraud investigations have been carried out by Ofgem since June 2010; what the outcome was of such investigations; and what financial penalties were imposed.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198377","198377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50540","2014-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he expects the nuclear sites at (a) Bradwell, (b) Hartlepool and (c) Heysham to be made available to new nuclear power station consortia.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198358","198358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50541","2014-05-15","House of Commons Commission","2014-05-12","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, whether GM food is sold in restaurants and bars in the House.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198437","198437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50543","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on operating breast network site specific groups in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198405","198405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50544","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding was allocated by each of the 12 strategic clinical networks for a breast network site specific group in 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198403","198403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50545","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding is planned to be provided to cancer strategic clinical networks in 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198402","198402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50546","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding has been allocated by each of the 12 strategic clinical networks for the running of a breast network site specific group in 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198401","198401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50548","2014-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department takes to ensure that support is provided to families bereaved by homicide.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198415","198415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50549","2014-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many whiplash cases in Bradford have been reported to the Compensation Recovery Unit since 2005.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198418","198418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50550","2014-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many whiplash cases in England have been reported to the Compensation Recovery Unit since 2005.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198412","198412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50551","2014-05-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many whiplash cases in Yorkshire and the Humber have been reported to the Compensation Recovery Unit since 2005.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198414","198414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50552","2014-05-14","Home Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will revise guidelines for the Metropolitan Police on whether domestic violence cases should be referred to the Crown Prosecution Service before prosecutions can be initiated by the police; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198445","198445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50553","2014-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much organic waste went into landfill in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198355","198355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50554","2014-05-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will review the policy of allowing organic waste to go to landfill.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198356","198356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50555","2014-05-15","Department for International Development","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that water scarcity in the least developed nations is addressed in the least Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198370","198370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50556","2014-05-15","Department for International Development","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that increases in demand for energy resources are addressed in the Sustainable Development Goals and targets and measures arising from those goals are set for (a) 2015 and (b) 2030.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198371","198371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50557","2014-05-15","Department for International Development","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to promote sustainable urban areas through technology.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198372","198372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50558","2014-05-15","Department for International Development","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether inclusion of disabled people is a core requirement for funding in UK-funded programmes; and how her Department defines and measures the quality of such inclusion across programmes.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198373","198373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50559","2014-05-15","Department for International Development","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department's country-level poverty analysis and social impact appraisals of UK-supported development programmes scrutinises those programmes in terms of provision for disability.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198374","198374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50560","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many publicly accessible defibrillators there are in (a) Hampshire and (b) Southampton; and whether there is a register or map showing where such defibrillators are located.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198420","198420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50561","2014-05-15","Department for Transport","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made in reviewing the adequacy of the time allowed for pedestrians to use pedestrian crossings, including pedestrian crossings out of the scope of those considered in the current consultation on the Traffic Signs Regulations and General Directions.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198393","198393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50562","2014-05-14","HM Treasury","2014-05-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many reports the Illegal Money Lending Team in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales, (c) England, (d) Northern Ireland and (e) the UK received in each of the last four years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198400","198400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50563","2014-05-14","HM Treasury","2014-05-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on publishers, authors and consumers of the proposed changes to VAT on eBooks in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Tom Harris","Mr Tom Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198452","198452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50564","2014-05-14","HM Treasury","2014-05-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what grounds he decided to introduce VAT at 20 per cent on eBooks while maintaining zero rate VAT on printed books.","Biography information for Mr Tom Harris","Mr Tom Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198451","198451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50565","2014-05-14","HM Treasury","2014-05-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of standard rate VAT on eBooks on (a) the UK's creative industries, (b) progress towards achieving the Government's aim of making the UK a hub for digital innovation and (c) benefits to the education sector from digital technology.","Biography information for Mr Tom Harris","Mr Tom Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198446","198446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50566","2014-05-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of growth in the UK market for eBooks on authors, publishers and readers.","Biography information for Mr Tom Harris","Mr Tom Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198447","198447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50567","2014-05-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will launch a public consultation on steps to be taken to promote the UK eBook industry.","Biography information for Mr Tom Harris","Mr Tom Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198448","198448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50568","2014-05-14","HM Treasury","2014-05-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of VAT at 20 per cent on eBooks on reading and literacy levels of young and teenage readers.","Biography information for Mr Tom Harris","Mr Tom Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198449","198449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50569","2014-05-14","HM Treasury","2014-05-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of standard rate VAT on eReading on children's reading for pleasure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Tom Harris","Mr Tom Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198454","198454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50570","2014-05-14","HM Treasury","2014-05-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the UK eBook market of the imposition of VAT at 20 per cent.","Biography information for Mr Tom Harris","Mr Tom Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198453","198453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50571","2014-05-14","HM Treasury","2014-05-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that VAT on eBooks at a standard rate will not damage UK authors and publishers and the UK book sector.","Biography information for Mr Tom Harris","Mr Tom Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198450","198450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50572","2014-05-15","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department will respond to the Fortieth Report of the Public Accounts Committee on Maternity Services in England, HC 776.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198392","198392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50573","2014-05-14","Cabinet Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, in what areas of policy the governments of the British Overseas Territories have been consulted ahead of negotiations on the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198381","198381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50574","2014-05-15","Cabinet Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the median gross hourly earnings excluding overtime for (a) full time and (b) part-time, (i) men and (ii) women were in each region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198367","198367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50575","2014-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many equal pay tribunal claims were made in each year since 2008; and how many of those claims were successful.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198368","198368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50576","2014-05-15","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many maternity and pregnancy discrimination tribunal claims were made in each year since 2008; and how many of those claims were successful.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198369","198369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50577","2014-05-15","Women and Equalities","2014-05-12","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what estimate the Government has made of the number of private companies which conduct gender pay audits on a regular basis.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198366","198366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50578","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department has allocated for antibiotic related research in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198404","198404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50579","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of healthcare professionals who (a) are aware of and (b) use the databases of the British Society of Urogynaecology and the British Association of Urological Surgeons to record adverse effects in transvaginal mesh implants.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198348","198348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50580","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received from (a) patients, (b) professional bodies, (c) the MHRA and (d) mesh manufacturers on the use of the databases of the British Society of Urogynaecology and British Association of Urological Surgeons to record adverse effects in transvaginal mesh implants.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198349","198349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50581","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made as to the accuracy of the databases of the British Society of Urogynaecology and British Association of Urological Surgeons as indicators of the total number of adverse effects in transvaginal mesh implants.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198350","198350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50582","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration he has given to making the reporting of adverse effects in transvaginal mesh implants mandatory.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198351","198351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50583","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representation he has received from (a) patients, (b) professional bodies, (c) the MHRA and (d) mesh manufacturers on a mandatory adverse effect register for transvaginal mesh implants.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198352","198352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50584","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to (a) commission research on, (b) consult on and (c) introduce a standard patient consent form for transvaginal mesh implants.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198353","198353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50585","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had about transvaginal mesh implants with (a) the Scottish Government, (b) NHS Scotland, (c) NHS England and (d) NHS Wales in the last three years.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198354","198354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50586","2014-05-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the total market value of his Department's properties in each country.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198406","198406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50587","2014-05-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assets have been assigned to (a) Standing NATO Maritime Group 1, (b) Standing NATO Maritime Group 2, (c) Standing NATO Mine Countermeasures Group 1 and (d) Standing NATO Mine Countermeasures Group 2 since July 2013; and for how long each such asset was so assigned.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198409","198409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50588","2014-05-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the contract for the (a) Challenger 2 Main Battle Tank and (b) BR90 Capability Sustainment Life Extension Programme will be awarded; what estimate he has made of the cost of this contract to the public purse; and what the work will comprise.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198407","198407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50589","2014-05-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the contract for the Armoured Battlegroup Support Vehicle will be awarded; what estimate he has made of the cost of this contract; and what the work will comprise.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198408","198408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50590","2014-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent reports that Iran denied International Atomic Energy Agency inspectors access to the Parchin military site.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198436","198436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50591","2014-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of France on its proposals to provide helicopter carriers to the Russian Navy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198430","198430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50592","2014-05-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has held with the Russian government on the right to self-determination of people in the North Caucasus.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198431","198431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50593","2014-05-14","Department for Education","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much special educational needs funding has been allocated per pupil in special schools in (a) Staffordshire, (b) Birmingham, (c) Wolverhampton and (d) the UK in (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198383","198383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50594","2014-05-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the additional costs of restarting the recruitment process for the post of Service Complaints Commissioner.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198416","198416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50595","2014-05-15","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Statement by the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs of 28 April 2014, Official Report, columns 537-55 and to the Answer of 12 May 2014 by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Defence to the hon. Member for Corby, Official Report, column 416, when the Government received the request from the Ukranian government for non-lethal support.","Biography information for Gemma Doyle","Gemma Doyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198440","198440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50596","2014-05-15","House of Commons Commission","2014-05-12","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what halal meat is served in the catering and retail outlets in the House.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198363","198363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50597","2014-05-15","House of Commons Commission","2014-05-12","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, whether halal meat served in the catering and retail outlets in the House is labelled as such.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198364","198364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50598","2014-05-15","Prime Minister","2014-05-12","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will establish a Cabinet Committee, chaired by the Chancellor of the Exchequer, to direct and co-ordinate policy on the development of shale gas.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198417","198417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50599","2014-05-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department is taking to simplify regulations applying to the shale gas industry.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198413","198413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50600","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether data on prescriptions dispensed in hospitals is collected centrally.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198382","198382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50601","2014-05-15","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice is given on the validity of European Health Insurance cards while UK citizens are aboard cruise ships in the European Economic Area.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198390","198390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50602","2014-05-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make a statement on the future status of the Land Registry.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198389","198389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50603","2014-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans he has for the Energy Company Obligation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198423","198423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50604","2014-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make it his policy to return the Energy Company Obligation to its originally announced level.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198422","198422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50605","2014-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for what reason his Department's consultation on the Energy Company Obligation does not include a return to its originally announced level.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198421","198421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50606","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what response his Department plans to make to the findings and recommendations of the All-Party Parliamentary Hepatology Group's recent report into liver disease, Today's Complacency, Tomorrow's Catastrophe, published on 25 March 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198359","198359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50607","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that his Department, NHS England, Public Health England, clinical commissioning groups and local authorities co-ordinate a national approach to improving the prevention, testing, diagnosis and treatment of Hepatitis C.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198360","198360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50608","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the feasibility of effectively eliminating Hepatitis C in the UK in the next 15 to 20 years.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198361","198361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50609","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of progress in reducing avoidable deaths from liver disease as set out in his call to action to reduce avoidable premature mortality; and what further steps his Department will be taking.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198362","198362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50610","2014-05-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had and with which bodies on giving local authorities greater powers to deal with the consumption of legal highs in a public place; and what support he is providing to councils which wish to put by-laws in place to prevent such consumption.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198391","198391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50611","2014-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many jobs in his Department are based in (a) London and (b) Aberdeen as part of the Licensing Exploration and Development Unit.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198410","198410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50612","2014-05-15","Home Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department or its Centre for Applied Science and Technology have made of the need for a separate national policy on data gathered by unmanned aerial systems in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198394","198394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50613","2014-05-15","Home Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has provided any advice to public communications providers on the consequences of the decision of the European Court of Justice in Digital Rights Ireland and Seitlinger and Others on data retention by those companies.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198396","198396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50614","2014-05-15","Home Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what role her Department's Centre for Applied Science and Technology has in the trial of the Aeryon Skyranger drone around Gatwick Airport.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198397","198397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50615","2014-05-15","Home Office","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether public communications providers have sought advice from her Department on the consequences of the decision of the European Court of Justice in Digital Rights Ireland and Seitlinger and Others regarding data retention.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198395","198395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50616","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have had their permanent injury benefit reduced because of the change from sickness benefit to employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198357","198357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50617","2014-05-14","Department for Transport","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps are being taken to ensure that funding is made available to maintain bus services in rural areas of Lancashire.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198385","198385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50618","2014-05-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to encourage more women to pursue a career in advanced manufacturing.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198398","198398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50619","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the impact of loneliness on the quality of life of elderly people.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198384","198384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50620","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the early intervention in and treatment for rheumatoid arthritis.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198399","198399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50621","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department has made available in Lancashire to improve the early diagnosis of breast cancer.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198388","198388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50438","2014-05-13","Cabinet Office","2014-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of levels of unemployment amongst recent university graduates in the North East.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198292","198292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50439","2014-05-13","Cabinet Office","2014-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many university graduates in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK were (i) employed and (ii) unemployed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198294","198294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50440","2014-05-13","HM Treasury","2014-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of qualifying companies in the Tonnage Tax scheme were in the (a) public and (b) private sector in each year the scheme has been in operation.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198293","198293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50441","2014-05-13","Home Office","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a new offence whereby a prosecution can be brought on the basis of a course of conduct in which a person has acted strategically to control, isolate, intimidate and degrade their victim in domestic violence cases.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198295","198295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50442","2014-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will assess the potential merits of retaining brownfield enclaves within urban areas as greenspaces for local amenity rather than being used for in-fill building.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198307","198307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50443","2014-05-14","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what economic benefit has accrued to the Afghan people from work on the Kajaki Dam project to date.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198301","198301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50444","2014-05-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to remove UK nuclear weapons from deployment and towards their subsequent destruction.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198302","198302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50445","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the beneficial effects on patient wellbeing and rate of recovery of hospital beds overlooking green spaces.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198308","198308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50446","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what studies his Department has assessed on the treatment of depression and anxiety by increasing access to green spaces in urban areas.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198306","198306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50447","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 May 2014, Official Report, column 244W, on prescriptions: fees and charges, what the cost of administering the exemption arrangements for prescription charges was in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198340","198340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50448","2014-05-13","HM Treasury","2014-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many single people have had sanctions placed on their tax credits on the ground that someone else was also resident at the property in the last three years; and how many such sanctions have subsequently been overturned.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198297","198297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50449","2014-05-14","Department for Education","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 May 2014, Official Report, column 63W, on schools: land, what his policy is on requiring school land which has been transferred to a person involved in the running of an academy to be returned to the local authority should that academy trust cease to operate a state-funded school.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198386","198386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50450","2014-05-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the performance of plotr; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198320","198320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50451","2014-05-13","Cabinet Office","2014-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many university graduates in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK secured (i) graduate level and (ii) non-graduate level employment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198296","198296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50452","2014-05-14","Cabinet Office","2014-05-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he plans to take to improve digital skills within the Government.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198327","198327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50453","2014-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what (a) targets have been set and (b) rates have been achieved for take up of the enterprise allowance in each Jobcentre district and individual job centre.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198339","198339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50454","2014-05-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for personal independence payments remained outstanding in each month since April 2013 in (a) Leicester West constituency and (b) total.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198345","198345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50455","2014-05-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for personal independence payments have been made in each month since April 2013 in (a) Leicester West constituency and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198346","198346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50456","2014-05-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many decisions on applications for personal independence payments have been made in each month since April 2013 in (a) Leicester West constituency and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198347","198347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50457","2014-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of whether proceeding with Contract for Difference auctions prior to the introduction of the Offtaker of Last Resort will be compatible with EU state aid guidelines on competitive bidding.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198321","198321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50458","2014-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effect of proceeding with contract for difference auctions prior to the introduction of the Offtaker of Last Resort.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198323","198323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50459","2014-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will assess the effect of bringing forward by three years the contract for defence auctions on independent generators wishing to enter the auctions and the market conditions in which they will operate.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198298","198298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50460","2014-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will provide additional support to assist independent renewable energy generators to know PPA terms from suppliers in their contract for difference auction bids; and whether he will assess the effect of the absence of an Offtaker of Last Resort on the level of support so needed.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198299","198299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50461","2014-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he intends that the Offtaker of Last Resort will have fostered the creation of a bankable offtake PPA market for independent renewable energy generators; and what assumptions this estimate is based on.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198300","198300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50462","2014-05-19","HM Treasury","2014-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any HM Revenue and Customs properties disposed of by Mapeley Steps Contractor Limited will be a chargeable disposal for UK capital gains tax purposes.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198328","198328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50463","2014-05-14","HM Treasury","2014-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to increase value for money for the Exchequer from private finance initiative arrangements.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198322","198322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50464","2014-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of solar farm planning applications were approved by local planning authorities in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198312","198312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50465","2014-05-14","Department for Transport","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to his Department of introducing a refund and vehicle excise duty system based on the day a vehicle is bought and sold.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198303","198303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50466","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much and what proportion of the maternity tariff is spent on insurance.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198341","198341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50467","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children have been treated in hospital for (a) burns from hair straighteners and (b) injuries from trampolines in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198342","198342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50468","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of NHS trusts have conducted a review their maternity workforce needs in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198343","198343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50469","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many officials in his Department are on the Connecting programme; and how many and what proportion of those officials have spent time working in mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198344","198344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50470","2014-05-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which Government department or office keeps a list of flights that passed through Diego Garcia between January 2002 and January 2009.","Biography information for Lord Tyrie","Mr Andrew Tyrie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198304","198304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50471","2014-05-13","HM Treasury","2014-05-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse was of tax evasion cases brought on behalf of HM Revenue and Customs in each of the last three years for which figures are available; how many such cases resulted in a guilty verdict; and how much has been recovered following successful prosecution of those cases.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198305","198305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50472","2014-05-14","Home Office","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which body has been provided with copies of the section 94 directions issued by her in order to provide oversight since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198387","198387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50473","2014-05-13","Department for International Development","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to improve the transparency of bilateral and multilateral aid spending.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198316","198316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50474","2014-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost was of translation and interpreter services used by (a) the courts system, (b) Crown courts and (c) magistrates courts in (i) Bury St Edmunds, (ii) Suffolk, (iii) the East of England and (iv) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198315","198315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50475","2014-05-13","Department for Transport","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much from the public purse was spent on rebranding (a) engines and (b) rolling stock used on rail services in (i) Bury St Edmunds, (ii) Suffolk, (iii) the East of England and (d) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198331","198331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50476","2014-05-13","Home Office","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost of translation and interpreter services used by each police force in England and Wales has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198313","198313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50477","2014-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of (a) incapacity benefit and employment support allowance, (b) disability living allowance and (c) severe disablement allowance claiming for each type of disability there were in (i) Bury St Edmunds constituency, (ii) Suffolk, (iii) the East of England and (iv) England and Wales in each of the last five years; and how much was spent in each such category in each such year.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198338","198338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50478","2014-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent representations he has received on levels of remuneration for local government executives.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198330","198330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50479","2014-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many temporary national insurance numbers were issued in (a) Bury St Edmunds constituency, (b) Suffolk (c) the East of England and (d) England and Wales by HM Revenue and Customs in each of the last five years; and what proportion of such numbers were issued for tax credit purposes.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198329","198329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50480","2014-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people have been declared bankrupt in (a) Bury St Edmunds constituency, (b) Suffolk, (c) East of England and (d) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198314","198314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50481","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost was of translation and interpreter services used by each individual NHS trust in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198333","198333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50482","2014-05-13","Department for Education","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of young people aged (a) 16, (b) 17 and (c) 18 were not in full-time education or training in (i) Bury St Edmunds constituency, (ii) Suffolk, (iii) the East of England and (d) England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198332","198332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50483","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) pharmacological treatments and (b) associated indications the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence has recommended for cancer treatment through either single or multiple technology appraisals in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013 and (iii) 2014.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198317","198317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50484","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the determined population size for each pharmacological treatment and associated indications which the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence has (a) recommended for cancer treatment and (b) recommended for cancer treatment under the end-of-life criteria in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013 and (iii) 2014.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198325","198325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50485","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the final calculated cost per quality adjusted life year of each pharmacological treatment and associated indications which the  National Institute for Health and Care Excellence has recommended for cancer treatments; and which such treatments and indications have been recommended under the end-of-life criteria in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198318","198318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50486","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) pharmacological treatments and (b) associated indications the  National Institute for Health and Care Excellence has recommended against in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013 and (iii) 2014.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198319","198319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50487","2014-05-14","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the final calculated cost per quality adjusted life year of each pharmacological treatment and associated indications which the  National Institute for Health and Care Excellence has not recommended for cancer treatment in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198324","198324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50488","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made on the potential effect of MERS virus in the UK.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198311","198311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50489","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure the safety of UK nationals at risk of contracting MERS virus whilst travelling to and from Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198335","198335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50490","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will put safety precautions in place for UK nationals returning from Saudi Arabia at risk of having contracted the MERS virus.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198334","198334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50491","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has received reports of UK nationals having contracted the MERS virus.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198309","198309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50492","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the World Health Organisation and his counterparts in Saudi Arabia on the risk of MERS virus spreading to (a) the UK and (b) other countries.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198310","198310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50493","2014-05-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library research he has commissioned on the effect that turning off street lighting and relying on ambient lighting has on levels of crime.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198326","198326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50288","2014-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will set out the steps he plans to take to remove UK nuclear weapons from deployment and their subsequent destruction.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198199","198199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50289","2014-05-14","Department for International Development","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department is offering to Nigeria for the promotion of education for women and girls in a safe environment.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198261","198261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50290","2014-05-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of UK nationals living or working in Nigeria; and whether his Department has issued any updated advice to them since the abduction of more than 200 Nigerian schoolgirls.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198260","198260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50291","2014-05-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the UK's energy requirement that will be generated by (a) onshore wind, (b) offshore wind, (c) solar and (d) nuclear energy sources by the end of 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198258","198258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50292","2014-05-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the average satisfaction rating given by tenants relating to maintenance service in public housing in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198259","198259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50293","2014-05-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans the Government has to hold events in Northern Ireland to commemorate the centenary of the First World War.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198257","198257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50294","2014-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 May 2014, Official Report, column 72W, on Iran, if he will provide a detailed itemisation of works of art, antiquities, fixtures and fittings and other items of public property damaged or destroyed by rioters in HM Embassy in Tehran in 2011.","Biography information for Michael Ellis","Michael Ellis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198221","198221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50295","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made the effect of recent NHS pay policy on the ability of the NHS to recruit and retain nursing staff.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198270","198270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50296","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 April 2014, Official Report, column 43W, on medical records: databases, whether his Department plans any procurement in connection with care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198271","198271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50297","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to his Answer of 13 March 2014, Official Report, column 355W, on medical records: databases, if he will bar ATOS from having any involvement with care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198272","198272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50298","2014-05-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to protect the UK's forests.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198252","198252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50299","2014-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the provisions of the EU Deep and Comprehensive Free trade Agreement with Morocco apply outside the sovereign territory of Morocco.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198209","198209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50300","2014-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, who the de facto administering power is in the area of Western Sahara not under Moroccan control; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198207","198207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50301","2014-05-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions, he has had with (a) EU officials, (b) Indian authorities and (c) affected UK businesses regarding the European Commission's ban on the import of Indian mangoes.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198233","198233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50302","2014-05-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department has undertaken any assessment into the European Commission's ban on the import of Indian mangoes and the economic impact on UK businesses.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198234","198234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50303","2014-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the oral Answer of 30 April 2014, Official Report, column 815, how the assisted digital service for lasting power of attorney is provided and accessed; and what assisted digital services are in place for other Government digital services.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198286","198286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50304","2014-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 10 April 2014, Official Report, column 312W, on building regulations, what assessment he has made of the cybersecurity implications of the Building Information Modelling Smart City project.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198285","198285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50305","2014-05-13","Women and Equalities","2014-05-08","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what guidance she has given to other Departments on commissioning publicly-funded research into gender differences in brain development and functioning.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198267","198267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50306","2014-05-12","Department for Transport","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what civil service restrictions will be removed should the Highways Agency be moved to a GoCO.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198246","198246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50307","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 24 March 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Sherratt.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198191","198191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50308","2014-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he intends to reply to the letter to the Minister for Skills and Enterprise dated 27 February 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr John Mannion.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198190","198190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50309","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to the Immigration and Security Minister dated 27 March 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Dr M Hatamleh.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198195","198195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50310","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to the Minister for Immigration and Security dated 16 March 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms S Ejaz.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198196","198196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50311","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 19 March 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr F. Mir.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198192","198192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50312","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 17 March 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Asif Rafiq.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198193","198193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50313","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 17 March 2014 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr M. Barzi.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198194","198194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50314","2014-05-13","Department for Education","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to rule-out the introduction of fees for admission to over-subscribed schools supported by public funds.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198167","198167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50315","2014-05-13","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether all independent renewable energy generators will have agreed project terms with their financiers at the time of submitting a Contracts for Difference auction bid.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198289","198289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50316","2014-05-13","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the proportion of applicants for scrap metal dealer's licences who were not known to their local authority under the previous registration system.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198269","198269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50317","2014-05-13","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on the export of stolen scrap metal.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198210","198210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50318","2014-05-13","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what advice her Department has issued to police forces on working with the UK Border Force in preventing the export of stolen scrap metal.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198211","198211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50319","2014-05-13","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what organisation will take over the competencies of the National Metal Theft Taskforce once funding for that body ends.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198212","198212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50320","2014-05-13","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the level of stolen scrap metal exported for sale abroad.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198268","198268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50321","2014-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to publish the Government's response to the review of property conditions in the private rented sector.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198174","198174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50322","2014-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answers of 6 May 2014, Official Report, column 29W, and of 21 November 2013, Official Report, columns 980-1W, on local government publications, if he will list all councils that publish magazines or newsletters more than four times a year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198175","198175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50323","2014-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the link between (a) street and (b) ambient lighting and the incidence of burglaries.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198177","198177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50324","2014-05-15","HM Treasury","2014-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with his foreign counterparts about reforms to transfer pricing arrangements.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198184","198184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50325","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to include (a) marriage fraud and (b) marriage achieved through a material misrepresentation in the criteria for the annulment of a marriage.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198278","198278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50326","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to tackle (a) immigration marriage fraud and (b) immigration marriage fraud through bigamy.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198279","198279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50327","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people convicted of immigration marriage fraud through bigamy have been deported in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198280","198280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50328","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many successful prosecutions for immigration marriage fraud through bigamy there have been in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198281","198281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50329","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that all those convicted of marriage fraud through bigamy are deported.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198282","198282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50330","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what joint actions her Department is taking with the Foreign and Commonwealth Office to tackle immigration marriage fraud through bigamy.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198283","198283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50331","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of immigration marriage fraud through bigamy have been reported to her Department in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198262","198262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50332","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department takes to assist the victims of immigration marriage fraud through bigamy.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198284","198284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50333","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the average annual change in income for GP practices in Fareham and Gosport arising from the withdrawal of the minimum practice income guarantee.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198213","198213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50334","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of how many GP practices in Fareham and Gosport will lose income as a consequence of the withdrawal of the minimum practice income guarantee; and what actions his Department has put in place to mitigate the impact of any such losses on services.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198214","198214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50335","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent work his Department has undertaken to raise awareness of the effects of diabetes on people with that condition; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198155","198155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50336","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent per capita in each general practice area in Fareham constituency in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198156","198156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50337","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the quality of foot care provided in primary care to patients with diabetes.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198163","198163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50338","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who is responsible for auditing compliance with National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidelines relating to the care of patients with diabetes.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198188","198188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50339","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued to GPs on the assessment and treatment of foot conditions where a patient has diabetes.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198189","198189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50340","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 May 2014, Official Report, column 127W, if he will list the outlier practices and the amount each is forecast to lose as a result of removing performance indicators from the Quality Outcomes Framework.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198248","198248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50341","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors have opted to retire and remove themselves from the medical register before facing an impending disciplinary hearing in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198222","198222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50342","2014-05-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment his Department has made of the competitiveness of green deal finance loans.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198244","198244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50343","2014-05-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average value is of (a) new, (b) pending and (c) live green deal plans.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198245","198245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50344","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to promote potatoes as part of a healthy diet.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198227","198227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50345","2014-05-13","Department for Transport","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what level of uptake there has been for the cycle-to-work scheme in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Northern Ireland and (d) Scotland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198239","198239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50346","2014-05-13","Department for Transport","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the cycle to work scheme in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198223","198223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50347","2014-05-13","Northern Ireland Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will provide funding for Praxis to support the relocation of employees working on the Hillsborough Estate.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198178","198178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50348","2014-05-13","Northern Ireland Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent support her Department has offered to Praxis to help relocate their services off the Hillsborough Estate.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198179","198179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50349","2014-05-13","Northern Ireland Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will meet representatives of Praxis to discuss their eviction from the Hillsborough Estate.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198180","198180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50350","2014-05-13","Northern Ireland Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she was informed by officials in her Department that records for the period 1987 to 1988 relating to the Royal Prerogative of Mercy had gone missing; and whether she instigated an inquiry.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198181","198181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50351","2014-05-13","Northern Ireland Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to her Answer of 30 April 2014, Official Report, column 723W, on Northern Ireland government, when she last met with the Northern Ireland Minister for Social Development.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198182","198182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50352","2014-05-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of property level protection measures on flood insurance premiums.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198264","198264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50353","2014-05-13","Department for International Development","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that the problem of rising health costs, in part owing to ageing populations, is addressed in the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198208","198208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50354","2014-05-13","Department for International Development","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that the Sustainable Development Goals effectively recognise the potential human and environmental costs arising from a growing proportion of the global population living in urban slums.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198205","198205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50355","2014-05-13","Department for International Development","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that the problems of youth unemployment and other forms of unemployment are addressed effectively in the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198206","198206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50356","2014-05-13","Department for International Development","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that action is taken in the Sustainable Development Goals to address the pressures which rapid urbanisation is placing upon the infrastructure of cities around the world and their inhabitants.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198216","198216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50357","2014-05-13","Department for Transport","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions officials or Ministers of his Department have had with bus company representatives on disability awareness training and EU Regulation 181/2011 since 9 January 2014.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198250","198250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50358","2014-05-13","Department for Transport","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how his Department plans to monitor voluntary compliance with disability awareness training by bus and coach companies.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198251","198251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50359","2014-05-13","Department for Transport","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will commission independent research to analyse the effectiveness of a voluntary approach to disability awareness training for bus staff.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198249","198249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50360","2014-05-13","Department for Transport","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Transport of 9 January 2014, Official Report, column 174WH, on disabled people (access to transport) and to his oral Answer of 8 May 2014, what his Department's policy is on reviewing the UK's derogation from the requirement to have disability awareness training for bus drivers as set out in EU Regulation 181/2011.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198288","198288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50361","2014-05-13","Department for Transport","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions officials and Ministers in his Department have had with disability or transport groups on bus driver awareness training and EU Regulation 181/2011 since 9 January 2014.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198287","198287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50362","2014-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department first approached the Computer Electronics and Surveillance Group of GCHQ about security in the universal credit IT system.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198224","198224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50363","2014-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the net benefits in 2011-12 prices of the Universal Credit programme in the period 2010-11 to 2022-23.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198217","198217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50364","2014-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he commissioned recruitment firms to assist in the appointment of a new Director General for Universal Credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198225","198225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50365","2014-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people claimed how much support for mortgage interest in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to April 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198226","198226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50366","2014-05-13","Cabinet Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many of his Department's employees are currently working on the digital solution for universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198243","198243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50367","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle obesity in the NHS staff.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198166","198166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50368","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will investigate reports that the Neurology department at Royal Preston Hospital is allocating appointments to patients and then instructing them not to attend on the date and time given as the appointment is only made for consultants to view the patient's referral letter; whether (a) his Department for (b) NHS England issues guidance on the allocation of appointments which patients are instructed not to attend; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198218","198218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50369","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether all abortions commissioned by NHS England from private providers are recorded in the abortion statistics.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198165","198165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50370","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what scrutiny arrangements the Care Quality Commission applies to (a) abortion and (b) other counselling.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198157","198157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50371","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many sick notes have been recorded as missing by Jobcentre plus (a) annually since 2010 and (b) in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198235","198235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50372","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what training is provided to front-desk jobcentre staff on understanding and being sympathetic to the variety of difficulties that some people with ill health or disability face.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198185","198185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50373","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department takes to ensure that a claimant suffers no financial hardship as a result of paperwork lost by a jobcentre.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198186","198186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50374","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what procedures his Department has put in place to ensure that mail received by recorded delivery at jobcentres is logged and dealt with immediately; and what assessment he has made of whether such procedures are carried out across all jobcentres.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198187","198187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50375","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to improve awareness of and early intervention for rheumatoid arthritis.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198171","198171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50376","2014-05-13","Department for Education","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools and academies have (a) opened a new sixth form and (b) closed their sixth form in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198172","198172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50377","2014-05-13","Department for Education","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of the cohort achieved an A* to C grade in (a) GCSE mathematics, (b) GCSE English and (c) GCSE English literature at the end of (i) Year 11, (ii) Year 12 and (iii) Year 13 in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198173","198173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50378","2014-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will ensure that North Lincolnshire Council has first refusal for the acquisition of the Kirtin in Lindsey base.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198169","198169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50379","2014-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to apply in all circumstances the Defence Infrastructure Organisation's principles that local councils should have first refusal when assets are being disposed of.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198170","198170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50380","2014-05-12","HM Treasury","2014-05-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to respond to Question 193089, tabled on 20 March 2014 for answer on 25 March 2014.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198277","198277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50382","2014-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the situation for religious minorities in northern Nigeria.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198231","198231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50383","2014-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the situation for religious minorities in Burma.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198232","198232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50384","2014-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the situation of Christian communities in Syria.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198237","198237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50385","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the West Midlands Ambulance Service's system's indicators performance in 2012-13; and what assessment he has made of the reasons for changes in that level of performance.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198247","198247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50386","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he last amended his Department's guidelines on the authorising of abortions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198255","198255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50387","2014-05-13","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the role is of UK military personnel in Nigeria in connection with the mass abduction of schoolgirls.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198219","198219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50388","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed to work on cancer policy in his Department in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198265","198265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50389","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed by NHS England to work on cancer policy at a national level in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198266","198266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50390","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed by strategic health authorities in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and how many such staff worked specifically in cancer networks.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198197","198197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50391","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed by each of the 28 cancer networks in England in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198198","198198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50392","2014-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answers of 28 April 2014, Official Report, columns 594-5W, on official visits, whether any of the six received requests for special mission status were refused (a) by reference to duties to prosecute or extradite persons alleged to have committed or to have ordered to be committed grave breaches of the Fourth Geneva Convention or other international crimes and (b) on other human rights grounds.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198228","198228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50393","2014-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 April 2014, Official Report, columns 594-5W, on official visits, whether the six received requests for special mission status were refused or granted, by country making the request.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198229","198229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50394","2014-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 28 April 2014, Official Report, columns 594-5W, on official visits, if he will provide details of the six received requests for special mission status; and from which countries they were received.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198230","198230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50395","2014-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what visits he has made to Australia in the last year; what the primary purpose was of any such visits; and who accompanied him on such visits.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198263","198263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50396","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 1 April 2014, Official Report, column 714, on physical and mental health (parity of esteem), if he will collect and publish mental health spending data for (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) future years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198290","198290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50397","2014-05-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects the Pension Regulator to conclude its investigation into the Carrington Wire pension scheme.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198254","198254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50398","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the findings of the recent Global Forum on Incontinence into improving health and social care in incontinence.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198200","198200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50399","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will discuss with the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists the decision of its faculty of sexual and reproductive health not to allow doctors and nurses who have a conscientious objection to supplying contraceptive drugs or devices which act after fertilisation to receive its diploma in sexual and reproductive health.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198176","198176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50400","2014-05-13","Department for International Development","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to reorganise its funding model to ensure that it is encouraging service delivery for complex multiple needs, in line with an intregrated model of healthcare solutions.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198203","198203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50401","2014-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Pakistan on (a) the fairness of the hearing of Asiya Noreen Bibi who was sentenced to death in 2011 at the provincial Lahore High Court and (b) providing adequate protection to judiciary officials to allow a further hearing to take place.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198202","198202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50402","2014-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the fairness of the hearing of Asiya Noreen Bibi sentenced to death in 2011 at the provincial Lahore High Court.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198201","198201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50403","2014-05-13","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he expects to consult on the introduction of custodial sentences under section 77 of the Criminal Justice and Immigration Act 2008 relating to data protection breaches; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198236","198236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50404","2014-05-13","Women and Equalities","2014-05-08","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what steps he is taking to advance equal rights for LGBT citizens in the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198168","198168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50405","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research he has commissioned on the effect of patients receiving urgent investigations and treatment following a transient ischaemic attack on reducing (a) the risk of future strokes and (b) the cost to the NHS of treating strokes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198240","198240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50406","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had on ways of improving awareness of transient ischaemic attacks on the part of (a) GPs, (b) staff in A&E departments and (c) other health staff.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198241","198241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50407","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many specialist transient ischaemic attack clinics are currently operating in each NHS trust in each region of England.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198253","198253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50408","2014-05-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 3 April 2014, Official Report, column 805W, on renewable energy, what the standard period is for stakeholders to be given to respond to a Government consultation.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198159","198159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50409","2014-05-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will recconsider the proposal to introduce Contract for Difference auctioning three years earlier than planned.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198160","198160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50410","2014-05-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of (a) the readiness of markets for a Contract for Difference (CfD) competitive bidding process and (b) the effect on independent generators of early introduction of CfD auctioning.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198161","198161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50411","2014-05-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the impact on independent generators of introduction of Contract for Difference auctioning before the Offtaker of Last Resort is in place.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198162","198162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50412","2014-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of empty properties in (a) Bristol North West constituency and (b) Bristol.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198256","198256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50413","2014-05-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that local authorities take into account the effect of planning decisions on neighbouring authorities when making those decisions.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198291","198291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50414","2014-05-13","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to criminalise psychological abuse and coercive control in domestic violence situations.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198183","198183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50415","2014-05-14","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what payments her Department makers to destination countries for visas allowing entry to people being deported from the UK to those countries.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198275","198275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50416","2014-05-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what response the UK has made to the application of the Marshall Islands to the International Court of Justice in respect of compliance by the UK with Article VI of the Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198273","198273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50417","2014-05-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what level of representation the UK will have at the humanitarian effects of nuclear weapons war conference being hosted by the Austrian government in December 2014.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198274","198274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50418","2014-05-14","Women and Equalities","2014-05-08","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, when the Government plans to introduce regulations under the Equalities Act to prevent discrimination by caste and descent.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198276","198276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50419","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 17 September 2012, Official Report, column 512W, on torture, what the result of the audit was; if she will publish the audit; what training requirements were identified by the audit; whether that training has been delivered; if she will publish the training materials; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198158","198158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50420","2014-05-13","Department for Education","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were on child protection plans in each Greater Manchester local authority area in the last three years for which data is available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198220","198220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50421","2014-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the arrest of Mario Masuku in Swaziland.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198215","198215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50422","2014-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will instruct HM High Commissioner to Swaziland to raise the case of Mario Masuku and the Zakhele Remand Centre with the Swaziland government.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198204","198204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50423","2014-05-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports the Government has received on the Zakhele Remand Centre in Swaziland.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198164","198164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50424","2014-05-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government will publish the National Pollinator Strategy: for bees and other pollinators in England.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198238","198238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50425","2014-05-13","Department of Health","2014-05-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 April 2014, Official Report, column 461W, on NHS: insolvency, when he plans to place in the Library the minutes of the meeting on 2 April 2014.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198242","198242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50043","2014-05-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of the work done on the Kajaki Dam project in Afghanistan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198096","198096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50044","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of deaths from (a) liver disease and (b) viral hepatitis which were preventable in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198103","198103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50045","2014-05-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel were in the Army Cadets in Northern Ireland on 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197992","197992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50046","2014-05-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel were in the Sea Cadets in Northern Ireland on 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197993","197993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50047","2014-05-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make representations to the BBC Trust in support of publishing the salaries of all BBC staff earning more than £100,000 per annum.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198045","198045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50048","2014-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance he has offered to the Nigerian authorities to resolve the continued abduction of girls from the North East of that country.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197989","197989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50049","2014-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of the involvement of the Somali group al Shabaab in attacks in Kenya.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197990","197990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50050","2014-05-12","Department for International Development","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will raise at the UN the prospects of severe famine in South Sudan.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197991","197991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50051","2014-05-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies on voluntary restrictions by network providers of adult content of recent proposals from the European Parliament on a European single market for electronic communications.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198046","198046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50052","2014-05-20","Department for Transport","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department has allocated to local authorities for road repairs in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Alun Cairns","Alun Cairns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198146","198146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50053","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to include financial capability education in the national curriculum; and what guidance his Department has issued on such education.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198136","198136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50054","2014-05-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to implement the recommendations of the Arts on Prescription 2010-2012 report produced by the charity Arts & Minds.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197995","197995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50055","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average compensation payment to people of each gender was ordered in employment tribunal cases relating to claims of discrimination on the grounds of sex in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198087","198087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50056","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest compensation payment ordered in employment tribunal cases relating to discrimination on the grounds of (a) sex, (b) disability, (c) religion, (d) sexual orientation, (e) age and (f) race was in each of the last five years; and if he will list the nature of the complaint upheld in each case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198068","198068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50057","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average compensation payment ordered in employment tribunal cases relating to discrimination on the grounds of race was, by ethnicity of complainant, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198069","198069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50058","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average compensation payment ordered in employment tribunal cases relating to discrimination on the grounds of religion was by the religious belief of the complainant in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198070","198070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50059","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of cases costs have been awarded to an employer following an unsuccessful claim being brought against them at each stage of the proceedings at an employment tribunal in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198065","198065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50060","2014-05-12","Department for International Development","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much the UK plans to give to the Global Partnership for Education at its next funding round.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198097","198097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50061","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what technology he plans to use to restrict the sharing of NHS patient data extracted under care.data to countries inside the European Economic Area.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198108","198108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50062","2014-05-12","Department for International Development","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to encourage all UK clothing companies which use suppliers in Bangladesh to join the Accord on Fire and Building Safety in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198109","198109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50063","2014-05-12","HM Treasury","2014-05-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will undertake a review of the effectiveness of the Debt Relief (Developing Countries) Act 2010 in preventing the use of the English legal system by vulture funds to extract funds from developing countries.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198104","198104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50064","2014-05-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 1 May 2014, Official Report, column 791W, on fossil fuels: imports, how much in thousand tonnes of (a) oil and (b) gas was (i) exported from and (ii) imported to the UK in 2012 and 2013.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198118","198118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50065","2014-05-12","Cabinet Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much has been spent on the Digital Services Framework in each month to date; and what proportion of such spending was with small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198052","198052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50066","2014-05-12","Cabinet Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of (a) digital and (b) Agile skill in (i) his Department and (ii) other Government departments; and if he will make it his policy to report on digital skills in departmental reporting plans.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198053","198053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50067","2014-05-12","Cabinet Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many Agile coach positions there are in his Department; and how many such posts are filled by (a) permanent and (b) contract staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198054","198054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50068","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any (a) internal and (b) external reports were commissioned by Serco in relation to any steps taken by HM Prison Thameside to eliminate race discrimination in the workplace.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198094","198094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50069","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employment tribunal cases were presented on the grounds of race discrimination in HM Prison Thameside in the last three years; what the nature was of each complaint; when each such tribunal began and ended; what the outcome was in each such case; and what the cost to the public purse was of defending such cases.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198086","198086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50070","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many grievances on the grounds of race discrimination have been made in HM Prison Thameside in the last three years; what the nature was of each such grievance; when each grievance was made and resolved; and what the outcome was in each case.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198085","198085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50071","2014-05-12","HM Treasury","2014-05-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he will take to implement the Fourth Anti-Money Laundering Directive; and what plans he has to distinguish between high and low risk trusts.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198101","198101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50072","2014-05-12","Cabinet Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what basis the Government calculates entitlement to holiday pay for civil servants.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198115","198115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50073","2014-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will introduce legislative proposals that employers be required to calculate holiday pay solely by reference to standard contract hours.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198114","198114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50074","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse was of interpretation services provided to the (a) magistrates' courts and (b) Crown Court in England and Wales in each of the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198150","198150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50075","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign nationals from (a) the EU and (b) countries outside the EU have been defendants in the (i) magistrates courts and (ii) Crown courts in England and Wales in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198112","198112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50076","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of defendants being held in custody pending trial are foreign nationals.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198113","198113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50077","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many calls were made to the National Domestic Violence Helpline in 2013; and how many such calls mentioned use of (a) any weapon and (b) a firearm.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198132","198132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50078","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of incidents of domestic violence involving a legally owned (a) firearm and (b) airgun in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198133","198133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50079","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of air rifles in the UK.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198134","198134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50080","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on (a) the number of companies that provide indemnity insurance for nurses and midwives and (b) the policies that are available for this.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198141","198141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50081","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assistance his Department provides for small independent schools making applications for free school status; and if he will take steps to increase such assistance.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198078","198078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50082","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to increase the required contributions to NHS pensions before the introduction of the new pension scheme in 2015.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198084","198084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50083","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that a proportion of any future underspend within the NHS is allocated to nurses' pay.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198082","198082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50084","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the pay of community staff nurses rises in line with inflation.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198081","198081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50085","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many new members of (a) staff and (b) nursing staff have been taken on by the NHS in North Herefordshire in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198083","198083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50086","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will discuss with (a) the Whitbourne Independent School and Hub and (b) other projects whose applications for free school status were turned down those applicants' feedback on how the application process can be made easier for small independent schools.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198079","198079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50087","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to give free schools more flexibility on requirements relating to (a) the involvement of volunteers and (b) provision of flexi-school places.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198080","198080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50088","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in North Herefordshire have unsuccessfully applied for free school status.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198057","198057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50089","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications for free school status for which the Church of England has agreed to provide school premises have been (a) approved and (b) rejected.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198038","198038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50090","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the average length of time between an application for free school status being made and a successful applicant school opening; and what plans he has to reduce the time taken.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198056","198056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50091","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress he has made on making the process for school leaving local education authority control to become free schools easier.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198076","198076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50092","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many applications for free school status from applicants which already have premises have been refused.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198077","198077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50093","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place a copy of the Beloff Review on UK asset recovery in the Library.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198036","198036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50094","2014-05-14","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answers of 30 April 2014, Official Report, column 717W and of 14 January 2014, Official Report, column 481W, on human trafficking: victim support schemes, for what reason the gender and location of each individual is not included in the information for February 2014; and if she will provide this information for future questions on the subject.","Biography information for Angie Bray","Angie Bray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198075","198075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50095","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April 2014, Official Report, column 717W, on human trafficking: victim support schemes, how many of those referred were (a) men and (b) women; what steps are taken to ensure that after victims leave the shelter into which they have been placed by the Salvation Army they are not re-trafficked and do not contact their former traffickers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angie Bray","Angie Bray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198100","198100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50096","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has allocated to the School Fruit and Vegetable Scheme for the 2014-15 financial year.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198030","198030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50097","2014-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Written Statement of 7 April 2014, Official Report, column 1WS, on higher education (student support), what estimate he has made of how many prospective students will no longer be eligible for the disabled students' allowance once the changes set out in the statement are introduced; and what steps he plans to take to support those prospective students.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198137","198137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50098","2014-05-12","HM Treasury","2014-05-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of (a) directly employed staff and (b) contracted staff in HM Revenue and Customs are paid less than the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198151","198151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50099","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which local authorities have withdrawn from the School Fruit and Vegetable Scheme to date.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198050","198050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50100","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in which local authorities 30 per cent or more pupils entitled to free school meals are not claiming them; and what steps he is taking to improve the take-up of free school meals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198051","198051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50101","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the performance of the School Food Plan in increasing healthy breakfast provision in more deprived areas; and how much had been spent on this programme by April 2014.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198049","198049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50102","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent on the Universal Jobmatch programme between (a) April and September 2012, (b) October 2012 and March 2013, (c) April and September 2013, (d) October 2013 and March 2014 and (e) April and September 2014.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198055","198055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50103","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the recent study by City University, London and the Nuffield Foundation of deaf children in the education system; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198139","198139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50104","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information-sharing systems his Department recommends agencies  to use in respect of sharing information regarding vulnerable children and children at risk.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198098","198098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50105","2014-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help find the 230 Nigerian schoolgirls kidnapped by Boko Haram; and whether the UK will commit military aid to the search effort if required.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198005","198005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50106","2014-05-12","HM Treasury","2014-05-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has undertaken any work to assess how many jobs in the UK are dependent on trade with the EU.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198142","198142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50107","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers left Prison Service employment within (a) six months, (b) one year and (c) two years of becoming an officer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198003","198003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50108","2014-05-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much financial support his Department provided to Hope not Hate in each of the last three years; and what steps he takes to prevent the use of such monies for party political campaigning.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198044","198044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50109","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what research her Department has undertaken on the relationship between levels of street lighting and the incidence of (a) burglaries, (b) offences against the person and (c) other crimes.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197999","197999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50110","2014-05-12","Department for Transport","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department has undertaken on the relationship between levels of street lighting and (a) road traffic accidents and (b) injuries to pedestrians.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198000","198000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50111","2014-05-12","HM Treasury","2014-05-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has paid to Mapeley STEPS Contractor Limited since the sale of HM Revenue and Customs' estate to that company.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198041","198041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50112","2014-05-15","HM Treasury","2014-05-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to tackle aggressive tax avoidance.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198067","198067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50113","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date the speed camera at Thorney Toll on the A47 was re-activated; and how many motorists have been detected as travelling in excess of the 60 mph speed limit at Thorney Toll since that date.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198037","198037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50114","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he last met the Chair of the College of Emergency Medicine; what subjects were discussed at that meeting; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198029","198029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50115","2014-05-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will discuss with London Zoo the (a) size of the lion enclosure and (b) general animal welfare standards at that zoo.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198064","198064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50116","2014-05-12","Cabinet Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people died from cold-related causes in the winter of (a) 2012-13 and (b) 2013-14.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198092","198092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50117","2014-05-12","Cabinet Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people died from heat-related causes in the summer of (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198095","198095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50118","2014-05-12","HM Treasury","2014-05-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his most recent planning assumption is for the last date on which new claims for working tax credit will be accepted.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197998","197998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50119","2014-05-12","HM Treasury","2014-05-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many requests for annual PAYE status have been received in each month since the introduction of PAYE Real Time Information; and how many such requests in each such month have been granted.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198002","198002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50120","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his most recent estimate is of the date on which the last new claims will be made for jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198001","198001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50121","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress he has made in implementing the Simple Payment initiative; how many people use it; and what steps he has taken to ensure its resilience.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197994","197994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50122","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how long tenants who move from direct payment of housing support to managed payment because they have eight weeks of rent arrears will be allowed to stay on managed payment before they revert to direct payment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198004","198004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50123","2014-05-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Cabinet Secretary for Education and Lifelong Learning in Scotland on the use of zero-hour contracts in Scottish education establishments.","Biography information for Jim Sheridan","Jim Sheridan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198063","198063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50124","2014-05-12","Northern Ireland Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many of the Royal Prerogative of Mercy certificates issued by her Department in the last 30 years have been issued to people accused of terrorism-related offences.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198119","198119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50125","2014-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the threat to human rights defenders and journalists in Honduras.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198025","198025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50126","2014-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the President of Honduras about human rights abuses in Honduras.","Biography information for Andy Sawford","Andy Sawford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198026","198026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50127","2014-05-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the replacement of the fuel tanks at the oil fuel depot in Gosport is scheduled to take place.","Biography information for Caroline Dinenage","Caroline Dinenage","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198028","198028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50128","2014-05-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what comparative assessment he has made of superfast broadband coverage in (a) Hampshire and (b) other counties in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198022","198022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50129","2014-05-12","Department for Transport","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been invested in road infrastructure in (a) Portsmouth South constituency and (b) Hampshire in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198023","198023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50130","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people on (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance have moved from the Work Programme to Work Choice in (a) Portsmouth South constituency and (b) Hampshire in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198021","198021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50131","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Portsmouth South constituency and (b) Hampshire who applied to the jobseeker's allowance hardship regime were (i) successful and (ii) unsuccessful in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198024","198024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50132","2014-05-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to commemorate the 70th Anniversary of VE Day in 2015.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198122","198122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50133","2014-05-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to commemorate the 70th Anniversary of VE Day in 2015.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198123","198123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50134","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who owns data on police information notices issued by police services in England and Wales.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198127","198127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50135","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police information notices were issued in England and Wales, by constabulary area, in each of the last five years; and how many such notices have been revoked.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198126","198126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50136","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance is issued by (a) her Department, (b) ACPO and (c) the College of Policing to ensure consistency of practice in the issuing of police information notices by police services.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198128","198128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50137","2014-05-12","Women and Equalities","2014-05-07","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, whether his Department will attend the International Day against Homophobia and Transphobia Forum 2014 in Valletta.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198074","198074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50138","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what underspend there has been on the Youth Contract scheme; and how any such underspend has been used.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198110","198110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50139","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will meet the hon. Member for Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland to discuss recent developments in South Tees NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198124","198124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50140","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on demand for accident and emergency services at James Cook University Hospital of the proposed closure of minor injuries units at (a) East Cleveland and (b) Guisborough hospitals.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198111","198111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50141","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of policing of demonstrations and parades in London.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198088","198088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50142","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officers have been seconded to the Police Service of Northern Ireland from police forces in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198090","198090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50143","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in England and Wales have been arrested following the issue of a warrant by the Police Service of Northern Ireland in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198089","198089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50144","2014-05-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on the potential for growth in tourism as a result of the opening stages of the Giro d'Italia taking place in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198091","198091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50145","2014-05-12","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-05-07","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what consultation there has been with charities in Northern Ireland on the Electoral Commission's guidance on the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198135","198135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50146","2014-05-12","Northern Ireland Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of her Department's policies to combat the glorification of terrorism in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198062","198062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50147","2014-05-12","Northern Ireland Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many meetings she has had with the (a) Northern Ireland Human Rights Commission, (b) Northern Ireland Parades Commission and (c) Equality Commission for Northern Ireland since 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198099","198099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50148","2014-05-12","Northern Ireland Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what contribution her Department made towards the cost of the staging of the Giro d'Italia in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198093","198093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50149","2014-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department provides to non-governmental organisations working in Vietnam to combat child trafficking and to help repatriated victims of trafficking.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197996","197996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50150","2014-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Vietnamese counterpart on preventing child trafficking from that country to the UK.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 197997","197997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50151","2014-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with (a) the Sultan of Brunei or (b) his representatives on the introduction of sharia criminal law in Brunei.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198032","198032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50152","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2014, Official Report, column 346W, on private investigations, when the terms and conditions for private investigator licences will be published.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198138","198138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50153","2014-05-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect on the UK's relationship with Bangladesh of the activities in the UK of Tareque Rahman, Vice Chairman of the Bangladesh Nationalist Party.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198033","198033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50154","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the immigration status is of Tareque Rahman, Vice Chairman of the Bangladesh Nationalist Party.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198034","198034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50155","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which people from Wales responded to the consultation on the relaxation of licensing hours during the 2014 FIFA World Cup.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198131","198131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50156","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which protocols are used in hospitals for withdrawal treatment following long and short-term use of benzodiaepines and Z-drugs.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198059","198059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50157","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department takes to prevent to over-prescribing of psychotropic drugs in hospitals.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198058","198058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50158","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data his Department collects on prescriptions dispensed to prisoners.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198140","198140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50159","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to prevent over-prescribing or mis-prescribing of psychotropic drugs to prisoners.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198060","198060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50160","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which protocols are used in prisons for withdrawal of treatment following long and short-term use of benzodiazepines and Z-drugs.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198061","198061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50161","2014-05-12","Department for Transport","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance on the procurement process is available to companies wishing to bid for work on the High Speed 2 project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198040","198040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50162","2014-05-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to reply to Question 191523, on homeless households, tabled by the hon. Member for Westminster North on 11 March 2014.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198152","198152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50163","2014-05-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to reply to Questions 191722, 191723, 191726, 191727, 191728, 191729, 191730 and 191731, on homeless households, tabled by the hon. Member for Westminster North on 12 March 2014.","Biography information for Ms Karen Buck","Ms Karen Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198153","198153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50164","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what advance estimate he made of the number of students enrolled in (a) school sixth forms, (b) academy sixth forms and (c) 16 to 19 years free schools estabished since September 2011 in 2012-13; and what the number of students was in each case.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198071","198071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50165","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost was of student places that were not filled in (a) school sixth forms, (b) academy sixth forms and (c) 16 to 19 free schools estabished since September 2011 in 2012-13.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198072","198072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50166","2014-05-12","Department for Education","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department will publish guidance for sixth form colleges that wish to convert to become 16 to 19 academies.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198073","198073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50167","2014-05-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will provide details of the projects supported by the Armed Forces Covenant (LIBOR) Fund since its inception; and how much funding has been given to each of those projects.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198149","198149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50168","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking and what budget he has allocated to help tackle youth unemployment in (a) Barnsley and (b) South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198129","198129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50169","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what ambulance response times were in each local authority area in the Yorkshire and the Humber region in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198043","198043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50170","2014-05-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what operational contingency plans he has made for future capability requirements in the event of further flooding.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198125","198125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50171","2014-05-12","Cabinet Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new jobs have been created in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013 in (i) Barnsley central constituency, (ii) Yorkshire and the Humber and (iii) England.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198130","198130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50172","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will invite the Sentencing Council to consult and report on the adequacy of current sentences available for killing with one punch.","Biography information for Nick de Bois","Nick de Bois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198154","198154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50173","2014-05-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what evidence there is of contamination of the bacterial pathogen, Melissoccocus plutonius, from countries within the EU.","Biography information for Simon Reevell","Simon Reevell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198102","198102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50174","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average ambulance response time for each category of call was in Warrington in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198047","198047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50175","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, by how much each ambulance trust in England underspent or overspent their budget in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198048","198048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50176","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to raise public awareness of transient ischaemic attacks (TIAs) and of the need to seek immediate treatment for TIAs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198145","198145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50177","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward proposals for regulations to ensure that ME and chronic fatigue syndrome are included in all pre- and post-registration training of (a) GPs and (b) other healthcare professionals.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198120","198120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50178","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to improve information and support for GPs regarding ME or chronic fatigue syndrome; and if he will take steps to improve access to specialist services for people with those conditions.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198121","198121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50179","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support is in place to help people with ME or chronic fatigue syndrome who are well enough to consider a return to work.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198031","198031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50180","2014-05-12","Department of Health","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to social care assessments for people with ME or chronic fatigue syndrome.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198039","198039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50181","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that specialist training on (a) ME or chronic fatigue syndrome and (b) other fluctuating conditions is given to healthcare professionals assessing claimants for the personal independence payment.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198106","198106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50182","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress he has made towards achieving his Department's aim of processing 97 per cent of assessments for personal independence payments within 30 days.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198107","198107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50183","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people with ME or chronic fatigue syndrome and their healthcare professionals are (a) helped to access appropriate support and (b) given the correct out of work support.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198105","198105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50184","2014-05-12","Department for International Development","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 6 May 2014, Official Report, column 80W on the Pacific Islands, how much support and under what categories her Department gave directly to Pitcairn Island in 2013-14.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198148","198148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50185","2014-05-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the letter of 30 April 2014 from the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government to the chairmen of fire and rescue authorities and the Chairman of the Local Government Association's Fire Service Management Committee, if he will put forward the revised proposals for consideration by firefighters and the Fire Brigades Union.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198066","198066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50186","2014-05-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make an assessment of the British Medical Journal editorial Public Health England's draft report on shale gas extraction: Mistaking best practices for actual practices published on 17 April 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198116","198116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50187","2014-05-12","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will discuss the potential health risks of fracking with (a) medical professionals and (b) the Secretary of State for Health; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198117","198117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50188","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) mean and (b) median number is of half-day sittings at magistrates' courts in the last year.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198018","198018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50189","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of half-day sittings in the Youth Court by members of the Youth Court Bench was in the last year.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198019","198019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50190","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many magistrates sat more than 70 half days in the last year.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198010","198010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50191","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total number of sittings was by magistrates who sat more than 70 half days in the last year.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198011","198011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50192","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many magistrates were recruited in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198012","198012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50193","2014-05-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the annual cost is of the (a) administration of advisory committees, (b) HM Courts and Tribunals Service staff servicing such committees and (c) training and recruiting members of such committees.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198013","198013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50194","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has issued guidance to Atos on how to prioritise work capability assessments between reassessments and new claimants for employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198027","198027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50195","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether Atos staff have been offered any additional retention or performance-related payments since the decision to terminate the contract to carry out work capability assessments was announced.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198014","198014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50196","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what funding will be provided to local authorities after June 2016 to support former Independent Living Fund users.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198015","198015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50197","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work capability assessment reassessments were undertaken by Atos in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198016","198016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50198","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of recipients of the Independent Living Fund who will move into residential care following closure of the Fund.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198017","198017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50199","2014-05-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work capability assessments for new claims were undertaken by Atos in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198020","198020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50201","2014-05-12","Home Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officials are employed in her Department's Human Trafficking Unit; what the purpose of the unit is; and what the role is of each such official.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198147","198147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50202","2014-05-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many conversions of office premises to housing have been notified to him since the lifting of planning approval requirements for such conversions; and how many social housing units have been included in such conversions.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198144","198144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50203","2014-05-12","Department for Transport","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department has undertaken into (a) the safety effectiveness of voice warnings on freight vehicles reversing, (b) the extent of noise pollution arising from such warnings and (c) the potential benefits of introducing visually triggered automatic systems for giving warnings.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198143","198143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50204","2014-05-12","Cabinet Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, appointments to which public bodies and offices to which Ministers make appointments are not regulated by the Commissioner for Public Appointments, by appointing Minister.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198035","198035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50205","2014-05-12","Cabinet Office","2014-05-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what criteria are used to decide which public bodies and offices are regulated by the Commissioner for Public Appointments.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198042","198042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50206","2014-05-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of (a) the economic effect on and (b) changes in tourism revenue in Southend as a result of the closure of East Beach in Shoeburyness for his Department to survey for unexploded ordnance.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198006","198006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50207","2014-05-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timescale is for his Department to (a) survey East Beach in Shoeburyness for unexploded ordnance and (b) carry out remedial works.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198007","198007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50208","2014-05-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how long his Department expects East Beach in Shoeburyness to be closed.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198008","198008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50209","2014-05-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that East Beach in Shoeburyness is surveyed for any unexploded ordnance and that remedial works are carried out as a matter of urgency.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 198009","198009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50381","2014-05-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-05-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support the Government is giving to small and medium-sized businesses in Cumbria.","Biography information for Rory Stewart","Rory Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903988","903988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50542","2014-05-13","Attorney General","2014-05-07","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he has taken to improve prosecution of wildlife crime.","Biography information for Mr David Heath","Mr David Heath","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 904021","904021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50547","2014-05-13","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-07","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether he has reviewed the efficacy of the guidance of the Electoral Commission on referendums; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903992","903992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50622","2014-05-13","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-07","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps the Government is taking to raise the number of people registered to vote.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903990","903990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/50623","2014-05-13","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-05-07","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what support the Government is giving to business growth opportunities in Basildon and Thurrock.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 903986","903986"
