"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843606","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the Government's proposed energy price cap on the smart meter roll-out.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127947","127947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843607","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what business model his Department will use in determining the level of the proposed energy price cap.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127948","127948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843608","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish details of the business model his Department used to determine the pre-payment meter energy price cap.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127949","127949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843609","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations his Department has received from businesses on the effect on investment of the proposed removal of appeals from the Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill to an expert body.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127950","127950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843610","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his department has made an assessment of the potential effect of banning standard variable tariffs on (a) customer engagement (b) switching rates and (c) reducing the differentials between the highest and lowest tariffs.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127951","127951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843611","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of using distributed energy systems across the defence estate.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127952","127952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843612","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps the Government is taking to reduce energy costs across the defence estate.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127953","127953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843613","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish a breakdown by site of energy costs across the defence estate.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127954","127954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843614","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of deploying distributed energy resources across the NHS estate.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127955","127955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843615","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to reduce energy costs across the NHS estate.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127956","127956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843616","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will set out energy costs across the NHS estate.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127957","127957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843617","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will set out the usage of diesel generators be each NHS trust in the most recent 12-month period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127958","127958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843618","2018-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has held discussions with his counterpart in the Australian Government on the detention of two UK citizens from Edinburgh East by the Australian Border Force following the letter from the hon. Member for Edinburgh East of 16 January 2018.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127959","127959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843619","2018-02-21","Attorney General","2018-02-19","To ask the Attorney General, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of prosecutions for female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127960","127960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843620","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate her Department has made of the amount of savings that the introduction and roll-out of universal credit will generate for the public purse; and what the evidential basis is for that estimate.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127961","127961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843621","2018-02-21","Women and Equalities","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the timetable is for the publication of the consultation on the Gender Recognition Act 2004.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127962","127962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843622","2018-02-21","Women and Equalities","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on ensuring that the rights of women and other people with protected characteristics under EU law are retained after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127963","127963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843623","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department , what steps the Government is taking to protect women who are experiencing domestic abuse online.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127964","127964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843624","2018-02-21","Women and Equalities","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that companies meet their obligation to report on and produce an action plan to address gender pay gaps by 4 April 2018.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127965","127965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843625","2018-02-21","Women and Equalities","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what penalties are available for companies that fail to report on gender pay gaps by 4 April 2018.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127966","127966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843626","2018-02-21","Women and Equalities","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent steps the Government has taken to increase the representation of women on boards in FTSE 100 companies.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127967","127967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843627","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2017 to Question 118225, on mental illness: children, whether his Department plans to collect such information centrally; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127968","127968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843628","2018-02-21","Department for International Trade","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to Answer of 7 December to Question 118220 on trade agreements; arbitration, which which counterparts in other government departments and existing arms-length bodies his Department held discussions with on the appropriate number of staff needed for the trade remedies authority.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127969","127969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843629","2018-02-21","Department for International Trade","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to Answer of 7 December to Question 118220 on trade agreements: arbitration, which other international systems his Department is reviewing.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127970","127970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843630","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of removing bursaries for nursing, midwifery and most allied health students on the number of people applying to study in each of those areas.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127971","127971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843631","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2017 to Question 107540, on local government: accountability, whether his Department has made any progress on further steps to ensure compliance.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127972","127972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843632","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a compulsory registration scheme for landlords.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127973","127973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843633","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2017 to Question 119798, on adoption, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of collecting such information; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127974","127974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843634","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2017 to Question 120655, on public houses, whether his Department plans to collect that information; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127975","127975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843635","2018-02-22","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the proportion of primary schools that provided the Government's recommended number of hours of swimming tuition in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127976","127976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843636","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the proportion of primary schools in Haringey that provided the Government's recommended number of hours of swimming tuition in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127977","127977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843637","2018-02-22","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the proportion of primary schools in London that provided the Government's recommended number of hours of swimming tuition in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127978","127978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843638","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the recommendations of the 2017 joint report from the Professional Standards Authority and the  Royal Society for Public Health entitled Untapped Resources: Accredited Registers in the Wider Workforce.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127979","127979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843639","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been paid from the public purse in sustainment outcome payments to (a) Capita, (b) Interserve, (c) Ingeus UK Ltd, (d) Careers Development Group and (e) G4S in each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127980","127980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843640","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been paid from the public purse in outcome fees to (a) Capita, (b) Interserve, (c) Ingeus UK Ltd, (d) Careers Development Group and (e) G4S in each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127981","127981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843641","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been paid from the public purse for welfare to work services to (a) Capita, (b) Ingeus UK Ltd, (c) Careers Development Group and (d) G4S in each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127982","127982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843642","2018-02-22","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people with links to the UK who travelled to engage in the recent conflict in Syria and Iraq have been classified as not being a security concern.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127983","127983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843643","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average cost of recruitment to the Army was in each of the last three full years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127984","127984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843644","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average cost per Army recruit was of (a) recruiting and (b) providing Phase 1 training for recruits (i) under 18 years and (ii) 18 years or above in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127985","127985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843645","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average cost per recruit to the Army Foundation College, Harrogate, for non-military training and education was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127986","127986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843646","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of recruits who enlisted aged (a) under 18 and (b) over 18 years left the armed forces before completing (i) phase two training and (ii) the minimum initial service period in each of the last three full years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127987","127987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843647","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, (a) how many  and (b) what proportion of recruits who enlisted aged (i) under 18 and (ii) over 18 years left the armed forces within four years of joining in each of the last three full years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127988","127988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843648","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of armed forces personnel in the trained strength are under 18 years old.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127989","127989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843649","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average length of service is for a soldier who enlists (a) aged over 18 years and (b) below 18 years old.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127990","127990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843650","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average length of service is for an infantry soldier who enlists (a) aged over 18 years and (b) below 18 years old.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127991","127991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843651","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many recruits (a) enlisted at and (b) completed Phase 1 training at (i) AFC Harrogate (ii) ATC Pirbright (iii) ATR Bassingbourn (iv) ITC Catterick in each of the last three full years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127992","127992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843652","2018-02-22","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2018 to Question 126486, on further education: loans, what discussions he or Ministers of his Department have had with the (a) Student Loans Company and (b) Education and Skills Funding Agency on that matter.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127993","127993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843653","2018-02-22","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2018 to Question 126486 on further education: loans, how many learners do not have a new provider.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127994","127994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843654","2018-02-22","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2018 to Question 126486 on further education: loans, what additional resources his Department has allocated to help learners find new providers.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127995","127995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843655","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the outcome was of discussions between his Department, HS2 Ltd and the cycle-proofing working group on HS2 Ltd’s design standards.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127996","127996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843656","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has assessed HS2 Ltd’s design standards for temporary and permanent changes to on-and off-road highway infrastructure against (a) Transport for London’s London cycling design standards and (b) the Welsh Government’s Active Travel (Wales) Act 2013 design standards.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127997","127997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843657","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department’s cycle-proofing working group has identified locations where cycle access along or across the HS2 corridor should be maintained or enhanced.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127998","127998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843658","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps HS2 Ltd has taken to ensure the safety (a) of cyclists in relation to the design of lorries, (b) awareness of lorry drivers and (c) accreditation of lorry operators involved in HS2-related contracts.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127999","127999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843659","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support highway authorities on the HS2 route to provide joined-up cycling infrastructure.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128000","128000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843660","2018-02-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the consultation to review the effectiveness of current enforcement against unauthorised developments and encampments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128001","128001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843661","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many amputations were carried out in Lancashire and South Cumbria as a result of type 2 diabetes in (a)2015, (b) 2016 and c) 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128002","128002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843662","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many amputations were carried out in Kent and Medway as a result of type 2 diabetes in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128003","128003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843663","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many amputations were carried out in North Central London as a result of type 2 diabetes in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128004","128004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843664","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what structured education relating to the Diabetes Transformation Fund has taken place in Leicester; and what plans there are for the future deployment of such education in Leicester.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128005","128005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843665","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has set a timetable for commissioning groups to report back on the effectiveness of the Diabetes Transformation Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128006","128006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843666","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's objectives are for the Diabetes Transformation Fund.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128007","128007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843667","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who will be assisted by the Diabetes Transformation Fund.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128008","128008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843668","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to improve the early diagnosis of lung cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128009","128009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843669","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the reference in the Diabetes Transformation Fund guidelines to variation between clinical commissioning groups refers to; and what the reasons are for such such variation.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128010","128010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843670","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much has been disbursed from the Diabetes Transformation Fund to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128011","128011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843671","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many diabetes specialist nurses have been recruited by each sustainability and transformation partnership as a result of the Diabetes Transformation Fund.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128012","128012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843672","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many diabetic specialist nurses were employed by each sustainability and transformation partnership before the Diabetes Transformation Fund was made available.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128013","128013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843673","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many additional nurses have been trained as a result of the Diabetes Transformation Fund by each sustainability and transformation partnership.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128014","128014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843674","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, where advertisements were placed for the recruitment of diabetic specialist nurses employed by each sustainability partnerships as a result of the Diabetes Transformation Fund.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128015","128015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843675","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how long on average diabetic patients spent in hospital in (a) 205, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128016","128016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843676","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many referrals were made from primary care to multi-disciplinary foot teams for people with diabetic foot disease in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128017","128017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843677","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the announcement by NHS England on 18 December 2017 on new specialised treatments, on which date the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group will meet in May 2018 to consider new recommendations.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128018","128018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843678","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the announcement by NHS England on 18 December 2017 on new specialised treatments, what estimate he has made of the annual expenditure for new medicines approved for funding as a result of the November 2017 prioritisation process.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128019","128019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843679","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance is issued by NHS England to manufacturers on the negotiation of medical outcomes-based commercial agreements for products undergoing review by the specialised commissioning prioritisation process.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128020","128020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843680","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the budget is for the NHS England specialised commissioning prioritisation process in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128021","128021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843681","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department issues to manufacturers of products undergoing review by the NHS England specialised commissioning prioritisation process on the timelines for the reverse auction element of the process.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128022","128022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843682","2018-02-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the merits of combining data on rough sleepers from official night counts with estimates and information from local agencies to improve data accuracy.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128023","128023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843683","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that people and organisations which offer advice on changes to the Support for Mortgage Interest scheme are appropriately qualified and regulated.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128024","128024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843684","2018-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions officials in his Department have had with Mexican officials on the implementation of the new general law on disappearances.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128025","128025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843685","2018-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has assessed the potential merits of introducing a new criminal offence of theft of a pet.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128027","128027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843686","2018-02-22","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an impact assessment of its plans to discontinue funding for specialist speech, language and communication support.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128028","128028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843687","2018-02-22","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date he expects (a) the UK to be reviewed by the Financial Action Task Force and (b) the results of that review to be published.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128029","128029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843688","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on the affordability of access to justice for women escaping domestic abuse; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128030","128030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843689","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many support for mortgage interest claimants have (a) Parkinson's disease and (b) multiple sclerosis.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128026","128026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843691","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department is taking steps to ensure UK goods continue to enjoy EU protected food name status after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128186","128186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843692","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent reforms to legal aid on access to justice for women escaping domestic abuse; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128034","128034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843693","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his oral answer of 6 February 2018, Official Report, column 1351,  in which document di the King's Fund state that accountable care organisations and integrated care systems make a massive difference in care to patients.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128036","128036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843694","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to comply with the Waste Electric and Electronic Equipment Regulations and to reduce the wastage of goods.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128038","128038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843695","2018-02-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-02-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps the Commission is taking to comply with the Waste Electric and Electronic Equipment Regulations and to reduce the wastage by the House of goods covered by those regulations.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128041","128041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843696","2018-02-21","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse has been of the operation of the (a) Share Incentive Plan and (b) Save As You Earn all -employee share schemes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128043","128043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843697","2018-02-21","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of postponing the implementation of the Save As You Earn contributions holiday change scheduled to begin on 6 April 2018 to allow a longer preparatory period for the share plan industry to undertake IT and software changes and testing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128045","128045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843698","2018-02-21","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether proposals to increase the contributions holiday for Save As You Earn schemes from six to 12 months will apply to all employees who miss their payment contributions.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128047","128047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843699","2018-02-21","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings he has had with representatives of the UK's share plan industry to discuss the proposed increase in the contributions holiday for Save As You Earn schemes from six to 12 months.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128049","128049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843700","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department is making an assessment of the potential merits of providing support for consultants who wish to work flexibly beyond retirement age; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128051","128051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843701","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on responding to the recommendations of the Shape of Training review of October 2013.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128053","128053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843702","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that consultants have adequate protected time to support and mentor junior doctors.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128055","128055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843703","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on ensuring that overseas junior doctors are able to have access to tier 2 visas.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128057","128057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843704","2018-02-22","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many social care providers HMRC has written to in respect of such providers about allegedly underpaying minimum wage rates for sleep-in shifts; and how many of those providers have since opted into the Social Care Compliance Scheme.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128059","128059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843705","2018-02-22","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many social care providers have opted into the Social Care Compliance Scheme; how much money owed to workers has been identified through that scheme; and what estimate has been made of what that sum of money represents as a proportion of the total amount of money owed in sleep-in shift payments.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128060","128060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843706","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding from the public purse has been set aside to support care providers in funding the (a) historical capital costs and (b) ongoing revenue costs of complying with the tribunal ruling on sleep-in payments and the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128062","128062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843707","2018-02-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-02-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2018 to Question 125385, what the reason is for Parliament's general waste not being separated; and whether the Commission plans to take steps to ensure that such waste is separated in order to ensure compliance with the demands of the waste hierarchy.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128064","128064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843708","2018-02-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-02-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what the process and manner of disposal is for Parliament's (a) food waste and (b) unused packaged food.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128065","128065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843709","2018-02-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-02-19","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, to which incineration facility Parliament's general waste is sent.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128066","128066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843710","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking  to support British digital and cloud services its companies through procurement policies.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128067","128067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843711","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking in its procurement policy to tackle aggressive tax avoidance by government suppliers.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128069","128069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843712","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the volume of UK citizens’ data held by companies (a) supplying cloud services to Government and (b) contracted to deliver cloud services on behalf of Government that is subject to information requests from US Government bodies.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128071","128071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843713","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether it is Government policy to award cloud hosting contracts only to US hyperscale cloud providers; how many and what proportion of Government cloud hosting contracts have been awarded to hyperscale cloud providers and what the value was of those contracts in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128074","128074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843714","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2018 to Question 124937, if she will create a web page with information for employers wishing to employ refugees; and if she will include (a) information on the right of refugees to work in the UK, (b) the difference between the rights of asylum seekers and those of refugees, (c) a link to the check a biometric residence permit web page, (d) a link to the employer checking service web page, and (e) guidelines on the documentation needed to prove refugee status on that web page.","Biography information for Mrs Kemi Badenoch","Mrs Kemi Badenoch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128076","128076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843715","2018-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many operational ration packs have been disposed of in each of the last five years and what the total tonnage is of those packs.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128079","128079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843716","2018-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of providing surplus ration packs to homeless people.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128083","128083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843717","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of F-35’s ready for operations.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128085","128085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843718","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many hours of flight time have been recorded by UK F-35’s (a) in total and (b) per plane.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128088","128088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843719","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of the UK F-35 fleet are (a) in the US and (b) operating out of UK bases.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128091","128091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843720","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of patients who (a) had heart attacks, (b) needed hospitalising as a result of heart problems and (c) had fatal heart incidents after their heart procedures were postponed in the last twelve months.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128093","128093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843721","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to tackle telephone banking fraud.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128097","128097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843722","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support collaboration between banks and police banking fraud teams on tracing funds obtained through telephone banking fraud.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128100","128100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843723","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he intends to bring forward legislative proposals to reduce the success of telephone banking scams.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128103","128103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843724","2018-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department is conducting a review of the potential effects on the economy of (a) amending and (b) removing existing EU-derived employment regulations.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128106","128106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843725","2018-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has assessed the proportion of the judiciary who attended private school.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128110","128110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843726","2018-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the judiciary is female.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128113","128113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843727","2018-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of judicial selection panels were gender balanced in 2016.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128117","128117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843728","2018-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of judicial selection panels included at least one Black, Asian or Minority Ethnic member in 2016.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128121","128121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843729","2018-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to increase judicial diversity.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128124","128124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843730","2018-02-21","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy's press release of 7 February 2018 on the Government recovering £11 million in minimum wage arrears for 98,000 workers, how much of that sum was then paid to those workers; and how many of those workers received in full the minimum wage arrears owed to them.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128127","128127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843731","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to review the cost and supply of wood pellets in relation to Renewable Heat Incentive tariffs.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128130","128130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843732","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the news release Wood Pellet Shortages, published by UK Pellet Council on 18 January 2018, whether his Department plans to adjust the Renewable Heat Incentive (RHI) tariff for biomass boilers installed under the RHI scheme.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128133","128133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843733","2018-02-22","Department for International Trade","2018-02-19","To as the Secretary of State for International Trade, which national delegations the Government invited to the annual security and policing event; and of those delegations, how many representatives attended in each year from 2010-2017.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128137","128137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843734","2018-02-22","Department for International Trade","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many journalists his Department invited to the annual security and policing event in each year from 2010-2017 and for which publications or broadcasters those journalists worked.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128140","128140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843735","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve (a) rail and (b) bus links in (i) Jarrow constituency, (ii) South Tyneside, (iii) Tyne and Wear and (iv) the North East.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128143","128143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843736","2018-02-22","Department for International Trade","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many escort officers for international delegates his Department employed, from where those officers were recruited and what the grade or rank each officer was for the security and policing event in each year from 2010 to 2017.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128147","128147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843737","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average net weekly household income was for people in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East, (d) London, (e) the South East, (f) England and (g) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128150","128150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843738","2018-02-22","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many representatives from the British police attended the Security and Policing Event in each year since 2010; and what were their ranks and grades.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128153","128153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843739","2018-02-22","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what national delegations the College of Policing and its predecessor body supported with training, advice or consultancy at the annual Security and Policing Event in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128155","128155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843740","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to promote (a) commercial and (b) military shipbuilding in the North East.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128159","128159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843741","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many state school teachers in England have not had Qualified Teacher Status in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East, and (d) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128161","128161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843742","2018-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people started to receive statutory (a) paternity pay and (b) shared parental pay since April 2015.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128165","128165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843743","2018-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British nationals were seconded to EU military and civilian missions and operations, in which countries those missions were located and by which EU treaty those missions were created, in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128168","128168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843744","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of staff who will be employed by the New Futures Network on 1 April 2018.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128171","128171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843745","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her Department’s estates proposals of 26 January 2017, what progress has been made on the proposal for a back-of-house acquisition in Glasgow.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128175","128175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843746","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2018 to Question 126490, what contingency arrangements have been put in place to deal with a similar situation after the closure of Parkhead and Easterhouse jobcentres.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128178","128178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843747","2018-02-22","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, the (a) number and (b) location of new mobile sites under the Emergency Services Network contract that will be constructed in North Ayrshire and Arran constituency; how many of those sites have gained planning approval; how many sites in that same area have entered the build phase; how many sites in that same area were live as of 1 February 2018; how many sites in that same area are being built with the capacity for multi-occupancy; and how many sites in that same area have a confirmed second tenant.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128181","128181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843748","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, the (a) number and (b) location of mobile sites EE will build using state aid under the Emergency Services Network contract in North Ayrshire and Arran constituency; how many such sites have received planning approval; how many such sites have entered the build phase; how many such sites were live as of 1 February 2018; how many such sites are being built with the capacity for multi-occupancy; how many such sites have a confirmed second tenant; and how much money from the public purse has been allocated for each such site.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128184","128184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843749","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the level of increased footfall at Shettleston Jobcentre resulting from the closure of Bridgeton, Parkhead and Easterhouse jobcentres.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128187","128187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843750","2018-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the total budget was for the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate in each year from 2007-2008 to 2016-2017.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128188","128188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843751","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the international community's commitment to the Ottawa Mine Ban Treaty.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128189","128189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843752","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of live land mines laid by the British Army that are present in former war zones.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128190","128190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843753","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to train the security forces of the Yemini Government in landmine disarmament.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128191","128191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843754","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the number of landmines in Yemen.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128192","128192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843755","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has a target for the reduction of single use plastics.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128193","128193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843756","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Departments holds on the volume of plastic waste from the recycling facilities in Hertfordshire that has been sent to (a) landfill, (b) incineration, (c) energy recovery and (d) exported abroad.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128194","128194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843757","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to increase funding for HIV support services.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128195","128195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843758","2018-02-22","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what records her Department holds on the number of incidents in each of the last five years in which a member of the public has been injured by a used needle.","Biography information for Mr Simon Clarke","Mr Simon Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128196","128196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843759","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of changing support for mortgage interest to a loan on the take-up of other housing benefits.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128197","128197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843760","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of people who participate in the Home Ownership for people with Long-term Disabilities scheme who will be affected by the replacement of support for mortgage interest with a loan.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128198","128198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843761","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will set out the number of claimants of support for mortgage interest in each region of England and Wales in the most recent 12-month period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128199","128199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843762","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in receipt of support for mortgage interest had a property repossessed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128200","128200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843763","2018-02-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of the proposed future Dorset local government review.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128201","128201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843764","2018-02-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of the Future Dorset Proposal.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128202","128202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843765","2018-02-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the average cost to the public purse of local authority mergers in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128203","128203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843766","2018-02-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy that local referenda take place in advance of local authority mergers.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128204","128204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843767","2018-02-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the EU on retaining non-UK EU doctors after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128205","128205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843768","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to support the recruitment by the NHS of doctors from the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128206","128206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843769","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to increase awareness of the dangers of obesity in children and young people in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128207","128207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843770","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to encourage the use of quick build, flat pack homes for social and affordable housing.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128208","128208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843771","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many female asylum-seekers are housed in mixed-sex accommodation.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128209","128209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843772","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve the accessibility of railways, buses, coaches and trams for small children.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128210","128210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843773","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to increase support for victims of crime in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128211","128211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843774","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to deter people from committing minor offences in Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128212","128212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843775","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Chinese Government on (a) the status of and (b) human rights in Tibet.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128213","128213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843776","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether (a) Phalanx CIWS and (b) light gun mounts on board HMS OCEAN will be donated to Queen Elizabeth class carriers or other Royal Navy vessels once that vessel is decommissioned.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128214","128214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843777","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding was allocated to each clinical commissioning group area in London per head of population in 2017-18; what funding is proposed to be so allocated in 2018-19; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128215","128215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843778","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons provide prisoners with their possessions in a holdall on release.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128216","128216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843779","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights record of the Government of Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128217","128217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843780","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help ensure that the Sri Lankan Government observes UN Human Rights Council Resolution 30/1 on promoting reconciliation, accountability and human rights in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128218","128218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843781","2018-02-21","Department for International Trade","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that arms sold to the Government of Sri Lanka are not used to perpetrate human rights violations in that country.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128219","128219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843782","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to prevent unsustainable bids being accepted in Government procurement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128220","128220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843783","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Government websites were affected by the recent hack which used websites to mine cryptocurrency.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128221","128221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843784","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when her Department plans to publish the evaluation of the yellow card sanctions pilot in Scotland.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128222","128222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843785","2018-02-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the number of people affected by the cyber attack reported by the BBC on 11 February 2018 in which hackers took control of other people's computers to mine cryptocurrency.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128223","128223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843786","2018-02-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information the Government holds on the amount of personal data which was stolen as a result of the recent BrowseAloud hack.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128224","128224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843787","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the correspondence between his Department,  Public Health England and NHS England on the type of vaccine that GPs have been advised to order for winter 2018-19.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128225","128225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843788","2018-02-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which external recruitment agencies are used by his Department's non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128226","128226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843789","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who have contracted flu in winter 2017-18 after receiving the trivalent vaccine instead of the quadrivalent vaccine.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128227","128227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843790","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will set out (a) how many and (b) which hospitals in England have provided extracorporeal membrane oxygenation treatment, in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128228","128228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843791","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which external recruitment agencies are used by his Department's non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128229","128229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843792","2018-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which external recruitment agencies are used by his Department's non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128230","128230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843793","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which external recruitment agencies are used by his Department's non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128231","128231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843794","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions has he had with Cabinet colleagues on ensuring continued humanitarian assistance to those Overseas Territories in the Caribbean which were damaged by hurricanes in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Philip Dunne","Mr Philip Dunne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128232","128232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843795","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of retail crime to the UK economy in 2017; and what steps her Department is taking to tackle retail crime.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128233","128233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843796","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce incidences of knife crime against shop workers.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128234","128234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843797","2018-02-21","Women and Equalities","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February to Question 125982 with reference to the Equality and Human Rights Commission's recommendation that the Government reopen the Access to Elected Office Fund, what support she provides for people with disabilities who are seeking elected office.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128235","128235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843798","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of cases examined and cleared by the Independent Case Examiner between 2010-11 and 2017-18 and what steps she is taking to improve the performance of that service.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128236","128236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843799","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2018 to Question 122358, on Orkambi: Republic of Ireland, if he will place copies of that correspondence in the Library.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128237","128237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843800","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Government's response to e-petition 209455, on making Orkambi available on the NHS for people with cystic fibrosis, if he will place copies of the correspondence between NHS England and Vertex in the Library.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128238","128238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843801","2018-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the removal of appeal rights for energy companies to an independent body, as indicated in the draft Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill, will also apply to National Grid’s RIIO price controls.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128239","128239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843802","2018-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Regulatory Policy Committee will scrutinise the draft Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128240","128240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843803","2018-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department sought legal advice on the removal of appeal rights to an independent body as contained in the draft Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128241","128241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843804","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in each parliamentary constituency in Scotland receive support for mortgage interest; and how many of those people also receive (a) employment support allowance, (b) personal independence payments and (c) jobseeker’s allowance.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128242","128242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843805","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the level of competition in the funeral industry.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128243","128243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843806","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the public sector pay cap on the recruitment and retention of staff in schools in (a) England, b) London and (c) Lewisham Deptford constituency.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128244","128244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843807","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the extent of exploitative practices in the funeral industry.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128245","128245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843808","2018-02-22","Women and Equalities","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, which women's sporting events she has attended since becoming Minister for Women and Equalities.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128246","128246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843809","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of recruits under 18 years of age attended the Army Foundation College in Harrogate in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128247","128247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843810","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the amount of funding removed from individual school budgets by the Wakefield City Academy Trust.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128248","128248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843811","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to provide additional funding to Trusts which are taking over schools from the Wakefield City Academy Trust.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128249","128249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843812","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether funding removed from individual school budgets by Wakefield City Academy Trust will be reimbursed.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128250","128250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843813","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what mechanisms are in place to monitor compliance by former Ministers of conditions set by the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments for their appointments.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128251","128251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843814","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what mechanisms are in place to monitor compliance by former senior civil servants of conditions set by the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments for their appointments.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128252","128252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843815","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will place her Department’s guidance to JobCentre Plus staff on advising benefit claimants whether to claim for universal credit in areas where its roll-out has not yet been made compulsory in the Library.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128253","128253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843816","2018-02-22","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when (a) he or (b) Officials of his Department last met with unions or individuals to discuss aerotoxic syndrome.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128254","128254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843817","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on the number of (a) universal credit claimants who have lost benefit income as a result of benefit migration and (b) single parents who have lost benefit income as a result of universal credit in areas of Lancashire where its roll-out has not yet been made compulsory.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128255","128255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843818","2018-02-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 February 2018 to Question 127028, on owner occupation, whether his Department (a) holds or (b) is able to place in the Library the information requested.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128256","128256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843819","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much money was spent by the Advisory Committee on Business Appointments (a) on staffing and (b) in total in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128257","128257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843820","2018-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support his Department provides, in addition to the probate and inheritance tax helpline, for vulnerable people and people with learning difficulties who are engaging with the probate process.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128258","128258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843821","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on what date £1.75 million in funding from the Diabetes Transformation Fund was transferred to the Kent and Medway Sustainability and Transformation Partnership.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128259","128259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843822","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on what date £1.14 million in funding from the Diabetes Transformation Fund was transferred to the Lancashire and South Cumbria Sustainability and Transformation Partnership.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128260","128260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843823","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on what date £1.15 million in funding from the Diabetes Transformation Fund was transferred to the North Central London Sustainability and Transformation Partnership.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128261","128261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843824","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of funding provided by the Diabetes Transformation Fund on health outcomes in Lancashire and South Cumbria.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128262","128262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843825","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of funding provided by the Diabetes Transformation Fund on health outcomes in Kent and Medway; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128263","128263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843826","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of funding provided by the Diabetes Transformation Fund on health outcomes in North Central London.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128264","128264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843827","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps health authorities in Lancashire and South Cumbria have taken as a result of funding from the Diabetes Transformation Fund.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128265","128265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843828","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps health authorities in Kent and Medway have taken as a result of funding received from the Diabetes Transformation Fund.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128266","128266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843829","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps health authorities in North Central London have taken as a result of funding from the Diabetes Transformation Fund.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128267","128267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843830","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of removing or reducing the NHS pension annual allowance or increasing its limits to improve the retention of experienced senior hospital doctors and GPs.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128268","128268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843831","2018-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much was spent from the public purse on the provision of plastic forks, knives, stirrers, spoons, cups and straws at the canteen in his Department's offices in Nobel House, Smith Square, London, in the last three years; and what the timetable is for such items to be phased out of use at that canteen.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128269","128269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843832","2018-02-22","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, to what countries the College of Policing and its predecessor body has provided (a) training, (b) advice and (c) consultancy services in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128270","128270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843833","2018-02-22","Department for International Trade","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2018 to Question 126452, what steps the Government is taking to comply with section three of the EU Firearms Directive in respect of (a) establishing a system for the regulation of the activities of dealers and brokers and (b) checking the private and professional integrity and the relevant abilities of the dealer or broker.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128271","128271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843834","2018-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs what assessment his Department has made of the contribution of Official Development Assistance to the achievement of sustainable development goals.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128272","128272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843835","2018-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to increase the transparency of Official Development Assistance spending.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128273","128273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843836","2018-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to table a resolution on Yemen in the UN Security Council.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128274","128274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843837","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints relating to women born in the 1950s and affected by changes in state pension age have been fully reviewed by the Independent Case Examiner's Office.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128275","128275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843838","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints relating to women born in the 1950s who are affected by changes in state pension age are awaiting allocation to an investigation case manager at the Independent Case Examiner's Office.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128081","128081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843839","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, from what acceptance date the Independent Case Examiner's Office is allocating complaints to an investigation case manager.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128276","128276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843840","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disability, pensions, working age and debt management complaints are awaiting allocation to an investigation case manager at the Independent Case Examiner's Office.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128277","128277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843841","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Child Maintenance Group complaints are awaiting allocation to an investigation case manager at the Independent Case Examiner's Office.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128086","128086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843842","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of her Department's service providers' complaints are awaiting allocation to an investigation case manager at the Independent Case Examiner's Office.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128278","128278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843843","2018-02-21","Scotland Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he plans to visit a food bank in March.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128279","128279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843844","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of people who overdose on prescription opioids.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128090","128090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843845","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on the draft Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128280","128280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843846","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the number of households in (a) Scotland, (b) England, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland which will be affected by Ofgem’s decision to increase its price cap by £57 a year from April 2018.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128094","128094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843847","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the implications are for his legislative proposals on requiring Ofgem to review the price cap only once a year from 2020 of Ofgem’s decision to increase the level of its pre-payment meter price cap as a result of increasing wholesale costs.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128281","128281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843848","2018-02-22","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2018 to Question 122931 on Carillion, of the 1,200 apprentices affected, how many of those apprentices (a) have been found alternative employers and (b) are in receipt of jobseeker’s allowance.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128282","128282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843849","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of re-classifying electricity storage vessels to enable distribution network operators to utilise such vessels without paying generation charges.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128098","128098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843850","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to identify locations for potential electricity storage schemes that would best supplement the existing National Grid system; what steps his Department is taking to facilitate such installations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128283","128283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843851","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Office, whether Guernsey has introduced a private register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Dame Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128102","128102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843852","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of exempting operators of electricity storage from balanced services use of system charges.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128284","128284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843853","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of eating disorder services for children and young people in Brighton and Hove.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128105","128105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843854","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to introduce a new code of practice for green deal providers and assessors in the relaunched green deal.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128285","128285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843855","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many green deal providers were not certified by UKAS as meeting the green deal standard in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128108","128108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843856","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many green deal providers were refused the right to produce green deal reports.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128286","128286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843857","2018-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many green deal providers were investigated by the green deal oversight body between 2013 and 2015.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128112","128112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843858","2018-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many green deal providers were investigated by the green deal oversight body between 2015 and 2018.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128287","128287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843859","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many green deal providers have registered with the Green Deal Registration and Oversight Body in each year since that body has been established.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128115","128115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843860","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether existing providers will have to undergo new quality and standards checks before participating in the new green deal scheme.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128288","128288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843861","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will set out (a) the number of complaints relating to the equalisation of the state pension age that her Department's independent case examiner is currently considering and (b) the number of cases that the independent case examiner has resolved since 2 October 2017.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128116","128116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843862","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will set a maximum waiting time for responses to complaints regarding the equalisation of the state pension age received by the Independent Case Examiner.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128289","128289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843863","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the average time taken for a reply to be issued to a complaint submitted to the Independent Case Examiner regarding the equalisation of the state pension age.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128119","128119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843864","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of suicides of people under 25 years of age.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128122","128122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843865","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 November 2018 to Question 113185 on funerals: fees and charges, if she will place in the Library a copy of the criteria for judging applications for the first element of The Social Fund Funeral Expenses Payments.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128290","128290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843866","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many of the 24 NHS neuroscience centres have been commissioned to perform mechanical thrombectomy from April 2018.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128126","128126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843867","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what contingency plans are in place if all nationally designated extra corporeal membrane oxygenation beds are in use.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128291","128291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843868","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the inclusion of doctors on the shortage occupation list; and what recent discussions officials of his Department have had with officials of other Departments on that same subject.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128129","128129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843869","2018-02-21","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to Answer of 13 July 2017 to Question 4057 on Revenue and Customs: ICT, if he will provide an update on the provision or procurement of replacement services previously provided through the Aspire contract.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128292","128292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843870","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Scottish Government's review of foster care in Scotland and to the Education Committee report on fostering, published on 22 December 2017, HC 340, if the Government will undertake a review of the foster care system in England and Wales.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128132","128132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843871","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of Government digital and technology spending was with large companies in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128293","128293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843872","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will make training on supporting looked-after children a mandatory part of teacher training.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128135","128135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843873","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment the Government has made of the effectiveness of peer-to-peer support groups for foster carers.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128294","128294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843874","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Glasgow South constituency are in receipt of Support for Mortgage Interest payments in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128139","128139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843875","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect of variation in staff contracts on the development of shared services across Government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128295","128295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843876","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his policy is on enforcing Government Digital Service standards on providers of shared services.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128142","128142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843877","2018-02-21","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of using distributed ledger technology for any new customs system after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128296","128296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843878","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which Ministers of his Department have taken part in (a) beach cleans and (b) other activities to remove plastic and other litter from the environment since June 2015; and what steps he is taking to enable officials of his Department to take part in such activities.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128146","128146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843879","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how information from his Department's meetings with civil society groups on freedom of religion or belief will inform foreign policy.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128297","128297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843880","2018-02-21","Department for International Development","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department conducts due diligence assessments and evaluates the commitment of its partners to the partnership principles and to promoting freedom of religion or belief.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128149","128149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843881","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to update the strategic supplier risk management policy.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128298","128298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843882","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 64325 and the Answer of 2 March 2018 to Question 64326, how many incidents of (a) drugs by weight, (b) SIM cards and (c) mobile phones were found in prisons in 2017.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128154","128154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843883","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2018 to Question 122582, on eating disorders, when he plans to publish (a) his Department’s, (b) NHS England’s and (c) NHS Improvement’s response to the recommendations of the Parliamentary and Health Ombudsman's report.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128299","128299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843884","2018-02-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how he plans to encourage uptake and monitor compliance of the code of practice provided for by s103 of the Digital Economy Act 2017 by social media companies.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128300","128300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843885","2018-02-22","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Under-Secretary of State for Education of 19 January 2018, Official Report, column 1247, how local authorities can apply to become a pilot area for schemes to combat school holiday hunger.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128157","128157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843886","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) two (b) three and (c) four year olds have attended maintained nursery schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128301","128301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843887","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many childminders have (a) joined and (b) left the early years Ofsted register in each year since August 2012.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128160","128160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843888","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency who will be directly affected by changing support for mortgage interest from a benefit to a Government loan.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128302","128302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843889","2018-02-21","Department for International Development","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what policies her Department has in place for its staff to report sexual harrassment and other non-consensual sexual behaviour; how many of her Department's staff have been reported for sexual harrassment and other non-consensual sexual activity in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017; in how many cases such reports have led to the suspension, demotion or sacking of the staff in question; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128163","128163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843890","2018-02-22","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 119278, on Department for Exiting the European Union: Procurement, what consultancy services have been provided by McKinsey and Company to his Department.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128303","128303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843891","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the article on the Puckeridge Hunt in the Hertordshire Mercury published on 8 February 2018, whether he will (a) make an assessment of the risks of laying scent trails and (b) make and assessment of the potential merits of banning the laying of scent trails.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128166","128166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843892","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the risks posed by hunting hounds using scents laid by trail hunts drifting across the transport network.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128304","128304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843893","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has (a) conducted and (b) is aware of any research into whether women and children in any (i) post code and (ii) county area were disproportionately affected by hormone pregnancy testing.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128169","128169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843894","2018-02-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions his Department has held with (a) the Independent Press Standards Organisation and (b) Impress on the (i) rights and (ii) routes of complaint for groups allegedly subject to press discrimination.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128305","128305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843895","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the recent arrest of Ahed Tamimi, if the Government will seek the establishment of an urgent independent investigation into allegations of ill-treatment of young people in Israel's military detention system.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128173","128173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843896","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse is of contracting Serco to advise people on the provisions of the Loans for Mortgage Interest Regulations 2017.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128306","128306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843897","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that vulnerable people affected by the Loans for Mortgage Interest Regulations 2017 (a) receive face-to-face advice on and (b) fully understand the effect of the new provisions; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128176","128176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843898","2018-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that strong conclusions are adopted on the Rohingya crisis at the EU Foreign Affairs Council on 26 February.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128307","128307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843899","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Home Office, what assessment he has made of the effect of the increase in the NHS health charge for students on the number of international students.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128180","128180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843900","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what provisions are in place for palliative care in privately managed prisons.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128308","128308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843901","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what arrangements Her Majesty’s Prison and Probation Service has with the NHS in relation to palliative care for prisoners.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128183","128183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843902","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many prisoners aged over (a) 60, (b) 70 and (c) 80 receive palliative care from Her Majesty’s Prison and Probation Service.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128309","128309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843903","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many exceptions to the legal requirements set out in the Civil Service Commission's Recruitment Principles there have been since 2010; and to which appointments those exceptions applied.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128185","128185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843904","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in the Inverclyde constituency will have their personal independence payment claim reviewed by the Government.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128310","128310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843905","2018-02-22","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many parents or carers entitled to 30 hours free childcare have failed to receive a code from Childcare Services as a consequence of technical issues in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128311","128311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843906","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of new jobs created by the One Public Estate Programme in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128312","128312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843907","2018-02-21","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will establish an MP enquiry number for the Childcare Office to assist Members' constituents as a result of technical failures relating to the generation of codes for free childcare provision.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128313","128313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843908","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet, how many people are in the One Public Estate programme's Pool of Experts; from which parent teams in the Civil Service those people have come; and for each such team which of its members of the Pool of Experts have (a) master planning, (b) feasibility studies, (c) options appraisals, (d) surveyors, (e) design and (f) procurement expertise.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128314","128314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843909","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many applications have been made for repayable grants by the One Public Estate programme pilot scheme.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128315","128315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843910","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, the value of property sold by Network Rail in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128316","128316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843911","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what data the One Public Estate programme holds on local authority land released since 2015 which has been collected through applications to that programme.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128317","128317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843912","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many local authority applications to the One Public Estate programme were (a) joint applications and (b) applications by a sole local authority in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128318","128318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843913","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many applications to the One Public Estate programme included (a) joint ventures, (b) land swaps and (c) development by small and medium-sized enterprises in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128319","128319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843914","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) applications and (b) successful applications to the One Public Estate programme include key projects that will be delivered by SMEs.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128320","128320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843915","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department takes to assess supply chain risks in government procurement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128321","128321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843916","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department takes to assess potential conflicts of interest between suppliers in government procurement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128031","128031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843917","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department takes to assess compliance with the supplier code of conduct.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128032","128032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843918","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 119603 on prescription drugs, what information his Department holds on the number of unique patients prescribed (a) benzodiazepines and (b) z drugs, including the duration of those prescriptions, for the last full two years for which data is available.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128033","128033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843919","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of unique patients who have been prescribed (a) anti-depressants and (b) opioids, including the duration of those prescription in each of the last full two years for which data is available.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128035","128035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843920","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospital admissions with a primary diagnosis of drug-related mental health or behavioural disorder there were by (a) drug and (b) group of drugs in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128322","128322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843921","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospital admissions with a primary diagnosis of poisoning by illicit drugs there were by (a) drug or (b) group of drugs in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128037","128037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843922","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to appoint a Chief Data Officer.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128323","128323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843923","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the incidence of mental health problems identified during the postnatal period; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128039","128039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843924","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has held with Kensington and Chelsea Council on the provision of (a) housing and (b) other support services for individuals bereaved by the Grenfell Tower fire who do not have (i) settled immigration status in the UK and (ii) recourse to public funds but who are core participants in the Grenfell Inquiry.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128324","128324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843925","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the evidential basis was for the decision to move personal independent payment mobility criteria from 50 metres to 20 metres.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128040","128040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843926","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on patients with cystic fibrosis of making Orkambi available on the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128042","128042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843927","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much money non-resident parents owed resident parents in child maintenance arrears in each Scottish local authority area in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128325","128325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843928","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the level of knowledge of (a) multiple sclerosis and (b) neurological conditions among personal independence payment assessors; and what steps her Department is taking to improve the knowledge of those conditions and their symptoms among such assessors.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128044","128044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843929","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) quantum and (b) value of finfish (i) landed at (A) Portavogie, (B) Ardglass and (C) Kilkeel ports and (ii) produced through aquaculture in Northern Ireland between 2007 and 2017.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128326","128326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843930","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letter of 11 January 2018 from the right hon. Member for Warley regarding Mr Alex.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128046","128046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843931","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to consult the aquaculture sector on the effect of the UK leaving the EU; and what plans his Department has to minimise the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the aquaculture sector.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128327","128327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843932","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to regulate the aquaculture sector after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128048","128048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843933","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans there to progress the outline business case for re-provision of the mental health hospital in Walsall approved by NHS Improvement to assist in mental health care in the Black Country.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128328","128328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843934","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the level of (a) implementation of the strategy for mental health care and (b) mental health care provision in the Black Country.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128050","128050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843935","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to provide fiscal support to increase the provision of emergency beds for mental health crisis patients in the Black Country.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128329","128329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843936","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of including first aid in the driving test.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128052","128052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843937","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to page 23 of his Department's document Public Bodies 2017, published in November 2017, what work has been commissioned on the implementation of the recommendations as a result of  the functional review of regulators.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128330","128330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843938","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to page 31 of his Department's document, Public Bodies 2017, published in November 2017, for what reason his Department does not anticipate major changes in the number of bodies as a result of leaving the European union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128054","128054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843939","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to page 32 of his Department's document Public Bodies 2017, published in November 2018, what progress he has made on the review of arrangements for arms length bodies with advisory functions; and what the timetable is for that review to be completed.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128331","128331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843940","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reviews of his Department's single source contract regulations have occurred since their introduction; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128056","128056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843941","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to provide financial support for self-employed people taking adoption leave.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128332","128332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843942","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons self-employed and employed people are treated differently on the provision of statutory adoption leave.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128058","128058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843943","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 30 March 2017 to Question 68451 on Immigration, how many people who passed through the National Referral Mechanism as victims of (a) modern slavery and (b) human trafficking with positive conclusive grounds status were granted discretionary leave to remain in the UK in 2017.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128333","128333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843944","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many self-employed people adopted a child in (a) Oxfordshire and (b) England in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128334","128334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843945","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who passed through the national referral mechanism as victims of (a) modern slavery and (b) human trafficking with positive conclusive grounds status were refused (i) international protection and (ii) limited leave to remain in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128061","128061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843946","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many agencies applied to be included in the Campaign Solutions Framework for GCS; and when he plans to reopen the framework for new agencies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128335","128335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843947","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons his Department has reduced funding for the Communications Trust.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128063","128063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843948","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding his Department has allocated to Speech Language and Communication Needs in each of the last 5 years.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128336","128336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843949","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department plans to allocate to Speech Language and Communication Needs in 2018.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128337","128337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843950","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department has taken to support the embedding of diversity and inclusion in single departmental plans.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128338","128338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843951","2018-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to respond to the letter dated 20 December 2016 from Eamon O'Hearn.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128339","128339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843952","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made of the clinical benefits of making Symdeko available to people with cystic fibrosis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128340","128340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843953","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women in South Tees died from a ruptured aortic abdominal aneurysm in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128068","128068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843955","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the funding the Office for Product Safety and Standards has been allocated from existing Departmental budgets; and whether it represents an increase in spending on product safety.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128341","128341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843956","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to support the under-10 metre fishing fleet in the Fisheries Bill.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128072","128072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843957","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on the allocation of fishing opportunities in UK waters to reflect the ability of boats to meet environmental, social and economic sustainability criteria.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128342","128342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843958","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions she has had with the Office for National Statistics on its decision to suspend the publication of statistics on the labour market status of disabled people.","Biography information for Peter Aldous","Peter Aldous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128073","128073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843959","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many staff are planned to work within the Office for Product Safety and Standards; and what proportion of those staff will be (a) newly recruited and (b) transferred from within his Department.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128075","128075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843960","2018-02-22","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of people who live within 10km of Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Justine Greening","Justine Greening","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128343","128343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843961","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will ask the Pensions Regulator to extend negotiations on the universities superannuation scheme.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128077","128077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843962","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether non-EEA immigrants who have been issued an ancestry visa and already live and work in the UK will be affected by the planned increase in the immigration healthcare surcharge.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128344","128344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843963","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 7023 on Prisons: Education, whether as part of the work to introduce a core common curriculum across the prison estate consideration will be given to including a module on discrimination, equality and hate crime.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128078","128078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843964","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employees of her Department have undertaken unpaid work periods in each financial year since 2010; and what the average length of an unpaid work period in her Department is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128080","128080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843965","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employees of her Department based in Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency have undertaken unpaid work periods in each financial year since 2010; and what the average length of those unpaid work periods was.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128345","128345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843966","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have undertaken unpaid work periods within her Department since 2010 and have not subsequently been offered a full-time work position.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128082","128082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843967","2018-02-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when his Department plans to publish a Cyber Security Skills Strategy.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128346","128346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843968","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish a Smart City narrative and action plan.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128084","128084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843969","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to publish its big data scoping study; and whether any external bodies were consulted on the creation of the big data scoping study.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128347","128347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843970","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how his Department's cyber-security awareness campaigns take account of behavioural and social sciences; and whether his Department has worked with the Behavioural Insights Team on cyber-security awareness.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128087","128087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843971","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has estimated the number of devices in Government buildings that are connected to the Internet of Things.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128348","128348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843972","2018-02-21","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it is the Government's policy to build a bridge across the English Channel.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128349","128349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843973","2018-02-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to page 17 of the Interim Cyber Security Science and Technology Strategy, how frequently the National Cyber Security Centre will publish advice on emerging technologies; who will be consulted on the preparation of such advice; and which technologies will be the subject of the reports.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128089","128089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843974","2018-02-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish a cyber security research plan.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128350","128350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843975","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the information note Open Book Contract Management published by the Crown Commercial Service in May 2016, whether Open Book Contract Management is used for strategic suppliers that have triggered one of the high risk criteria in the Strategic Suppliers Risk Management Policy.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128092","128092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843976","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the information note Open Book Contract Management, published by the Crown Commercial Service in May 2016, whether timely payment of subcontractors and the assumed profit margins of those subcontractors are tracked in the Government's open book accounting.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128351","128351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843977","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 10 of the information note Open Book Contract Management published by the Crown Commercial Service in May 2016, what steps he has taken to increase the understanding of Open Book.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128352","128352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843978","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 13 of the information note Open Book Contract Management, published by the Crown Commercial Service in May 2016, who provided the services of the 3rd party provider; and how much was paid for that service.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128095","128095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843979","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 10 of the procurement policy note, Publication of payment performance statistics published by the Crown Commercial Service in March 2015, how many Mystery Shopper spot checks have been undertaken, when those spot checks took place, and which bodies were subject to those spot checks.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128353","128353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843980","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to undertake a review of the effectiveness of Procurement Policy Note 01/16, Ensuring compliance with wider international obligations when letting public contracts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128354","128354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843981","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has reviewed the effect of the green deal on average energy bills.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128096","128096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843982","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that new developments benefit first-time buyers and rather than buy-to-let landlords.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128099","128099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843983","2018-02-21","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government plans to take as a result of the findings of the Barber Review, published in November 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128355","128355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843984","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for BEIS, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential role for (a) carbon capture, utilisation and storage and (b) other cleaner coal technologies in facilitating the end of unabated coal power.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128356","128356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843985","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding has been disbursed from the public purse on investment into research and development of the use of carbon capture, utilisation and storage to meet the UK's energy needs in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128101","128101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843986","2018-02-21","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how long the recruitment of a replacement chief executive of the Crown Commercial Service is planned to take; where that position will be advertised; and for how long those advertisements will run.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128357","128357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843987","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what applications have been made by (a) Indivior and (b) Braeburn to license drugs to treat addiction.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128104","128104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843988","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what applications have been received by the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence to recommend use of drugs to treat addiction.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128358","128358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843989","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Office, whether his Department has provided any funding to Syria Civil Defence, which is also known as the White Helmets.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128359","128359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843990","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will review the quarterly financial reports on UK funding for the Syria Civil Defence.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128107","128107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843991","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Ministers of his Department have held meetings with external stakeholders on projects funded by his Department in relation to the Syria Civil Defence.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128360","128360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843992","2018-02-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has received representations on the provisions for data protection breaches in the Data Protection Bill; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128361","128361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843993","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a fund to reimburse the historic back pay directly to sleep-in care workers.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128109","128109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843994","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that providers of local authority-commissioned care for people with learning disabilities do not close as a direct result of their back pay liability for sleep-in shifts.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128362","128362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843995","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for the publication of the results of the Deloitte survey on sleep-in back pay liability.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128111","128111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843996","2018-02-21","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department issues guidance for banks on reviewing accounts of elderly and vulnerable customers to ensure that the financial products they hold are suitable and relevant to their needs.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128363","128363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843997","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness among students of vocational internships as an alternative to university.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128114","128114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843998","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether there are plans to provide free flash glucose monitoring systems to type 1 diabetics on the NHS.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128364","128364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/843999","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to encourage increased support for victims of modern slavery at the Commonwealth Summit in London in April 2018.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128365","128365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844000","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to allow the Care Quality Commission individually to assess local authority and NHS providers where services have not been integrated.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128366","128366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844001","2018-02-22","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the publication of the Marine Investigation Branch report into the sinking of the Solstice trawler off Plymouth in 2017.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128118","128118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844002","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to encourage inmates to take up distant learning courses while in prison.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128367","128367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844003","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure equality in diagnosis and treatment of mental health problems among LGBT+ youth; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128368","128368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844004","2018-02-22","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Home Department, how many non-EEA doctors have had visas declined in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128120","128120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844005","2018-02-22","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions (a) she or (b) Officials of her Department have had with (i) other Government departments and (ii) the Migration Advisory Committee on including doctors on the Shortage Occupation List; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128369","128369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844006","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve cervical screening rates among black and minority ethnic women.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128123","128123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844007","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce levels of cervical cancer among 25 to 29 year olds.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128370","128370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844008","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions the Breast Cancer Clinical Reference Group has had with organisations in the devolved administrations on the sharing of best practice.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128371","128371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844009","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to remove disproportionate financial turnover requirements in tendered Government contracts for SMEs.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128125","128125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844010","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to support SME to compete for tendered Government contracts.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128372","128372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844011","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to increase the number of nursing degree places offered at universities in the UK.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128128","128128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844012","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps the Government has taken financially to assist people who are seeking to train as a nurse.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128373","128373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844013","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of including a replacement for the Reduced Earnings Allowance benefit within universal credit; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128374","128374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844014","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of establishing a separate stakeholder group to the Migration Advisory Committee with representatives from (a) the devolved administrations and (b) regional and city mayors.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128131","128131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844015","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the oral answer of the Prime Minister to the hon. Member for Rutherglen and Hamilton West on 7 February 2018, Official Report, column 1489, what progress she has made on the establishment of an online password reset function for universal credit claimants.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128375","128375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844016","2018-02-21","Department for International Development","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department provides to developing countries that want to move towards clean coal technologies to meet their obligations under the Paris climate agreement.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128376","128376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844017","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to respond to the letter of 8 February from the hon. Member for Glasgow Central on Mr Wasim Iqbal.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128134","128134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844018","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the merits of increasing the monthly cash allowance in line with inflation for people claiming asylum.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128377","128377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844019","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the living conditions in asylum accommodation centres; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128378","128378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844020","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of religious freedom in Sudan; and what steps he is taking to help promote the right to freedom of religion or belief in that country.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128136","128136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844021","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total budget for Operation Kingfisher is for the current financial year; and what proportion of that budget has been spent to date.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128379","128379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844022","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of sleep-in back pay for social care providers in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Ashfield District Council area and (c) Nottinghamshire County Council area.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128138","128138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844023","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure a high uptake in the HPV vaccine across all the regions of England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128380","128380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844024","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that local authorities have sufficient resources to meet increasing demand for social care.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128141","128141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844025","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons why the proportion of girls who did not complete the two-dose HPV vaccination course in 2016-17 failed to so do.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128381","128381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844026","2018-02-21","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assumptions were made on the type of US trade deal, the sectors it covered and its implementation in the preparation of the EU Exit Analysis – Cross Whitehall briefing paper.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128382","128382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844027","2018-02-21","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to EU Exit Analysis – Cross Whitehall Briefing, what assumptions were made in preparing that document; and whether it was assumed that the UK's participation in the 759 EU Treaties would roll over.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128144","128144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844028","2018-02-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of sentences in deterring fly-tipping; and when the penalties for fly-tipping will next be reviewed.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128383","128383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844029","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Transforming children and young people’s mental health provision: a green paper, published by his Department in December 2017, if his Department will consider taking steps for (a) children in care and (b) children from deprived areas when implementing actions arising from that green paper.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128384","128384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844030","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many (a) new-build planning approvals were granted and (b) how many new houses were built in Telford constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128145","128145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844031","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking increase the provision of starter homes in Telford constituency; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128148","128148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844032","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what funding is available to regenerate and renew new town infrastructure.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128385","128385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844033","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his Department's policy is on the future of New Towns.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128386","128386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844034","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the value added to the UK economy by businesses based in Shropshire.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128151","128151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844035","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to review the annual quota of Tier 2 visas.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128387","128387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844036","2018-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Bridgend of 12 January 2018 on training fatalities in 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128388","128388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844037","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to expedite the issuing of Tier 2 visas.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128152","128152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844038","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a national fostering college; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128156","128156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844039","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of conducting a national survey of fostering households.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128389","128389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844040","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of standardised cost analyses of Local Authority and IFA foster placements.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128390","128390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844041","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has plans to include fostering as a recognised professional occupation.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128391","128391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844042","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Government's response to the consultation, Eligibility for free school meals, the early years pupil education entitlement for two-year-olds under universal credit, for what reasons the responses from supporters of the Children’s Society were excluded from the overall data analysis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128158","128158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844043","2018-02-21","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Financial Conduct Authority's decision on BrightHouse, announced on 24 October 2017, whether his Department plans to bring forward legislative proposals to (a) further regulate the rent-to-own market and (b) introduce a price cap on rent-to-own goods.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128392","128392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844044","2018-02-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of introducing a national interest-free credit scheme to provide universal credit claimants with short-term loans to obtain household essentials.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128162","128162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844045","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government intends to review the policy of reducing the size of the House of Commons from 650 seats to 600.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128393","128393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844046","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports he has received on the status of Royal Navy war graves on the shipwrecks of HMS Electra, HMS Exeter and HMS Encounter near Indonesia and Malaysia and on similar wrecks in other areas of the world at risk from metal scavengers.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128394","128394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844047","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has had recent discussions with the Foreign Secretary on reburying the remains of Royal Navy sailors from HMS Exeter.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128395","128395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844048","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to deter metal scavenging from shipwrecks and war graves.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128164","128164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844049","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's consultation on Schools that work for everyone, which closed in December 2016; when his Department plans to respond to that consultation; for what reason the Department has not yet responded to that consultation; and whether the Government has any plans to amend the guidance on consultation principles which state a response should be issued within 12 weeks of a consultation.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128396","128396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844050","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the net change in levels of employment in (a) Royal Navy personnel and (b) civilian staff supporting such personnel at Devonport resulting from the sale of HMS Ocean to Brazil.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128167","128167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844051","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's consultation on Analysing family circumstance and education, which closed in July 2017, when his Department plans to respond to that consultation; and for what reason his Department has not yet responded.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128397","128397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844052","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how his Department monitors the requirement that schools must consult on their admissions arrangements at least once every seven years; and what information his Department collects on such consultations.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128398","128398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844053","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the crew of HMS Ocean will (a) remain in Devonport, (b) transfer to Portsmouth, (c) transfer to other Royal Navy bases and (d) leave the Royal Navy after the ship is decommissioned.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128170","128170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844054","2018-02-21","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2018 to Question 126599, on Cash Dispensing: Fees and Charges, if he will make the correspondence between his Department and LINK on proposals to reduce the interchange fee available to those Members who request it.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128399","128399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844055","2018-02-22","Department for International Trade","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the evidential basis was for the approval of the licensing of 5A001 surveillance equipment to the Philippines on 25 July 2016 under the clear risk qualification for internal repression of the Export Control Order 2008, following the statement made by President Duterte on drug dealers and addicts on taking office on 30 July 2016.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128400","128400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844056","2018-02-22","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what systems are in place for a Children Missing Education Officer to contact HM Revenue and Customs to request information on a family where there are concerns about a child not receiving a suitable education.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128172","128172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844057","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has had recent discussions with the Chair of the Public Administration and Constitutional Affairs Committee on the review of parliamentary constituency boundaries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128401","128401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844058","2018-02-22","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure guidance on medical checks for firearms licensing is applied consistently.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128174","128174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844059","2018-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if the Government will amend the Incentives and Earned Privileges scheme classification for children's visits to parents in male prisons to make them consistent with guidelines for visits to parents in women's prisons.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128402","128402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844060","2018-02-22","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to increase awareness of back-dated Home Responsibilities Protection payments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128177","128177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844061","2018-02-22","HM Treasury","2018-02-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many requests for back-dated Home Responsibilities Protections payments have been made to HMRC (a) in total, (b) by residents in Scotland and (c) by residents in Glasgow South West constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128403","128403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844062","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications have been made for Attendance Allowance by residents in Glasgow South West constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128404","128404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844063","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to encourage applications for Attendance Allowance; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128179","128179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844064","2018-02-21","Department for International Development","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if her Department will publish a response to the report of Save The Children entitled War on Children, published in February 2018; and what steps her Department is taking better to protect children in those conflict zones referred to in the report.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128405","128405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844065","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of the offence of using their mobile phone while driving in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128182","128182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844066","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many Female Genital Mutilation Protection Orders have been (a) applied for and (b) issued by courts since 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128406","128406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844067","2018-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which countries have been involved in cases reported to the Forced Marriage Unit since 2010; and how many cases have been reported for each such country.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128407","128407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844068","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many telephone calls received by the forced marriage unit were from (a) domestic and (b) international locations since 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128408","128408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844069","2018-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with disabilities in Glasgow South West constituency were affected by the removal of the spare room subsidy in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128409","128409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844070","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many calls the 24-hour female genital mutilation hotline has received since January 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128410","128410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844071","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which organisations applied for funding from her Department for community projects to tackle female genital mutilation since 2016; and which applications were (a) accepted and (b) rejected.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128411","128411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844072","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government allocated for the provision of (a) domestic abuse services, (b) female rape support centres, (c) independent domestic violence advisers and (d) independent sexual violence advisers since 2016; and how many (i) rape support centres, (ii) IDVAs and (iii) ISVAs were supported by that funding in each of those years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128412","128412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844073","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many medical professionals have completed Health Education England’s e-learning training sessions on female genital mutilation since 2016; and which e-learning training packages on female genital mutilation are available for medical professionals.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128413","128413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844074","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding NHS England has provided for stem cell transplant centres since 2015; and how many stem cell transplant centres there are.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128414","128414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844075","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people are registered as stem cell donors on the NHS stem cell registry; and what proportion of people who are registered as stem cell donors are from black and ethnic minority ethnic backgrounds.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128415","128415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844076","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much Government funding has been provided to (a) NHS Blood and Transplant and (b) Anthony Nolan for stem cell donation since 2015.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128416","128416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844077","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department provided to the Association of Independent Local Safeguarding Children’s Board Chairs in each financial year since 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128417","128417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844078","2018-02-21","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many local authority-maintained nurseries there were in (a) London, (b) Brent, (d) Camden and (d) Hampstead and Kilburn constituency in each year since 2015; how many staff were employed in those nurseries in each year since 2015; and how much funding has been allocated to those nurseries in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128418","128418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844079","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2018 to Question 125536 on the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012, if he will publish a timetable for when the post-implementation review will (a) take place and (b) report back to Parliament.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128419","128419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844080","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visas from (a) businesses (b) UK Government Departments and (c) the Scottish Government in Scotland were rejected as a result of the cap on Tier 2 visas for skilled non-European workers in (i) December 2017, (ii) January 2018 and (iii) February 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128420","128420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844081","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department makes a comparative assessment of salary differentials in different parts of the UK in respect of granting visas for skilled non-European workers.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128421","128421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844082","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department made of salary differentials in the different parts of the UK for visas for skilled non-European workers in (a) December 2017, (b) January 2018 and (c) February 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128422","128422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844083","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for NHS England to publish the Neonatal Critical Care Clinical Reference Group’s draft report of the neonatal care review.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128423","128423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844084","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of people sent to prison for council tax non-payment were women in each year from 2010 to 2017.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128424","128424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844085","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of people who served time in prison for each year between 2010 and 2017 for not paying their council tax had (a) a full means assessment undertaken (b) their caring responsibilities taken into account by the court and (c) their mental health needs assessed prior to their committal.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128425","128425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844086","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what comparative assessment he has made of the average (a) cost to the public purse of a prison sentence and (b) amount of debt outstanding in cases where people have been sent to prison for council tax non-payment in each year between 2010 and 2017.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128426","128426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844087","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people were diagnosed with carbon monoxide poisoning from exposure in their homes to (a) solid wood, (b) gas and (c) other fuel burning appliances since 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128427","128427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844088","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) hospital admissions and (b) deaths from carbon monoxide poisoning in each year since 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128428","128428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844089","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the level of risk to private sector tenants of  carbon monoxide poisoning from (a) solid fuel burning appliances, (b) gas burning appliances and (c) other fuel burning appliances; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128429","128429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844090","2018-02-22","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's plans are for the Shared Service Centre in Swansea.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128430","128430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844091","2018-02-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish his Department’s response to the consultation on the Smoke and Carbon Monoxide (England) Regulations 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128431","128431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844092","2018-02-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times s72 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 has been invoked in each year since it gained Royal assent.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128432","128432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844093","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when NICE plans to publish its evaluation report on Patent Foramen Ovale Closure.","Biography information for Rosie Duffield","Rosie Duffield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128433","128433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844094","2018-02-22","Department for Transport","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of assaults on (a) staff and (b) customers on public transport in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128434","128434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844095","2018-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish his Department's (a) legal framework and (b) guidance on the use of lethal force.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128435","128435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844096","2018-02-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January to Question 124261, and with reference to paragraph 12.6 and Diagram 40 of Approved Document B, whether materials that are not of limited combustibility are permitted on the external wall surface of a building with a storey of 18 metres or more above ground level.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128436","128436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844097","2018-02-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January to Question 124261, and with reference to paragraph 12.6 and Diagram 40 of Approved Document B, whether (a) class 0 (national class) and (b) class B-s3, d2 must be composed only of materials that are of limited combustibility.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128437","128437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844098","2018-02-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average length of time taken is between the start of phase one training and deployable capability for an infantry soldier aged (a) 18 or over and (b) 16; and what the average (i) training, (ii) salary and (iii) other costs are for that training.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128438","128438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844099","2018-02-21","Home Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding her Department provides to support support local and regional anti- modern slavery groups.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128439","128439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844100","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he had with his counterpart in the Scottish Government on the Industrial Strategy White Paper prior to its publication.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128440","128440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844101","2018-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of wells projected to be drilled by the shale gas industry in (a)2025 and (b) 2030; whether those estimates have changed since (i) 2012 and (ii) 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128441","128441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844102","2018-02-22","Department for Education","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many University Vice-Chancellors were members of their institution’s remuneration committees at the start of the (a)  2009-10 and (b) 2017-18 academic year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128442","128442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844103","2018-02-22","Cabinet Office","2018-02-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, reference to the written statement HCWS464, on 8 February 2018 on the Infected Blood Inquiry, whether the Chair of the inquiry will operate with the support of a Panel.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128443","128443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844104","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 24 February 2017 to Question 63667 on Philip Morley, what the timetable is for the (a) conclusion and (b) publication of NHS Protect’s investigation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128444","128444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844105","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on how many occasions have NHS Trusts received concerns about alleged unfitness to practice of trust directors since the Fit and Proper Persons Regulations came into force; how many of those concerns led to an (a) internal and (b) independent investigation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128445","128445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844106","2018-02-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on how many occasions the Care Quality Commission has notified trust Chairs of non-compliance with the  Fit and Proper Persons Regulations, since those regulations came into force.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128446","128446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/844107","2018-02-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on how many occasions the Care Quality Commission (a) received concerns from third parties about an alleged lack of fitness of a trust director and (b) notified the relevant trust of those concerns since the Fit and Proper Persons Regulations came into force.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128447","128447"
