"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690523","2017-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what account was taken of (a) the cost of land, (b) the effect on the transmission system and (c) balancing costs of the strike price for Hinkley Point C.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64043","64043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690524","2017-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2017 to Question 58726, on wind power, whether the costs associated with electricity generation that make up each Strike Price comparator in the BEIS Electricity Generation Cost report are based on Frontier Economics' research into whole system impacts; and what plans he has to publish that research.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64050","64050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690525","2017-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to help increase productivity for the (a) chemical, (b) steel, (c) aluminium and (d) other energy-intensive industries.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64060","64060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690526","2017-02-21","Home Office","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people aged 65 or over have been involved in fires caused by (a) portable electrical fires and (b) electric blankets in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64130","64130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690527","2017-02-21","Home Office","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to encourage transparency within supply chains for the textile industry to ensure that workers are not victims of modern slavery.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64128","64128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690528","2017-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of foreign company takeovers on the UK economy.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64187","64187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690529","2017-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to prevent hostile foreign takeovers of UK firms.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64188","64188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690530","2017-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to increase female representation on the boards of local enterprise partnerships.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64218","64218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690531","2017-02-22","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will review payment dates for the Warm Home Discount Scheme to ensure that discounts are applied at the start of the winter season.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64224","64224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690532","2017-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans the Government has to support the Ser Cymru II programme in Wales after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64149","64149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690533","2017-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) mean and (b) median pay was for staff in his Department who were (i) male, (ii) female, (iii) white, (iv) from an ethnic minority background, (v) disabled and (vi) non-disabled in the most recent year for which information is available, broken down by (A) full-time and (B) part-time workers.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64157","64157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690534","2017-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much (a) Birmingham and (b) the West Midlands has received in financial support through local projects funded by the Green Investment Bank since that bank was established.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64204","64204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690535","2017-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has to implement the EU's Clean Energy for All Europeans package if it is adopted before Spring 2019.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64205","64205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690536","2017-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62374, what plans he has to report on the progress of industry implementation of the recommendations in his Department's Each Home Counts review, published in December 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64311","64311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690537","2017-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of using decommissioned oil platforms for wind energy installations.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64320","64320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690538","2017-02-23","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Scotland and Ministers of the Scottish Government on the effect on Scotland of the UK ceasing to be a member of Euratom.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64290","64290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690539","2017-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the Government will respond to the request for an apology for actions by the UK Government in relation to industrial action at Cammell Laird in 1984 made by the Committee on Petitions of the European Parliament in December 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64262","64262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690540","2017-02-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent representations he has received from Xcite Energy Limited shareholders.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64263","64263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690541","2017-02-22","Department for International Trade","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 61491, which countries have expressed an interest in agreeing trade deals with the UK with whom a working group and dialogue on our future trading relationship have not been announced.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64291","64291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690542","2017-02-21","Department for International Trade","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2017 to Question 62539, how many security passes are issued on behalf of his Department by the Departmental Security teams in the buildings in which they are based to people who are not employees of his Department.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64317","64317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690543","2017-02-22","Department for International Trade","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 60711, how many UK-based full-time equivalent staff of his Department are in the working group on  the UK's future trading relationship with (a) Australia, (b) China, (c) India, (d) New Zealand, (e) Norway, (f) South Korea and (g) the Gulf Cooperation Council.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64292","64292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690544","2017-02-21","Department for International Trade","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the (a) mean and (b) median pay was for staff in his Department who were (i) male, (ii) female, (iii) white, (iv) from an ethnic minority background, (v) disabled and (vi) non-disabled in the most recent year for which information is available, broken down by (A) full-time and (B) part-time workers.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64171","64171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690545","2017-02-21","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the (a) mean and (b) median pay was for staff in his Department who were (i) male, (ii) female, (iii) white, (iv) from an ethnic minority background, (v) disabled and (vi) non-disabled in the most recent year for which information is available, broken down by (A) full-time and (B) part-time workers.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64165","64165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690546","2017-02-22","HM Treasury","2017-02-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 8.44 of the White Paper, entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm9417, published in February 2017, what the average time taken was for customs declarations submitted (a) electronically and (b) non-electronically in the UK to be cleared in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64251","64251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690547","2017-02-22","HM Treasury","2017-02-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 8.44 of the White Paper, entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm9417, published in February 2017, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of customs declarations in the UK were submitted electronically in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64252","64252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690548","2017-02-22","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to paragraph 8.42 of the White Paper entitled The United Kingdom's exit from and new partnership with the European Union, Cm 9417, published in February 2017, if he will list all the EU agencies to be included in discussions with the EU and Member States on the UK's future status and arrangements with regard to those agencies.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 64155","64155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687891","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Head of the Civil Service plans to reply to the letter and email he received from the right hon. Member for Hitchin and Harpenden on 23 January 2017 on flaws in HM Treasury's analysis of the impact of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63796","63796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687892","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in Hemsworth constituency (a) work in social care and (b) work in social care and are paid less that the living wage.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63816","63816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687893","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in each year from 2010 have been employed on zero-hour contracts in Hemsworth constituency.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63811","63811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687894","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in each year from 2010 have been on a temporary contract in Hemsworth constituency.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63812","63812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687895","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people under the age of 24 in each year from 2010 have been employed on a zero-hours contract in Hemsworth constituency.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63813","63813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687896","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in each year from 2010 have been in part-time work in Hemsworth constituency.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63814","63814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687897","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in each year from 2010 have been in false self-employment in Hemsworth constituency.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63815","63815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687898","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many workers from other EU countries were employed in the UK's adult social care workforce in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63833","63833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687899","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many properties and assets the Government fully owns in Glasgow Central constituency.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63839","63839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687900","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62529, what the number of security passes issued by his Department to people not employed by his Department is; what business needs suffice for such a security pass to be granted; and what the number of passes issued to people who work for private companies which have currently or previously been awarded government contracts or which are bidding for such contracts is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63866","63866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687901","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of how many staff and negotiators government departments will need to recruit for the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63877","63877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687902","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62723, on government secondments, (a) what positions the staff from PWC were seconded to, (b) what the purpose of those secondments were, (c) what the equivalent payscales were of the positions to which those staff were seconded and (d) how long those secondments lasted.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63901","63901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687903","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons the February 2017 release of the Overview of the UK Population series has been cancelled; what plans the Office of National Statistics has to publish such releases in the future; and what plans there are to continue that series in future.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63903","63903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687904","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 February 2017, HCWS458, whether his Department will publish a social economic distributional analysis of the cost savings from the Cabinet Office in the last financial year.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63949","63949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687905","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 February 2017, HCWS458, whether his Department will publish a gender impact assessment of the cost savings from the Cabinet Office in the last financial year.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63950","63950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687906","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 February 2017, HCWS458, what the criteria is for determining the level of economic or social return when considering the sales of government assets.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63951","63951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687907","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 February 2017, HCWS458, how his Department defines value for money in relation to the policy to sell public assets; and whether he will place a copy of the evidence base for that definition in the Library.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63952","63952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687908","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 February 2017, HCWS458, what criteria his Department is using to determine whether there is a policy reason to continue to own government assets.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63953","63953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687909","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 February 2017, HCWS458, who in his Department is responsible for the sale process of public assets.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63958","63958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687910","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 February 2017, HCWS458, what methodology his Department will use to assess market conditions as part of the sale process of public assets.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63959","63959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687911","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 February 2017, HCWS458, who will be overseeing the final value for money assessment in accordance with her Department's Green Book framework during the sale process of public assets.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63960","63960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687912","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ensure that the value of EU structural funds is met by the  Government after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63944","63944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687913","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 February 2017, HCWS458, how the Government plans to securitise the remaining future repayments on student loans as a part of their planned sale process.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63961","63961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687914","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Written Statement of 6 February 2017, HCWS458, how the Government will inform the House when a sale of a public asset is completed.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63962","63962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687915","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value is of (a) fraudulent tax credit claims, (b) benefit fraud and (c) tax avoidance in each of the last three years; and what the evidential basis is for those estimates.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63945","63945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687916","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many cases (a) HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) and (b) other bodies working on behalf of HMRC have pursued on (i) fraudulent tax credit claims, (ii) benefit fraud, (iii) tax avoidance and (iv) breaches of minimum wage legislation in each year since 2010.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63946","63946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687917","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much (a) HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) and (b) other bodies working on behalf of HMRC have spent from the public purse on tackling (i) fraudulent tax credit claims, (ii) benefit fraud, (iii) tax avoidance and (iv) breaches of minimum wage legislation in each year since 2010.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63948","63948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687918","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received inheritance tax relief for estates exempt of transfers to charities on death in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63965","63965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687919","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received the cross field allowance for petroleum revenue tax relief in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63966","63966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687920","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the correlation is between the amount HM Revenue and Customs has spent and recouped on tackling fraudulent (a) tax credit and (b) benefit claims.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63947","63947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687921","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received the acquisition relief from stamp duty land tax in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63967","63967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687922","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received inheritance tax exemption of transfers on death to surviving spouses in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63968","63968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687923","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received inheritance tax relief for estates left on death with conditional exemption for heritage property in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63969","63969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687924","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what mechanism has been put in place to assess whether the Government will guarantee funding for specific ESF and ERDF projects signed after the Autumn Statement; how such projects will be assessed against the two criteria of value for money and alignment with domestic priorities; and whether such assessments will be undertaken before or after agreements have been signed.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63865","63865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687925","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Markets and Competition Authority on the introduction of a cap on overdraft charges for personal current accounts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63848","63848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687926","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received capital gains tax relief for entrepreneurs' qualifying business disposals in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63825","63825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687927","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received inheritance tax relief for business relief including unlisted shares in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63826","63826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687928","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received inheritance tax relief for agricultural property in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63827","63827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687929","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received the annual exempt amount of capital gains tax in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63828","63828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687930","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received capital gains tax relief on investments in enterprise investment schemes in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63829","63829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687931","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Head of the Government Economic Service plans to reply to the letter and email he received from the right hon. Member for Hitchin and Harpenden on 23 January 2017 on flaws in his Department's analysis of the impact of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63797","63797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687932","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Permanent Secretary to the Treasury plans to reply to the letter and email he received from the right hon. Member for Hitchin and Harpenden on 23 January 2017 on flaws in his Department's analysis of the impact of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63795","63795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687933","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses received double taxation relief in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63801","63801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687934","2017-02-20","Church Commissioners","2017-02-09","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2017 to Question 62530, what the number of security passes issued by the Church Commissioners to people not employed by the Church Commissioners is; what business needs suffice for such a security pass to be granted; and what the number of passes issued to people who work for private companies which have currently or previously been awarded government contracts or which are bidding for such contracts is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63867","63867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687935","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fire station closures there have been in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63831","63831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687936","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people have been registered as council tenants in (a) Tynemouth constituency and (b) North Tyneside Borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63840","63840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687937","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many houses have been repossessed in (a) Tynemouth constituency and (b) North Tyneside Borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63841","63841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687938","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many families were on social housing waiting lists in (a) Tynemouth constituency and (b) North Tyneside Borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63842","63842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687939","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what record his Department keeps of text messages sent on departmental business by officials of his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63817","63817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687940","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, on what dates officials of his Department have met representatives from Surrey County Council in the last month; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63810","63810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687941","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Nottinghamshire Fire Service investigation of the former Trent Valley recycling site in Worksop in January 2017, what estimate she has made of the potential cost to the public purse should the site require ongoing fire service interventions.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63805","63805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687942","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 18 of the Casey Review, published in December 2016, what the Government's policy is on introducing an oath of allegiance to British values  for public office holders.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63788","63788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687943","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to publish its integration policy in response to the Casey Review of December 2016.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63789","63789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687944","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many social houses have been sold under the Right to Buy scheme in each of the last three years; and how many of those houses sold have been replaced with new social housing.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63920","63920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687945","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, by what process the £25 million of new funding to help ambitious authorities in areas of high housing need to plan for new homes and infrastructure announced in the Housing White Paper, published in February 2017, will be allocated; and what conditions will be set on that funding.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63900","63900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687946","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many deposits of tenants in London were protected by the Government-accredited tenancy deposit protection scheme in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63888","63888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687947","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many deposits of tenants in London were (a) submitted and (b) returned under the Government-accredited tenancy deposit protection scheme in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63889","63889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687948","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to introduce a cost floor for homes sold through the right to acquire scheme.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63909","63909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687949","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many online gambling websites located outside the UK and without a Gambling Commission remote-operating licence were sent letters reminding them of the legal position on licensing in the UK between the Gambling (Licensing and Advertising) Act 2014 coming into force and 31 December 2016.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63924","63924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687950","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many Gambling Commission remote-operating licences are held by gambling websites based outside of the UK; and in which jurisdictions such websites are located.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63922","63922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687951","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many Gambling Commission remote-operating licences are held by gambling websites based in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63923","63923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687952","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many times payment providers (a) were asked by the Gambling Commission to block payments to online gambling websites not licenced in the UK and (b) blocked such payments between the Gambling (Licensing and Advertising) Act 2014 coming into force and 31 December 2016.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63925","63925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687953","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2017 to Question 62532, what the number of security passes issued by her Department to people not employed by her Department is; what business needs suffice for such a security pass to be granted; and what the number of passes issued to people who work for private companies which have currently or previously been awarded government contracts or which are bidding for such contracts is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63868","63868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687954","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations she has received on improving disability access to sports venues; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63846","63846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687955","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will meet Muscular Dystrophy UK's Trailblazers to discuss accessibility at sports venues.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63862","63862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687956","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2017 to Question 63301, on the British Board of Film Classification (BBFC), for what reason she did not provide in her Answer the dates on which Ministers of her Department met the BBFC.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63863","63863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687957","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the staff headcount was at the Army Personnel Centre at Kentigern House in Glasgow in each year from 2006 to 2016.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63856","63856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687958","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2017 to Question 62604, what the number of security passes issued by his Department to people not employed by his Department is; what business needs suffice for such a security pass to be granted; and what the number of passes issued to people who work for private companies which have currently or previously been awarded government contracts or which are bidding for such contracts is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63869","63869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687959","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse was of (a) UK military operations in Libya between 1 March and 31 August 2011, (b) the personnel deployed during those operations, (c) the ordinance deployed during those operations and (d) the fuel used during those operations.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63821","63821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687960","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to increase troop numbers in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63830","63830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687961","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the new national funding formula for schools on the recruitment and retention of teachers in Nottingham City.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63798","63798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687962","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding her Department has provided to football academies in the last three years; and (a) what projects have been funded and (b) how many participants there have been in (i) those projects and (ii) each academy.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63804","63804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687963","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2016 to Question 47734, whether Ofsted's inspection of sex and relationships education taught in academies includes an assessment of whether the curriculum is inclusive of LGBT young people.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63806","63806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687964","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of potential change to the number of pupils eligible for pupil premium funding once universal credit has been rolled out.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63834","63834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687965","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether any change to the criteria which determine eligibility for pupil premium funding will result from the roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63835","63835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687966","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria the Government will use to determine eligibility for free school meals once universal credit has been rolled out.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63836","63836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687967","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether schools are required to inform her Department when their websites and servers are hacked.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63803","63803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687968","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the number of (a) academies and (b) maintained secondary schools that provide sex and relationships education.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63819","63819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687969","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the findings of the Royal College of Speech and Language Therapists' report, entitled The SEND reforms in England: supporting children and young people with speech, language and communication needs.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63908","63908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687970","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department will complete its internal review of health and safety advice to schools; when she plans to publish revised advice on school trips and travel; and whether that advice will take into account risks posed by poor driver accommodation and driver fatigue.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63897","63897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687971","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to publish its guidance on Key Stage 4 performance tables in qualifications in the technical award category for 2019.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63921","63921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687972","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has had with HM Treasury on whether the planned sale of the student loans book will affect the repayment formula for people paying off such loans.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63938","63938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687973","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2017 to Question 62534, what the number of security passes issued by her Department to people not employed by her Department is; what business needs suffice for such a security pass to be granted; and what the number of passes issued to people who work for private companies which have currently or previously been awarded government contracts or which are bidding for such contracts is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63870","63870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687974","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with her counterparts in HM Treasury and the Department for Communities and Local Government on environmental risks posed by the Crown Estate-owned site in Worksop previously occupied by Trent Valley recycling.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63802","63802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687975","2017-03-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her Department's policy is on paying the travel expenses of British musicians invited to overseas countries to perform with national orchestras.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63787","63787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687976","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will initiate a Call to Action by the Community of Democracies' Working Group on Enabling and Protecting Civil Society for an urgent intervention with the government of Sierra Leone to ask that Government to review its draft non-governmental organisation policy regulations to bring them into line with constitutional and international standards of freedom of association.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63807","63807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687977","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the effect of the conflict in eastern Ukraine on public opinion in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63790","63790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687978","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2017 to Question 62602, what the number of security passes issued by his Department to people not employed by his Department is; what business needs suffice for such a security pass to be granted; and what the number of passes issued to people who work for private companies which have currently or previously been awarded government contracts or which are bidding for such contracts is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63871","63871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687979","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support he is providing to EU accession countries to help them become full EU member states.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63849","63849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687980","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political situation in Ukraine.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63850","63850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687981","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much of his Department's spending has contributed towards the UK's Official Development Assistance total in 2016-17.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63851","63851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687982","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will provide an update on plans for the visit of President Trump to the UK.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63876","63876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687983","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Colombian counterpart on the conditions in which former FARC guerrillas are being required to camp under the terms of the peace agreement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63879","63879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687984","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) staff and (b) annual budget is of the UK diplomatic representation in Mauritania.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63822","63822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687985","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the treatment of human rights activists in that country.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63917","63917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687986","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of Egypt on alleged human rights abuses in that country.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63918","63918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687987","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the protection and promotion of human rights.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63919","63919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687988","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many of his Department's overseas-based staff work on climate change.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63939","63939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687989","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Afghan counterpart on the (a) security situation in the province of Jowzjan and (b) killing of International Committee of the Red Cross workers on 8 February 2017.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63943","63943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687990","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in the Jowzjan province of Afghanistan.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63954","63954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687991","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the political situation in Syria.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63975","63975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687992","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how long patients in Wolverhampton waited on average to start treatment following diagnosis for (a) lung cancer, (b) breast cancer, (c) cervical cancer, (d) ovarian cancer, (e) prostate cancer, (f) testicular cancer, (g) pancreatic cancer, (h) head and neck cancers, (i) leukaemia, (j) bowel cancer, (k) kidney cancer, (l) colon cancer, (m) GIST cancers, (n) stomach cancer, (o) liver cancer, (p) melanoma, (q) non-Hodgkin Lymphoma and (r) myeloma in each year since 1997; what the average (i) one, (ii) five and (iii) 10 year age-standardised net survival rate for each of those cancers was in each year since 1997; and what proportion of people with each of those cancers was diagnosed at stage (A) 1, (B) 2, (C) 3 and (D) 4 in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63971","63971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687993","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many technology appraisals NICE has undertaken for medicines granted accelerated approval by the European Medicines Agency due to high unmet medical needs; and what the NICE recommendation was for each of those appraisals.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63972","63972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687994","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many extractions of multiple teeth for children under the age of 18 in University Hospitals Coventry and Warwickshire NHS Trust took place in each of the last five years; what the cost of such extractions was in each such year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63927","63927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687995","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 December 2016 to Question 58050, on neuromuscular disorders: South East, how many neuromuscular care advisers will cover Kent, Surrey and Sussex; which clinical commissioning groups in Kent, Surrey and Sussex will be contributing to funding neuromuscular care adviser roles; when the relevant clinical commissioning groups will be meeting to finalise job descriptions and begin recruitment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63963","63963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687996","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many technology appraisals NICE has undertaken where phase three clinical trial data has been absent or incomplete.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63974","63974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687997","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of NICE's methodologies to appraise treatments for small patient populations.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63973","63973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687998","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of nationals of other EU countries working in the NHS as cleaners; what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the number of such cleaners; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on NHS productivity of that change in the number of such cleaners.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63893","63893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687999","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of nationals of other EU countries working in the NHS as health visitors; what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the number of such health visitors; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on NHS productivity of that change in the number of such health visitors.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63894","63894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688000","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the level of cervical screening uptake is in Wolverhampton Clinical Commissioning Group; what steps his Department is taking to increase cervical screening uptake among women in Wolverhampton; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63890","63890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688001","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what costs have been (a) incurred and (b) committed for future periods for the development and management of the sustainability and transformation plan process for Wolverhampton Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63891","63891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688002","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to increase the number of people registered as organ donors in the UK.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63912","63912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688003","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to emotional and psychological support for people with muscle-wasting conditions.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63913","63913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688004","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has received a request for further funding from the (a) Macfarlane Trust and (b) Caxton Foundation infected blood scheme administrators beyond the 2017-18 fiscal year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63916","63916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688005","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to disallow the current infected blood scheme administrators from bidding in the tender to be the new Infected Blood Scheme Administrator.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63914","63914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688006","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure that the current scheme administrators are given further government financial support in the event that the new Infected Blood Scheme Administrator is not in position by April 2017.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63915","63915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688007","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of nationals of other EU countries working in the NHS as nurses; what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the number of such nurses; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on NHS productivity of that change in the number of such nurses.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63895","63895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688008","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of nationals of other EU countries working in the NHS as psychiatrists; what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the number of such psychiatrists; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on NHS productivity of that change in the number of such psychiatrists.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63896","63896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688009","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of nationals of other EU countries working in the NHS as midwives; what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the number of such midwives; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on NHS productivity of that change in the number of such midwives.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63892","63892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688010","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to increase the length of time that data is collected on the evaluation of treatment funded by the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63820","63820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688011","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish all documents produced by NHS Improvement on accident and emergency waiting times in January 2017.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63878","63878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688012","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the £900 million extra funding announced by the Government for social care on 15 December 2016 will be received by St Helens Council.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63845","63845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688013","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding has been provided from the public purse to GP practices in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63799","63799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688014","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average amount of funding from the public purse provided to GP practices was in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63800","63800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688015","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether women in Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre are tested for TB, HIV and malaria on arrival from (a) West Africa, (b) East Africa, (c) South Africa and (d) South-East Asia.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63781","63781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688016","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to commence the appointment process for the second Independent Anti-Slavery Commissioner.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63858","63858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688017","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to (a) protect businesses subject to CEO fraud and (b) hold accountable banks which have not followed money-laundering check procedures in opening accounts.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63881","63881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688018","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cyber specials there are in police forces in England Wales; and how many of those officers have been recruited since January 2015.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63910","63910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688019","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many passports have been lost in the post in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63861","63861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688020","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that premises used by asylum accommodation providers as temporary accommodation are fit to house vulnerable people.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63852","63852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688021","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that people granted asylum in the UK in initial accommodation are properly supported for the duration of their stay.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63853","63853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688022","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fraud offences were recorded by Action Fraud in each year since 2013; and how many of those offences were then passed onto the police.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63933","63933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688023","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many call-handling staff are employed by Action Fraud.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63934","63934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688024","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will make an assessment of the effect of its decision to stop direct funding for the digital media investigators course on the level of take-up of that course.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63935","63935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688025","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much of the Police Transformation Fund for 2017-18 has been allocated to bids related to improving police forces' capacity to deal with cybercrime.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63936","63936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688026","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officers have completed the College of Policing (a) Digital Communications, Social Media, Cybercrime and Policing, (b) Cybercrime and digital policing - an introduction, (c) Cybercrime and digital policing - First responder Training, (d) Cybercrime and digital policing - Investigation, (e) Communications Data in Investigations, (f) Introduction to Communications Data and Cybercrime, (g) Communications Data - Introduction to the Internet and (h) Communications Data and Cybercrime - Introduction to Law and Procedure e-learning packages.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63937","63937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688027","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62601, on security at her Department, how many security passes have been issued to people who work for private companies who have (a) currently or previously been awarded government contracts and (b) previously or are currently bidding for government contracts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63902","63902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688028","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many National Crime Agency Special Officers there are whose area of expertise is cybercrime; and how many such officers were recruited since January 2015.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63928","63928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688029","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62601, on Home Office Security, how many passes for the groups provided in that Answer were have been issued.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63904","63904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688030","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2016 to Question 54640, on passports, what the age profile is of UK passport holders.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63956","63956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688031","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps her Department has taken to end the practice of dog fighting.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63955","63955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688032","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what meetings she has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on the financial, legal and logistical implications for local authorities of the Immigration Act.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63899","63899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688033","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what meetings she or the Minister of State for Immigration have had with Lord Dubs to discuss implementation of the Immigration Act.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63898","63898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688034","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will provide additional financial and other resources to the police to assist them in tackling the practice of dog fighting.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63941","63941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688035","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that its initial decisions on granting asylum are made accurately and fairly.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63970","63970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688036","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what audits her Department conducts on imported fur originating from (a) China, (b) Denmark, (c) the US and (d) other countries.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63964","63964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688037","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the fraudulent use of aid disbursed by her Department.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63929","63929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688038","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2016 to Question 54679, which domestic human rights organisations in Sierra Leone the Government has consulted on the Government of Sierra Leone's draft revised Non-Government Organisation Policy Regulations.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63907","63907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688039","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2016 to Question 54679, if her Department will make representations to the Government of Sierra Leone on publishing the detailed technical assessment of the draft revised Non-Governmental Organisation Policy Regulations produced by the International Center for Not-for-Profit Law.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63906","63906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688040","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the National Audit Office report of 9 February 2017, entitled Investigation into the Department's approach to tackling fraud, how much of the two-thirds of the reported fraud loss recovered since 2003 was recovered between (a) 2003 and 2009 and (b) 2010 and 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63931","63931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688041","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the National Audit Office report of 9 February 2017, entitled Investigation into the Department's approach to tackling fraud, what the value is of the third of reported fraud loss not recovered since 2003.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63932","63932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688042","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2017 to Question 62538, what the number of security passes issued by her Department to people not employed by her Department is; what business needs suffice for such a security pass to be granted; and what the number of passes issued to people who work for private companies which have currently or previously been awarded government contracts or which are bidding for such contracts is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63872","63872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688043","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has provided in the current financial year to projects supporting developing states in tackling illegal, unreported and unregulated fishing.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63818","63818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688044","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many prisons operational capacity was exceeded in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63837","63837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688045","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2017 to Question 62540, what the number of security passes issued by her Department to people not employed by her Department is; what business needs suffice for such a security pass to be granted; and what the number of passes issued to people who work for private companies which have currently or previously been awarded government contracts or which are bidding for such contracts is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63873","63873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688046","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many remand first receptions there were in each prison establishment in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63882","63882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688047","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who will lead the UK delegation at the UN Human Rights Council for the UK's Universal Periodic Review on 4 May 2017.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63905","63905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688048","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time spent by prisoners on remand was in each prison establishment in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63883","63883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688049","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many recalls to prison there have been for (a) breach of licence and (b) new offence in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63884","63884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688050","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many recalls to prison to each prison establishment there have been in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63885","63885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688051","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the time spent in custody on recall was for each prisoner so recalled in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63886","63886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688052","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what communications she has had with President Trump's nominee for Attorney General since his formal nomination.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63942","63942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688053","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals for more punitive sentences for people involved in the practice of dog fighting.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63940","63940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688054","2017-02-20","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) cost, (b) take up and (c) effectiveness in reducing fraud of the electoral identity card. in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63957","63957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688055","2017-02-20","Scotland Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2017 to Question 62543, what the number of security passes issued by his Department to people not employed by his Department is; what business needs suffice for such a security pass to be granted; and what the number of passes issued to people who work for private companies which have currently or previously been awarded government contracts or which are bidding for such contracts is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63874","63874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688056","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2017 to Question 62544, what the number of security passes issued by his Department to people not employed by his Department is; what business needs suffice for such a security pass to be granted; and what the number of passes issued to people who work for private companies which have currently or previously been awarded government contracts or which are bidding for such contracts is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63875","63875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688057","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what dates leases for the Driving Test Theory Centre in Glasgow are due for renewal.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63854","63854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688058","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, from which landlord his Department leases the Driving Test Theory Centre in Glasgow.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63855","63855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688059","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to revise Local Transport Note 2/08, Cycle Infrastructure Design, to reflect the Traffic Signs Regulations and General Directions 2016.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63857","63857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688060","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many full-time equivalent staff have been employed at Glasgow Theory Test Centre in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63838","63838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688061","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Government's policy will be on the level of parking charges at new parkway stations along the proposed High Speed 2 line in Yorkshire; and if he will make it his policy that revenues from such charges will be reinvested in the local community.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63785","63785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688062","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what comparative assessment he has made of the number and capacity of passengers using (a) parkway stations and (b) stations located in towns or cities near parkway stations.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63786","63786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688063","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has for the UK to ratify the UN Declaration on the Construction of Main International Traffic Arteries 1950.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63794","63794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688064","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many miles of track have been electrified since June 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63930","63930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688065","2017-02-20","Women and Equalities","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure the effective application of the public sector equality duty.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63793","63793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688066","2017-02-20","Women and Equalities","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how the Government plans to increase the level of engagement between government, civil society and women's organisations on gender equality.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63792","63792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688067","2017-02-20","Women and Equalities","2017-02-09","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent discussions she has had with her Cabinet colleagues on the implementation plan for Sustainable Development Goal 5.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63791","63791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688068","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the regulation of health and safety at work of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63782","63782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688069","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to bereavement payments on food poverty in (a) rural areas and (b) Hemsworth constituency.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63783","63783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688070","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to tackle food insecurity in rural areas; and if he will make an assessment of the reason for recent trends in the levels of such food insecurity.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63784","63784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688071","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of claimants subject to the lower benefit cap in Tynemouth are in receipt of (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) employment and support allowance, (c) income support, (d) housing benefit and (e) another benefit.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63843","63843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688072","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has further plans to meet Women Against State Pension Inequality campaigners; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63844","63844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688073","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people on release from Young Offender Institutions have had their benefits sanctioned or suspended in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63847","63847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688074","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2017 to Question 61821, on child poverty, what the evidential basis is to demonstrate that parental worklessness and children's educational attainment are the main two measures that can make the difference to child poverty.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63887","63887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688075","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2017 to Question 61821, on children: poverty, what the evidential basis is for replacing income-related targets with statutory measures of parental worklessness and children's educational attainment areas.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63926","63926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688076","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to publish a new emissions reduction plan.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63859","63859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688077","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of projects for which the Green Investment Bank will provide funding in the first 12 months after its sale to the Government's preferred bidder.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63860","63860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688078","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Government plan to publish its strategy on climate change.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63864","63864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688079","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to reply to the letter from the right hon. Member for Delyn of 10 January 2017 on construction industry blacklisting which sought a response to a letter from the right hon. Member for Delyn transferred to his Department by the Prime Minister on 28 October 2016.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63911","63911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688080","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the names are of the members of the High Level Stakeholder Working Group on EU Exit, Universities, Research and Innovation; how regularly that group meets; and what that group's terms of reference are.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63880","63880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688081","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent representations he has received from Toshiba on the future of the planned nuclear plant at Moorside; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63809","63809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688082","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Government plans to publish its strategy to fight climate change.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63823","63823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688083","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to publish its Emissions Reduction Plan.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63824","63824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688084","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received from firms interested in the planned nuclear plant at Moorside; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63808","63808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/688085","2017-02-20","Department for International Trade","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the value is of total exports from each UK region to (a) the EU, (b) the US and (c) China.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63832","63832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/690514","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that employers are encouraged to recruit and retain disabled people.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908756","908756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691580","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of trends in the number of people in work in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908774","908774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/691890","2017-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to help promote peace and human rights in South Sudan.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908740","908740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692238","2017-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to (a) support democracy in and (b) strengthen UK relations with countries in Africa.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908818","908818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692239","2017-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of civilian casualties in Syria as a result of UK air strikes.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908817","908817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692240","2017-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of progress towards a two-state solution for Israel and Palestine.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908821","908821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692241","2017-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political situation in the Republic of Congo.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908827","908827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692242","2017-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political and security situation in the Gambia.","Biography information for John Cryer","John Cryer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908816","908816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692243","2017-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to (a) support democracy in and (b) strengthen UK relations with countries in Africa.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908822","908822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692248","2017-02-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Chinese counterpart on the treatment of human rights activists in that country.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908826","908826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692751","2017-02-22","Department for International Development","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the Common External Tariff on developing countries.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908742","908742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692752","2017-02-22","Department for International Development","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to promote development across the Commonwealth.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908743","908743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692753","2017-02-22","Department for International Development","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Yemen.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908741","908741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/692754","2017-02-22","Department for International Development","2017-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to NGOs promoting human rights in the Occupied Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 908744","908744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686929","2017-02-23","Attorney General","2017-02-08","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the compatibility of the European Arrest Warrant system with the principle of habeas corpus; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63780","63780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686930","2017-02-20","Attorney General","2017-02-08","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2017 to Question 62528,what the number of security passes issued by his Department to people not employed by his Department is; what business needs suffice for such a security pass to be granted; and what the number of passes issued to people who work for private companies which have currently or previously been awarded government contracts or which are bidding for such contracts is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63757","63757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686931","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make provisions to allow military personnel who have served in Northern Ireland as part of Operation Helvetic to receive operational service medals, where merited.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63773","63773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686932","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether there is a Memorandum of Understanding between the Government and Surrey County Council regarding the funding of social care.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63735","63735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686933","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the population of (a) Bury North constituency, (b) the Metropolitan Borough of Bury, (c) the area covered by the Greater Manchester Combined Authority and (d) the UK was in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63659","63659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686934","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the population of (a) Bury North constituency, (b) the Metropolitan Borough of Bury, (c) the area covered by the Greater Manchester Combined Authority and (d) the UK is projected to be in each year until 2035.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63660","63660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686935","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average household size is projected to be for each year up to 2035 for (a) Bury North constituency, (b) the Metropolitan Borough of Bury, (c) the area covered by the Greater Manchester Combined Authority and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63658","63658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686936","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions the Government has had with electoral management system suppliers to assess the viability of an online registration checking tool; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63662","63662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686937","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average household size was for each year since 1997 for (a) Bury North Constituency, (b) the Metropolitan Borough of Bury, (c) the area covered by the Greater Manchester Combined Authority and (d) the UK.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63657","63657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686938","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average annual pay for (a) men and (b) women in (i) St Helens North constituency, (ii) Merseyside and (iii) the UK was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63592","63592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686939","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received national insurance contributions relief for approved company share option plans in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63587","63587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686940","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses made use of the corporation tax rate for small companies in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63597","63597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686941","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received national insurance contributions relief for share incentive plans in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63598","63598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686942","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses had their profits charged to tonnage tax in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63596","63596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686943","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received inheritance tax successive charges relief in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63627","63627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686944","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received petroleum revenue tax relief for exploration and appraisal expenditure in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63615","63615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686945","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received capital gains tax relief for the Seed Enterprise Investment Scheme in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63616","63616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686946","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received capital gains tax relief for the Venture Capital Trusts in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63617","63617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686947","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses claimed lower profits limit on national insurance contributions in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63618","63618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686948","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received inheritance tax exemption of certain expenses of hon. Members, government ministers etc. in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15; and what categories of expenses are exempt.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63628","63628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686949","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received national insurance contributions relief for employer contributions to registered pensions schemes in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63619","63619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686950","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received national insurance contributions relief for employer supported childcare including workplace nurseries in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63620","63620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686951","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received inheritance tax relief for transfers to political parties on death in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63623","63623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686952","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received inheritance woodlands relief for inheritance tax in  (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63624","63624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686953","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received double taxation relief for inheritance tax in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63625","63625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686954","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received inheritance tax taper relief on transfers between three to seven years before death in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63626","63626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686955","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received inheritance tax relief for interest-free instalments in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63622","63622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686956","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) people and (b) businesses received national insurance contributions relief for Save As You Earn in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63621","63621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686957","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on small investors of the cancellation of the public offer of shares in Lloyds Banking Group.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63554","63554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686958","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons the public offer of shares in Lloyds Banking Group was cancelled.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63555","63555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686959","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employees at (a) Bradford Centenary Court, (b) Bradford The Interchange, (c) Grimsby Imperial House, (d) Harrogate Victoria Avenue, (e) Hull Cherry Court, (f) Leeds Munroe Court, (g) Leeds Castle House, (h) Leeds Peter Bennett House (i) Leeds Windsor House, (j) Sheffield Concept House, (k) Shipley Accounts Office and (l) York Swindon House have (i) left or (ii) signalled their intention to leave the employment of HM Revenue and Customs as a result of the estate transformation programme.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63689","63689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686960","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of adult UK citizens without a UK bank account.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63665","63665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686961","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs assessed the effect of introducing its Making Tax Digital proposals on (a) freelance workers in the creative industries and (b) other specific sectors as part of its recent impact assessment of the net cost to businesses of implementing those proposals.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63739","63739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686962","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the details of any memorandum of understanding between his Department and Surrey County Council in relation to funding for social care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63775","63775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686963","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.10 of the Government's response to the independent review of the Money Advice Service, published in March 2015, when his Department plans to publish the terms of reference for an in-depth review of the impacts of additional statutory consumer protections.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63759","63759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686964","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the details of any memorandum of understanding between his Department and Surrey County Council in relation to funding for social care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63774","63774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686965","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether there is a memorandum of understanding between the Government and Surrey County Council regarding the funding of social care.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63734","63734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686966","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish all written or electronic correspondence between ministers and officials in his Department and Surrey County Council on social care funding and the council's proposed referendum on that subject.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63697","63697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686967","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many families with children aged under five have taken part in the Troubled Families programme; and what proportion of the Troubled Families programme budget has been allocated to support those families in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63712","63712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686968","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 20 January 2016 to Question 21620, what assessment he has made of the implications for (a) the number of Starter Homes to be delivered over the course of this Parliament, (b) the proportion of such homes reserved for first-time buyers and (c) the cost of such homes relative to the market price of the publication of Fixing our broken housing market, on 7 February 2017.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63713","63713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686969","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has to mark Hanukkah in 2017.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63566","63566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686970","2017-02-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will issue advice to local authorities on increasing the minimum size of car parking spaces in their car parks to take account of the increasing average size of new cars; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63589","63589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686971","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) households and (b) businesses have participated in the Government's Better Broadband Subsidy Scheme.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63575","63575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686972","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the General Data Protection Regulation will be implemented in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63551","63551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686973","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to announce the Government's new youth policy statement before the 2017 Spring Budget.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63558","63558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686974","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which organisations she has consulted on the Government's proposed new youth policy statement.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63559","63559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686975","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on broadcasting rights for UK companies in other EU member states.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63691","63691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686976","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the facility people have to move and re-use data held by social networking websites; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63701","63701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686977","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraph 2.289 of Budget 2015, how much of the £3.5 million announced to trial the development and provision of call blocking technology and tackle nuisance calls has been spent or allocated to date.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63703","63703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686978","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure that the new youth policy statement (a) takes account of changes in and (b) increases funding for youth services.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63640","63640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686979","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the leasing arrangements are for the Army Personnel Centre at Kentigern House in Glasgow; and when such arrangements are due for renewal.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63722","63722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686980","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to raise the minimum age of enlistment into the armed forces to 18 years of age.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63709","63709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686981","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff are employed at the Army Personnel Centre at Kentigern House in Glasgow.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63723","63723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686982","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has put in place to ensure the continuation of secure personal correspondence between armed forces personnel deployed in remote locations and their families after the e-bluey system ends on 31 March 2017.","Biography information for Robert Courts","Robert Courts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63576","63576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686983","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which date his Department has identified for the total withdrawal of British troops from Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63590","63590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686984","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Army Reserve's Order of Battle.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63647","63647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686985","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2017 to Question 59691, what (a) proportion and (b) number of children who did not achieve a good level of development in 2016 according to the early years foundation stage framework attended a maintained nursery school.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63599","63599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686986","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average class size was in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63591","63591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686987","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children's centres have been de-designated in each local authority since 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63594","63594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686988","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children's centres were deemed (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) requiring improvement and (d) unsatisfactory (i) nationally, (ii) regionally and (iii) in each local authority in the last 12 months for which figures are available; and how many such centres remain to be inspected.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63595","63595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686989","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to publish its revised statutory guidance and model agreement for local authorities on the provision of early education and childcare.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63552","63552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686990","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the three and four year-old extended childcare entitlement pilot scheme in York.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63553","63553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686991","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings her Department has had with (a) City of York Council and (b) early years providers in York to discuss the three and four year-old extended childcare entitlement pilot scheme since September 2016.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63556","63556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686992","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will introduce compulsory education on antibiotics and antibiotic resistance as part of the primary school curriculum.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63726","63726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686993","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what framework his Department plans to use to evaluate the roll-out of tax-free-childcare and its effect on (a) parental employment, (b) childcare prices and (c) quality of childcare.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63767","63767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686994","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which grammar schools have requested funding from her Department for onsite or annex expansion of existing selective schools since September 2016.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63742","63742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686995","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many full-time equivalent staff are working in her Department's selective education team.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63743","63743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686996","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many times (a) Ministers and (b) officials of her Department have met the (i) Grammar School Heads' Association and (ii) National Association of Secondary Moderns in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63744","63744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686997","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she made of the effectiveness of the Early Years Apprenticeship Trailblazer Group.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63745","63745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686998","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to change the membership of the Early Years Apprenticeship Trailblazer Group.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63746","63746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686999","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made by the Early Years Apprenticeship Trailblazer Group.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63747","63747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687000","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students from each ethnic background at state-funded schools and further education colleges achieved three or more A* or A grades at A level in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63760","63760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687001","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on attainment at A-level by students from different ethnic backgrounds.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63761","63761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687002","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on attainment at A-level by students from different socio-economic backgrounds.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63762","63762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687003","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps her Department has taken to encourage the uptake of STEM subjects by female students.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63715","63715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687004","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the number of Sure Start children's centres for the provision of children's services.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63700","63700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687005","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2017 to Question 61138, on adult education, whether her Department has decided not to publish its approach to lifetime learning for adults.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63698","63698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687006","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions the Environment Agency has had with local authorities in the Anglian region on reopening the navigable waterways in that region which have been closed by the Environment Agency since 2006.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63670","63670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687007","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will have discussions with the Environment Agency on reopening the navigable waterways in the Anglian region which have been closed by that agency since 2006.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63671","63671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687008","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the cost to the public purse of reopening the navigable waterways in the Anglian region which have been closed by the Environment Agency since 2006; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63674","63674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687009","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the oral evidence of the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State to the Environmental Audit Committee of 31 January 2017, what powers of oversight and enforcement the Council of Europe has in relation to monitoring marine protected areas in compliance with the Bern Convention.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63740","63740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687010","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what penalties there are for (a) supplying and (b) serving illegally caught sea bass.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63577","63577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687011","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she plans to pursue enforcement action on the site owned by the Crown Estate in Worksop previously occupied by Trent Valley Recycling; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63646","63646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687012","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential risks to public safety from the Trent Valley Crown Estate site used for recycling in Worksop.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63644","63644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687013","2017-02-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the Government's potential liabilities in the event that fire occurs at the Crown Estate site in Worksop previously occupied by Trent Valley Recycling.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63645","63645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687014","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Palestinian authorities on water quality in Gaza.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63583","63583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687015","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Israeli authorities on the quality of people's health in Gaza.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63584","63584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687016","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed tax (a) avoidance and (b) evasion with the Government of the Pitcairn Islands since the last Joint Ministerial Council.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63562","63562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687017","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed tax (a) avoidance and (b) evasion with the Government of Tristan da Cunha since the last Joint Ministerial Council.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63563","63563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687018","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has discussed tax (a) avoidance and (b) evasion with the Government of St Helena since the last Joint Ministerial Council.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63560","63560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687019","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to promote stability and support the Philippines during its state of national emergency.","Biography information for Claire Perry","Claire Perry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63561","63561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687020","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which Minister in his Department leads on discussions at EU level on the wellbeing of Syrian refugees who have entered mainland Europe.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63772","63772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687021","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Bahrainian Government on the case of Zainab Al-Khawaja.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63677","63677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687022","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to work with the Governments of Turkey and Russia on maximising the likelihood of adherence to the ceasefire in Syria.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63717","63717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687023","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to monitor adherence to the ceasefire in Syria.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63718","63718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687024","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to make representations to the US Administration on the recent changes in US immigration policy.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63692","63692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687025","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Bahrainian Government on the case of Ebrahim Sharif.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63682","63682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687026","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Bahrainian Government on the case of Sheikh Isa Qassim.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63683","63683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687027","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Bahrainian Government on licence renewals for journalists.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63684","63684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687028","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Bahrainian Government on the (a) dissolution of the Al-Wefaq political party and (b) imprisonment of Sheikh Ali Salman.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63681","63681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687029","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Egyptian authorities on the case of Ibrahim Halawa.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63685","63685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687030","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of reports that Bahrain's anti-terrorism legislation has been used to target civil society organisations and human rights activists in that country.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63680","63680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687031","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Bahrainian Government on the imposition of travel bans on human rights defenders, trade unionists, lawyers and political activists.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63678","63678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687032","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Bahrainian Government on the operation of civil societies.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63679","63679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687033","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the capacity of the Ukrainian authorities to provide government services to civilians living in districts under separatist control; and what representations he has made to his Ukrainian counterpart on the provision of services to such civilians.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63634","63634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687034","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of (a) Ukraine and (b) Russia on the presence of military equipment and troops in civilian-populated areas of eastern Ukraine.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63635","63635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687035","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of foreign fighters in eastern Ukraine.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63636","63636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687036","2017-02-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of Ukrainian civilians living along the line of separation between the breakaway districts of the Donetsk and Luhansk oblasts and the rest of Ukraine; and the number of civilians living in combat zones on either side of that line.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63637","63637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687037","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proposals he has received on the organisational form of the new body to be created from the merger of NHS Property Services and Community Health Partnerships; and what role sustainability and transformation plans will play in determining that organisational form.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63649","63649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687038","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 January 2017 to Question 60683, on neuromuscular disorders: South East, how many neuromuscular care advisors will cover Kent, Surrey and Sussex; which clinical commissioning groups in Kent, Surrey and Sussex will contribute to funding neuromuscular care advisor roles; what the remit will be of Brighton and Sussex University Hospitals NHS Trust in this process; and when it is planned for relevant clinical commissioning groups to finalise job descriptions and begin recruitment.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63661","63661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687039","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to phase out the practice of out-of-area placements across England, as recommended by the Commission on Acute Adult Psychiatric Care.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63648","63648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687040","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans for NHS England to publish its plans for allocation of the £326,000 of funding from the General Practice Forward View to be spent in the Bristol, North Somerset and South Gloucestershire Sustainability and Transformation Plan.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63651","63651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687041","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timescale is for NHS Protect's investigation into the conduct of Phil Morley while he was Chief Executive of the Hull and East Yorkshire Hospitals NHS Trust.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63667","63667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687042","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Welsh Assembly Government on holding a public inquiry into the contaminated blood scandal.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63668","63668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687043","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the ovarian cancer-specific service specification submitted for approval by the Complex Gynaecological Services Clinical Reference Group in 2015.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63653","63653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687044","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to continue to provide additional funding to cover increases in market rents in buildings from which clinical commissioning groups commission services.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63650","63650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687045","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the business case for the creation of a new organisation from NHS Property Services and Community Health Partnerships.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63652","63652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687046","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of how many relapsed/refractory Hodgkin lymphoma patients will not receive stem cell transplants if brentuximab vedotin is removed as a standard of care.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63694","63694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687047","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of trends in hospital admissions due to alcohol in the last 10 years; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce such admissions.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63710","63710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687048","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many registered health professionals were directly employed by his Department on 1 February (a) 2017 and (b) 2016; and how many such professionals in each of those years were in which profession.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63716","63716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687049","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the Internal Medicine commissioning policy plans are for the provision of Transcatheter Aortic Valve Implantation; and if he will ensure that such plans are published.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63751","63751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687050","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of nationals of other EU countries currently working in the NHS as psychiatric nurses; what the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU would be on the number of such nurses; and what the potential effect on NHS productivity of that change in the number of such nurses would be.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63731","63731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687051","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of (i) male and (ii) female prisoners who have a personality disorder.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63732","63732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687052","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether there is a memorandum of understanding between the Government and Surrey County Council on social care funding.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63733","63733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687053","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2017 to Question 62839, how many people waited more than 28 days for a transfer to hospital under the Mental Health Act 1983 in each quarter since quarter one of 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63730","63730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687054","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many blue code emergencies there were in prisons in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63728","63728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687055","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many self-inflicted deaths there were of former prisoners in England within 14 days of their release in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63729","63729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687056","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 February 2017 to Question 62427, on nurses: pay, what other recommendations or advice his Department takes into account when determining pay awards.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63725","63725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687057","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of hospital beds taken up because of delayed transfers of care in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63695","63695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687058","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England plans to publish its commissioning policy on Transcatheter Aortic Valve Implantation.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63752","63752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687059","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England has placed a cap on the number of Transcatheter Aortic Valve Implantation procedures that can be performed nationally or in any locality.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63750","63750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687061","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people with relapsed and refractory Hodgkin lymphoma receive brentuximab vedotin through the NHS.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63755","63755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687062","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NICE plans to report on the availability of FreeStyle Libre on the NHS.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63557","63557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687063","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what procedures are in place to ensure that clinical commissioning groups fund preventative medicines in accordance with NICE guidelines.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63585","63585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687064","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full time equivalent health visitors there were in (a) England, (b) each region and (c) each local authority in (i) May 2015 and (ii) the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63586","63586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687066","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of progress with and the effectiveness of the Sustainability Transformation Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63569","63569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687067","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total amount recovered was from non-EU nationals in respect of (a) accident and emergency admissions, (b) non-urgent care and surgery and (c) urgent care and surgery in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63581","63581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687068","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the viability of making valid travel medical insurance a requirement for all persons applying for a UK visit visa.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63582","63582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687069","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of children receive an assessment of their development by health visitors (a) after birth, (b) at six to eight weeks, (c) at one year old and (d) between two and two and a half years old in (i) England, (ii) each region and (iii) each local authority.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63578","63578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687070","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS was of care provided to non-EU nationals in (a) accident and emergency, (b) non-urgent care and surgery and (c) urgent care and surgery in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63579","63579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687071","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was recovered from medical travel insurance for care provided to non-EU nationals in (a) accident and emergency, (b) non-urgent care and surgery and (c) urgent care and surgery in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63580","63580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687072","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the amount of funding spent by (a) clinical commissioning groups and (b) local authorities on supporting children and families in the early years in (i) England, (ii) each region and (iii) each local authority.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63571","63571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687073","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of perinatal depression there have been recorded in each (a) region and (b) clinical commissioning group area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63572","63572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687074","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the number and proportion of visitors to the UK in possession of valid travel medical insurance in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63573","63573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687075","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the number of non-EU nationals using NHS services who had valid travel medical insurance in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63574","63574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687077","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will create a single database for incident reporting in care homes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63641","63641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687078","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the amount from the Sustainability Transformation Fund that has been diverted to pay down NHS Trust deficits since that fund was established.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63642","63642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687079","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question 49671, the Answer of 31 October 2016 to Question 50008 and the Answer of 8 November 2016 to Question 51652, what the role is of NHS England in ensuring that clinical commissioning groups (CCGs) are fulfilling their statutory role when changing local policy or local guidelines related to access to medical nutrition; what mechanisms are in place to ensure that when CCGs do not follow NICE guidance there is a clear clinical case for not doing so; and what oversight NHS England has in making sure that CCG decisions are consistent with NICE and NHS England guidance on commissioning.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63614","63614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687080","2017-02-20","Department of Health","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Schengen area travel visa insurance scheme on the level of health tourism in the UK.","Biography information for Gareth Johnson","Gareth Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63613","63613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687081","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2017 to Question 61991, on what date the issue of the omission relating to the recording of licence conditions on the Police National Computer was resolved.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63593","63593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687082","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of prisoners in England and Wales have a profile on the national DNA database.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63609","63609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687083","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been given 15 cautions or more in each of the last five years by age group.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63610","63610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687084","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to publish the Counter Extremism Bill.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63630","63630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687085","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 61413, on general practitioners: foreign nationals, on how many occasions the Tier 2 (General) category annual limit has been reached since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63605","63605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687086","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 61413, on general practitioners: foreign nationals, which occupations are on the Shortage Occupation List.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63606","63606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687087","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 61413, on general practitioners: foreign nationals, whether GPs are on the Shortage Occupation List.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63607","63607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687088","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she plans to take in response to the letter of 10 January 2017 from the Independent Anti-Slavery Commissioner on identifying, referring and supporting victims of modern slavery in the UK's National Referral Mechanism.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63608","63608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687089","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 61413, on general practitioners: foreign nationals, on how many occasions the Tier 2 (General) category annual limit has been reached only by occupations on the Shortage Occupation List since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63604","63604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687091","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether UK Visas and Immigration plans to publish guidelines on how earnings and dividends should be presented where the income threshold is met by the sponsor for entry clearance under Appendix FM applications.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63753","63753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687092","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of Official Development Assistance funding was used to support people trafficked into the sex industry in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63748","63748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687093","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the task force announced by the Prime Minister on 31 July 2016 to accelerate progress on tackling modern slavery.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63763","63763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687094","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been referred to drug and alcohol dependency programmes under Section 17 of the Policing and Crime Act 2009 since that Act came into force.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63764","63764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687095","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of Section 17 of the Policing and Crime Act 2009 on improving safety and support for people involved in prostitution.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63765","63765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687096","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of Section 14 of the Policing and Crime Act 2009.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63766","63766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687097","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, where people can receive advice on how to present evidence on earnings and dividends as part of the financial requirement to be considered as part of an entry clearance application for a family member.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63754","63754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687098","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what standards of prison (a) conditions and (b) accommodation must be met by a country applying under the European Arrest Warrant system for a UK resident to be extradited, before a UK court will agree to such an application; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63778","63778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687099","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria a resident of the UK would have to meet to resist the application of a European Arrest Warrant for extradition to another EU country.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63779","63779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687100","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Written Statement of 8 February 2017, HCWS467, on immigration, on what date she decided to change the number of unaccompanied child refugees taken by the UK under the Dubs amendment.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63727","63727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687101","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what standards of evidence are required in UK courts for an application for extradition under a European Arrest Warrant to be granted; and what the safeguards are to prevent UK residents being extradited to another EU country, without evidence being produced against them in UK courts.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63777","63777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687102","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Minister of her Department leads on discussions at EU level on the wellbeing of Syrian refugees who have entered mainland Europe.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63770","63770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687103","2017-02-23","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications have been made for the extradition of residents in the UK under the provisions of the European Arrest Warrant in each of the last five years; which countries made those applications; and how many of those applications (a) were granted, (b) were rejected and (c) are still under consideration by UK courts.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63776","63776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687104","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness, value for money and implications for the police code of ethics of the practice of paying informants on the part of the police and security services.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63707","63707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687105","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) how many and (b) which local authorities offered no spaces for unaccompanied asylum-seeking children under the Dubs amendment.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63693","63693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687106","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on applicants for further leave to remain, indefinite leave or citizenship losing their jobs on account of not being able to show original documents to support such applications; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63688","63688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687107","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken is to respond to requests by hon. Members to visit immigration removal centres.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63656","63656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687108","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what  her policy is on granting hon. Members clearance to visit immigration removal centres outside of their constituency.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63654","63654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687109","2017-02-20","Home Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many hon. Members have (a) requested and (b) been granted clearance to visit (i) immigration removal centres and (ii) Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63655","63655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687110","2017-02-20","House of Commons Commission","2017-02-08","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many contract staff the House employs on zero-hours contracts; and what information it holds on the number of such staff employed by the House of Lords.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63603","63603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687111","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support and cooperation her Department is providing to the Middle East Desalination Research Centre in Oman.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63588","63588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687112","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much and what proportion of her Department's spending was made in India through the World Bank in 2015-16.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63600","63600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687113","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's financial contribution to the World Bank was in 2015-16.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63601","63601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687114","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to deliver the UN's Step it Up for gender equality agenda.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63686","63686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687115","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to protect female refugees against exploitation and sexual violence.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63687","63687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687116","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to assess the practicability of delivering aid to besieged areas of Syria by drone; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63719","63719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687117","2017-02-20","Department for International Development","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that its humanitarian programme is gender-responsive.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63669","63669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687118","2017-02-20","Department for International Trade","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether rulings of the World Trade Organisation (WTO) Dispute Settlement Body constitute binding legal obligations with which all members of the WTO must comply; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63699","63699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687119","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many remand prisoners have been held in police stations until a prison place became available rather than returned to prison following a court appearance in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63714","63714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687120","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions under section 14 of the Policing and Crime Act 2009 have been successful.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63749","63749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687121","2017-02-20","Ministry of Justice","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have had 15 criminal convictions or more in each of the last five years by age group.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63611","63611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687122","2017-02-20","Leader of the House","2017-02-08","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will hold discussions with his Cabinet colleagues to ensure that Standing Orders Numbers 83J to 83Y do not apply to proceedings relating to the Great Repeal Bill; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63629","63629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687123","2017-02-20","Northern Ireland Office","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps he plans to take to safeguard the implementation bodies set up under the Belfast Agreement 1998 after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63724","63724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687124","2017-02-20","Prime Minister","2017-02-08","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she discussed matters relating to (a) Israel's nuclear weapons arsenal and (b) prospects of Israel joining the multilateral Nuclear Non-Proliferation Treaty with her Israeli counterpart during his visit of 6 February 2017.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63602","63602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687125","2017-02-20","Prime Minister","2017-02-08","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she discussed a two-state solution with the Prime Minister of Israel during his visit to the UK of February 2017.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63570","63570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687126","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what evidence has been provided by Govia Thameslink Railway in its claim of force majeure to support the assertion that industrial action by staff is unofficial.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63567","63567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687127","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with the Office of Rail and Road on the new dual carriageway planned for 13 miles of the A1 north of Newcastle.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63738","63738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687128","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date the new dual carriageway planned for 13 miles of the A1 north of Newcastle will begin construction.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63736","63736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687129","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of the new dual carriageway planned for 13 miles of the A1 north of Newcastle.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63737","63737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687130","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's news story of 7 February 2017 on fines for taxi drivers who refuse to transport wheelchair users, whether those fines will be applied to taxi drivers refusing to transport guide dog users.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63756","63756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687131","2017-02-22","Department for Transport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many hackney carriage licences have been revoked by local authorities on the grounds of the licence holder no longer being a fit and proper person in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63704","63704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687132","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the (a) transparency and (b) impartiality of its assessment of the force majeure claims made by Govia Thameslink Railway for industrial action.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63675","63675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687133","2017-02-20","Department for Transport","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many UK citizens do not hold either a (a) UK driving licence or (b) provisional UK driving licence.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63666","63666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687134","2017-02-20","Women and Equalities","2017-02-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how Sustainable Development Goal 5 has been incorporated into the Government Equality Office's single department plan.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63676","63676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687135","2017-02-20","Women and Equalities","2017-02-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the planned date is for publication of the evaluation report on the Access to Elected Office pilot fund.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63565","63565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687136","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of allowing women affected by the increase in state pension age to retire early on a reduced pension; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63564","63564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687137","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effect of changes in the level of inflation on working age benefit claimants in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63631","63631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687138","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effect of changes in the level of inflation on the value of social security benefits in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63632","63632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687139","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many young people leaving care have had their benefits sanctioned or suspended in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63643","63643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687140","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of universal credit claimants who have been threatened with eviction because of the six-week waiting period to receive a payment.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63708","63708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687141","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward legislative proposals to repeal section 1 of the Employment of Women, Young Persons and Children Act 1920 in so far as that provision applies to voluntary work by persons under the age of 16 engaged in heritage railways, canal charities and similar undertakings.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63672","63672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687143","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with financial services providers on the potential role of equity release in helping to meet challenges posed by an ageing population.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63720","63720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687144","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department has issued to Jobcentre Plus on referrals of claimants to JD Sports.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63702","63702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687145","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of universal credit on (a) levels of rent arrears, (b) numbers of evictions and (c) in other areas for people in temporary accommodation in universal credit pilot areas.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63664","63664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687146","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what advice services there are for people with a child maintenance arrangement who (a) are moving away from Child Support Agency (CSA) arrangements and (b) have a child maintenance arrangement with the CSA.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63663","63663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687147","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of the effect of universal credit on people in temporary accommodation in the universal credit pilot areas compared to people in temporary accommodation in other areas.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63639","63639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687148","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2017 to Question 58104, if he will estimate the number of (a) parents and (b) lone parents with a youngest child aged three are expected to look for work if they want to claim universal credit or tax credits from April 2017.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63741","63741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687149","2017-02-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government plans to carry out an assessment or reconsideration of the six-week waiting period for universal credit claimants to receive payments.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63706","63706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687151","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received about energy price rises in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63696","63696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687152","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government takes into account the track record of companies interested in purchasing Green Investment Bank assets when deciding whether to permit a sale to go ahead.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63769","63769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687153","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government plans to put in place any measures to prevent asset stripping or other abuses by companies which purchase Green Investment Bank assets.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63768","63768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687154","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2017 to Question 62603, what the number of security passes issued by his Department to people not employed by his Department is; what business needs suffice for such a security pass to be granted; and what the number of passes issued to people who work for private companies which have currently or previously been awarded government contracts or which are bidding for such contracts is.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63758","63758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687155","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to publish the Government's response to the consultation on the post office network which closed on 21 December 2016.","Biography information for Simon Hoare","Simon Hoare","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63638","63638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687156","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of EU regulations on the labelling of animal fur on consumer protection; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63705","63705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687157","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the continued financial viability of the Post Office network; and whether he plans to change the level of funding provided to that network.","Biography information for Simon Hoare","Simon Hoare","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63673","63673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687158","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions his Department has had with energy companies on arrangements for the recovery of the cost from customers' bills of the installation of smart meters.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63711","63711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687159","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of use of Post Office branches for banking.","Biography information for Simon Hoare","Simon Hoare","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63633","63633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687160","2017-02-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2016 to Question 47517, whether the Government has completed an assessment of the legal and policy implications of the UK's membership of Euratom.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63612","63612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687161","2017-02-20","Department for International Trade","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what account he plans to take of other countries' observance of Article 18 of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights when planning new trade deals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63568","63568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687162","2017-02-20","Department for International Trade","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he plans to maintain the same trading relationship with Bangladesh after the UK leaves the EU as that which was established by the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63721","63721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687163","2017-02-20","Department for International Trade","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure that trade deals which he negotiates after the UK leaves the EU are equitable to and provide support for poorer and developing countries.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63771","63771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/687164","2017-02-20","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-02-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2017 to Question 60045, how many full-time equivalent staff his Department had as of 1 January 2017.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63690","63690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686043","2017-02-09","Attorney General","2017-02-07","To ask the Attorney General, whether the CPS has made an assessment of the potential grounds for prosecuting Phil Shiner for the false allegations he made against members of the Armed Forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63373","63373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686044","2017-02-09","Attorney General","2017-02-07","To ask the Attorney General, what discussions he has had with the CPS on the potential grounds for prosecuting Phil Shiner for his role in making false allegations against members of the Armed Forces and the misuse of public funds.","Biography information for Sir Julian Brazier","Sir Julian Brazier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63372","63372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686045","2017-02-09","Attorney General","2017-02-07","To ask the Attorney General, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the Government's consultation on sentences for dangerous driving.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63425","63425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686046","2017-02-09","Attorney General","2017-02-07","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he is taking to ensure that the CPS deal sensitively with elderly witnesses who are afraid of giving evidence in court.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63426","63426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686047","2017-02-09","Cabinet Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many premature deaths have been attributed to the effects of particulate air pollution in London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63497","63497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686050","2017-02-20","Cabinet Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to reform postal voting to protect against voter fraud.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63547","63547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686051","2017-02-09","Cabinet Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2017 to Question 59728, for what reasons the minutes of the Data Steering Group's meetings from February to September 2016 were not published until January 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63361","63361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686052","2017-02-09","Cabinet Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January 2017 to Question 59728, what steps he plans to take to ensure that minutes of meetings of the Data Steering Group are published in a timely fashion.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63362","63362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686053","2017-02-09","Cabinet Office","2017-02-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent discussions he has had with the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman (PHSO) on staffing and funding levels in the PHSO offices.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63352","63352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686054","2017-02-20","HM Treasury","2017-02-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a cap on early exit charges for people over the age of 55 seeking to transfer their personal pensions.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63447","63447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686055","2017-02-09","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what criteria his Department used to determine the preferred bidder in the sale of the Green Investment Bank; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63460","63460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686056","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the proportion of local councillors who are (a) women and (b) black, Asian or minority ethnic; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63526","63526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686057","2017-02-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the potential revenue that will be raised by local authorities after July 2017 as a result of the proposed changes in the level of planning fees local authorities may charge.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63539","63539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686058","2017-02-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will place in the Library the terms of reference for the review of the cost-effectiveness of current energy performance standards mentioned in Fixing our broken housing market, Cm 9352, Paragraph 150.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63492","63492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686059","2017-02-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average weekly rent in (a) social and (b) private sector rented housing in Warrington; and what proportion of the average weekly income in the borough each of those figures represent.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63411","63411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686060","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to review the effect of alcohol advertising on 10 to 15-year-olds following the recent report from Public Health England on alcohol control policies.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63376","63376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686061","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the findings of the Public Health England report entitled The Public Health Burden of Alcohol and the Effectiveness and Cost-Effectiveness of Alcohol Control Policies on the violation of self-regulation alcohol marketing codes in the UK; and what steps she plans to take in relation to vulnerable populations as a result.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63377","63377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686062","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations she has received on the implications for the UK continuing to access the Digital Single Market of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63325","63325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686063","2017-02-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the relevant European Commissioner on an adequacy decision for the protection of data transferred between the EU and the UK.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63548","63548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686064","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has undertaken an assessment of the potential merits of introducing proposals for the regulation of online dating sites.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63421","63421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686065","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to increase the reliability and affordability of mobile coverage in Morley and Outwood.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63471","63471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686066","2017-02-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to support the rollout of 5G.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63472","63472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686067","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to recognise the bravery and sacrifice of members of Army bomb disposal units who were killed or maimed during the Troubles in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63458","63458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686069","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to respond to the recent allegations of torture in Northern Ireland in the 1970s by army personnel; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63511","63511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686070","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made in contracting for the new mechanised infantry vehicles as outlined in the Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015, Column 9161.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63493","63493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686071","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the SA80 L85 A2's lifecycle.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63503","63503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686072","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to fill the vacancy of Chief Scientific Adviser to his Department; and what the timetable is for advertising and filling that vacancy.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63484","63484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686073","2017-02-09","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the progress of the UK military training programme in Ukraine; what assessment he has made of the effect of recent fatalities on the operational effectiveness of the Ukrainian armed forces; and what steps he is taking within the training programme to reduce the risk of further Ukrainian military casualties.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63388","63388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686074","2017-02-20","Ministry of Defence","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of current availability of tank transporters for the armed forces.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63451","63451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686075","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase out-of-hours support for foster carers (a) in Coventry South constituency and (b) nationally; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63416","63416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686076","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the potential effect of the new school funding formula on the level of funding for schools in Warrington North constituency in real terms for each of the next three years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63412","63412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686077","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 61381, what financial information her Department has provided to the community and stakeholders to inform their representations on the proposed closure of Baverstock Academy.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63407","63407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686078","2017-02-20","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2017 to Question 61379, what criteria her Department uses to assess the value for money of school closures.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63408","63408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686080","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2016 to Question 54215, on apprentices: females, how much funding her Department has (a) allocated and (b) spent on encouraging women to take up apprenticeships in construction, IT and engineering.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63338","63338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/686081","2017-02-09","Department for Education","2017-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2016 to Question 54215, on apprentices: females, what assessment she has made of the effect of the Get In Go Far campaign on the number of women taking up apprenticeships in construction, IT and engineering.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 63339","63339"
