"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866988","2018-03-21","Cabinet Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants by grade in each Government Department have completed formally recognised apprenticeships under (a) the Specification of Apprenticeship Standards for England scheme and (b) previous schemes.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133106","133106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866989","2018-03-22","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the findings of the recent report by Hope Not Hate, The state of hate 2018, what steps her Department plans to take to tackle neo-Nazism in the UK.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133107","133107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866990","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of people undertaking paid apprenticeships in Leeds North West constituency.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133108","133108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866991","2018-03-21","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has commissioned research on solar panel roadways and associated  technology; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133109","133109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866992","2018-03-22","Department for International Development","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions her Department has had with the United Nations Office for the Coordination of Humanitarian Affairs on steps to establish medical evacuations and increased humanitarian assistance in Eastern Ghouta.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133110","133110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866993","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he has taken to reduce the average waiting time for treatment for an eating disorder.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133111","133111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866994","2018-03-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what disability-specific training is provided to personal independence payment assessors to enable them to assess blind and partially sighted applicants.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133112","133112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866995","2018-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints (a) ATOS and (b) Capita received from blind and partially sighted applicants in respect of personal independence payments assessments in 2016-17.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133113","133113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866996","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of smoking cessations as a result of the introduction of regulations on the minimum size of tobacco and cigarette packs in 2017.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133114","133114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866997","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the adequacy of (a) support and (b) funding for staff employed at Pupil Referral Units.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133115","133115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866998","2018-03-21","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the European Union counterparts on the retention of free movement for British musicians working throughout Europe after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133116","133116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/866999","2018-03-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has in place to prevent a potential outbreak of foot and mouth disease among livestock.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133117","133117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867000","2018-03-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps he has taken to improve the recording of hate crimes against Gypsy, Roma and Traveller communities (a) in Yorkshire and the Humber and (b) throughout England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133118","133118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867001","2018-03-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to evaluate the effectiveness of the Disability Confident scheme.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133119","133119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867002","2018-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average hourly rate paid by his Department for agency staff is by grade.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133120","133120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867003","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people his Department has employed as contingent labour in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133121","133121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867004","2018-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average hourly rate paid by his Department for an agency probation officer is.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133122","133122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867005","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average hourly rate paid by his Department is for an agency worker in each category of role for which his Department uses agency workers.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133123","133123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867006","2018-03-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of households that use less than the average amount of water whose bills will increase as a result of the installation of a smart meter.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133124","133124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867007","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he has had with Northumberland County Council on that council's proposals to close 32 schools.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133125","133125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867008","2018-03-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the electromagnetic fields produced by smart meters are within the guidelines exposure levels set by his Department.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133126","133126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867009","2018-03-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to conduct future freedom of navigation operations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133127","133127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867010","2018-03-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with his (a) US, (b) Australian and (c) Chinese counterparts on freedom of navigation operations.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133128","133128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867011","2018-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of political interference in the (a) judiciary and (b) judicial system in Romania.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133129","133129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867012","2018-03-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 December 2017 to Question 117695, when his Department plans to publish its new strategic equality objectives.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133130","133130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867013","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 131630 on Dame Glenys Stacey, what date did was the secondment of the HM Chief Inspector of Probation to the Department of Food and Rural Affairs agreed by Ministers; and what assessment was made of the effect of that secondment on the work of  HM Inspectorate of Probation for England and Wales .","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133131","133131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867014","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 131630 on Dame Glenys Stacey, what additional (a) costs (b) staffing has the Department allocated to HM Inspectorate of Probation for England and Wales as a result of the secondment of Dame Glenys Stacey to the Department for Food and Rural Affairs.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133132","133132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867015","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 131630 on Dame Glenys Stacey, what changes to the (a) pay and (b) conditions will be made in respect of the secondment of Dame Glenys Stacey to the Department of Food and Rural Affairs.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133133","133133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867016","2018-03-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the new UN Special Envoy to Yemen on the conflict in that country.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133134","133134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867017","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for asylum are awaiting a decision.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133135","133135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867018","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of applications for asylum that are awaiting decision.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133136","133136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867019","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national offenders there are in UK prisons.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133137","133137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867020","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the value was of the assets seized under Unexplained Wealth Orders in 2017-18.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133138","133138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867021","2018-03-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many properties in the UK are owned by companies registered in (a) British Overseas Territories and (b) Crown Dependencies.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133139","133139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867022","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were detained at immigration centres at the end of each financial quarter in 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133140","133140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867023","2018-03-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the number of properties in the UK which are owned by companies registered in the Isle of Man.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133141","133141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867024","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of tier one visas were granted to Russian nationals between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133142","133142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867025","2018-03-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions has he had with the Secretary of State Designate in the United States on the war in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133143","133143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867026","2018-03-22","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Education of 13 March 2018, Official Report, Column 802, what steps he plans to take during the six month extension to the childcare voucher scheme to address the concerns raised in that debate.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133144","133144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867027","2018-03-22","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the (a) questions and (b) answers in the financial section of the Pre-Qualification Questionnaire completed by Carillion in respect of the contracts for HS2 awarded in July 2017.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133145","133145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867028","2018-03-22","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to include child and adolescent psychiatrists to the Shortage Occupation List.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133146","133146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867029","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many NHS child and adolescent psychiatrists have been employed in the East of England in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133147","133147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867030","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Tier 2 visa applications sponsored by the NHS for NHS child and adolescent psychiatrists were turned down in the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133148","133148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867031","2018-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2018 to Question 132158, on Prisons: Computers and Telephones, whether there were any prisons in which the pilot was started but ended before its scheduled completion.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133149","133149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867032","2018-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2018 to Question 132158, on Prisons: Computers and Telephones, whether there were any prisons in which work was undertaken in preparation for the pilot but the full pilot was not commenced.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133150","133150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867033","2018-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent to which the first round of elections held in Sierra Leone on 7 March 2018 were conducted in a free, fair and transparent manner.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133151","133151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867034","2018-03-22","Department for International Development","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with her counterpart in Sierra Leone on the temporary ban on female genital mutilation introduced by that Government; and if she will make representations to that Government to make the ban permanent.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133152","133152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867035","2018-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women in HMP New Hall gave birth while imprisoned in 2017.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133153","133153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867036","2018-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many pregnant women at HMP New Hall were given a place in a mother and baby unit in 2017.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133154","133154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867037","2018-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many women in HMP New Hall who had babies or infants resident with them in prison had those children taken away from them in 2017.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133155","133155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867038","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many lower limb amputations associated with peripheral arterial disease and diabetes have taken place in the NHS in each year since 2008-09; and how many of those amputations have taken place in each (a) strategic health authority area prior to 2012-13 and (b) clinical commissioning group area since 2012-13 .","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133156","133156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867039","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the NHS has spent on lower limb amputations in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133157","133157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867040","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the NHS has spent on rehabilitation following lower limb amputations in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133158","133158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867041","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much the NHS has spent on treating diabetic foot ulcers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133159","133159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867042","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many multidisciplinary foot care teams there are in the NHS; and how many of those teams have been established in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133160","133160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867043","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding will be made available for multidisciplinary foot care teams through the Diabetes Transformation Fund in each of the next financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133161","133161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867044","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on negotiating a new Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133162","133162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867045","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to allocate funding from the public purse to (a) businesses and (b) Government Departments to replace funding from the European Investment Bank when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133163","133163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867046","2018-03-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the timetable is for the launch of the Midlands Engine Investment Fund.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133164","133164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867047","2018-03-21","Department for International Development","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with (a) the UK financial services sector and (b) multilateral financial institutions on the (i) development and (ii) issue of catastrophe bonds as a tool for mitigating catastrophic risk for developing countries.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133165","133165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867048","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of primary school children were eligible for free schools meals in (a) 2009-2010, (b) 2013-2014 and (c) 2017-2018.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133166","133166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867049","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 132253 on Schools: Admissions, whether he has plans to strengthen the provisions of the Schools Admissions Code in respect of siblings.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133167","133167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867050","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 132251 on Asylum: Health Services, what recent discussions her Department has had with the Department of Heath and Social Care on the provision of health care for asylum seekers who will be housed in the proposed interim accommodation centre in Halton.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133168","133168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867051","2018-03-22","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 132219 on Home Office: Buildings, if she will publish the (a) area  and (b) expenditure on property represented by the information provided in the table.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133169","133169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867052","2018-03-21","Cabinet Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the success rates of the Gov.uk contracts finder.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133170","133170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867053","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has had with Telford and Wrekin Council on commissioning an independent inquiry into child sexual exploitation in that borough.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133171","133171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867054","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will commission an independent inquiry into child sexual exploitation in Telford.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133172","133172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867055","2018-03-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many staff from (a) his Department and (b) Homes England attended MIPIM international property conference 2018; and what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of their attending that event.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133173","133173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867056","2018-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress has been made on the Future Combat Air System; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133174","133174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867057","2018-03-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £185.1 million in EU exit funding for his Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133175","133175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867058","2018-03-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £26.2 million in EU exit funding for his Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133176","133176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867059","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if she will publish a list of where the £395 million in EU exit funding for her Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133177","133177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867060","2018-03-22","Department for International Development","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Answer of 23 February 2017 to Question 64650, of how many Palestinian Authority Ministry of Education public servants her Department pays the salaries.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133178","133178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867061","2018-03-22","Department for International Development","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Answer of 23 February 2017 to Question 64650, of how many Palestinian Authority Ministry of Education teachers her Department pays the salaries.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133179","133179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867062","2018-03-21","Department for International Trade","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £74 million in EU exit funding for his Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133180","133180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867063","2018-03-22","Department for International Development","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which the schools are in the West Bank for which her Department pays the salaries of the teachers.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133181","133181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867064","2018-03-21","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £75.8 million EU exit funding for his Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133182","133182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867065","2018-03-22","Department for International Development","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2017 to Question 64650, whether any of those public servants in the West Bank, whose salaries are paid by her Department, are responsible for writing, approving or implementing the 2017 Palestinian Authority schools curriculum.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133183","133183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867066","2018-03-22","Department for International Development","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Answer of 23 February 2017 to Question 64650, whether any teachers in the West Bank whom her Department pays the salaries of are teaching at schools that deliver the revised 2017 Palestinian Authority curriculum.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133184","133184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867067","2018-03-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many households in (a) Barandon Walk, (b) Testerton Walk, (c) Hurstway Walk, (d) Treadgold House and (e) Bramley House require rehousing as a result of the Grenfell Tower fire; and how many of those households have been rehoused in (i) emergency accommodation, (ii) temporary accommodation and (iii) permanent accommodation.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133185","133185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867068","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people under the age of 18 have been admitted to hospital as a result of overdosing on (a) paracetamol and (b) ibuprofenin in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133186","133186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867069","2018-03-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the consultation on Funding for supported housing, published on 31 October 2017, when he plans to publish his Department's final proposals.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133187","133187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867070","2018-03-21","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what penalties his Department imposes on rail operators who repeatedly use short-formed trains.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133188","133188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867071","2018-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many left-hand drive vehicles the Armed Forces have; what those vehicles are; and how many of those vehicles are being used in the UK.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133189","133189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867072","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Early Years Workforce Strategy published in March 2017,whether his Department has completed a feasibility study into a programme to grow the graduate early years workforce in disadvantaged areas.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133190","133190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867073","2018-03-21","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many short-formed trains were run by Northern in each month from the beginning of its current franchise agreement to date.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133191","133191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867074","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number and proportion of (a) maintained primary schools, (b) maintained secondary schools, (c) academies, (d) free schools and (e) sixth form colleges in England which have not fulfilled the legal requirement to organise a daily act of collective worship in each academic year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133192","133192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867075","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what research (a) his Department and (b) other public bodies have commissioned into the practices of schools in England in relation to acts of collective worship since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133193","133193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867076","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many individual schools have been reported to his Department for non-compliance with the statutory requirement for an Act of Collective Worship in each academic year since 2010-2011.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133194","133194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867077","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is for when his Department learns that a school is in breach of its statutory duties relating to acts of collective worship; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133195","133195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867078","2018-03-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent progress his Department has made on reforming ground rents for leasehold property.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133196","133196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867079","2018-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Llanelli dated 6 February 2018 on his Department's Better Defence Estate strategy.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133197","133197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867080","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what powers he has to ensure schools comply with their statutory responsibilities.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133198","133198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867081","2018-03-21","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to meet representatives of British in Europe to discuss the effect of the UK leaving the EU on UK citizens living in non-UK, EU countries.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133199","133199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867082","2018-03-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political situation in Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133200","133200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867083","2018-03-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of his Department’s national air quality monitoring data from Preston Park and Worthing for the purpose of assessing the compliance of Brighton and Hove Local Authority area with EU limits of nitrogen dioxide NO2 air pollution; if he will make it his policy to include Brighton and Hove City Council local NO2 pollution monitoring data from (a) North Street Low Bus Emission Zone and (b) Lewes Road link to the universities in the national assessment; if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the national model assessment in determining which cities comply with the NO2 limit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133201","133201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867084","2018-03-22","Department for International Trade","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his European Union counterparts on the potential merits of bringing a case to the World Trade Organisation on the US Administration's proposed steel and aluminium tariffs.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133202","133202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867085","2018-03-22","Department for International Trade","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he has received legal advice on effectiveness of bringing a case to the World Trade Organisation on the introduction of steel and aluminium tariffs by the US administration.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133203","133203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867086","2018-03-22","Department for International Trade","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the effect on World Trade Organisation rules of using national security as a reason to impose trade barriers.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133204","133204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867087","2018-03-22","Department for International Trade","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to increase market access for UK steel to (a) existing and (b) new markets as a result of the tariffs on steel proposed by the US administration.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133205","133205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867088","2018-03-22","Cabinet Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information he holds on the use of payroll companies by strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133206","133206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867089","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the article in Nursery World, Colleges cause confusion by stating need for GCSEs, published on 19 March 2018, if he will publish the correspondence between his Department and the Association of Colleges of their duties in relation to early years recruitment.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133207","133207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867090","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that the Education and Skills Funding Agency’s publication, Guidance for Young People 2017 to 2018 reflects the policy of his Department to reinstate functional skills as an entry route for those wanting to work in early years settings.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133208","133208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867091","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to tackle the increase in infant mortality identified by the Office for National Statistics from 2.6 neonatal deaths per 1,000 births in 2015 to 2.7 neonatal deaths per 1,000 births in 2016.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133209","133209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867092","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the recommendations of the Nuffield Trust report International comparisons of health and wellbeing in early childhood, published in March 2018.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133210","133210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867093","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to extend business rates relief to early years providers before the next re-evaluation of rates in 2021.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133211","133211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867094","2018-03-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office, if the Government will include imports of coal from Russia in the list of sanctions against that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133212","133212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867095","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many former Carillion directors are employed as advisers on the completion of the Royal Liverpool University Hospital.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133213","133213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867096","2018-03-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which UK coal-fired power stations supplied the National Grid during the week commencing 26 February 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133214","133214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867097","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the regulation of the sale of concentrated hydrochloric acid online.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133215","133215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867098","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department plans to make of the effect of the Healthy Start scheme on the nutrition of pregnant women and young children; and if he will increase the value of the vouchers to meet the increasing cost of food.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133216","133216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867099","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will remove the necessity for mothers to contact the Healthy Start Unit to inform them of the birth of their baby in order to receive Healthy Start vouchers and vitamins.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133217","133217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867100","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will introduce a free telephone number for Healthy Start recipients to contact the Healthy Start Issuing Unit.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133218","133218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867101","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships starts there were in the East Midlands; and what the level was of each of those starts in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133219","133219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867102","2018-03-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that consumers can access the cheapest energy tariffs without the need to install a smart meter.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133220","133220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867103","2018-03-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the outcome of the Credit Union Expansion Project.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133221","133221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867104","2018-03-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to publish the accounts of the Credit Union Expansion Project.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133222","133222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867105","2018-03-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what effect the Credit Union Expansion Project had on access to finance for people who are financially excluded.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133223","133223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867106","2018-03-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many Plant Health Inspectors have been stationed at (a) Heathrow and (b) Manchester airports in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133224","133224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867107","2018-03-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many vacancies there are for Plant Health Inspectors at (a) Heathrow and (b) Manchester airports.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133225","133225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867108","2018-03-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has held with officials in the Israeli Government on the case of Ahed Tamimi since her court appearance on 12 March 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133226","133226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867109","2018-03-22","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to provide Tier 2 visa cap exemptions for foreign nationals on (a) Government Shortage Occupation Lists and (b) working at PhD level roles in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133227","133227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867110","2018-03-21","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions his Department have held with the European Union on maintaining collaboration between UK-based scientists and non-UK organisations in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133228","133228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867111","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release, Funding boost to give more children healthy start to the day, published on 19th March 2018, whether the funding announced is additional to the £26 million of funding allocated for breakfast club provision in the tender published by his Department on 23 October 2017.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133229","133229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867112","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release, Funding boost to give more children healthy start to the day, published on 19 March 2018, how much of that funding will be spent in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133230","133230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867113","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release, Funding boost to give more children healthy start to the day, published on 19 March 2018, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children that will benefit from the funding.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133231","133231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867114","2018-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to report on progress with the Modernising Defence Programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133232","133232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867115","2018-03-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of ensuring that the Universal Credit IT system automatically links to a prior employment and support allowance claim and awards any components contained in that claim.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133233","133233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867116","2018-03-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of universal credit claimants who have received two pay packets in one assessment period and none in the following assessment period.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133234","133234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867117","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information NHS Blood and Transplant holds on the amount of blood and tissue imported from other EU countries in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133235","133235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867118","2018-03-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of public funding for tourism in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133236","133236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867119","2018-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support is available for people with memory loss to undertake a personal independence payment assessment.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133237","133237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867120","2018-03-21","Cabinet Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2018 to Question 129513, on Carillion, and with reference to paragraph 21 of procurement policy note 04/15, whether Crown Commercial Services maintains a database of certificates.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133238","133238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867121","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of bed capacity in University Hospitals Coventry and Warwickshire NHS Trust.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133239","133239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867122","2018-03-22","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made a recent assessment of the effect of the change in the level of police funding on the capacity of local police forces in Coventry to investigate violent crimes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133240","133240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867123","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the take-up rate for bowel cancer screening in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry was in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133241","133241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867124","2018-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many civil servants within his Department made use of a Cycle-To-Work Scheme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133242","133242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867125","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of state-funded pupils benefited from a partnership between an independent school and a state-funded school in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133243","133243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867126","2018-03-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to replace the provisions of the Audiovisual Media Services Regulations 2014 to ensure that the distribution of content across borders is possible after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Lewer","Andrew Lewer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133244","133244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867127","2018-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to reduce waiting times for personal independence payment claims for people with hearing loss.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133245","133245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867128","2018-03-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to (a) make the personal independence payment application process more accessible for people with hearing loss and (b) ensure communication support is provided during face-to-face personal independence payment assessments.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133246","133246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867129","2018-03-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to increase recycling rates of disposable coffee cups.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133247","133247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867130","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the English Baccalaureate on access to creative subjects.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133248","133248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867131","2018-03-22","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he and his Department have taken to ensure that there is (a) adequate track capacity and (b) adequate train numbers to support the proposed May 2018 rail timetable change implementation in the North West.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133249","133249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867132","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has issued on how to include and integrate mental health into Sustainability and Transformation Partnerships; and if he will publish any such guidance.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133250","133250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867133","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to inform Sustainability and Transformation Partnerships (STP) leads on how to integrate mental health into STP plans.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133251","133251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867134","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the the reasons for the low proportion of total funding for NHS trusts for the Sustainability and Transformation Fund that is made available for mental health trusts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133252","133252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867135","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to ensure that Sustainability and Transformation Plans do not reduce how much they spend on mental health care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133253","133253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867136","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government has made an assessment of the implications for its policy of restrictions imposed by King's College London on the freedom of speech of Israeli speakers on its campus following disruption by violent students.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133254","133254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867137","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what date his Department plans to publish the application criteria for the construction skills fund announced in the Autumn Budget 2017.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133255","133255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867138","2018-03-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to publish the (a) details of what constitutes high affordability and (b) criteria used in determining how support will be allocated under the Housing Revenue Account borrowing cap announced in Autumn Budget 2017.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133256","133256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867139","2018-03-22","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department was made aware of the decision to expand the 26-30 railcard trial to 10,000 extra participants.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133257","133257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867140","2018-03-22","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Government will introduce retrospective changes to the law, to allow people who were born outside the UK  before 1 January 1983 to a British parent, to inherit their parent's UK citizenship.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133258","133258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867141","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of dental practices in Bradford achieved 96 percent or more of their contracted units of dental activity in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133259","133259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867142","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money was clawed back by NHS England from dental practices in Bradford in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133260","133260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867143","2018-03-22","Cabinet Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the number of Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman cases that have been awaiting allocation to an investigator for (a) one month, (b) two months, (c) three months, (d) four months, (e) five months, (f) six months, (g) seven months, (h) eight months and (i) nine months.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133261","133261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867144","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money clawed back from dental practices by NHS England was re-invested in dental practices in Bradford in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133262","133262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867145","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of money clawed back from dental practices by NHS England was re-invested in dental care in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133263","133263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867146","2018-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Estonian, (b) Lithuanian, (c) Latvian, (d) Polish and (f) Ukrainian nationals received training at (i) the Royal Military Academy Sandhurst, (ii) RAF Cranwell and (iii) Britannia Royal Naval Academy in each year between 2010 and 2018.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133264","133264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867147","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2018 to Question 30635, what proportion of mental health patients are signposted to money advice services as part of their care.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133265","133265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867148","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State of Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 6 March 2018 to Question 130638, whether his Department will trial integrated money advice in primary mental health care settings.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133266","133266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867149","2018-03-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to (a) monitor and (b) assess the efficacy of universal support.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133267","133267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867150","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the level of availability of lymphodema services in England.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133268","133268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867151","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether there is a plan to introduce NICE guidance for lymphedema treatment.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133269","133269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867152","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have been diagnosed with lymphedema in each of the three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133270","133270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867153","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the quality of mobile phone coverage at Yarl's Wood immigration detention centre.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133271","133271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867154","2018-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Defence of 5 March 2018, Official Report, column 12, when his Department plans to write to the hon. Member for Merthyr Tydfil and Rhymney on its definition of a core activity and an additional facility.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133272","133272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867155","2018-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 131619, on armoured fighting vehicles, which eight organisations returned questionnaires.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133273","133273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867156","2018-03-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2018 to Question 132534, how much money councils have returned to the Treasury in right to buy receipts in each year since 2012.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133274","133274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867157","2018-03-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2018 to Question 132534, how much money councils have returned to the Treasury in right to buy receipts in each year since 2012 by local authority.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133275","133275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867158","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions have been brought for the use of illegal car registration plates in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133276","133276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867159","2018-03-21","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the use of illegal car registration plates.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133277","133277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867160","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2018 to Question 130814, if he will take steps to provide guidance to NHS Trusts on responding to correspondence from hon. Members.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133278","133278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867161","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress his Department has made on giving summer-born and premature children the right to start reception at the age of five.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133279","133279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867162","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of giving summer-born and premature children the right to start reception at the age of five.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133280","133280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867163","2018-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Israeli Government on the security of Israeli cities within range of rocket attacks from Gaza.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133281","133281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867164","2018-03-22","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timescale is for rolling out the 26-30 Railcard scheme throughout the UK.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133282","133282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867165","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to monitor the number of applications for university nursing courses in England in the current 2018 undergraduate cycle, including applications for (a) mental health and (b) learning disability courses.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133283","133283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867166","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations his Department has received from Early Years providers on the effect of the level of business rates on the financial viability of their companies.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133284","133284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867167","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is to publish information on the number of applications for university nursing courses in England in the current 2018 undergraduate cycle by nursing discipline in each region of the UK.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133285","133285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867168","2018-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the savings accrued to the public purse in 2017-18 as a result of the removal of the automatic eligibility of 18 to 21 year-olds to claim universal credit for housing costs.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133286","133286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867169","2018-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish the categories of decisions for turning down applications from 18 to 21 year olds for universal credit claims for housing costs .","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133287","133287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867170","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what research his Department has commissioned on the cost of screening young people at 14 years of age for cardiac abnormalities.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133288","133288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867171","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what research his Department has commissioned on the cost of genetic screening at birth for cardiac abnormalities.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133289","133289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867172","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children under the age of 18 have been screened for cardiac abnormalities in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Priti Patel","Priti Patel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133290","133290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867173","2018-03-22","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with his Egyptian counterpart on the resumption of flights to Sharm el-Sheikh.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133291","133291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867174","2018-03-22","Cabinet Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of Civil Service Fast Stream applicants were from (a) each of the nine English regions, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) Scotland and (d) Wales in each financial year since 2013..","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133292","133292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867175","2018-03-22","Cabinet Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of successful Civil Service Fast Stream applicants were from (a) each of the nine English regions, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) Scotland and (d) Wales in each financial year since 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133293","133293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867176","2018-03-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to help protect SMEs from cyber threats.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133294","133294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867177","2018-03-22","Home Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to help protect shop workers from (a) physical abuse, (b) threats and (c) intimidation.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133295","133295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867178","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will bring forward the scheduled review of the Cystic Fibrosis drug Orkambi.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133296","133296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867179","2018-03-22","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will retain the NHS Bursary for postgraduate pre-registration nursing students.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133297","133297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867180","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the pupil-teacher ratio, including teaching assistants, is in schools in Southampton.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133298","133298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867181","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made for the implications for its policy of new data published by Vertex Pharmaceuticals in February 2018 on the Cystic Fibrosis drug Orkambi.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133299","133299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867182","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions has his Department had with Cystic Fibrosis sufferers on the provision of the drug Orkambi by the NHS.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133300","133300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867183","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will ensure that safeguards are in place so that tax rulings are properly scrutinised before coming into force and subject to monitoring thereafter.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133301","133301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867184","2018-03-22","Department for International Development","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her counterparts in NATO countries on providing humanitarian assistance in Turkish-held parts of northern Syria.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133302","133302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867185","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff employed by HMRC are involved in creating and approving each individual tax ruling.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133303","133303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867186","2018-03-22","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what procedures his Department plans to use to assess where the proposed Channel 4 hubs will be located; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133304","133304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867187","2018-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the extent to which ISIL is present in Afrin and other parts of northern Syria.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133305","133305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867188","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of whether the transition to regional HMRC centres through the Building Our Future programme will be effected by the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133306","133306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867189","2018-03-22","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff are  employed within HMRC’s High Net Worth Unit.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133307","133307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867190","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many high net worth individuals have been placed under criminal investigation for tax affairs in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133308","133308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867191","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much income tax was paid by people who fall under the jurisdiction of HMRC’s high net worth unit in each year since 2014-15.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133309","133309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867192","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many penalties HMRC issued to high net worth individuals in each year since 2009; and what was the total value of these penalties.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133310","133310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867193","2018-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he or his Department has made to Turkey's President Erdogan or his Government's representatives on military action in northern Syria.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133311","133311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867194","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse of HMRC’s connect programme was; and what the value of revenue raised through the programme was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133312","133312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867195","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Statement, how much of the £155 million in resources and technology for HMRC has already been invested; and how much has been raised as a result of that investment.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133313","133313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867196","2018-03-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March 2018 to Question 132701, on finance, how the Government defines the term additional flexibility in this context; and what estimate his Department has made of the funding available via additional flexibility.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133314","133314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867197","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much of the contingency funding that has been made available for Border Taskforce preparedness has been drawn down by HMRC to manage customs at ports in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133315","133315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867198","2018-03-21","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2018 to Question 131899, and with reference to the Second Reading debate on the Pavement Parking (Protection of Vulnerable Pedestrians) Bill on 4 December 2015, when his Department plans to conclude the work to examine more closely the legal and financial implications of a new law on pavement parking.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133316","133316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867199","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has undertaken a recent assessment of warehouse and storage capacity at UK ports.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133317","133317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867200","2018-03-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to respond to the recent finding by HMRC that 98,150 workers were paid less than the minimum wage in 2016-17.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133318","133318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867201","2018-03-21","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken since 2015 to increase compliance with minimum wage regulations by employers.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133319","133319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867202","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how his Department scrutinises the operation of red diesel relief.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133320","133320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867203","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the report published by the NAO in April 2014, entitled the exchequer departments - tax relief, whether his Department has increased the use of sunset clauses when instituting new forms of tax relief.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133321","133321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867204","2018-03-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 19 March to Question 132701, on finance, what the sources of income referred to in the Answer are.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133322","133322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867205","2018-03-22","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2018 to Question 131688, which local authorities have rehoused the 64 households located outside the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133323","133323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867206","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many female offenders received an immediate custodial sentence of (a) less than six months and (b) more than six months in each police force area in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133324","133324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867207","2018-03-22","Women and Equalities","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of including partnership income in the calculation of gender pay gaps; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133325","133325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867208","2018-03-22","Women and Equalities","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Women and Equalities, whether her Department has modelled the effect on gender pay gaps of including partnership income in the calculation.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133326","133326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867209","2018-03-22","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department had with (a) Network Rail and (b) the Office of Rail and Road before the decision was taken to postpone the reopening of the railway line between Blackpool North and Preston for three weeks over Easter.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133327","133327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867210","2018-03-22","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department had with (a) Network Rail and (b) Northern Rail before the announcement of the three-week postponement of the reopening of the railway line between Blackpool North and Preston on the economic consequences for Blackpool's tourist industry.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133328","133328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867211","2018-03-22","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the consultation conducted by Network Rail with (a) Blackpool Council, (b) other local authorities and (c) Members of Parliament before the decision was taken to postpone the reopening of the railway line from Blackpool North to Preston for three weeks over Easter.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133329","133329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867212","2018-03-22","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with (a) Northern Rail and (b) Network Rail about the effect on residents and visitors to Blackpool of the decision to introduce weekend blockades on the railway line from Manchester to Preston in summer 2018.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133330","133330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867213","2018-03-22","Department for Transport","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of occasions in the past 12 months when Network Rail has extended agreed timetables to close railway lines for engineering works without consulting (a) local authorities and (b) local Members of Parliament.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133331","133331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867214","2018-03-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of commercially available slug pellets on garden birds and hedgehogs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133332","133332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867215","2018-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Government of Hong Kong Special Administrative Region and the Government of the Republic of China on maintaining the one country, two systems approach in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133333","133333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/867216","2018-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect of the erosion of the rule of law in Hong Kong on UK businesses.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133334","133334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865102","2018-03-20","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much his Department has spent on (a) Ministerial salaries, (b) staff salaries, (c) travel and transport costs,  (d) accommodation, (e) staff expenses, (f) hospitality, (g) publicity and information and (h) administrative costs since its creation.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132969","132969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865103","2018-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if will take steps to guarantee that a claimant in receipt of a higher rate of daily living or mobility components of personal independence payments.will not receive a lower rate as a result of reassessment.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132970","132970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865104","2018-03-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will grant powers to local councils to set deadlines for the completion of roads in new developments.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132971","132971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865105","2018-03-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to give local authorities the power to impose completion targets as a condition when granting planning consents for housing.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132972","132972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865106","2018-03-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the proposed National Planning Policy Framework will enable councils to require fibre to home broadband to be installed on new developments.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132973","132973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865107","2018-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether personal independence payment claimants are able to choose to undergo a face-to-face reassessment.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132974","132974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865108","2018-03-20","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 February 2018 to Question 127990, on Army: Recruitment, whether drop-out rates for soldiers in basic training  were included in the calculations for the average career length for each of those groups.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132975","132975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865109","2018-03-20","Home Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will certify the attempted murder of Sergei Skripal and his daughter in Salisbury on 4 March 2018 as an act of terrorism.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132976","132976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865110","2018-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the Government's policy is on (a) international and (b) EU recognition of the United Kingdom Accreditation Service after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132977","132977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865111","2018-03-20","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2018-03-16","To ask the hon. Member for Houghton and Sunderland South, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many complaints the Commission received in relation to breaches in election law after (a) during and (b) after General Election 2017; and how many of those complaints (i) related to electoral fraud or other breaches, (ii) have been resolved, (iii) have been passed to the police and (iv) have resulted in prosecutions.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132978","132978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865112","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, in what proportion of cases her Department received information that it did not already hold in each month since the Memorandum of Understanding between NHS Digital and the Home Office entered into operation.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132979","132979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865113","2018-03-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions,  if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the level of the cap on Social Fund Funeral Payments to cover the basic cost of a funeral.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132980","132980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865114","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2018 to Question 130494 on Ministry of Justice: Amey, what the evidential basis is for private contractors achieving the majority of their contractual targets.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132981","132981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865115","2018-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what contracts for consultancy services (a) his Department and (b) his Department's arms length bodies agreed in 2017; what the value of each of those contract is; who the signatories to those contracts are; what the performance measures relating to each of those contract are; to which geographic areas the delivery of those contracts relate; what the terms of those contracts are; how many people are employed by those contract providers to deliver those contracts; and if he will place copies of those contracts in the Library.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132982","132982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865116","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer 13 March 2018 to Question 131298 on Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre; of the 98 reports made by a medical practitioner under Rule 35 in Yarl's Wood during Q3 of 2017, how many caseworker reviews of the appropriateness of continued detention led to a detainee's release from detention.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132983","132983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865117","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2018 to Question 131300, how many of the 148 arrivals into the UK from Greece under the Dublin Regulation in Q4 of 2017 were children.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132984","132984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865118","2018-03-21","Department for Transport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2018 to Question 130371, how many (a) new and (b) refurbished TransPennine Express trains will be released by the year 2020.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132985","132985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865119","2018-03-20","Department for International Development","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of its support for internally displaced people; and whether her Department plans to take any steps to improve the effectiveness of that support.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132986","132986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865120","2018-03-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the consultation on Animal welfare: banning the use of electronic training collars for cats and dogs, published by his Department in March 2018, whether anti-bark dog collars are covered within the scope of that consultation.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132987","132987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865121","2018-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the consultation on Animal welfare: banning the use of electronic training collars for cats and dogs, published by his Department in March 2018, what the timescale is for his Department to publish a response to that consultation.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132988","132988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865122","2018-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a ban on the sale of electric shock collars.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132989","132989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865123","2018-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions how much was awarded to staff of her Department in bonuses in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132990","132990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865124","2018-03-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of public funding for tourism in (a) the East Midlands and (b) Mansfield in the last five years.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132991","132991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865125","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department makes any additional maintenance funding available to student nurses who work on placements during the university holiday period each summer.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132992","132992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865126","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the (a) courts and (b) tribunals that had contracts with Carillion for the provision of services.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132993","132993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865127","2018-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will use the upcoming Consumer Law Green Paper to commit to solving data sharing issues in order to improve the protection of vulnerable consumers.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132994","132994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865128","2018-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if will make representations to the UN on the murder of Jan Kuciak in Slovakia.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132995","132995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865129","2018-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on the number of people in Feltham and Heston constituency transferred onto universal credit who are in rent arrears.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132996","132996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865130","2018-03-20","Home Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of community response police in Hounslow in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132997","132997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865131","2018-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the budget for probation hostels has been in each year since 1 June 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132998","132998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865132","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2018 to Questions 131226, 131234 and 131225 on Bedford Prison, for what reasons the separate incidents were not referred to in that answer.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132999","132999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865133","2018-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many days of court time have been lost in each court due to unscheduled maintenance becoming necessary in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133000","133000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865134","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the standard rate of subsistence paid to prison officers on detached duty per overnight stay is.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133001","133001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865135","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has plans to change the level of subsistence paid to prison officers on detached duty.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133002","133002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865136","2018-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, How much money has been spent on subsistence payments to prison officers on detached duty in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133003","133003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865137","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what (a) assessment he has made of the potential benefits to charities and (b) estimate he has made of the potential cost to the public purse of introducing a de minimis limit of £20 on retail Gift Aid claims made by charity shops.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133004","133004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865138","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Early Years Workforce Strategy published in March 2017, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the feasibility of and (b) the potential timescale for increasing the graduate early years workforce working in disadvantaged areas.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133005","133005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865139","2018-03-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to reform leaseholder rights.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133006","133006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865140","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March to Question 131949 on Huddersfield Royal Infirmary, on what date the Independent Reconfiguration Panel's report on the potential downgrading of Huddersfield Royal Infirmary will be made public.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133007","133007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865141","2018-03-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral statement of 15 March 2018, Official Report, column 1018, on Building Safety, how many different fire doors his Department is testing.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133008","133008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865142","2018-03-20","Scotland Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133009","133009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865143","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the decision to reduce Jisc’s funding and introduce fees for further education colleges to pay for essential IT infrastructure and technology support services on the adequacy of provision of those services.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133010","133010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865144","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support his Department will provide to further education colleges that are unable to meet the cost of fees for Jisc’s essential IT infrastructure and technology support services as a result of the funding changes to Jisc.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133011","133011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865145","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many cyber security related incidents affected (a) further education colleges and (b) higher education institutions in 2017.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133012","133012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865146","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the potential risk to cyber security of further education colleges deciding to opt-out of paying for Jisc’s essential cyber security support services as a result of the decision to reduce Jisc’s funding and introduce subscription fees.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133013","133013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865147","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department plans to take for people from at-risk groups, as identified in NICE Public Health Guideline 56, who are no longer able to access appropriate licensed vitamin D maintenance treatments as a result of only over the counter treatments being available under NHS England proposals.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133014","133014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865148","2018-03-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to Hard as well as soft power: the case for modern defence, published by his Department on 15 March 2018, whether the £48 million funding that he announced for a new chemical weapons defence centre is in addition to the £115 million allocated to project Helios.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133015","133015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865149","2018-03-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the new chemical weapons defence centre at Porton Down will be separate from the new Defence Science and Technology Laboratory facilities being built there.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133016","133016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865150","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133017","133017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865151","2018-03-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133018","133018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865152","2018-03-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to page, 88, section 21, Defence Science and Technology Laboratory Annual Report and Accounts 2016-2017, when he expects the final £48.3 million for Project Helios to be approved.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133019","133019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865153","2018-03-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133020","133020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865154","2018-03-21","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his speech, Hard as well as soft power: the case for modern defence, made on 15 March 2018, whether he has plans to review Project Helios as a result of the development of a new Chemical Weapons Defence Centre.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133021","133021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865155","2018-03-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133022","133022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865156","2018-03-21","Department for Transport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133023","133023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865157","2018-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much money her Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133024","133024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865158","2018-03-20","Home Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much money her Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133025","133025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865159","2018-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133026","133026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865160","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133027","133027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865161","2018-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133028","133028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865162","2018-03-20","Wales Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133029","133029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865163","2018-03-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133030","133030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865164","2018-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133031","133031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865165","2018-03-20","Scotland Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133032","133032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865166","2018-03-20","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money his Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133033","133033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865167","2018-03-20","Northern Ireland Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much money her Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133034","133034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865168","2018-03-20","Department for International Development","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much money her Department has raised from the sale of (a) assets, (b) land and (c) buildings in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133035","133035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865169","2018-03-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to his oral Statement of 15 March 2018, Official Report, column 1018 on Building Safety, whether he plans to publish the results of the fire door safety tests.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133036","133036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865170","2018-03-22","Treasury","2018-03-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of tax-free childcare in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133037","133037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865171","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2018 to Question 126280, whether it has been agreed that apprentices transferred from Carillion Training Services will be paid beyond the end of March.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133038","133038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865172","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the apprentices transferred from Carillion Training Services have been found placements with (a) Government Departments and (b) other public sector employers.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133039","133039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865173","2018-03-22","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of apprentices transferred from Carillion Training Services to the Construction Industry Training Board have been placed with alternative employers.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133040","133040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865174","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions of 13 March 2018, Official Report, column 767, what the specific circumstances affecting public sector employees in relation to childcare vouchers are; and what steps he is planning to take to address them.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133041","133041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865175","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to restore normal mobile connectivity in Yarl's Wood Immigration Removal Centre.","Biography information for Tony Lloyd","Tony Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133042","133042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865177","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution made by the Secretary of State for Education of 13 March 2018, Official Report, Column 804, what steps he plans to take to review his policy on the closure of childcare vouchers during the six-month delay.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133044","133044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865178","2018-03-21","Cabinet Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2018 to Question 131358, on Defence: Modernisation, whether the National Security Capability Review will include new risk assessments separate to the National Security Risk Assessment.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133045","133045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865179","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2018 to Question 132172, on Adult Education: Finance, for what reason it is necessary to be a residential provider to qualify for that transitional funding.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133046","133046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865180","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March to Question 132171, on adult education: finance, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of those proposed changes on (a) WEA and (b) other national providers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133047","133047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865181","2018-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the changes made to the Widowed Parent's Allowance on the long-term financial security of widowed spouses.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133048","133048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865182","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to his Answer of 13 March 2018 to Question 131756, what the reasons are for the feasibility study taking longer than March 2018 to be completed; and what the timetable is for completion of that study.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133049","133049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865183","2018-03-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the Lawn Tennis Association on the accessibility of lawn tennis to people with (a) different socioeconomic backgrounds and (b) the protected characteristics listed in section 4 of the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133050","133050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865184","2018-03-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his  Department holds on the participation of people with (a) different socioeconomic backgrounds and (b) the protected characteristics listed in section 4 of the Equality Act 2010 in the sport of lawn tennis.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133051","133051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865185","2018-03-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the equalities and non-discrimination policies of the Lawn Tennis Association.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133052","133052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865186","2018-03-20","Home Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the level of debt has been for each fire authority in each of the last eight financial years.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133053","133053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865187","2018-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with the Prime Minister's oral contribution of 25 October 2017, Official Report, column 300, what the evidential basis is for shale gas to support thousands of jobs in the oil and gas industries and in other sectors; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133054","133054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865188","2018-03-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-03-16","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131599 on House of Commons: Catering, what guidance is available to customers who wish to pay a (a) tip and (b) gratuity to House of Commons catering staff by (i) cash and (ii) debit or credit card; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133055","133055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865189","2018-03-21","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2018 to Question 131015 on Social Services: Minimum Wage, what the (a) cost to the public purse is of and (b) procurement process was for the (i) Deloitte and (ii) Frontier Economics and Laing Buisson study of sleep-in back pay liabilities; and how many other organisations applied to undertake those studies.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133056","133056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865190","2018-03-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-03-16","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131599 on House of Commons: Catering, how long a House of Commons catering staff member has to wait to receive a (a) tip and (b) gratuity from a customer using a bank card; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133057","133057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865191","2018-03-21","House of Commons Commission","2018-03-16","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, further to the Answer of 14 March 2018 to Question 131599, on House of Commons: Catering, what (a) policies and (b) procedures are in place to ensure House of Commons catering services staff are paid any (i) tips and (ii) gratuities from a paying customer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133058","133058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865192","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of mandating the provision of access to counselling in schools and colleges.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133059","133059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865193","2018-03-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of gross value added has been generated by the tourism sector in each of the regions of England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133060","133060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865194","2018-03-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what the proportion of gross value added is which has been generated by the heritage sector in each region of England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133061","133061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865195","2018-03-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many jobs have been generated by the tourism industry in England in each of the last five years; and what the value of tourism was to the economy in each of those years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133062","133062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865196","2018-03-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the number of (a) domestic and (b) international tourism visits made to each region of England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133063","133063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865197","2018-03-21","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information he holds on the amount of funding spent by local authorities on tourism in each region of England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133064","133064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865198","2018-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions his Department has had with National Grid on its superfast charging network; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133065","133065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865199","2018-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the adequacy of motorway electric vehicle infrastructure.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133066","133066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865200","2018-03-20","Treasury","2018-03-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with its international counterparts on developing regulations for crypto-currencies.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133067","133067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865201","2018-03-20","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department is taking steps to ensure that prospective undergraduates understand the potential effect of their choice of course on their prospects post-graduation.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133068","133068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865202","2018-03-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when his Department plans next to meet (a) Perth and Kinross and (b) Clackmannanshire Council to discuss the (i) roll-out of superfast broadband and (ii) mobile phone coverage in those council areas.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133069","133069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865203","2018-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has further to help reduce dependency on single-use plastics items.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133070","133070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865204","2018-03-20","Treasury","2018-03-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he next plans to meet representatives of the Royal Bank of Scotland to discuss rural branch closures.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133071","133071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865205","2018-03-20","Treasury","2018-03-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he next plans to meet representatives of the Bank of Scotland to discuss rural branch closures.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133072","133072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865206","2018-03-20","Department for International Development","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government takes to help share UK civil service expertise with developing nations.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133073","133073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865207","2018-03-20","Treasury","2018-03-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he next plans to meet representatives of the Clydesdale Bank to discuss rural branch closures.","Biography information for Luke Graham","Luke Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133074","133074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865208","2018-03-20","Department for International Development","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department plans to take to ensure best ethical practice by the NGOs it supports.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133075","133075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865209","2018-03-20","Department for International Development","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department takes to ensure data gathering on the effects of its programmes is (a) accurate and (b) comprehensive.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133076","133076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865210","2018-03-20","Department for International Development","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to strengthen its oversight of the NGOs it supports.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133077","133077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865211","2018-03-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government’s priorities are for the Commonwealth Heads of Government Summit in April 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133078","133078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865212","2018-03-20","Department for International Development","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what arrangements her Department has to reimburse the Ministry of Defence for resources used in disaster response.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133079","133079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865213","2018-03-20","Treasury","2018-03-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he is taking steps to enable the return of duty free sales to passengers travelling to the EU from the UK after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133080","133080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865214","2018-03-21","Department for International Trade","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the EU on imposing safeguards on steel and aluminium imports into the EU in order to protect our industries from redirected imports.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133081","133081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865215","2018-03-21","Department for International Trade","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with the European Commission on the potential for bringing a case to the WTO against the USA in respect of steel tariffs.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133082","133082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865216","2018-03-21","Department for International Trade","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the potential for some countries to receive exemptions from the tariffs imposed on steel and aluminium imports; and what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of those counties receiving such an exemption on the countries that are not exempt.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133083","133083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865217","2018-03-21","Department for International Trade","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how he plans to increase market access for UK steel to existing and new markets in order to make up for any loss of market access in the US.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133084","133084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865218","2018-03-21","Wales Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the (a) Secretary of State for Transport and (b) Welsh Government on checking freight at Holyhead and Pembroke docks after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133085","133085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865219","2018-03-21","Treasury","2018-03-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an assessment of the state of readiness of Holyhead and Pembroke docks to enforce custom checks in the event that the UK does not agree a deal with the European Union.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133086","133086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865220","2018-03-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will permit employment and support allowance claimants with motor neurone disease to have their diagnosis confirmed by medical professionals as part of the reassessment process instead of by means of paper forms completed by those claimants.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133087","133087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865221","2018-03-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has had any discussions with the (a) Welsh Government and (b) Welsh Local Government Association on the operation of the Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133088","133088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865222","2018-03-21","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government,  whether the Government plans to permit the Welsh Assembly Government to bid for funds under the Shared Prosperity Fund programme.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133089","133089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865223","2018-03-20","Department for Education","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve careers advice for pupils with special educational needs.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133090","133090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865224","2018-03-21","Scotland Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will list the external recruitment agencies that are used by his Department's non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133091","133091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865225","2018-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when (a) he and (b) a Minister of his Department plans to meet the hon. Member for Glasgow South West to discuss the Workers (Definitions and Rights) Bill.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133092","133092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865226","2018-03-20","Home Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether resources are being allocated to protect mosques and Muslim communities on and around 3 April as a result of letters inciting hate against Muslims and designating that date as punish a Muslim day.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133093","133093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865227","2018-03-21","Home Office","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government supports objective 13(g) of the UN's draft Global Compact for Safe, Orderly and Regular Migration to end the practice of child detention in the context of international migration.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133094","133094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/865228","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to explore the potential for a mandatory data set to provide transparency about the continence service which clinical commissioning groups are commissioning to enable NHS England to check how those groups are meeting the health needs of their population.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133095","133095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864266","2018-03-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Construction Supply Chain Payment Charter; how many companies have signed up to that charter; and what steps he is taking to ensure that 30 day payments become standard across the industry.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132751","132751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864267","2018-03-19","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an estimate of the efficiency savings that better use of technology has enabled for departmental spending since 2010.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132752","132752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864268","2018-03-19","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of using blockchain in the public sector.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132753","132753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864269","2018-03-19","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve transparency in government.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132754","132754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864270","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, from which Government budgets the £540m of additional funding for the NHS for 2018-19 announced on 2 February 2018 will come.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132755","132755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864271","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Digital Charter, published by the Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport on 25 January 2018, what her Department's definition of terrorist material is; and whether the Government’s plans to strengthen the offences under section 58 of the Terrorism Act 2000 will include changing that definition.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132756","132756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864272","2018-03-20","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on changes in the level of life expectancy of living (a) males and (b) females in each local authority area in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132757","132757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864273","2018-03-20","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the change in the level of local government finance on the geographical variation in life expectancy.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132758","132758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864275","2018-03-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the European Parliament’s negotiating team for the UK leaving the European Union on the legal status of a proposed associate European Union citizenship should the UK leave the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132759","132759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864276","2018-03-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will take steps to preserve the rights, freedoms and legal protections for UK citizens enshrined in the Maastricht treaty.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132760","132760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864277","2018-03-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what consideration he has made of the effect of Article 70 (1)(b) of the Vienna Convention on the Law of Treaties on UK citizens retaining EU citizenship should the UK leave the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132761","132761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864278","2018-03-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of the recommendations of the report by Professor Volker Roeben, The feasibility of the of associate EU citizenship for UK citizens post-Brexit.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132762","132762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864279","2018-03-19","Women and Equalities","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the list of protected characteristics in the Equality Act 2010 and in Article 14 of the Human Rights Act 1998.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132763","132763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864280","2018-03-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to rectify the 31 per cent mean gender pay gap in the Lawn Tennis Association.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132764","132764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864281","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on how many occasions people resident in the UK for (a) 10 years, (b) 20 years, (c) 30 years and (d) 40 years have been refused access to healthcare as a result of disputed immigration status.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132765","132765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864282","2018-03-20","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is mandatory for (a) local education authorities and (b) school management boards to (i) consult and (ii) inform School Governing Bodies when actions plans are developed between authorities and boards as a result of a school's performance.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132766","132766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864283","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131413, what assessment she has made of the legality of threats of expedited deportation and the compatibility of such threats with human rights and immigration law.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132767","132767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864284","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary State for Health and Social Care, whether the NHS (a) fit and proper person requirement and (b) duty of candour applies to an individual who undertakes an independent review commissioned by an NHS body that is funded by his Department.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132768","132768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864285","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 March 2018 to Question 131413, whether her Department requested legal advice on the legality of threatening accelerated deportation to detainees on hunger strike in immigration detention centres.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132769","132769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864286","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many full time equivalent MP account management staff are on secondment to her Department; and what the cost is to the public purse of those secondments.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132770","132770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864287","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential for bias against people on the basis of (a) gender and (b) ethnicity of the automated facial recognition software used by the (i) Metropolitan Police and (ii) South Wales Police.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132771","132771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864288","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who have not been convicted of a criminal offence are recorded on the Police National Database.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132772","132772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864289","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his counterpart in the Government of Bangladesh on the disqualification of the leader of the opposition from participation in parliamentary elections in that country.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132773","132773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864290","2018-03-21","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Higher Education Statistics Agency's non-continuation performance indicators, published on 8 March, what steps he he is taking to tackle the increase in non-continuation rates for mature students.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132774","132774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864291","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the higher charges applied to rates of vehicle tax when paid biannually as opposed to annually on the ability of people on lower incomes to afford that tax.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132775","132775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864292","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether there are mechanisms in place to provide oversight of independent reviews commissioned by NHS bodies that are funded by his Department.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132776","132776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864293","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations his Department has received on recent work undertaken by East Lancashire Clinical Commissioning Group and the charity Salute.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132777","132777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864294","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the validity of Midlands and Lancashire Commissioning Support Unit's policy of allowing themselves up to 40 working days to respond to constituent casework regardless of whether an investigation is needed.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132778","132778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864295","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he will assess the potential merits of introducing a separate assessment process for rare disease medicines that do not meet the criteria set out by the National Institute of Health and Care Excellence for their Highly Specialised Technology route.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132779","132779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864296","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of (a) private and (b) public investment in the economy in each year since 2000; and how that investment compares with other G8 countries.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132780","132780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864297","2018-03-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on whether companies are increasing the training opportunities available for their employees.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132781","132781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864298","2018-03-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an assessment of the proportion of expenditure spent by businesses on training.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132782","132782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864299","2018-03-19","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the response times of the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman to complaints referred by Members of Parliament.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132783","132783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864300","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to require schools to make available online their medical conditions policies under the statutory guidance for children with medial conditions.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132784","132784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864301","2018-03-19","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department issues guidance to the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman on timescales for responding to complaints that have been referred by Members of Parliament.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132785","132785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864302","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2018 to Question 129143 on Carillion: Insolvency, what discussions he has had with representative of Royal Liverpool University Hospital on a new contractor for the completion of the new Royal Liverpool University Hospital since 1 March 2018.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132786","132786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864303","2018-03-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has made an estimate of the charity sector's income from 1p and 2p coin donations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132787","132787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864304","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of people who have been unlawfully detained in immigration centres for (a) 1 week, (b) 1 month, (c) 3 months, (d) 6 months and (e) 1 year or more.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132788","132788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864305","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the effect of new guidance issued by NHS England relating to items that should not routinely be prescribed in primary care on trends in the levels of prescriptions in primary care.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132789","132789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864306","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to facilitate the resolution of the ongoing industrial action in response to changes to pensions.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132790","132790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864307","2018-03-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the number of foreign companies that have moved their headquarters to the UK since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132791","132791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864308","2018-03-20","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect on kit car owners of the implementation of proposals on emissions in paragraph 4.11 of the consultation on Road vehicles: Improving air quality and safety.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132792","132792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864309","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many children have been refused access to a school nurse since the introduction of the NHS (Charges to Overseas Visitors) (Amendment) Regulations 2017.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132793","132793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864310","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the independent review of full-time social action, published in January 2018, what assessment he has made of the effect of extending the youth full-time social action programme to disadvantaged pupils on their attainment levels in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132794","132794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864311","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the effect of making efficiencies in the cost of medicines on research investment by the pharmaceutical industry.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132795","132795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864312","2018-03-20","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Education of 13 March 2018, Official Report, Column 802, on Universal Credit, for what reason the change to the childcare vouchers salary sacrifice policy was not included in the Spring statement.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132796","132796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864313","2018-03-20","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109411, what the timetable is for the publication of his Department's response to the 2016 consultation into tipping, gratuities, cover and service charges.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132797","132797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864314","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps to review the regulatory framework for occupational pension schemes including the Universities Superannuation Scheme.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132798","132798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864315","2018-03-20","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications have been received from (a) Irish citizens and (b) citizens of other EU countries for British citizenship under the naturalisation rules in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132799","132799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864316","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect on the wellbeing of children who may be permitted to change gender below the age of 18 without parental consent.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132800","132800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864317","2018-03-20","Women and Equalities","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what plans she has to amend the Gender Recognition Act 2004 to permit children under the age of 18 to change their gender without parental consent.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132801","132801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864318","2018-03-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will ensure that the Commonwealth Heads of Government joint communique makes reference to the right to freedom of religion and belief.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132802","132802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864319","2018-03-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many and what proportion of full-time equivalent staff (a) of his Department and (b) employed by his Department's agencies have been employed on fixed-term contracts in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132803","132803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864320","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which eligible benefits are (a) lost and (b) suspended when a young person aged between 16 and 24 becomes an apprentice.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132804","132804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864321","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many asylum seekers who have indefinite leave to remain are awaiting the allocation of a national insurance number.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132805","132805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864322","2018-03-20","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make an assessment of the implications for the Government's policies of the Oliver Wyman report entitled The Red Tape Cost of Brexit, published on 12 March 2018.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132806","132806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864323","2018-03-20","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to encourage people aged under 30 in employment to save towards their pensions.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132807","132807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864324","2018-03-20","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to encourage self-employed people to save towards their retirement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132808","132808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864325","2018-03-20","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what barriers to investing in savings by people aged under 30 his Department has identified.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132809","132809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864326","2018-03-20","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of refugees residing in the UK who have been separated from their family due to not being eligible for family reunification.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132810","132810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864327","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of young people who have been identified as having special educational needs or disability were (a) eligible for free school meals and (b) included in the Children in Need census in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132811","132811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864328","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, What the average proportion of children in mainstream education who were diagnosed with special educational needs or disability was in each year between 2010 and 2017.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132812","132812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864329","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to amend the list of long-term and orphan diseases which qualify for free prescriptions; and when he last consulted (a) patients, (b) doctors and (c) those in the (i) pharmaceutical and (ii) health industries on that subject.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132813","132813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864330","2018-03-20","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of business rate rises for onsite battery storage on the development of the UK battery storage market.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132814","132814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864331","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which Key Performance Indicators (KPI) apply to the patients registration area of work carried out by Primary Care Support England (PCSE); how often PCSE reported against those KPIs; which targets were reached and how many complaints were received on those targets in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132815","132815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864332","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  which Key Performance Indicators (KPI) apply to the medical records area of work carried out by Primary Care Support England (PCSE); how often PCSE reported against those KPIs; which targets were reached and how many complaints were received on those targets in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132816","132816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864333","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  which Key Performance Indicators (KPI) apply to the local performers list area of work carried out by Primary Care Support England (PCSE); how often PCSE reported against those KPIs; which targets were reached and how many complaints were received on those targets in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132817","132817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864334","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which Key Performance Indicators (KPI) apply to the performers list date and local medical committee area of work carried out by Primary Care Support England (PCSE); how often PCSE reported against those KPIs; which targets were reached and how many complaints were received on those targets in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132818","132818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864335","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which Key Performance Indicators (KPI) apply to the pensions area of work carried out by Primary Care Support England (PCSE); how often PCSE reported against those KPIs; which targets were reached and how many complaints were received on those targets in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132819","132819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864336","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  which Key Performance Indicators (KPI) apply to the GP payments area of work carried out by Primary Care Support England (PCSE); how often PCSE reported against those KPIs; which targets were reached and how many complaints were received on those targets in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132820","132820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864337","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of HMRC's (a) transactions and (b) transaction value came through application programming interfaces in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132821","132821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864338","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many claims for financial loss have been made against the Primary Care Support England by (a) GPs, (b) local medical committees (c)  dentists and (d) other people for each of the last three years; how many and what proportion of those claims have been settled; what the average time taken was to settle those claims; how much has been paid out in compensation; and which organisation is liable for that compensation.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132822","132822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864339","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what sanctions are available to his Department in the event of Primary Care Support England failing to deliver contracted services.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132823","132823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864340","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that charging infrastructure for plug-in electric cars is included in new housing developments.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132824","132824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864341","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with (a) the Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, on reviewing the support to SMEs which have installed electric vehicle charging facilities but need to upgrade to more expensive rapid chargers to meet public preference and demand.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132825","132825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864342","2018-03-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2018 to Question 126434 and with reference to House of Commons Library Deposited Paper, DEP2018-0202, if he will publish the reports provided to his Department under the project titles listed under Column C; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132826","132826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864343","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report by the Food Research Collaboration, Weakening UK food law enforcement: a risky tactic in Brexit, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for food security when the UK leaves the EU of the report’s conclusions on the Food Standards Agency’s programme of change, Regulating Our Future.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132827","132827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864344","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 17 of the Early Years workforce strategy 2017, what steps he has taken to engage the childcare sector in exploring ways to target support where it is most needed.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132828","132828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864345","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the early years workforce working in group-based settings have (a) entered and (b) left the profession in each year since September 2013.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132829","132829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864346","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of childminders hold (a) level 2, (b) level 3 and (c) level 4, 5, 6 childcare qualifications.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132830","132830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864347","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information his Department holds on the number of people working for the Enterprise Adviser Network who have previously worked in childcare settings.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132831","132831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864348","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many events have taken place in schools or colleges in (a) England and (b) each region with the Education and Employers Charity to promote opportunities in the early years sector referred to in the Early Years Workforce Strategy 2017.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132832","132832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864349","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding his Department has made available to the National Apprenticeship Service to raise awareness of early years apprenticeships as detailed in the Early years workforce Strategy 2017.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132833","132833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864350","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 23 of the Early Years Workforce Strategy 2017, when the training needs analysis for early years tutors in FE settings took place; who conducted that analysis; and what the outcomes of that analysis have been.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132834","132834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864351","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 25 of the Early Years Workforce Strategy 2017, who the members of the task and finish group on gender diversity in the childcare sector are; what progress that group has made on identifying the factors influencing the number of men employed in childcare roles; whether that group has suggested any solutions to increase the number of men employed in such roles; and if his Department will publish that group's report.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132835","132835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864352","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish the next childcare and early years providers survey.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132836","132836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864353","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which NHS health care services in the Borough of Halton were provided by the private sector in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132837","132837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864354","2018-03-19","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful payments were made on GOV.UK Pay in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132838","132838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864355","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of level of staff turnover in each type of early years childcare setting; and what the level of turnover is by level of qualification.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132839","132839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864356","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 28 of the Early Years Workforce Strategy 2017, what progress has been made on establishing the early years panel to implement the skills plan and develop the childcare and early education occupational route.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132840","132840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864357","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding has been (a) made available and (b) to which organisations to support early years settings on (i) SEND, (ii) speech and language development and (iii) effective business management; and how many early years staff have taken part in continuing professional development in each of those areas since grants were made available.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132841","132841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864358","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 31 of the Early Years Workforce Strategy 2017, how much funding and to whom the Government has allocated funding to develop an online portal that sets out career paths, brings effective online continuing professional development together and provides online training modules; when that portal was launched; and how many visits that portal has received in each month since it was launched.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132842","132842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864359","2018-03-19","Attorney General","2018-03-15","To ask the Attorney General, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132843","132843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864360","2018-03-19","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132844","132844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864361","2018-03-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132845","132845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864362","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132846","132846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864363","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to require banks to inform customers at the expiration of a finance deal the best interest rates available through any bank.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132847","132847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864364","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what work capability assessment exemptions exist for people diagnosed with motor neurone disease.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132848","132848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864365","2018-03-19","Department for Education","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132849","132849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864366","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he will plans to ask Northern to extend the delay repay compensation scheme to commuters affected by delays of 15 minutes.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132850","132850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864367","2018-03-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132851","132851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864368","2018-03-19","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132852","132852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864369","2018-03-19","Department for International Development","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132853","132853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864370","2018-03-19","Department for International Trade","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132854","132854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864371","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132855","132855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864372","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information she holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in her Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132856","132856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864373","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132857","132857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864374","2018-03-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132858","132858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864375","2018-03-19","Treasury","2018-03-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132859","132859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864376","2018-03-19","Home Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information she holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in her Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132860","132860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864377","2018-03-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132861","132861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864378","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he takes to ensure that every patient newly diagnosed with rheumatoid arthritis is referred to podiatry services for early examination.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132862","132862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864379","2018-03-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132863","132863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864380","2018-03-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132864","132864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864381","2018-03-19","Northern Ireland Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what information she holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in her Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132865","132865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864382","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of autonomous technology in the maritime sector on the (a) training and (b) employment of UK seafarer (i) Ratings and (ii) Officers over the next decade.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132866","132866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864383","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to ensure all passengers using Northern's delay repay scheme have their claims processed within at most 28 days.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132867","132867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864384","2018-03-19","Wales Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what information he holds on the rate of remuneration for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132868","132868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864385","2018-03-20","Ministry of Justice","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March to Question 131737, what the maximum length of time is for a prisoner to continue to be incarcerated after a Parole Board has granted release where there are no further adjudications.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132869","132869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864386","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the total cost of developing the UK’s major ports infrastructure over the next 10 years to accommodate (a) hybrid and (b) electrically powered commercial ships above 150 gross tonnage.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132870","132870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864387","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will work with (a) Northern and (b) other rail operators to simplify delay repay schemes for passengers using multimodal transport tickets.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132871","132871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864388","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to shipping companies operating in the Irish Sea of compliance with Annex IV of the International Maritime Organisation Convention for the Prevention of Pollution from Ships from 1 January 2020.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132872","132872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864389","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will hold discussions with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the application and enforcement of national minimum wage pay rates for seafarers working in the UK shipping industry.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132873","132873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864390","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance the Maritime and Coastguard Agency provides on the decommissioning of (a) semi-submersible drilling rigs and (b) other commercial vessels deployed in the North Sea oil and gas industry.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132874","132874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864391","2018-03-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will list the suppliers who are registered with the gigabit broadband voucher scheme in the west of Scotland.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132875","132875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864392","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost to the NHS of delivering emergency dental treatment in hospitals has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132876","132876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864393","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people presented at NHS Accident and Emergency departments with dental issues in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132877","132877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864394","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to encourage NHS dentists to remain in the public sector.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132878","132878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864395","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to NHS dentists.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132879","132879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864396","2018-03-19","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what suppliers have been contracted to work on Gov.uk Pay; and what services those suppliers provide.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132880","132880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864397","2018-03-20","Cabinet Office","2018-03-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many page views published Ministerial diaries have received in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132881","132881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864398","2018-03-20","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2018 to Question 122074, on Respiratory System: Medical Equipment, if he will publish the number of adult extra-corporeal membrane oxygenation beds occupied in each week in (a) January 2018 and (b) February 2018.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132882","132882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864399","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of reviewing the effect of changes to the National Institute of Health and Care Excellence Highly Specialised Technology Programme earlier than three years after their implementation in April 2017.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132883","132883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864400","2018-03-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 60 of his Department's paper Government Transformation Strategy, published in February 2017, what progress the Government has made on developing a platform for making payments out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132884","132884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864402","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to issue guidance to pharmaceutical companies entering into negotiations with the commercial medicines unit, as a result of that unit's move to NHS England.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132885","132885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864403","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS nurses have the ability to (a) access training and (b) attain the minimum level of qualifications in respect of the treatment of  diabetes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132886","132886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864404","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that diabetes specialist nurses who are unable to access continuing professional development courses as a result of (a) staff shortages and (b) financial restrictions have the ability to gain the minimum level of qualifications.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132887","132887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864405","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that carbohydrates are (a) clearly and (b) consistently displayed on pre-packaged food.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132888","132888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864406","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to improve people's awareness of free sugars and associated health risks.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132889","132889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864407","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with retailers on providing information on the carbohydrate content of food sold in restaurants, cafes and takeaways.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132890","132890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864408","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to address regional variations in access to flash glucose monitoring.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132891","132891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864409","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with clinical commissioning groups on ensuring that guidance from the NHS England Regional Medical Optimisation Committee is implemented and that the committee is consulted on funding decisions.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132892","132892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864410","2018-03-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to record the number of (a) diabetic specialist nurses and (b) podiatrists in order to ensure that adequate numbers of such staff are employed in the NHS.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132893","132893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864411","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) meetings and (b) correspondence the Government has had with the German Government on steps against Volkswagen after its manipulation of data emissions.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132894","132894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/864412","2018-03-19","Department for Transport","2018-03-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans the Government has to bring forward legislative proposals to make the manipulation of emissions data a criminal offence attracting (a) custodial sentences and (b) financial penalties.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 132895","132895"
