"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384649","2015-06-24","HM Treasury","2015-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment HM Revenue and Customs has made of the potential economic effect on Cumbernauld of moving its office there to a new regional West of Scotland campus in or around Glasgow, as proposed in Building our Future - Continuing the Conversation - Phase 2.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3601","3601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384650","2015-06-24","HM Treasury","2015-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what weight HM Revenue and Customs plans to give to the potential economic effect on towns where tax offices are sited of the establishment of regional centres under Building our Future - Continuing the Conversation - Phase 2 when making a decision on that programme.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3602","3602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384651","2015-06-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the replacement rate of council homes sold through the right to buy scheme has been in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) nationally for each year since 2012.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3462","3462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384652","2015-06-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what research reports his Department commissioned from external bodies between September 2010 and December 2014 have not been published; when each such report was commissioned; what the nature of the research commissioned for each such report was; from whom each such research report was commissioned; what the value of each such commission was; on what date each such report was received by his Department; for what reason each such report has not yet been published; and when he plans to publish each such report.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3580","3580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384653","2015-06-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will review the Government's allocation of funding to Merseyside Fire and Rescue Authority and closure of the two fire stations in Wirral West constituency.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3581","3581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384654","2015-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) policy objectives and (b) measurable outcomes are the Northern Powerhouse initiative.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3501","3501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384655","2015-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to encourage councils to implement the zero-carbon home standard from 2016.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3546","3546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384656","2015-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many non-executive directors of his Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments he has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3552","3552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384657","2015-06-24","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many non-executive directors of his Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments he has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3553","3553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384658","2015-06-25","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the benefit to the economy from tourists visiting the Palace of Westminster.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3537","3537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384659","2015-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when an officer of the Ministry of Defence Police last visited the Pitcairn Islands.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3440","3440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384660","2015-06-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many onshore windfarms are situated on Ministry of Defence land; and where each such wind farm is based.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3526","3526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384661","2015-06-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what planning applications for windfarms in what locations on Ministry of Defence land are pending.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3527","3527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384662","2015-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many non-executive directors of his Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments he has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3554","3554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384663","2015-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what additional military training or assistance is being offered to the government of Afghanistan following the recent attack on the Afghan Parliament.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3500","3500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384664","2015-06-24","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many armed forces personnel travelled to Colombia in 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3588","3588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384665","2015-06-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many experiments were carried out by his Department on each animal species in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3596","3596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384666","2015-06-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what animal species were used by his Department in experiments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3597","3597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384667","2015-06-25","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to publish his Department's report, undertaken in December 2014, on the training of Libyan soldiers at Bassingbourn Barracks and subsequent attacks in Cambridge.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3604","3604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384668","2015-06-25","Department for Education","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to respond to the Fifth Report of the Education Committee, Session 2014-15, HC 145 on Life Lessons: PSHE and SRE in schools.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3595","3595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384669","2015-06-25","Department for Education","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase the study of STEM subjects by women; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3582","3582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384670","2015-06-25","Department for Education","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding her Department has made available to increase the study of STEM subjects by women in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3583","3583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384671","2015-06-24","Department for Education","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children live in Scotland and go to school in England.","Biography information for John Stevenson","John Stevenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3510","3510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384672","2015-06-24","Department for Education","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many non-executive directors of her Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments she has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3555","3555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384673","2015-06-25","Department for Education","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps she has taken to promote cardiopulmonary resuscitation in schools.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3525","3525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384674","2015-06-24","Department for Education","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many times her Department has met (a) Norfolk County Council and (b) the Inspiration Trust to discuss the land on which the Hewlett School sits in Norwich South.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3446","3446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384675","2015-06-24","Department for Education","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons she exercised an academy order under section 4 of the Academies Act 2010 in appointing a sponsor for the Hewett School in Norwich.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3507","3507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384676","2015-06-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of 18 to 24 year old (a) women and (b) men were not in education, employment or training in each (i) parliamentary constituency and (ii) region in England in each of the last four quarters for which data is available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3536","3536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384677","2015-06-24","Department for Education","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how often her Department has made an academy order under section 4 of the Academies Act 2010 in each year since 2010; and in what region each school so affected is based.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3486","3486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384678","2015-06-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of granting local communities the right to veto wind farm applications.","Biography information for Phil Wilson","Phil Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3451","3451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384679","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Written Statement of 18 June 2015, HCWS 40, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the early closure of the Renewables Obligation to new onshore wind on the Levy Control Framework.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3452","3452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384680","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to reduce industrial energy costs.","Biography information for Richard Harrington","Richard Harrington","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3455","3455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384681","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 2 June 2015 to Question 418, whether her Department received reports from the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority (NDA) which were not published by the NDA or her Department.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3456","3456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384682","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 2 June 2015 to Question 419, on energy: infrastructure, in which (a) region and (b) companies the jobs in (i) offshore wind and (ii) renewable electricity are supported.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3457","3457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384683","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the proportion of the UK's (a) electricity, (b) heat and (c) transport demand that will be met by renewables by 2020.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3532","3532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384684","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the proportion of the UK's electricity demand that will be met each type of renewables technology by 2020.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3533","3533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384685","2015-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many non-executive directors of her Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments she has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3556","3556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384686","2015-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what (a) funds and (b) subsidies are available to encourage people to install renewable energy in their homes.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3545","3545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384687","2015-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 1 June 2015 to Question 596, how many UK supply chain (a) jobs and (b) apprenticeships were created by each type of renewable energy for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3569","3569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384688","2015-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 1 June 2015 to Question 601, where components of the Rampion wind farm will be manufactured; and which aspects of the supply chain will be UK manufactured.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3591","3591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384689","2015-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2015 to Question 603, what estimate she has made of the likely relative benefit for supply chains in (a) the UK and (b) other countries of investment in off-shore wind.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3592","3592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384690","2015-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the capacity is of wind turbines (a) built and (b) with planning consent awaiting construction in Northamptonshire.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3590","3590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384691","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether there is any (a) local and (b) national Government support available for decommissioning wind farms at the end of their productive life span; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3610","3610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384692","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to her oral statement of 22 June 2015, HC Deb, column 618, on onshore wind subsidies, if she will publish a list of wind farms and turbine applications in Morecambe and Lunesdale constituency that can be appealed under the grace period.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3611","3611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384693","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to her oral statement of 22 June 2015, HC Deb, column 618, on onshore wind subsidies, if she will clarify the status of grace period and the proposed wind farm recently given planning permission on Heysham headlands port area; to what areas such a review would apply; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3612","3612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384694","2015-06-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ask or require local planning authorities to publish the planning routes for any application of (a) fracking and (b) any other energy facilities.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3613","3613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384695","2015-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 1 June 2015 to Question 610, what amount of coal has been imported to the UK from each country in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3593","3593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384696","2015-06-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 1 June 2015 to Question 610, what forecasts her Department has made of the amount of coal that will be imported from each country in (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3594","3594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384697","2015-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many non-executive directors of her Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments she has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3557","3557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384698","2015-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the study commissioned by her Department in 2009 to provide scientific evidence on whether cage-based breeding for pheasants and partridges can fully meet birds' needs will be published.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3518","3518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384699","2015-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many non-executive directors of his Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments he has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3558","3558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384700","2015-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2015 to Question 1570, what commitments he has received from his Chinese counterpart in response to his concerns on the treatment of Muslims in Xinjiang province.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3512","3512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384701","2015-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what additional aid and assistance is being offered to the government of Afghanistan following the recent attack on the Afghan Parliament.","Biography information for Stephen Pound","Stephen Pound","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3502","3502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384702","2015-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, in what ways the Balance of Competences review on the EU has informed the Government's negotiating position on EU reform.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3586","3586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384703","2015-06-24","Department of Health","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that whistle-blowers in the NHS remain anonymous.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3513","3513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384704","2015-06-24","Department of Health","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual cost to the NHS is of providing screening for (a) sickle cell disease, (b) cystic fibrosis, (c) congenital hypothyroidism, (d) phenylketonuria, (e) medium-chain acyl-CoA dehydrogenase deficiency, (f) maple syrup urine disease, (g) isovaleric acidaemia, (h) glutaric aciduria type 1, and (i) homocystinuria (pyridoxine unresponsive) (i) in total and (ii) on average per each test delivered; and how many such tests were undertaken in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3515","3515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384705","2015-06-24","Department of Health","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many non-executive directors of his Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments he has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3559","3559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384706","2015-06-24","Cabinet Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) gender, (b) age-group at death, (c) International Classification of Disease (10th revision) code for the underlying cause of death, (d) registration delay in days, (e) calendar year of death and (f) calendar year of death registration was for each death registered in Stockton North constituency from 2010 to 2014 with a registration delay of 366 days or more.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3571","3571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384707","2015-06-24","Cabinet Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths were registered in Stockton North constituency in each year from 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3572","3572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384708","2015-06-24","Cabinet Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths registered in Stockton North constituency from 2010 to 2014 had a registration delay of at least 366 days between the date of death and the date of death registration.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3573","3573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384709","2015-06-24","Cabinet Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths registered in Stockton North constituency from 2010 to 2014 had a registration delay of at least 183 days between the date of death and the date of death registration.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3574","3574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384710","2015-06-24","Department of Health","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people resident in Wales are registered with a GP in England.","Biography information for John Stevenson","John Stevenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3509","3509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384711","2015-06-25","Department of Health","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his speech of 19 June 2015, A New Deal for General Practice, and the announcement of a £10 million fund to support struggling GP practices, (a) whether such funding represents a new investment or the diversion of existing funds from elsewhere, (b) from where the £10 million will be sourced, (c) how eligibility for financial support under that programme will be determined, (d) whether such support will be contingent upon efforts on the part of qualifying practices to extend access to their services to seven days a week and (e) when he expects the first instalments of that fund to be paid to qualifying practices.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3540","3540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384712","2015-06-24","Department of Health","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of trialling HPV vaccinations for men who have sex with men in a small number of GUM clinics as part of a wider cost-effectiveness evaluation.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3498","3498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384713","2015-06-24","Department of Health","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve access to talking therapies.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3511","3511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384714","2015-06-24","Department of Health","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure at least one mental health specialist is on duty at each Accident and Emergency unit at all times.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3439","3439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384715","2015-06-25","Home Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much compensation her Department paid following the unlawful detention of individuals under immigration powers in the financial year 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3519","3519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384716","2015-06-24","Home Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department takes to monitor the safety of people who have been removed or deported from the UK after their asylum application has been refused (a) on the basis that internal relocation to avoid persecution would be possible and (b) for other reasons.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3447","3447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384717","2015-06-24","Home Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who came to the UK to (a) take part in and (b) spectate at the 2014 Commonwealth Games in Glasgow have (i) remained in the UK illegally, (ii) applied for or been granted asylum and (iii) been granted another form of legitimate leave to remain.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3491","3491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384718","2015-06-25","Home Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when a reply will be sent to the hon. Member for Harrow West's letters of 23 March 2015 and 14 May 2015 on Ms Dubla of Harrow.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3528","3528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384719","2015-06-24","Home Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who came to the UK to (a) take part in and (b) spectate at the London 2012 Olympic and Paralympic Games have (i) remained in the UK illegally, (ii) applied for or been granted asylum and (iii) been granted another form of legitimate leave to remain.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3489","3489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384720","2015-06-24","Home Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from Commonwealth countries were granted indefinite leave to remain in the UK in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3575","3575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384721","2015-06-24","Home Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from Commonwealth countries were refused indefinite leave to remain in the UK in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3589","3589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384722","2015-06-24","Home Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-executive directors of her Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments she has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3560","3560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384723","2015-06-24","Department for International Development","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many non-executive directors of her Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments she has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3561","3561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384724","2015-06-24","Department for International Development","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what effect the auditing of her Department's projects by the Independent Commission for Aid Impact has had on the performance of her Department's projects.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3505","3505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384725","2015-06-24","Department for International Development","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on the Independent Commission for Aid Impact (ICAI) in the last year; how often the ICAI audits the projects of her Department; and under what criteria such audits are carried out.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3503","3503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384726","2015-06-24","Department for International Development","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how the reports, evidence and recommendations of the Independent Commission for Aid Impact are scrutinised within her Department.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3504","3504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384727","2015-06-24","Department for International Development","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to sustain the outside contact enjoyed by the population of the Pitcairn Islands.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3506","3506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384728","2015-06-24","Department for International Development","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to help reduce youth unemployment in (a) Ghana, (b) Kenya and (c) South Africa.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3441","3441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384729","2015-06-24","Department for International Development","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to implement her Department's Start-Up initiative in (a) Ghana, (b) Kenya and (c) South Africa.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3442","3442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384730","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether an internal review has taken place of the Parole Board's decision to authorise the moving of Alan Wilmot to an open prison; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3488","3488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384731","2015-06-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many unimplemented judgements of the European Court of Human Rights there have been in each member state of the Council of Europe in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3535","3535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384732","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library a copy of the course materials and training plans used for the Building Better Relationships programme for male perpetrators of domestic violence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3487","3487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384733","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many and what proportion of cases the maximum sentence for each offence was given in (a) Crown Courts and (b) Magistrates' Courts in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3497","3497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384734","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will issue guidance to court users on the appropriateness of the use of the term victim to describe a complainant in a court case at the pre-conviction stage of proceedings.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3492","3492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384735","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the monetary value is of criminal courts charges (a) imposed and (b) collected since 13 April 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3490","3490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384736","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what programmes are available in the prison service to help prisoners with gambling problems.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3508","3508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384737","2015-06-24","Home Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) women and (b) men safety officers are employed to work with victims of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3496","3496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384738","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the new out of court disposal framework being piloted in West Yorkshire, Staffordshire and Leicestershire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3493","3493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384739","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what community programmes are available in lieu of prison sentences for (a) female and (b) gay or lesbian perpetrators of domestic violence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3495","3495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384740","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people (a) of each sex, (b) in each age group and (c) who committed each type of offence are in prison under sentence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3547","3547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384741","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people who committed each type of offence have been sentenced to a suspended term of imprisonment of over 51 weeks since 3 December 2012.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3548","3548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384742","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many non-executive directors of his Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments he has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3562","3562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384743","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of (a) adult and (b) juvenile offenders who committed each indictable offence received a caution for their first offence in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3577","3577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384744","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of sentence was served by people convicted of murder in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3576","3576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384745","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders in (a) Magistrates' Courts and (b) Crown Courts have received a fine for breaching a suspended sentence since 3 December 2012.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3579","3579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384746","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions magistrates in youth courts have handed down maximum two-year sentences since 2012.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3584","3584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384747","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) number and (b) proportion of first-time offenders who committed each type of offence were sentenced to custody in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3585","3585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384748","2015-06-25","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what account his Department took of the performance of Concentrix in its contract with HM Revenue and Customs in the decision to award that company the contract to collect court fines.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3598","3598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384749","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the trends in the prison population for (a) male and (b) female prisoners over the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3600","3600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384750","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) absconds and (b) escapes took place from each prison in the last five years; and what offences had been committed by the people who absconded or escaped in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3603","3603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384751","2015-06-25","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she last met the Minister for Justice in the Northern Ireland Executive and the Chief Constable of the Police Service of Northern Ireland to discuss the police investigation into the Loughinisland massacre on 18 June 1994; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3599","3599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384752","2015-06-24","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many non-executive directors of her Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments she has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3563","3563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384753","2015-06-25","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will take steps to introduce a Bill of Rights for Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3534","3534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384754","2015-06-25","Scotland Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many public engagement events to support the voluntary sector in Scotland have been held at Dover House in the last five years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3521","3521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384755","2015-06-25","Scotland Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many public engagement events to support Scottish culture have been held at Dover House in the last five years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3522","3522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384756","2015-06-25","Scotland Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many public engagement events to support Scottish enterprise, business and produce have been held at Dover House in the last five years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3523","3523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384757","2015-06-25","Scotland Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many public engagement events to increase understanding of (a) Scottish issues in general and (b) the Scottish Parliament have been held at Dover House in the last five years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3524","3524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384758","2015-06-25","Scotland Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many public engagement events to support (a) Scotland's place in the world and (b) the reputation of Scotland internationally have been held at Dover House in the last five years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3520","3520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384759","2015-06-24","Scotland Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many non-executive directors of his Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments he has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3564","3564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384760","2015-06-24","Scotland Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many people who live in Scotland work in England.","Biography information for John Stevenson","John Stevenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3578","3578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384761","2015-06-24","Department for Transport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many non-executive directors of his Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments he has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3565","3565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384762","2015-06-25","Department for Transport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1550, on what date he received the Stakeholder Executive's review of Network Rail's governance.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3529","3529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384763","2015-06-24","Department for Transport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the percentage change in real terms of the cost to the traveller of travelling by (a) private car, (b) bus, (c) train and (d) domestic aeroplane since (i) 1980, (ii) 1997 and (iii) 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3443","3443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384764","2015-06-24","Department for Transport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the reason is for the time taken to allocate funding under the Regional Air Connectivity Fund; and when an announcement of the launch of the new air links under the Fund will be made.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3445","3445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384765","2015-06-24","Department for Transport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to raise the child rail fare age limit from 15 to 18.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3438","3438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384766","2015-06-25","Department for Transport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question 2610, what his Department's annual expenditure on the South East Flexible Ticketing programme (SEFT) has been; and what the value was of the funding that was transferred from the ITSO on Prestige programme to SEFT.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3531","3531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384767","2015-06-25","Department for Transport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question 3009, whether all Pacer trains will be withdrawn from service once they are displaced from the Northern and Great Western franchises.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3530","3530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384768","2015-06-25","HM Treasury","2015-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ensure that the National Infrastructure Plan of 2014 is implemented in full.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3453","3453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384769","2015-06-25","Department for Transport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were employed in the Highways Agency Traffic Officer Service in each year since 2010; and how many people are employed in the comparable section of Highways England.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3454","3454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384770","2015-06-24","Department for Transport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2015 to Question 2297, what the reasons are for the recent increase in the number of vehicles clamped by other authorities.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3517","3517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384771","2015-06-25","Department for Transport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on Manchester Airport of a new runway at (a) Heathrow and (b) Gatwick Airport.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3538","3538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384772","2015-06-25","Department for Transport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the purpose is of his Department's Rail Infrastructure Futures unit; on what date that unit was created; how many officials work in the Rail Infrastructure Futures team; and whether any external bodies have seconded staff to that unit or undertaken work at Rail Infrastructure Futures' request.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3539","3539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384773","2015-06-24","Wales Office","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many non-executive directors of his Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments he has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3567","3567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384774","2015-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many non-executive directors of his Department who were in post before May 2015 have since left the Department's board; what the names and length of tenure of such directors were; and how many and what non-executive director appointments he has made since May 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3568","3568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384775","2015-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment assessment appointments failed to take place as a result of double booking of appointments between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3516","3516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384776","2015-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of lone parent families with two children affected by the benefit cap have (a) one child and (b) two children aged under five.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3459","3459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384777","2015-06-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of lone parent families with three children affected by the benefit cap have (a) one child, (b) two children and (c) three children aged under five.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3458","3458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384933","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to incentivise greater use of renewable and non-fossil fuel forms of energy.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900543","900543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384948","2015-06-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to support research and innovation in adaptation to climate change.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900553","900553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385139","2015-06-25","Department for Transport","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of automotive emissions on climate change in the next five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900550","900550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385637","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress she has made on the rollout of smart meters.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900556","900556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385638","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to maximise renewable energy generation through public procurement.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900551","900551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/385639","2015-06-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress is being made on reaching an international climate change agreement in Paris.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 900542","900542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384340","2015-06-23","Attorney General","2015-06-19","To ask the Attorney General, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for the Law Officers' Departments and their subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3307","3307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384341","2015-06-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1895, what funding his Department has allocated to the review of consumer protection measures in the online secondary ticketing market.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3285","3285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384342","2015-06-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for his Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3306","3306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384343","2015-06-23","Cabinet Office","2015-06-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to educate young people in secondary schools about electoral registration.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3295","3295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384344","2015-06-23","Cabinet Office","2015-06-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to increase electoral registration in (a) London and (b) the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3296","3296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384345","2015-06-23","Cabinet Office","2015-06-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for his Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3308","3308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384346","2015-06-24","HM Treasury","2015-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the (a) age and (b) reliability of the nation's financial services' IT systems and risks represented to the nation's critical infrastructure.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3352","3352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384347","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the state of the financial service sector's IT systems is recorded on any risk register.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3344","3344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384348","2015-06-24","HM Treasury","2015-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the financial industry on the state of the financial services sector's IT systems.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3333","3333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384349","2015-06-24","HM Treasury","2015-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reasons he did not discuss the sale of the Government's shareholding in Royal Bank of Scotland (RBS) Group with RBS, NatWest Bank or Ulster Bank; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3332","3332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384350","2015-06-24","HM Treasury","2015-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to ensure that the sale of the Government's shareholding in Royal Bank of Scotland Group does not have detrimental financial implications for customers of the banks in that group.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3331","3331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384351","2015-06-24","HM Treasury","2015-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of reducing air passenger duty on tourism, visitor numbers and regional economies.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3330","3330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384352","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to roll out tax-free childcare over 12 months from autumn 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3350","3350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384353","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for his Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3323","3323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384354","2015-06-24","HM Treasury","2015-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress National Savings and Investments (NS&I) has made on developing the IT infrastructure that will underpin tax-free childcare; and whether NS&I expect that system to be ready to begin taking registration from parents in autumn 2015.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3298","3298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384355","2015-06-24","HM Treasury","2015-06-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects parents to begin opening online accounts under the new tax-free childcare scheme; and when he expects eligible parents to receive top-up payments.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3299","3299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384356","2015-06-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for his Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3309","3309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384357","2015-06-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a statutory duty for the fire and rescue service to respond to a major flooding incident; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3341","3341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384358","2015-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of properties bought under the help to buy scheme that have since been sold to private sector landlords.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3334","3334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384359","2015-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of properties bought under the help to buy scheme in each (a) constituency and (b) local authority area are now rented.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3335","3335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384360","2015-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the letter of 27 March 2015 from the Minister of State for Housing and Planning to the Chief Executive of the Planning Inspectorate, what his policy is on landscape character and prematurity in planning decisions.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3336","3336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384361","2015-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Statement of 25 March 2015, HCW488 what his policy is on solar energy.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3337","3337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384362","2015-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's policy is on proposals by developers to build new towns that do not accord with local plans.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3338","3338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384363","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of trends in the levels of employment in the local newspaper industry since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3346","3346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384364","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress his Department is making on determining a permanent memorial to mark the Sikh contribution to the First World War.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3351","3351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384365","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2015 to Question 613, how many libraries were open for 10 hours or more a week in each year between 2010 and 2015; if he will estimate the cost of collecting information on the number of volunteer-run libraries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3288","3288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384366","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2015 to Question 614, on libraries: wi-fi, if he will place in the Library a list of all libraries which his Department's current desktop research indicates do not currently have wi-fi, together with information on which local authority has responsibility for each.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3327","3327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384367","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1896, what representations he has received about creating a cultural protection fund; and what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on such a fund.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3292","3292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384368","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2015 to Question 614, on libraries: wi-fi,  when Arts Council England plans to finish the scheme.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3339","3339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384369","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for his Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3310","3310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384370","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1895, what the commencement dates are of the relevant aspects of the Consumer Rights Act 2015.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3325","3325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384371","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2015 to Question 617, on non domestic rates: local areas, which other departments his Department is working with; and on what dates Ministers in his Department have had discussions on this issue with their counterparts in other departments.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3326","3326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384372","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2015 to Question 611, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the difference between the number of premises with access to superfast broadband and the number of premises using such broadband; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3289","3289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384373","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish his Department's Annual Report and Accounts.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3290","3290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384374","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many full-time equivalent officials are working on Charter Renewal.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3291","3291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384375","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the value is of arts assets in the vaults of the museums and galleries which receive grant-in-aid.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3286","3286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384376","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 215 to Question 614, whether the £7.4 million being made available to help all public libraries to install wi-fi is only for the capital cost of installation; what estimate he has made of the average cost of installing wi-fi; and what estimate has he made of the non-capital costs over each of the next five years of providing free wi-fi in the libraries that do not have it.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3287","3287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384377","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many local and regional newspapers there were in each of the last five years; whether he has estimated the (a) numbers of such newspapers in any future years and (b) trends in that number; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3283","3283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384378","2015-06-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for his Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3311","3311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384379","2015-06-23","Department for Education","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for her Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3312","3312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384380","2015-06-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make an assessment of the effect of the removal of the Renewables Obligation from onshore wind in 2016 on investor confidence in renewable energy in the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3278","3278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384381","2015-06-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for her Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3313","3313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384382","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for her Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3314","3314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384383","2015-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the need for security of supply of potash minerals.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3328","3328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384384","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on beak trimming of chickens; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3279","3279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384385","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made on research on non-beak trimmed birds; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3305","3305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384386","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the Scottish Government on (a) the effects of seals on fishing populations, (b) minimising the need to kill seals to maintain fishing populations and (c) improving the level of protection for seals.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3275","3275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384387","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect seals have on (a) fish populations and (b) fishing equipment.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3349","3349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384388","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department has taken to improve protection for the seal population.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3348","3348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384389","2015-06-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for his Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3315","3315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384390","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for his Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3316","3316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384391","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria are used to allocate budgets to each NHS Strategic Clinical Network.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3277","3277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384392","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients in the Lewisham and Greenwich NHS Trust had to wait longer than 48 hours for a GP appointment in (a) 2010 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3293","3293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384393","2015-06-24","Department of Health","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funds his Department has provided for mental health research (a) in cash terms, (b) in real terms and (c) as a proportion of the total research and development budget in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3297","3297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384394","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether individuals who were released from Young Offender Institution Swinfen Hall since October 2014 have been identified and screened for tuberculosis.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3276","3276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384395","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the case of tuberculosis diagnosed at Young Offender Institution Swinfen Hall in October 2014 is directly linked to the three cases identified at the same site between March and May 2015.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3304","3304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384396","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will update its impact assessment for funding reform to care and support services in England to take account of the Government's policy to increase inheritance tax thresholds by 2020.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3345","3345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384397","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what budget has been allocated to each NHS Strategic Clinical Network in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Neil Carmichael","Neil Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3353","3353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384398","2015-06-23","Home Office","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from the Kurdistan Region in Iraq (a) applied for and (b) were refused entry clearance to the UK in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3343","3343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384399","2015-06-23","Home Office","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the economic effect on universities in Scotland of the removal of the post-study work visa.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3282","3282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384400","2015-06-23","Home Office","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for her Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3317","3317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384401","2015-06-23","Department for International Development","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for her Department are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3318","3318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384402","2015-06-23","Department for International Development","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the use by Hamas of (a) UK and (b) UN humanitarian aid.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3281","3281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384403","2015-06-23","Department for International Development","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her Department's policies of the findings of Irresponsible Investment: Agrica's broken development model in Tanzania, published on 17 June 2015 by Global Justice Now, the Oakland Institute and Greenpeace Africa.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3347","3347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384404","2015-06-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for his Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3319","3319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384405","2015-06-23","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for her Department are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3320","3320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384406","2015-06-23","Prime Minister","2015-06-19","To ask the Prime Minister, when the (a) Earn or Learn and (b) Digital infrastructure and inclusion implementation taskforces will meet; who will participate in those meetings; when minutes of these meetings will be published; whether those minutes will list attendees; whether the taskforces have secretariats; what resources are assigned to the taskforces; and how many full-time equivalent officials work on those taskforces.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3284","3284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384407","2015-06-23","Scotland Office","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for his Department are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3321","3321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384408","2015-06-23","Department for Transport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for his Department and its subsidiary agencies are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3322","3322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384409","2015-06-23","Department for Transport","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish a response to the Law Commission report, Reforming the law on taxis and private hire services, Cm 8864, published in May 2014.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3340","3340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384410","2015-06-23","Wales Office","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for his Department are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3324","3324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384411","2015-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of working households claiming housing benefit in (a) Lewisham, (b) London and (c) England.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3294","3294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384412","2015-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many working recipients of universal credit have had their benefits reduced or stopped because a sanction was applied as a result of in-work conditionality.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3329","3329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384413","2015-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many landlords have trusted partner status for the purpose of placing tenants under alternative payment arrangements for universal credit; what proportion of universal credit recipients they cover; and what plans he has to extend that status.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3300","3300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384414","2015-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit recipients have been placed under alternative payment arrangements by social landlords with trusted partner status.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3301","3301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384415","2015-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit recipients have been placed under alternative payment arrangements for the housing cost element of universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3302","3302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384416","2015-06-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of in-work conditionality applied to recipients of universal credit who are in work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3303","3303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384417","2015-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to help people with disabilities back into work.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3280","3280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/384418","2015-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to ensure that employers comply with legislation and guidance on controlling excessively high temperatures in the workplace.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3342","3342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383751","2015-06-22","Attorney General","2015-06-18","To ask the Attorney General, which buildings occupied by the Law Officers' Departments are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3095","3095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383752","2015-06-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to recommendation 73 of Lord Heseltine's No Stone Unturned report, published in October 2012, and to paragraph 1.48 of the Government's response to the Heseltine review, published in March 2013, how the Government distinguishes between investment which benefits the UK economy and investment which does not; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3079","3079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383753","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3094","3094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383754","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the potential economic benefit of a city region deal to Aberdeen.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3127","3127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383755","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of customs duties the UK contributed to the EU budget arose from (a) Africa, (b) Asia, (c) South America and (d) the Middle East in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3150","3150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383756","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the cost to UK manufacturers of customs duties imposed on their products by non- EU countries.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3152","3152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383757","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to raise awareness among people travelling within European Economic Area countries in order to ensure all such travellers hold an EHIC card.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3068","3068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383758","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received on the practice of voided travel insurance policies as a result of alcohol consumption; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3069","3069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383759","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that holidaymakers are treated fairly and equitably when they claim on the travel insurance policies they may take out.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3070","3070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383760","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government has taken to notify holidaymakers about the importance of taking out travel insurance when travelling abroad on holiday.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3071","3071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383761","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of the UK contribution to the EU budget for customs duties is attributable to (a) manufactured goods, (b) new materials and (c) agricultural produce.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3161","3161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383762","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many learners used 19 plus adult learning services in each of the last five academic years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3182","3182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383763","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, by what average proportion adult learning services budgets have varied in (a) this and (b) the next financial year.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3183","3183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383764","2015-06-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of invoices from suppliers to his Department were paid within 10 days of receipt in (a) March and (b) April 2015.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3264","3264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383765","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will meet the Skills Funding Agency to discuss the number of course places his Department will fund in the coming year.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3233","3233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383766","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will meet the Edcuation Funding Agency to discuss the number of course places his Department will fund in the coming year.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3234","3234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383767","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will set out the different rates of customs duty applied to imports into the UK and the nature of the goods to which each rate applies.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3203","3203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383768","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many adult learning service departments in England are judged by Ofsted to be (a) outstanding, (b) good and (c) needs improvement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3180","3180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383769","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people are employed by local authorities in adult learning services in England.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3181","3181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383770","2015-06-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations his Department has received from current and former sub-postmasters on the performance of the Post Office sub-postmaster mediation scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3257","3257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383771","2015-06-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the Post Office sub-postmaster mediation scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3258","3258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383772","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will meet representatives of Dudley College to discuss upcoming funding allocations for (a) adult skills, (b) the Skills Funding Agency and (c) the Education Funding Agency.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3231","3231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383773","2015-06-22","Cabinet Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent representations he has received on the decision of Lord Lyon to prevent Airdrieonians Football Club from using its current badge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3274","3274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383774","2015-06-22","Cabinet Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many full-time equivalent staff of each civil service grade are employed in the private office of each Minister of his Department; and what the pay band of each such member of staff is.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3165","3165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383775","2015-06-23","Cabinet Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of extending the franchise in all elections to 16 and 17 year olds on voter turnout.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3147","3147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383776","2015-06-22","Cabinet Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3096","3096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383777","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households were in receipt of child tax credit in Renfrewshire (a) on the last date for which figures are available and (b) in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3091","3091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383778","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will make an assessment on the UK economy of removing all custom duties on products from Africa.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3151","3151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383779","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will reduce the rate of VAT on (a) alcohol sold in the hospitality sector and (b) alcohol served with a meal in the hospitality sector.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3088","3088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383780","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3111","3111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383781","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department made any payments to the Institute of Fiscal Studies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mhairi Black","Ms Mhairi Black","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3119","3119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383782","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate his Department has made of the level of spare capacity in the economy; and on what analysis that estimate is based.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3067","3067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383783","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the income tax gap in Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3046","3046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383784","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the public purse of the overall cost of intervention in UK banks following the financial crisis of 2007-08.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3133","3133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383785","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made in each of the last five years of the effect on the public purse of the sale of the Government's stake in the Royal Bank of Scotland.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3134","3134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383786","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many lone parents have been in receipt of (a) child tax credit and (b) working tax credit in Renfrewshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3143","3143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383787","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households receive child benefit in Renfrewshire; and how many such households received child benefit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3138","3138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383788","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average waiting time is for callers to the tax credits renewal hotline.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3172","3172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383789","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households were in receipt of working tax credit in Renfrewshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3173","3173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383790","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many households received the married couple's allowance in Renfrewshire (a) on the last day for which figures are available and (b) in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3174","3174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383791","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the economy of UK membership of the EU and what effect leaving the EU would have on the economy.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3239","3239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383792","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have received (a) face to face and (b) telephone advice through Pension Wise since that service opened; and what those numbers are as proportions of all people eligible to take advantage of new pension flexibilities.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3251","3251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383793","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1914, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the implementation of IR35  anti-avoidance legislation.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3254","3254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383794","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1915, what the total revenue collected in corporation tax for personal service companies was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3255","3255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383795","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the potential cost to the public purse of converting HM Revenue and Customs helpline numbers to Freephone services.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3221","3221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383796","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will fund a major retrofit programme for energy efficiency; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3227","3227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383797","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has made to the Royal Bank of Scotland on ensuring (a) pensioners and (b) other customers receive payments on time.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3228","3228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383798","2015-06-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that local councils uphold their statutory duty to promote community cohesion.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3050","3050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383799","2015-06-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3097","3097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383800","2015-06-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with (a) housing associations and (b) lenders on the potential effects of the extension of the right to buy scheme on the credit ratings and ability to access credit of housing associations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3189","3189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383801","2015-06-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the average loss to housing associations in (a) rental income over a period of 25 years and (b) capital for each housing association property sold under the proposed extension of the right to buy scheme in Warrington.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3187","3187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383802","2015-06-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many properties in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency will qualify for sale to existing tenants under the proposed extension of the right to buy scheme to housing association tenants; and if he will estimate the average price on the open market of those properties.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3188","3188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383803","2015-06-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many affordable homes have been built in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3202","3202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383804","2015-06-22","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of libraries that will close in England and Wales between 2015 and 2020.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3184","3184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383805","2015-06-22","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, on what date he expects the review of BBC Charter renewal to commence.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3136","3136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383806","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department made of the proportion of (a) Copeland and (b) Cumbria covered by (i) 2G voice and low data rate mobile coverage, (ii) 3G high-speed data mobile coverage and (iii) 4G very high-speed data mobile coverage.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3245","3245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383807","2015-06-22","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many and what proportion of staff in his Department are paid less than the living wage.","Biography information for John Nicolson","John  Nicolson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3211","3211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383808","2015-06-22","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3098","3098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383809","2015-06-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2015 to Question 1237 on television: disability, what targets his Department uses to judge if significant progress has been made on the provision of access service on Video on Demand.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3145","3145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383810","2015-06-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual cost to his Department of redundancy payments for staff employed in his Department has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin John Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3130","3130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383811","2015-06-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many full-time equivalent staff at each civil service grade are employed in the private office of each Minister in his Department.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3129","3129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383812","2015-06-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to publish the details of the Gurkha mixed marriage compensation scheme.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3066","3066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383813","2015-06-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3099","3099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383814","2015-06-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) desktop, (b) laptop and (c) tablet computers were lost by his Department in 2014-15.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3048","3048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383815","2015-06-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to Paragraph 12 of the European Parliament resolution on the situation in Ukraine (2014/2965(RSP)), if he will take steps to provide (a) communications equipment, (b) night vision equipment and range finders and (c) other non-lethal military equipment to Ukraine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3053","3053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383816","2015-06-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with Ukraine on providing forces in that country with non-lethal military equipment.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3054","3054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383817","2015-06-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has made with his EU and NATO counterparts on providing non-lethal military equipment to Ukraine.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3055","3055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383818","2015-06-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department made in each of the last five years of how much fuel would be needed in that year to accomplish all Royal Navy maritime tasking; and how much fuel was provided to the fleet in each such year.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3047","3047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383819","2015-06-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2015 to Question 1740, whether infrastructure work in advance of the arrival of the F-35 squadron has begun at RAF Marham.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3212","3212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383820","2015-06-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will consult political parties which are not in government on development of the Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3250","3250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383821","2015-06-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2015 to Question 1740, what complex weapons he expects to be operational on the F-35 (a) by 2018, (b) by 2019, (c) by 2020 and (d) after 2020.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3213","3213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383822","2015-06-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to consult businesses as part of the Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3252","3252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383823","2015-06-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how he plans to liaise with other government departments on the development of the Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3253","3253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383824","2015-06-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library notes and minutes of meetings between representatives of his Department and Cambridge City councillors on the effect on the local community of basing Libyan personnel at Bassingbourn; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3199","3199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383825","2015-06-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library the internal Ministry of Defence and Home Office review report on Libyan training at Bassingbourn; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3198","3198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383826","2015-06-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which UK treaty obligations will be taken into account in development of the Strategic Defence Review.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3240","3240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383827","2015-06-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for public consultation on the contents of the Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3241","3241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383828","2015-06-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made in seeking a replacement for the Nimrod aircraft for the RAF's maritime reconnaissance capability; and what alternative aircraft platforms are under elevation for this role.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3244","3244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383829","2015-06-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what arrangements his Department is making to ensure that US and UK F-35 squadrons at RAF Lakenheath and RAF Marham benefit from joint through-life support.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3168","3168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383830","2015-06-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the number of aircraft necessary to meet the threshold of initial operating capability for the F-35.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3169","3169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383831","2015-06-22","Department for International Development","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, who will lead and which ministers will be part of the British delegation to the Financing for Development Summit in Addis Ababa in July 2015.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3135","3135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383832","2015-06-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what functions he plans to delegate to a combined authority should Clause 6 of the Cities and Local Government Devolution Bill pass into law.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3160","3160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383833","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence her Department holds to support the proposition that academies are better performers than local authority schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3142","3142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383834","2015-06-23","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the expectation that all students should take Ebacc subjects applies to university technical college and studio school students.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3191","3191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383835","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of children's centres which have (a) closed and (b) opened in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3237","3237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383836","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Health about child and adolescent mental health services in England; and what the conclusion was of those discussions.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3206","3206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383837","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of children's centres which will close in England and Wales between 2015 and 2020.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3205","3205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383838","2015-06-22","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many crimes were committed against people aged under 18 in supported accommodation in each region and constituent part of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3216","3216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383839","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will meet the Skills Funding Agency to discuss the number of places her Department will fund in the coming year.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3232","3232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383840","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the average cost of establishing a free school in temporary accommodation before moving that school to another building; and whether costs of such temporary accommodation and moves are included by her Department in value for money assessments.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3210","3210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383841","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will meet the Education Funding Agency to discuss the number of course places her Department will fund in the coming year.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3229","3229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383842","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will meet representatives of Dudley College to discuss upcoming funding allocations for (a) adult skills, (b) the Skills Funding Agency and (c) the Education Funding Agency.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3230","3230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383843","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many free schools of a religious character have (a) 50 to 100 per cent (b) 40 to 49 per cent, (c) 30 to 39 per cent, (d) 20 to 29 per cent, (e) 10 to 19, (f) less than 10 per cent, (g) less than five per cent and (h) less than one per cent of children from other faiths or no faith.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3207","3207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383844","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of free schools is single-sex.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3208","3208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383845","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of single-sex free schools is of a religious character.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3209","3209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383846","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which buildings occupied by her Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3100","3100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383847","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 4 March 2014 to Question 189394, what comparative assessment she has made of the value for money of (a) community schools other than academies and (b) free schools.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3063","3063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383848","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 12 February 2014 to Question 187197, on school admissions, if she will place in the Library copies of (a) all those letters to local authorities where a free school is being proposed and (b) any representations from local authorities in response to those letters.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3064","3064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383849","2015-06-23","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish in one place on gov.uk where each school is located, each school's unique reference number and local authority establishment number, the URL for each such school's page on her Department's school and college performance tables website, the URL for each such page on Ofsted's Inspection Report website, the name of the company which has an academy funding agreement, and the Companies House registration number of each of those companies.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3077","3077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383850","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many full-time equivalent staff at each civil service grade are employed in the private office of each Minister in her Department.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3131","3131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383851","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will offer financial incentives to the UK oil and gas sector to stimulate growth.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3122","3122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383852","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policies on climate change of the Papal encyclical issued on 18 June 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3120","3120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383853","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her policy is on the continuation of operation of the Renewables Obligation Closure Order 2014, no 2388, before the introduction of primary legislation to close the Renewables Obligation to new onshore wind from 1 April 2016.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3082","3082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383854","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which buildings occupied by her Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3101","3101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383855","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions she Department has had with investors who have sunk costs in the onshore wind pipeline under the Renewables Obligation.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3092","3092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383856","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 June 2015, HC WS40, whether her Department plans to offer support under the Renewables Obligation to the proposed Temple Hill wind farm.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3217","3217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383857","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 June 2015, HC WS40, whether her Department plans to offer support under the Renewables Obligation to the proposed Fulbeck Airfield wind farm.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3218","3218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383858","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 June 2015, HC WS40, whether her Department plans to offer support under the Renewables Obligation to the proposed Nocton Fen wind farm.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3219","3219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383859","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Written Statement of 18 June 2015, HC WS40, whether her Department plans to offer support under the Renewables Obligation to the proposed Sewstern Lane wind farm.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3220","3220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383860","2015-06-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will publish a plan committing to phase-out coal without carbon capture technology from the power sector by 2032.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3265","3265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383861","2015-06-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will bring forward proposals for a regulated social tariff for all energy suppliers to ensure all low income customers automatically receive the cheapest tariff.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3200","3200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383862","2015-06-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government will be taking in the (a) short, (b) medium and (c) long-term to achieve the G7's goal of decarbonising the global economy by the end of this century.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3247","3247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383863","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which onshore wind farms are registered as having a grid connection offer and acceptance.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3144","3144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383864","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she plans to take to develop the potential for on-shore wind in Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross constituency; and how she plans to take account of that potential in reviewing on-shore wind subsidies.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3162","3162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383865","2015-06-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what length of waterbodies is being removed from the current round of river basin management planning; and what assessment her Department has made of the effects on wildlife of removing those waterbodies.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3164","3164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383866","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Hunting  Act 2004 in each police force area in 2014.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3270","3270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383867","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Wild Animals (Protection) Act 1996 in each police force area in 2014.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3271","3271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383868","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Protection of Badgers Act 1992 in 2014.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3262","3262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383869","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people were (a) proceeded against and (b) convicted of an offence under the Deer Act 1991 in 2014.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3261","3261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383870","2015-06-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which buildings occupied by her Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3102","3102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383871","2015-06-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure the Government meets its commitments in the 2011 Natural Choice White Paper on (a) removing barriers to learning outdoors and (b) increasing the ability of schools to teach outdoors.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3061","3061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383872","2015-06-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dogs entered the UK from each country for (a) non-commercial purposes under the Pet Travel Scheme and (b) commercial purposes under the Balai Directive 92/45/EEC in 2014.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3114","3114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383873","2015-06-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to tackle the decline in the bee population.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3118","3118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383874","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research her Department plans to undertake to establish a fair and objective criteria for an assessment of land classes across the UK in advance of her Department's review of convergence of uplift payment allocation.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3149","3149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383875","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what timetable she has set for her Department to become a living wage employer.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3146","3146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383876","2015-06-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to carry out the review of the convergence of uplift payment allocation in 2016.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3148","3148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383877","2015-06-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to encourage Thailand, Indonesia and Malaysia to (a) protect the human rights of Rohingyan refugees and (b) provide those refugees with asylum.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3153","3153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383878","2015-06-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on proposals to introduce EU sanctions on Israeli products.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3065","3065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383879","2015-06-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3103","3103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383880","2015-06-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the proposed permanent nuclear deal between Iran and the P5+1 would permit the IAEA to conduct anytime, anywhere inspections of Iran's nuclear facilities.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3058","3058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383881","2015-06-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the IAEA has been granted access to the Arak facility in Iran.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3059","3059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383882","2015-06-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the franchise for the proposed referendum on the UK's membership of the EU.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3266","3266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383883","2015-06-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of Iran's ballistic missile research and development programme.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3201","3201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383884","2015-06-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of Iran's financial and material support for Hezbollah.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3166","3166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383885","2015-06-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of Iran's financial and material support for Hamas.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3167","3167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383886","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children and young people accessed child and adolescent mental health services in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3186","3186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383887","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2015 to Question 740, if he will commission comparative research into the incidence of hepatitis B and HIV infection in (a) the national population, (b) the population of men who have sex with men and (c) men in a civil partnership or married to a man.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3163","3163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383888","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children and young people who are projected to need access to child and adolescent mental health services in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3185","3185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383889","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1756, what consultation his Department plans to undertake on the action plan for diabetes.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3155","3155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383890","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1756, if he will include in the action plan for diabetes a national patient experience survey for patients with diabetes.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3154","3154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383891","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what initiatives his Department has created in order to destigmatize mental health issues.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3272","3272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383892","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish its response to the consultation on updating the NHS constitution that closed in April 2015; and what plans his Department has to publish responses received by that consultation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3196","3196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383893","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has for the future implementation of the No Health without Mental Health strategy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3197","3197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383894","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on the implementation of the new Care Certificate; and what recent estimate he has made of the number of health and care workers who are making progress towards obtaining that certificate.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3195","3195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383895","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons proposed plans for a new appeals system in adult social care do not include making recommendations of independent appeals panels binding on local authorities.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3194","3194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383896","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on the future of the Cancer Drugs Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3177","3177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383897","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the funding and availability of medicines for blood cancer patients in England compared to their counterparts in Scotland and Wales.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3175","3175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383898","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the work of the Scottish New Medicines Fund in funding treatments for rarer cancers.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3176","3176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383899","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions were issued for bupropion in each year since 2001.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3204","3204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383900","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage (a) more of the total population and (b) eligible MSM to donate blood; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3093","3093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383901","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues in the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs about bringing forward targets for reducing the inappropriate use of antibiotics in agriculture in line with comparable targets for reducing their use in medicine in the UK Five Year Antimicrobial Resistance Strategy 2013-18; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on human health of not so adjusting those targets.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3078","3078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383902","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3104","3104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383903","2015-06-23","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to provide funding for everolimus.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3075","3075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383904","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on research into Patau and Edwards Syndrome in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3083","3083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383905","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of planned Government-funded spending on research into Patau and Edwards Syndrome in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3084","3084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383906","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on paediatric bereavement nurses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3085","3085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383907","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what proportion of prescriptions a charge was levied in 2014-15.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3121","3121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383908","2015-06-23","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects that a decision will be reached on pre-licence application SPL5298000134 made by Bridgend College Coleg Penybont on 2 July 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3116","3116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383909","2015-06-22","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent representations she has received on disparities between the level of pensions paid to the widows of police officers in Northern Ireland and the rest of the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3086","3086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383910","2015-06-22","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what mechanisms there are to appeal against decisions made by the Police and Crime Commissioner for Norfolk on the Child Abuse Inquiry Support Fund and the Child and Adult Victims of Sexual Abuse Support Fund.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3087","3087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383911","2015-06-22","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which buildings occupied by her Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3105","3105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383912","2015-06-22","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department gives to chief police officers on dealing with illegal Traveller encampments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3057","3057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383913","2015-06-23","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2015 to Question 1466, what additional resources her Department plans to make available to ensure that all Disclosure and Barring Service checks are completed on time nationally in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3256","3256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383914","2015-06-22","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures she plans to take to implement the recommendations of the most recent report on Tinsley House Immigration Removal Centre by HM Chief Inspector of Prisons; and if she will conduct a review of the operation of (a) the families unit and (b) alternatives to detention at that centre.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3178","3178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383915","2015-06-22","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of detainees sent to Tinsley House Immigration Removal Centre were assessed by a nurse upon arrival in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3179","3179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383916","2015-06-22","Cabinet Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people from Commonwealth countries who remained longer than a year entered the country in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3235","3235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383917","2015-06-22","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people from Commonwealth countries entered the country in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3236","3236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383918","2015-06-22","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will commission an audit of reports submitted by healthcare professionals in Immigration Removal Centres under Detention Centre Rule 35 to maintain compliance with policy on the detention of victims of crime.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3223","3223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383919","2015-06-23","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Yemenis have been granted refugee leave since the beginning of the present political and military crisis in Yemen.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3193","3193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383920","2015-06-23","Home Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications made by asylum seekers under Article 8 of Schedule 1 of the Human Rights Act 1988 were upheld by the courts in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3157","3157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383921","2015-06-22","Department for International Development","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department plans to provide for (a) research on and (b) treatment of malaria until 2020.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3060","3060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383922","2015-06-23","Department for International Development","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2015 to Question 1293, in what countries her Department is working on projects with the International Labour Organisation; and what the value of her Department's funding is for each such project.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3056","3056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383923","2015-06-23","Department for International Development","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2015 to Question 1293, what funding her Department has provided to International Labour Organisation programmes in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3052","3052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383924","2015-06-22","Department for International Development","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which buildings occupied by her Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3106","3106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383925","2015-06-25","Department for International Development","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much aid her Department has provided to people affected by the crisis in Yemen in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3074","3074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383926","2015-06-22","Department for International Development","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what consultancy firms her Department works with in the delivery of projects for (a) treatment of and (b) research on malaria.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3062","3062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383927","2015-06-24","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what changes have been or are to be made to how bailiffs operate as a result of HM Courts and Tribunals Service recent review of enforcement methods.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3073","3073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383928","2015-06-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3107","3107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383929","2015-06-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his plans are for the role of the Public Defender Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3140","3140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383930","2015-06-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on (a) external legal advice from Queen's Counsel and (b) other external legal advice between 7 May 2010 and the present day; what the 20 highest amounts paid for external legal advice by his Department were in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011 and (iii) 2012; to whom such payments were made; for what reasons such legal advice was sought; and what the highest day rate paid for external legal advice by his Department was since 7 May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3158","3158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383931","2015-06-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the monthly running cost is of each court building which has been closed but not disposed of since May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3159","3159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383932","2015-06-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employees in his Department have been (a) made redundant or (b) offered redundancy since 7 May 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3156","3156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383933","2015-06-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress he has made on plans for paperless working in the courts.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3249","3249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383934","2015-06-22","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which buildings occupied by her Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3108","3108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383935","2015-06-22","Scotland Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3109","3109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383936","2015-06-22","Scotland Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps he plans to take to reduce his Department's running costs between 2015 and 2020; and what savings he plans to make from reducing his Department's running costs in 2015-16.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3128","3128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383937","2015-06-23","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-06-18","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what proportion of electors in each local authority area are data matched.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3246","3246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383938","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what resources he (a) has made and (b) plans to make available to Transport for Greater Manchester to make the county's railway stations fully accessible for wheelchair users; and if he will meet the hon. Member for Denton and Reddish to discuss resources for wheelchair accessibility at Reddish North station.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3170","3170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383939","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many road traffic accidents have happened on the M56 between junctions 12 and 14 in the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3171","3171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383940","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to support Network Rail achieve and sustain journey time reductions on the Far North Rail Line from Inverness to Thurso and Wick; and if he will make increased funding available to the Scottish Government for investment in that line.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3214","3214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383941","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how the connectivity of Glasgow Airport compares to that of (a) London City, (b) Heathrow and (c) Gatwick airports.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3222","3222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383942","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to encourage greater use of rural rail lines by those over 50 years of age; and if he will provide increased funding to the Scottish Government to encourage uptake of the Club 50 scheme.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3215","3215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383943","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to investigate the management and communications with customers of (a) Southern and (b) Network Rail.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3132","3132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383944","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the application of Regulation EC 1071/2009 concerning occupation of transport operators.","Biography information for Sir Alan Meale","Sir Alan Meale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3124","3124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383945","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish his Department's response to the formal notification of infraction from the European Commission concerning the Government's application of Regulation EC 1071/2009 on access to the occupation of a road transport operator; and what steps he plans to take in response to that notification.","Biography information for Sir Alan Meale","Sir Alan Meale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3125","3125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383946","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3110","3110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383947","2015-06-23","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects to make a decision on whether to grant First Great Western permission to order new trains to operate on its intercity routes to Devon and Cornwall; and whether he expects that permission will require a section 54 undertaking of the designation of such trains, or their lease agreement as a franchise asset.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3081","3081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383948","2015-06-23","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2015 to Question 2371, what meetings (a) he, (b) other Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have held to discuss Network Rail since 1 March 2015; when each such meeting took place; and which organisations external to the core Department were present at each such meeting.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3117","3117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383949","2015-06-23","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to encourage research and development into the production of new diesel multiple units by UK-based manufacturers.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3080","3080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383950","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effects of each of the shortlisted options for a new runway in South East England on connectivity to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3051","3051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383951","2015-06-23","Department for Transport","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to include provisions on improving the quality of and access to training and continuing professional development for employeers of train operating companies in all future franchise agreements.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3072","3072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383952","2015-06-22","Wales Office","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3112","3112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383953","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3113","3113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383954","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants in Renfrewshire that appealed all or part of a sanction of their benefit were successful in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3089","3089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383955","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many sanctions were given to benefit claimants in Renfrewshire who are (a) lone parents and (b) have a learning disability in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3090","3090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383956","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the usability of the Stat-Xplore website.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3115","3115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383957","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to make payments of winter fuel allowance to those who qualify for such payments after the third Monday in September and before 1 January before the end of the same financial year.","Biography information for Sir Alan Meale","Sir Alan Meale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3123","3123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383958","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the number of claimants receiving benefits pertaining to a mental health condition who have been given an assessment of whether they are fit to work based only on their physical health.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3126","3126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383959","2015-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the number of children in the borough of Walsall living in poverty in (a) households including a person who is in employment and (b) other households.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3076","3076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383960","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that older people with disabilities are adequately supported to meet their higher costs through nationally-administered disability benefits.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3049","3049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383961","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how much benefit has been withheld from claimants as a result of sanctions in each quarter since 2005.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3238","3238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383962","2015-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been awarded in discretionary housing payments by each local authority in London (a) in total, (b) to people affected by the household benefit cap, (c) to people affected by a reduction in local housing allowance rates and (d) to people affected by the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3259","3259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383963","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to compile data on the number of people using food banks.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3225","3225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383964","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to reduce delays in benefits payments.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3226","3226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383965","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he will estimate the effect on the annual income of the (a) poorest 10 per cent, (b) poorest 20 per cent, (c) poorest 25 per cent, (d) poorest 30 per cent, (e) richest 40 per cent, (f) richest 30 per cent, (g) richest 25 per cent, (h) richest 20 per cent and (i) richest 10 per cent of households if the child element of child tax credit was reduced to 2003-04 levels in real terms.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3224","3224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383966","2015-06-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to further roll out the Universal Credit programme in Torbay constituency in 2015-16.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3273","3273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383967","2015-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people affected by the household benefit cap who were placed by the local authority in temporary accommodation were placed outside their local authority area in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3260","3260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383968","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department made any payments to the Institute of Fiscal Studies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mhairi Black","Ms Mhairi Black","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3139","3139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383969","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that all benefit claimants understand the Claimant Commitment.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3141","3141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383970","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what average length of time applicants in Renfrewshire have waited for personal independence payment assessments since the start of their rollout.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3137","3137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383971","2015-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what sanctions have been issued by each Jobcentre Plus in each month in 2014.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3263","3263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383972","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in London are affected by the household benefit cap; and how many such people have been placed by their local authority in temporary accommodation.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3267","3267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383973","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what savings he expects to accrue to the public purse as a result of freezing working-age benefits in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3268","3268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383974","2015-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he will estimate how many people who would otherwise be eligible for universal credit who would not be so eligible if the child element was reduced in real terms to the 2003-04 level of the child element of child tax credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3243","3243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383975","2015-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the pilot schemes aimed at in-work claimants.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3192","3192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383976","2015-06-23","HM Treasury","2015-06-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he will estimate the number of people who would no longer receive child tax credits if the child element was reduced to its 2003-04 level in real terms.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3242","3242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383977","2015-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people had their benefits sanctioned in East Lothian in each of the last 12 quarters for which figures are available.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3190","3190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383978","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit sanctions in Scotland there were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3269","3269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/383979","2015-06-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the feasibility of seconding Job Centre staff to do outreach sessions at food banks to support people who are experiencing problems with the administration of the welfare system.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3248","3248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381763","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the statement by the Minister of State for Energy and Climate Change of 17 June 2015, Official Report, columns 108-112WH, what the evidential basis is for the statements that (a) a geological disposal facility is internationally recognised as the safest means of managing radioactive waste and (b) that Sweden, Finland, Canada and the US are pursuing that type of facility.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3035","3035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381764","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the contribution of the Minister of State for Energy and Climate Change of 17 June 2015, Official Report, columns 108-112WH, what the evidential basis is for the statement that a nuclear programme will save households £78 on their energy bills in 2030.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3036","3036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381765","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the contribution of the Minister of State for Energy and Climate Change of 17 June 2015, Official Report, columns 108-112 WH, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the price of wholesale electricity will rise into the 2020s.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3037","3037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381766","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the contribution of the Minister of State for Energy and Climate Change of 17 June 2015, Official Report, columns 108-112WH, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the UK has one of the most robust regulatory regimes in the world for nuclear power.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3038","3038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381767","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the contribution of the Minister of State for Energy and Climate Change of 17 June 2015, Official Report, columns 108-112WH, what the evidential basis is for official the statement that nuclear power is a low-carbon, proven technology.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3039","3039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381768","2015-06-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his US counterparts on the ratification by that country of the Comprehensive Nuclear Test Ban Treaty.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2989","2989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381769","2015-06-22","Department for International Development","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what information her Department holds on how many houses have been built in Gaza to replace those destroyed during Operation Protective Edge; and what proportion that number is of the number destroyed.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2901","2901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381770","2015-06-22","Department for International Development","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to assist the Sahrawi people.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2831","2831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381771","2015-06-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage a free and fair referendum on the governance of Western Sahara.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2829","2829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381772","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1384, on fuels: rebates, when the filling station in the KW12 postcode area that submitted evidence as part of the Calls for Information did so; and what the content of that submission was.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2902","2902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381773","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1384, on fuels: rebates, whether the filling station in the KW12 postcode area that submitted evidence as part of the Calls for Information subsequently claimed relief through the rural fuel rebate scheme.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2903","2903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381774","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many applications her Department has received for licences for unconventional gas extraction since 2010; how many such applications were approved; how many applications her Department has received for onshore wind generation facilities since 2010; and how many such applications were approved.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2875","2875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381775","2015-06-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on the UK remaining a party to the European Convention on Human Rights; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2871","2871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381776","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost of constructing High Speed 2 (a) Phase 1 and (b) Phase 2 is in 2015 prices.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2856","2856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381777","2015-06-22","HM Treasury","2015-06-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will introduce a cap on pension company charges for people seeking to switch, cash-in or otherwise vary their pension policy.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2959","2959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381778","2015-06-22","Leader of the House","2015-06-17","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to end the payment of allowances to hon. Members who do not take their seats.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2962","2962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381779","2015-06-22","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what information she holds on the number of parades held in Northern Ireland in 2014 categorised by the Parades Commission as (a) loyal order or loyalist, (b) community or church based and (c) republican or nationalist in character.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2960","2960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381780","2015-06-22","Northern Ireland Office","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many voters were added to the electoral register between 1 December 2014 and 1 April 2015 in each constituency in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2961","2961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381781","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what financial resources the Government plans to allocate for the provision of basic English and mathematics in further education.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2973","2973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381782","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve the performance of careers services.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2994","2994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381783","2015-06-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward proposals to implement a ban on the killing of seals; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2988","2988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381784","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many measures of each type in each region have been installed under the Green Deal since it was introduced.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2966","2966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381785","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the value of loans is made under the Green Deal in each region since that scheme was introduced.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2965","2965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381786","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many loans have been made in each region under the Green Deal since it was introduced.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2964","2964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381787","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) desktop, (b) laptop and (c) tablet computers his Department has lost in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2939","2939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381788","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will introduce a right of appeal to a body outside the DVLA for drivers whose car was clamped or towed because  they failed to comply with the changes to the rules on tax discs, or who did comply but this was not noted because of an administrative error by the DVLA.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2889","2889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381789","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what statistics his Department collects on deaths of benefit claimants; and how it is decided and by whom in his Department which statistics on such claimants will be (a) collected and (b) published.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2905","2905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381790","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has had with the Information Commissioner on the Freedom of Information request on deaths of benefit claimants made on 25 June 2013.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2906","2906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381791","2015-06-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of (a) employment and support allowance and (b) incapacity benefit who were (i) in the assessment phase, (ii) found fit to work, (iii) placed in the work-related activity group, (iv) placed in the support group and (v) with an appeal pending have died in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2955","2955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381792","2015-06-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans she has to tackle risks associated with disused open cast mines; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2980","2980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381793","2015-06-22","Church Commissioners","2015-06-17","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what proposals the Church Commissioners have received to allow community energy generation using church roofs for solar panels.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 3028","3028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381794","2015-06-22","Church Commissioners","2015-06-17","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what support she is providing to churches for the installation of PV panels.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2916","2916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381795","2015-06-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether council houses (a) whose value exceeds the median value for properties of the same size in the same region and (b) the value of which is in the top third of the range will be included in the planned extension of the right-to-buy scheme for housing association tenants.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2987","2987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381796","2015-06-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of affordable homes that will be (a) started and (b) completed in (i) Greenwich and Woolwich constituency, (ii) the Royal Borough of Greenwich, (iii) Greater London and (iv) England in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2985","2985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381797","2015-06-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many council-owned properties have become vacant in (a) Greenwich and Woolwich constituency, (b) the Royal Borough of Greenwich, (c) Greater London and (d) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2976","2976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381798","2015-06-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the projected number of housing association tenants that will meet the eligibility criteria for discounts offered under the planned extension of the right-to-buy scheme to housing association tenants in each of the first five years after the introduction of that policy in (a) England, (b) Greater London and (c) Greenwich and Woolwich constituency.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2978","2978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381799","2015-06-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many housing association properties were sold under Right to Acquire provisions in each year since 2010 in (a) Greenwich and Woolwich constituency, (b) the Royal Borough of Greenwich, (c) Greater London and (d) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2979","2979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381800","2015-06-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the G15 group of London housing associations on the potential effects of the planned extension of the right-to-buy scheme for housing association tenants.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2981","2981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381801","2015-06-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the average sale price per property of houses to be sold under the proposed extension of the right to buy scheme for housing association tenants.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2972","2972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381802","2015-06-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of council houses which meet the criteria for sale under the planned extension of the right to buy scheme for housing association tenants; and what estimate he has made of how many of those properties will fall vacant in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2974","2974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381803","2015-06-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what date she plans to publish a new national air quality plan.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2970","2970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381804","2015-06-22","Department of Health","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people in London who have died as a result of air pollution in each year since 2010; and if he will estimate the forecast number of such deaths in the next 10 years.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2968","2968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381805","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the level of air pollutant emissions from (a) road traffic, (b) aviation and (c) shipping on the air quality in London.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2983","2983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381806","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) research and (b) information his Department holds on the performance of the (i) Southeastern and (b) Southern rail franchises.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2984","2984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381807","2015-06-22","Department for Transport","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings he has had with representatives of rail franchises operating in South London in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2982","2982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381808","2015-06-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to reply to the letter to him dated 13 May 2015 from the hon. Members for Aberdeen North, Aberdeen South and West Aberdeenshire and Kincardine regarding an Aberdeen City Region Deal.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2956","2956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381809","2015-06-22","Cabinet Office","2015-06-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Government departments are planning to become accredited living wage employers.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2952","2952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381810","2015-06-22","Home Office","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the Government's policy is on the detention of refugee women.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2832","2832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381811","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 26 March 2015 to Question 228386, what steps her Department plans to take in relation to the four authorities found to be in breach of visiting timescales for children in private fostering arrangements.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2986","2986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381812","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will take steps to raise the profile of the Care Planning and Fostering Regulations and Guidance among local authorities.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2918","2918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381813","2015-06-22","Department for Education","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to publish rates of re-entry to care rates in each local authority area.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2917","2917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381814","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to promote increased long-term share ownership in UK businesses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2826","2826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381815","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of the British-based aerospace sector is foreign-owned; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2827","2827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381816","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of foreign ownership of UK-based companies on productivity in the aerospace sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2835","2835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381817","2015-06-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assumptions his Department has made about the powers at its disposal to regulate investments by overseas (a) state-owned enterprises and (b) sovereign wealth funds; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2838","2838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381818","2015-06-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential risks posed to national security by investments in UK defence companies by foreign (a) state-owned enterprises and (b) sovereign wealth funds; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2837","2837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/381819","2015-06-22","Home Office","2015-06-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential risks posed to UK national security by investments in critical national infrastructure by foreign (a) state-owned enterprises and (b) sovereign wealth funds; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 2836","2836"
