"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417781","2015-09-11","Prime Minister","2015-09-08","To ask the Prime Minister, who the acting Prime Minister would be if he were incapacitated.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9591","9591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417782","2015-09-14","Prime Minister","2015-09-08","To ask the Prime Minister, what definitions the Government adopts of (a) self-defence and (b) imminence in authorising the Khan drones strike; and what assessment the Government has made of the difference between such definitions and those formulated by the US administration.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9653","9653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417783","2015-09-10","Scotland Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9545","9545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417784","2015-09-10","Scotland Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many officials in his Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9508","9508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417785","2015-09-10","Scotland Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which external organisations officials in his Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9526","9526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417786","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which external organisations officials in his Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9527","9527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417787","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many officials in his Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9509","9509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417788","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9546","9546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417789","2015-09-11","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 5809, when he expects to publish the terms of reference for Sir Peter Hendy's review of the rail investment programme.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9600","9600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417790","2015-09-11","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2015 to Question 7660, by what mechanism would the cost of Intercity Express Programme conversion be met should that option be taken up.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9601","9601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417791","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the value is of the Maritime and Coastguard Agency's (MCA) contract with the Met Office to provide the shipping forecast; what the terms and termination date of that contract are; and what assessment he has made of the effect of the decision by the BBC to terminate its weather contract with the Met Office on the latter's contract with the MCA.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9551","9551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417792","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to (a) monitor the usage of and (b) prevent accidents involving unmanned drones in airspace over the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9437","9437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417793","2015-09-11","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of people affected by the decision by Virgin Trains to end the easement whereby railcard holders can purchase discounted off-peak tickets for travel on peak time trains.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9446","9446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417794","2015-09-11","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he and his Ministers and officials had with Virgin Trains during or after the process of its tender for the West Coast mainline about the easement which allows concessions to pay off-peak prices for peak time travel for some customers with railcards.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9448","9448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417795","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what comparative assessment his Department has made of methods used in other European countries to detect and prevent speeding offences.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9353","9353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417796","2015-09-11","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2015 to Question 5189, whether Network Rail's Accounting Officer has sought formal direction to proceed on any matter from his Department's Principal Accounting Officer since 1 September 2014.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9397","9397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417797","2015-09-11","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the tender by Virgin Trains for the West Coast mainline included plans to end in September 2016 the easement whereby railcard holders can purchase discounted off-peak tickets for travel on peak time trains.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9447","9447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417798","2015-09-11","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will place in the Library the correspondence between his Department and Virgin Trains about its decision to end the easement for railcard holders to purchase discounted off-peak tickets for travel on peak time trains.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9445","9445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417799","2015-09-11","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when Network Rail will publish its new Electrification Route Utilisation Strategy.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9456","9456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417800","2015-09-11","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to his Department has been of external consultancy work in connection with developing the policies on Network Rail outlined in paragraph 1.255 of the Summer Budget, HC 264.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9602","9602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417801","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of public expenditure per person in Wales.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9589","9589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417802","2015-09-10","Wales Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many officials in his Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9511","9511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417803","2015-09-10","Wales Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which external organisations officials in his Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9529","9529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417804","2015-09-10","Wales Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9548","9548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417805","2015-09-10","Women and Equalities","2015-09-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how much funding has been allocated to Women and Broadband projects in each area in (a) 2015-16 and (b) each of the previous three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9380","9380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417806","2015-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of present Government guidance available to employers on managing the health and safety of new and expectant mothers at work.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9595","9595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417807","2015-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many new and expectant mothers were (a) dismissed, (b) made compulsorily redundant where others in their workplace were not and (c) treated so poorly they felt they had to leave their job over the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9639","9639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417808","2015-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the statistics his Department holds on sanctions applied to claimants of (a) job seeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance where the claimant is also in receipt of carer's allowance.","Biography information for Dr Eilidh Whiteford","Dr Eilidh Whiteford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9603","9603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417809","2015-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the shortfall in pension accrual experienced by employees who are employed through an umbrella payroll company or similar overarching employment contract and do not receive automatic enrolment pension contributions from their employer.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9648","9648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417810","2015-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of workers employed through an umbrella payroll company who will opt-out of automatic-enrolment into a workplace pension.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9649","9649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417811","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effect on (a) relative and (b) absolute child poverty of the four-year freeze announced in the July Budget on the uprating of (i) jobseeker's allowance and (ii) employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9628","9628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417812","2015-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of automatic-enrolment pension arrangements on workers employed through employment agencies.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9646","9646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417813","2015-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made on addressing the backlog in applications for personal independence payments; and for what median end-to-end time applicants are currently waiting.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9645","9645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417814","2015-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received from the UN Special Rapporteur on disabled rights on an investigation into welfare reforms since May 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9461","9461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417815","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 24 March 2015 to Question 228133, and pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2015 to Question 748, how much has been claimed in hardship payments in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9414","9414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417816","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was spent setting up the Preston Learning Academy by cost type to 23 July 2015; how many people have received training at that academy; and in which departments in HM Revenue and Customs those people were working at the time of that training.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9399","9399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417817","2015-09-11","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to extend the Blue Badge scheme to the carers or partners of those with dementia.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9403","9403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417818","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9549","9549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417819","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which external organisations officials in his Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9530","9530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417820","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to respond to the letter dated 24 June 2015 from the hon. Member for Ashfield on self-employment amongst women.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9550","9550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417821","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many officials in his Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9512","9512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417822","2015-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the effect of the welfare cap will be in (a) Wellingborough and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9590","9590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417823","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many representations he has received from hon. Members from the Conservative Party on the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9434","9434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417824","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what equality impact assessment of the recent change to the benefits cap his Department has undertaken.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9474","9474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417825","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received from the UN Committee on the Rights of Persons with Disabilities on an investigation into welfare reforms since May 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9424","9424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417826","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the highest amount of annual housing benefit paid to a single household was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9481","9481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418546","2015-09-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the building of homes for social rent.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901320","901320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418547","2015-09-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to speed up the planning process.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901317","901317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418548","2015-09-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the National Planning Policy Framework in addressing the housing needs of disabled people.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901319","901319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418549","2015-09-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with local government leaders on the provision of (a) housing and (b) other council assistance for refugees.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901300","901300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418550","2015-09-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent comparative assessment he has made of (a) the level of funding for and (b) the costs of local authorities.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901305","901305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417128","2015-09-09","Attorney General","2015-09-07","To ask the Attorney General, how much the Law Officers' Departments spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9162","9162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417129","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average sentence for the offence of assisted suicide is for each year since 2009.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9328","9328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417130","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many employees of McKinsey are working on his Department's spending review; for how long those employees have been so engaged; what remit those staff have been given; what the cost to the public purse is of such staff; and if he will list which organisations and individuals his Department has consulted during that spending review.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9316","9316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417131","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what reviews his Department is conducting with assistance from McKinsey.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9317","9317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417132","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2015 to Question 7500, how many vouchers were redeemed under the Growth Vouchers scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9274","9274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417133","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that students from other EU countries repay student loans taken out in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9291","9291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417134","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received on the future of the Research Councils.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9318","9318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417135","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2015 to Question 5250, which projects and programmes that have been funded from the public purse since 2010 relate to each of the Eight Great Technologies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9310","9310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417136","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which (a) HEIs, (b) Research Institutes, (c) Catapult Centres and (d) other research institutions funded by HEFCE are located within the boundaries of two local enterprise partnerships.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9319","9319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417137","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress has been made on the Great Challenges programme; and what recent steps the Government has taken to support that programme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9311","9311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417138","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what work his Department is undertaking to review whether tribunal fees are acting as a barrier to justice; and how many officials were engaged in that work (a) in March 2015 and (b) on the last date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9301","9301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417139","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2015 to Question 4159, what (a) process and (b) performance metrics were used to determine the level of fees received by firms involved in the sale of Royal Mail shares.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9302","9302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417140","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what evaluation or evidence-gathering the Government (a) has carried out or commissioned and (b) plans to carry out into (i) the Grand Challenges programme announced on 17 December 2014 and (ii) the Eight Great Technologies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9312","9312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417141","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funds the HEFCE has allocated to (a) the Equality Challenge Unit and (b) the Athena SWAN programme in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) future financial years; and what effect his Department's announcement on 4 June 2015 has had on those programmes.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9303","9303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417142","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many members of staff are employed in the HEFCE Equality Challenge Unit.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9304","9304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417143","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) assessment criteria and (b) key outputs and performance indicators have been set for (i) the Eight Great Technologies and (ii) the Grand Challenges programme announced on 17 December 2014.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9313","9313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417144","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2015 to Question 6486, what the location is of each planned Next Generation Digital Economy Centre.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9238","9238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417145","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to his Answer of 6 July 2015 to Question 4950, what funds from the public purse (a) were spent and (b) he plans to spend on the HEFCE UK Research Partnership Investment Fund in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2020-21 in real terms.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9239","9239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417146","2015-09-09","Cabinet Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which premises are occupied by each of the seven What Works Centres; what the location is of each such centre; how many staff are employed at each such centre; and what key performance indicators or delivery metrics have been set for the What Works Network.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9240","9240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417147","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to secure an agreement between OECD countries to stop supporting all coal projects overseas through export credit agencies.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9260","9260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417148","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to publish the findings and results of the Growth Vouchers scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9275","9275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417149","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on what dates the Council for Science and Technology met in the last 12 months; on what dates and who was in attendance at each such meeting.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9285","9285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417150","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) fellowships and (b) other outputs have been delivered under the Newton Fund in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9286","9286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417151","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what threshold his Department set for the number of Growth Vouchers used to provide robust evidence-gathering under the programme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9276","9276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417152","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how he plans to spend the funds which were allocated but unused as part of the Growth Vouchers scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9277","9277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417153","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has for the future of the Growth Vouchers scheme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9278","9278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417154","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the commercial gain from the work of Catapult centres that has been realised overseas.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9267","9267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417155","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take in response to the completion of the Insolvency Service's review into the collapse of Comet.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9279","9279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417156","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what changes have been made to Research Council deadlines for grant funding applications since May 2015.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9268","9268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417157","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has for funds allocated under the Growth Vouchers scheme have not been claimed.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9269","9269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417158","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many Growth Vouchers redeemed after 31 March 2015 are undergoing assessment.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9270","9270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417159","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has for future projects under the Foresight Project of the Government Office for Science.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9280","9280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417160","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what public funds have been committed to the Sciencewise project in the next five financial years.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9281","9281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417161","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what provision he made for Growth Vouchers to be redeemed after the deadline for their use passed.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9271","9271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417162","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the Science and Innovation Network 2014 Annual Report will be published.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9282","9282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417163","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Government's press release of 20 May 2015, on machinery of government: Shareholder Executive and UK financial investments, what consultation was undertaken prior to the transfer of the Executive from his Department to HM Treasury; what factors were taken into account in reaching that decision; on what evidence that decision was based; on what date plans were first discussed by (a) officials and (b) Ministers; and when the formal transfer took place.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9287","9287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417164","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what forecasts he has made of revenues likely to accrue to the Medical Research Council from patents in future financial years; and how much the Medical Research Council generated from patents in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9272","9272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417165","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which patents the Medical Research Council holds; on what date each such patent will expire; and what revenue was generated by each such patent in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9273","9273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417166","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his Department's press release of 17 December 2014, what progress has been made on establishing the Inspiring Science Capital fund; and what timetable has been set for the establishment of that fund.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9283","9283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417167","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 16 March 2015 to Question 227103, how many businesses (a) applied for and (b) were granted Growth Vouchers to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9284","9284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417168","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what work his Department is undertaking to review and evaluate rules on company takeovers.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9314","9314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417169","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he has had discussions with his EU counterparts on competition in the European car rental market.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9342","9342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417170","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when Ministers were informed of the BBC's decision to terminate its contract with the Met Office; and by what means they were so informed.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9205","9205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417171","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to encourage students from low-income backgrounds to access higher education; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9131","9131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417172","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many Met Office staff are on secondment to (a) Government and (b) other publicly-funded departments, agencies and bodies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9204","9204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417173","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Met Office spent on research and development in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9206","9206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417174","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding from the public purse was allocated to subscription to the European Centre for Medium-Range Weather Forecasts in each financial year since 2010-11; what funding has been so allocated in the present financial year; what estimate he has made of the cost of such subscription in future financial years; and from which departmental budget such subscriptions are paid.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9207","9207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417175","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have had with (i) their counterparts in the Department for Culture Media and Sport and (b) the BBC on the termination of the BBC's contract with the Met Office.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9208","9208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417176","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which Government and publicly-funded bodies and agencies subscribe to Met Office services; what the value is of each such subscription; and what the termination date is of each such subscription.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9210","9210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417177","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will make an assessment of the likely effect of the abolition of student maintenance grants on widening participation in higher education.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9133","9133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417178","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value is of the contracts currently delivered by the Met Office to commercial organisations.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9211","9211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417179","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many Met Office staff are on secondment to the armed forces.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9212","9212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417180","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the budgetary implications for the Met Office of the termination of its contract with the BBC.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9209","9209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417181","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of the funds generated by the Met Office's contract with the BBC was spent on research in the last 12 months; and what research projects undertaken by the Met Office in that period the BBC has (a) collaborated with or (b) participated in.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9223","9223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417182","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff secondments (a) to and (b) from (i) universities, (ii) research institutes and (iii) research centres the Met Office has in place; and how many such secondments took place in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9224","9224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417183","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which collaborations with (a) universities, (b) research institutes and (c) research centres the Met Office is engaged in; when each such secondment is due to expire; and how many such collaborations have been discontinued since 2010.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9225","9225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417184","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Medical Research Council has spent on research projects relating to the treatment of cancer in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9226","9226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417185","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for his Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9242","9242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417186","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what research and evidence he has (a) assessed and (b) commissioned on the management of maternity cover by (i) small and (ii) large employers.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9215","9215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417187","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) guidance and (b) support his Department provides for employers on the management of maternity cover; and what plans he has to increase such support.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9216","9216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417188","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what public funding has been allocated to support the Astrea programme; what applications for funds for that programme his Department has received and under which Government programmes; and what plans he has for future funding of that programme.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9234","9234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417189","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what measure of inflation his Department uses for research and development spending; and what research he has (a) commissioned and (b) consulted in forming his policy.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9235","9235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417190","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, who the chief scientific advisers are; when each such adviser took up their post; and which chief scientific adviser posts currently remain unfilled.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9236","9236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417191","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many potential tribunal claims for pregnancy-related detriment or dismissal were notified to Acas under the early conciliation scheme in 2014-15; and how many of those claims (i) were settled by conciliation by Acas, (ii) progressed to a tribunal claim and (iii) were not settled by conciliation by Acas but did not progress to a tribunal case.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9119","9119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417192","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding his Department has allocated to encourage students from low-income backgrounds to access higher education in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9135","9135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417193","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the Green Investment Bank will invest in projects (a) according to its existing risk profile and sectoral focus and (b) exclusively in the UK economy during the period in which the Government is discussing privatisation of the Bank with private investors.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9137","9137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417194","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department, its agencies or Ofcom has made an assessment of (a) the appropriateness of the role of local authorities in the creation of addresses for the Postcode Address File and (b) whether that role constitutes a subsidy to Royal Mail.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9138","9138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417195","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9161","9161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417196","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many start-up loans the Government has made to young people under the age of (a) 25 and (b) 30 in each year since the commencement of the start-up loan scheme; what the current default rate is on such loans; and what estimate he has made of how many more such loans will be made over the next five years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9127","9127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417197","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received about retrospective changes to the terms and conditions of student loan repayments.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9129","9129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417198","2015-09-09","Cabinet Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what fees were paid to Sir John Chilcot for his work on the Iraq Inquiry in each quarter from January 2014 to the end of June 2015.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9090","9090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417199","2015-09-10","Cabinet Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has for tackling digital exclusion over this Parliament; and if he will publish the data that his Department collects on digital exclusion.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9157","9157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417200","2015-09-10","Cabinet Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the principles his Department follows for handling and sharing the data of members of the public.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9155","9155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417201","2015-09-10","Cabinet Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to appoint a Chief Data Officer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9156","9156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417202","2015-09-09","Cabinet Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for his Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9243","9243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417203","2015-09-09","Cabinet Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9163","9163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417204","2015-09-10","Cabinet Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average working days lost per full time equivalent member of staff was as a result of sick days and absences in the Civil Service in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9241","9241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417205","2015-09-09","HM Treasury","2015-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for his Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9256","9256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417206","2015-09-09","HM Treasury","2015-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to address telephone scamming related to banking services.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9262","9262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417207","2015-09-09","HM Treasury","2015-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will continue to ensure that the UK does not contribute to the EU bailout package for Greece.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9333","9333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417208","2015-09-09","HM Treasury","2015-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9178","9178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417209","2015-09-09","HM Treasury","2015-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department and the Government Chief Scientific Adviser had with Departments in advance of decisions to cut departmental research budgets or expenditure since May 2010; and on what dates each such discussion took place with each such department.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9237","9237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417210","2015-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new jobs have been created in each Enterprise Zone in each financial year since 2010-11; and what estimate he has made of the proportion of jobs at each Enterprise Zone which have been moved to other locations.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9221","9221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417211","2015-09-09","HM Treasury","2015-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what research he has (a) commissioned and (b) examined on the effect of Enterprise Zones on investment and job creation in other neighbouring localities.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9222","9222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417212","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have been contacted on behalf of HM Revenue and Customs by Concentrix; and for what purpose they were so contacted.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9146","9146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417213","2015-09-09","HM Treasury","2015-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will extend eligibility for the main residence nil rate band of inheritance tax to non-direct descendants.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9086","9086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417214","2015-09-09","HM Treasury","2015-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on potential Barnett consequentials arising from the Thames Tideway Tunnel project.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9088","9088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417215","2015-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to provide additional funding to local authorities to assist them to provide support to Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9124","9124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417216","2015-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the capacity of local authorities to provide support for refugees from Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9125","9125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417217","2015-09-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what meetings his Department has had with (a) Dart Energy, (b) Igas Energy, (c) Cuadrilla Resources, (d) INEOS Group, (e) Rathlin Energy and (f) Addison Project in the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9122","9122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417218","2015-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of changes in the Summer Budget 2015 to the level of rents paid by social tenants on the construction of new social housing.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9106","9106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417219","2015-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how she plans to apportion proposed fines relating to the target in the EU Waste Framework Directive to recycle 50 per cent of household waste by 2020 between local authorities.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9232","9232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417220","2015-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to issue guidance to local authorities on the EU Waste Framework Directive requiring them to recycle 50 per cent of household waste by 2020.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9228","9228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417221","2015-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to implement the target to recycle 50 per cent of household waste by 2020 set in the EU Waste Framework Directive at a waste disposal authority or waste collection authority level.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9229","9229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417222","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to reintroduce the landfill tax escalator.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9230","9230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417223","2015-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for his Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9244","9244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417224","2015-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9164","9164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417225","2015-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to monitor availability of homes in the Buy to Let category in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9305","9305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417226","2015-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of household waste each local authority recycles.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9231","9231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417227","2015-09-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9165","9165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417228","2015-09-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for his Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9245","9245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417229","2015-09-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he expects part two of the Leveson Inquiry, examining allegations of police corruption and the relationships between newspaper organisations and the police, prosecuting authorities and relevant regulatory bodies to take place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Mitchell","Mr Andrew Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9096","9096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417230","2015-09-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for his Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9246","9246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417231","2015-09-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9166","9166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417232","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many locally-employed Afghan interpreters who worked alongside the British Army have (a) applied for relocation to the UK and (b) been resettled in the UK under his Department's resettlement package to date.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9114","9114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417233","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the clean-up costs of land owned by his Department that (a) has been sold in the last year and (b) is earmarked for sale.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9158","9158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417234","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the value of commercial land owned by his Department that has been earmarked for sale.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9159","9159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417235","2015-09-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to increase the number of women in high-ranking positions in the armed forces.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9293","9293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417236","2015-09-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to retain personnel in the armed forces.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9307","9307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417237","2015-09-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) average and (b) maximum period for duty in battle zones is for (i) army, (ii) Royal Navy and (iii) RAF personnel.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9329","9329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417238","2015-09-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many ships cannot go to sea due to shortages in specialist personnel.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9330","9330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417239","2015-09-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to prevent veteran service personnel leaving to join private sector companies.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9331","9331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417240","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to continue the universal infant free school meals programme.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9136","9136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417241","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve procurement in the education sector; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9183","9183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417242","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in the county of West Sussex were funded (a) by the local authority and (b) centrally in the financial years 2010-11 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9184","9184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417243","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the name is of each (a) community school, (b) voluntary aided school, (c) voluntary controlled school, (d) foundation school and (e) academy school in the county of West Sussex.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9185","9185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417244","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding has been provided to each pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in the county of West Sussex (A) in cash terms and (B) at 2015 prices in each financial year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9186","9186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417245","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) budget and (b) pupil number was for each voluntary controlled school in the county of West Sussex in each year from 2005-06 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9191","9191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417246","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to alter the school funding formula; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9187","9187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417247","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils in the county of West Sussex were eligible for free school meals in each year from 2005-06 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9188","9188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417248","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) budget and (b) pupil number was for each academy school in the county of West Sussex in each year from 2005-06 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9189","9189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417249","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) budget and (b) pupil number was for each foundation school in the county of West Sussex in each year from 2005-06 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9190","9190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417250","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) budget and (b) pupil number was for each voluntary aided school in the county of West Sussex in each year from 2005-06 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9192","9192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417251","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) budget and (b) pupil number was for each community school in the county of West Sussex in each year from 2005-06 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9193","9193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417252","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) amount and (b) proportion of the capital funding budget for new school places was allocated to free schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9100","9100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417253","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average number of decisions on Academy Orders her Department has taken each week in the last three years; and what estimate she has made of the average number of hours taken each week to make such decisions.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9099","9099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417254","2015-09-10","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost has been of each academy conversion in Cheshire West and Chester since 2002.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9123","9123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417255","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9167","9167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417256","2015-09-15","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to reduce salt content in school meals.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9213","9213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417257","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils were eligible for free school meals in (a) state, (b) academy, (c) free, (d) faith and (e) private schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9214","9214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417258","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for her Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9247","9247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417259","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many officials her Department employs to administer the (a) academies and (b) free schools programme.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9097","9097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417260","2015-09-09","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the total held in reserves by academies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9098","9098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417261","2015-09-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for her Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9248","9248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417262","2015-09-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much her Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9168","9168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417263","2015-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what meetings Ministers or officials of her Department have had with (a) Dart Energy, (b) Igas Energy, (c) Cuadrilla Resources, (d) INEOS Group, (e) Rathlin Energy and (f) Addison Project in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9121","9121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417264","2015-09-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her Department's domestic energy bill estimates were for each Public Energy Supply region for the most recent period.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9107","9107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417265","2015-09-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps the Government is taking to encourage investors to develop and construct new gas plant such as the Gateway Energy Centre.","Biography information for Stephen Metcalfe","Stephen Metcalfe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9128","9128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417266","2015-09-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how she is working with her counterparts in the EU to increase the EU's Carbon Reduction Commitment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9258","9258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417267","2015-09-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will commit to phase out unabated coal from the power sector by 2023; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9259","9259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417268","2015-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to (a) reduce and (b) control the population of (i) gulls and (ii) black-backed gulls.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9338","9338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417269","2015-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she plans to take to improve air quality in Ellesmere Port and Neston constituency.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9105","9105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417270","2015-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much importance is accorded to food security in the determination of the Government's agricultural policy.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9198","9198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417271","2015-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for her Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9249","9249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417272","2015-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 27 July 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms J Walters.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9094","9094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417273","2015-09-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for his Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9250","9250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417274","2015-09-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9169","9169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417275","2015-09-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Hungarian government on the treatment of refugees in Hungary.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9108","9108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417276","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterparts in (a) Kuwait, (b) Saudi Arabia, (c) the United Arab Emirates and (d) Qatar on their role in the humanitarian effort to assist Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9140","9140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417277","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letter to her on the Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme dated 28 July 2015 from the hon. Member for Hammersmith.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9326","9326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417278","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the amount of salt in food consumed in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9290","9290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417279","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the prioritisation process for treatments on the National Cancer Drugs Fund list will take place in 2015-16.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9315","9315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417280","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in Northern Ireland have Parkinson's disease; and what the age profile of those patients is.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9294","9294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417281","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps he has taken to improve the treatment of breast cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9292","9292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417282","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure day patients attend their (a) GP and (b) hospital appointments.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9298","9298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417283","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to introduce the drug Duodopa for the treatment of NHS patients with Parkinson's disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9295","9295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417284","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Northern Ireland Executive on a regional strategy for Parkinson's disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9296","9296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417285","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make available on the NHS the skin cancer injection treatment Opdivo.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9297","9297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417286","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in Cambridgeshire and Peterborough Foundation Trust region were required to travel outside of their trust area to receive emergency mental health treatment for each year since 2010.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9324","9324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417287","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of Crisis Resolution and Home Treatment teams operating in England and Wales offer 24-hour home visits seven days a week.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9323","9323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417288","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department and the NHS provided to research projects related to the treatment of cancer in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9266","9266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417289","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many psychiatric wards in England exceed (a) 85, (b) 90 and (c) 95 per cent occupancy rates.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9325","9325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417290","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to make the dementia drug solanegement available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9339","9339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417291","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to promote public awareness of the danger of paracetamol overdoses.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9336","9336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417292","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Northern Ireland Executive on introducing seven day per week accident and emergency services.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9332","9332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417293","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the NHS has issued guidance on the safety of dieting schemes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9308","9308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417294","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cancer patients were initially diagnosed as not having cancer in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9309","9309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417295","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make the cardomems HF system to measure blood pressure available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9343","9343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417296","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to address the shortage of organ donors.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9344","9344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417297","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make available on the NHS lenosterol for the treatment of eye cataracts.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9345","9345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417298","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what help is available (a) nationally and (b) in Gloucestershire for soldiers suffering from post-traumatic stress disorders; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9141","9141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417299","2015-09-14","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the recent European Court of Justice ruling on the case brought against Iceland by the European Commission in respect of the Working Time Directive; and what discussions he has had with medical organisations on this matter.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9160","9160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417300","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9170","9170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417301","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the independent report entitled Qualitative Assessment of Visitor and Migrant use of the NHS in England: Observations from the Front-Line, which was commissioned by his Department and published on 22 October 2013, what steps he has taken in response to the concerns about the application process for European Health Insurance Cards raised in that report; and when he was first informed about such concerns.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9201","9201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417302","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England will continue to record and monitor weekly A&E performance following the decision to publish only monthly data.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9200","9200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417303","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many press officers are employed by the NHS.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9199","9199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417304","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of consultants who opt out of non-emergency work at weekends.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9196","9196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417305","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many press officers are employed by his Department.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9197","9197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417306","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many limb amputations were undertaken in the Plymouth area in each of the last five years; and how many such operations were as a result of (a) smoking and (b) diabetes.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9130","9130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417307","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will list what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for his Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9251","9251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417308","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of nurses earn 35,000 or more per year.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9227","9227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417309","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2015 to Question 3177, on the Cancer Drugs Fund, whether it is still his policy to continue to invest in the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9233","9233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417310","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the introduction of user charges in the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9091","9091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417311","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits and demerits of introducing user charges in the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9092","9092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417312","2015-09-09","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many scientists and engineers have been refused a Tier 2 (General) Certificate of Sponsorship since May 2015 due to the annual cap of 20,700; which Standard Occupational Classification codes have been affected by the cap; and how many applications have been refused for each such code.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9220","9220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417313","2015-09-09","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of officials that will be employed by the UK Border Agency in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9132","9132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417314","2015-09-09","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for her Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9252","9252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417315","2015-09-09","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9171","9171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417316","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officers are deployed in the Third Country Unit; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9115","9115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417317","2015-09-09","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officials are employed by the UK Border Agency; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9134","9134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417318","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review and clarify the law on joint enterprise.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9145","9145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417319","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have been removed to a third country under the terms of the Dublin Convention in each month of 2014 and 2015 to date; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9116","9116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417320","2015-09-09","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to stop the internet being used to attract Muslims to travel to Syria.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9306","9306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417321","2015-09-09","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in the French government on the provision of security at the Port of Calais.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9334","9334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417322","2015-09-09","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce the number of disability hate crimes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9340","9340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417323","2015-09-09","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of nurses from outside the European Economic area who will lose their Tier 2 visas because of the requirement that within six years of coming to the UK they must be earning 35,000 or more.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9263","9263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417324","2015-09-09","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to protect UK citizens from telephone scams from Nigeria.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9261","9261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417325","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employers have (a) applied for and (b) been refused UK Visa and Immigration sponsorship status in each of the last 10 six month periods.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9320","9320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417326","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people granted temporary asylum as children have been denied permanent asylum upon applying as an adult by country of origin in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9321","9321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417327","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people granted temporary asylum as children, having arrived in the UK under the age of 12, have been denied permanent asylum upon applying as an adult in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9322","9322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417328","2015-09-10","Department for International Development","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on changing the wording of Sustainable Development Goal 3.4 from premature mortality to preventable mortality in order to include people aged over 70 within the scope of the goal; and what discussions she has had with (a) interested parties and (b) her counterparts in other countries on this matter.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9144","9144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417329","2015-09-09","Department for International Development","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9172","9172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417330","2015-09-09","Department for International Development","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for her Department and its non-departmental public body in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9253","9253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417331","2015-09-09","Department for International Development","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much and what proportion of her Department's budget is spent in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9085","9085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417332","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the potential additional (a) travel expenses, (b) costs of non-attendance and (c) other costs to the public purse that would arise due to closure of magistrates courts in (i) Kettering and (ii) Corby.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9093","9093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417333","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 21 July 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Israr Hussain Malik.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9095","9095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417334","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations he has received on the recent reduction in the legal aid budget.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9101","9101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417335","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the cost per hour to the Public Defender Service of providing a legal representative in a police station; and what hourly rate is paid for such work under the Legal Aid system.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9103","9103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417336","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse is per case for defendants represented by (a) the Public Defender Service and (b) firms in private practice.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9102","9102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417337","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for his Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9254","9254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417338","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many women who were (a) dismissed, (b) made compulsorily redundant and (c) treated in a way that made them leave their job issued an employment tribunal claim in 2014-15; and what steps he is taking to reduce the incidence of such claims.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9219","9219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417339","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9173","9173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417340","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish for all courts in Greater Manchester travel time data comparable to that provided in his Department's consultation document for courts which have been proposed for closure.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9112","9112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417341","2015-09-10","Department for Education","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Government's work to increase awareness of children's human rights.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9117","9117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417342","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what costs were paid by HM Courts and Tribunals Service for (a) attendance, (b) travel, (c) loss of earnings, (d) childcare and (e) subsistence for all courts in Greater Manchester in each of the last three years; and what estimate he has made of the likely levels of such costs if his proposals for future courts provision are implemented.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9113","9113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417343","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the introduction of employment tribunal fees on access to justice for women subjected to pregnancy-related detriment or dismissal by an employer; and what steps he plans to take to improve access to justice for such women.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9118","9118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417344","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the (a) capital and (b) revenue costs of implementing his proposals for future provision of HM Courts and Tribunal services in the North West.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9110","9110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417345","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the operating costs were of each court in Greater Manchester by type of expenditure in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9111","9111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417346","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what contingency plans his Department has made for the possibility of all criminal defence firms withdrawing their bids for new legal aid contracts.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9104","9104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417347","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will review and reform legislation on the prosecution of teenagers engaging in consensual sexual relationships over social media and the internet.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9327","9327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417348","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will strengthen the penalties for disability hate crimes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9337","9337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417349","2015-09-09","Leader of the House","2015-09-07","To ask the Leader of the House, how much his Office spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9174","9174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417350","2015-09-09","Northern Ireland Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9175","9175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417351","2015-09-09","Northern Ireland Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps her Department is taking to assist in the transportation via Cork of donations of clothing and other materials from North Down to refugees stranded in Calais; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9181","9181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417352","2015-09-09","Northern Ireland Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the First and Deputy First Ministers of Northern Ireland on accepting refugees from UN camps in countries bordering Syria; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9182","9182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417353","2015-09-09","Northern Ireland Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when the Government papers containing reference to Kincora Boys Home, Belfast that were recently given to the Northern Ireland Historical Abuse Inquiry will be made available for public viewing.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9341","9341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417354","2015-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans her Department has to celebrate in Northern Ireland Her Majesty Queen Elizabeth II becoming the longest serving British monarch; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9289","9289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417355","2015-09-09","Northern Ireland Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate she has made of the number of Syrian refugees who will be accepted by Northern Ireland; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9264","9264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417356","2015-09-09","Northern Ireland Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will take steps to ensure additional funding is made available to the Northern Ireland Executive to assist the settlement of Syrian refugees in Northern Ireland over the lifetime of this Parliament; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9265","9265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417357","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Prime Minister's statement of 7 September 2015, how many of the at least six attempted terrorist attacks in the UK within the last 12 months were halted by drone strikes.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9288","9288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417358","2015-09-09","Department for International Development","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if the Government will provide additional aid assistance to EU member states receiving large numbers of refugees from Syria to help them with their humanitarian work.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9126","9126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417359","2015-09-09","Home Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to provide administrative assistance to EU member states receiving the highest numbers of Syrian refugees to help them to process asylum claims.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9109","9109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417360","2015-09-14","Prime Minister","2015-09-07","To ask the Prime Minister, what his policy is on reform of the House of Lords.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9202","9202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417361","2015-09-09","Prime Minister","2015-09-07","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will request information from Sir John Chilcott on (a) how many people have yet to respond to letters sent as part of the Maxwellisation process prior to the finalisation of the report of the Iraq Inquiry and (b) the names of each such person.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9089","9089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417362","2015-09-09","Scotland Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9176","9176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417363","2015-09-09","Department for Transport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9177","9177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417364","2015-09-15","Department for Transport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many civil servants in each region have been made redundant or left the service following closure of the regional DVLA offices.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9203","9203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417365","2015-09-09","Department for Transport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will list what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for his Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9255","9255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417366","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2015 to Question 3171, how many reported personal injury road accidents of each severity there were on the M56 between junctions 12 and 14 in 2014.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9120","9120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417367","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what Network Rail resources have been transferred since 25 June 2015 to the (a) Great Western electrification project and (b) North West electrification project from the (i) Midland Main Line electrification project and (ii) North Transpennine electrification project.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9142","9142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417368","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make the provision of turn-up-and-go facilities to be a requirement in the next award of franchises for (a) South Eastern railways and (b) South Western railways.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9143","9143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417369","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the validity of permitted deviations from the Railway Group Standards when the rolling stock to which those derogations were granted is subsequently repurposed.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9152","9152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417370","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he was informed by officials in his Department in March 2015 that Network Rail had advised his Department that decisions might be required in subsequent months regarding the deferral of certain projects.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9153","9153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417371","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2015 to Question 3926, for what reason the Ministerial transparency data series has not been updated in accordance with the timescale given in that Answer.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9148","9148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417372","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward proposals to introduce a default 20 mph speed limit in built-up areas.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9147","9147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417373","2015-09-09","Department for Transport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, to which publicly-funded bodies and organisations the Maritime and Coastguard Agency makes the shipping forecasts provided by the Met Office available.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9300","9300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417374","2015-09-09","Department for Transport","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will work with airlines to limit the amount of alcohol consumed on flights in and out of the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9335","9335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417375","2015-09-09","Wales Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the reasons are for the diversion of the Welsh Coast footpath inland around Plas Newydd on Anglesey; and whether the National Trust requested that diversion.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9194","9194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417376","2015-09-09","Wales Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will make an assessment of the extent to which the Welsh Coast footpath is (a) as close to the coast as is practical and (b) not unnecessarily diverted inland because of objections from landowners.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9195","9195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417377","2015-09-09","Wales Office","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9179","9179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417378","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of available research or evidence on the extent to which women experience discriminatory treatment at work in relation to (a) pregnancy, (b) maternity leave and (c) flexible working.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9217","9217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417379","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government plans to take to reduce the incidence of discriminatory treatment in relation to (a) pregnancy, (b) maternity leave and (c) flexible working.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9218","9218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417380","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on carbon offsetting in each of the last three years; and to which companies payments in respect of carbon offsetting were made in each such year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9180","9180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417381","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of housing benefit on the level of private-sector rents.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9149","9149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417382","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with (a) Covance and (b) other advertisers of clinical trials through Jobcentre Plus on the safeguarding and informed decisions aspects of such trials; and whether representatives of social services have been present.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9139","9139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417383","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will provide assistance to women who have depended on their husband's national insurance pensions contributions and will consequently suffer financial loss as a result of the increase in their retirement age; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9154","9154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417384","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the supply of one-bedroom properties for people affected by the under-occupancy penalty (a) on the Isle of Wight and (b) nationwide.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Turner","Mr Andrew Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9150","9150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417385","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason his Department invented quotes by non-existent jobseekers in its recent leaflet on benefit sanctions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9151","9151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417386","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will commission an assessment of the effect of changes to welfare benefits on the mental health of claimants.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9087","9087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417387","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who are eligible for jobseeker's allowance but who choose not to claim it.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9299","9299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417388","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what policy evaluations have been carried out by external organisations for his Department and its agencies in each financial year since 2010-11; whether the output of those evaluations was published; which organisation carried out each such evaluation; and what the value of each contract to provide that evaluation was.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9257","9257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418021","2015-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the animal carcass rendering industry on transportation of carcasses to rendering sites.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901269","901269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418158","2015-09-10","Church Commissioners","2015-09-07","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to support communities to the demand for Church-run food banks.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901263","901263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418159","2015-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support farmers in Cheshire.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901275","901275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416145","2015-09-08","Department for International Development","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress has been made on obtaining debt relief for Nepal following the recent earthquake in that country.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8398","8398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416146","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he expects the agreement with the new contractor on enforcing criminal fines to take effect.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8399","8399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416147","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the successful bidder for the contract to enforce criminal fines will be under any obligation to (a) keep employing the (i) existing staff in Birmingham and (ii) 1600 staff in the UK and (b) maintain current staff numbers, wages and working conditions.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8400","8400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416148","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many babies born in NHS hospitals have been born to mothers of non-UK citizenship in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8397","8397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416150","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether (a) the Secretary of State for Education and (b) the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State for Education have raised concerns about Kids Company with Ministers in his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8391","8391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416151","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what payments were made by the Government to Kids Company in each year since 2010; and what conditions were attached to such payments.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8392","8392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416152","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much of the grants awarded to Kids Company in 2015 he expects to recover.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8393","8393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416153","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions Ministers in his Department had with (a) the Prime Minister and (b) the Prime Minister's Special Advisers before deciding to overrule his Department's Permanent Secretary's advice not to proceed with funding for Kids Company.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8394","8394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416154","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to set conditions for the financing of (a) NHS trusts and (b) NHS Foundations Trusts to ensure that these bodies implement the NHS patient, visitor and staff car parking principles.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8396","8396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416155","2015-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to promote sustainable home design using sustainable materials.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8390","8390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416156","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what action his Department will take against paediatric audiology services which are not accredited under the Improving Quality in Physiological Services programme.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8388","8388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416157","2015-09-08","Department for Education","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate Ofsted has made of the cost of requiring inspectors of specialist provision for deaf children to be teachers of the deaf.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8389","8389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416158","2015-09-15","Home Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many reported burglaries there were in each Preston City Council ward in each of the first six months of 2015; and how many of those reported burglaries did the police attend to investigate.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8379","8379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416159","2015-09-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to amend the Harbours, Docks and Piers Clauses Act 1847 to allow individual ports in the UK to refuse to export live farm animals.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8382","8382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416160","2015-09-15","Home Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many burglaries were reported in each ward in Preston City Council in each of the first six months of 2015; and how many of those burglaries were attended by a member of Lancashire Constabulary to investigate.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8380","8380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416161","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much under each cost heading has been spent setting up Preston Learning Academy to date; how many people have received training at that Academy; and in which HM Revenue and Customs departments such people were working at the time of training.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8383","8383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416162","2015-09-11","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the transparency data for Ministerial expenses for his Department will be updated on the gov.uk website to show Ministerial expenses after 30 September 2013.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8384","8384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416163","2015-09-10","Church Commissioners","2015-09-04","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, how many Church of England churches in the (a) Diocese of Blackburn, (b) Diocese of Manchester, (c) Diocese of Liverpool and (d) Diocese of Carlisle were sold in 2014; how many such churches were sold to (i) other named protestant churches, (ii) named orthodox churches, (iii) other named Christian organisations, (iv) named non-Christian organisations, (v) be used for housing and (vi) other named community uses.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8386","8386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416164","2015-09-10","Church Commissioners","2015-09-04","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, which Church of England churches in the Diocese of Blackburn have been subject to metal theft from roofs in each year since 2012; and which such churches were redundant churches.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8387","8387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416165","2015-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what arrangements are in place at jobcentres to assist unemployed people formerly in senior management or executive positions in finding equivalent roles.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8385","8385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416166","2015-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the Government monitors feedback on the Armed Forces Community Covenant; and what steps he is taking to strengthen this covenant.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8395","8395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416167","2015-09-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what further steps his Department is taking to commemorate the First World War centenary leading up to 2018.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8381","8381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416168","2015-09-17","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to help local theatres over the next five years.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8378","8378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416169","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Azerbaijan; and what representations his Department has made to the government of that country on behalf of Leyla and Arif Yunus.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8410","8410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416170","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many European Health Insurance cards were issued to (a) Swiss nationals and (b) nationals of other EU-countries in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8414","8414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416171","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the reasons were for the redaction of material in Baroness Browning's letter of January 2015 to Alex Salmond on business appointments; and if he will publish the letter in full with the redacted material included.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8435","8435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416172","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he was first made aware of potential fraud involving foreign nationals using European Health Insurance cards; how much this fraud has cost the UK in each year since 2010; and what steps he is taking to eliminate such fraud.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8451","8451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416173","2015-09-08","Home Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much the UK spent on tackling opium production in Afghanistan in each year since 2005; and what the cultivation area of opium in that country was in each such year.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8452","8452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416174","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues on allowing full public access to the Royal Archives.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8464","8464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416175","2015-09-08","Home Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress she has made on reducing Class A drug use among young people.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8500","8500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416176","2015-09-08","Department for Education","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the speech given by the Prime Minister on 20 July 2015, on extremism, what her policy is on extending the 50 per cent cap on faith-based allocation of school places to all faith schools.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8505","8505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416177","2015-09-08","HM Treasury","2015-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2015 to Question 6495, how much he forecasts will be collected from the bank levy in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8526","8526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416178","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to Box 3, page 81, of her Department's Annual Report and Account 2014-15, what assessment she has made of the implications for her Department's policies of the increase in the estimated costs of nuclear decommissioning.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8545","8545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416179","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the risks posed by unmanned drones to prison security; and what steps he is taking to protect against drones dropping contraband material into prisons.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8567","8567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416180","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much each year is added to average consumer energy bills in the UK by solar power subsidies.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8579","8579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416181","2015-09-08","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what support he has made available to assist sports stadiums on improving their disabled accessibility.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8582","8582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416182","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of annual savings to the public purse of reducing the number of hon. Members from 650 to 600.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8595","8595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416183","2015-09-08","Prime Minister","2015-09-04","To ask the Prime Minister, what the average annual cost to the public purse is of a Member of the House of Lords; and how many peerages he estimates will be created over the next 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8596","8596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416184","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to her Department's press release, Controlling the cost of renewable energy, published on 22 July 2015, what assessment she has made of the potential effects of the proposed changes to solar power subsidies on the Government's ability to meet its climate change targets.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8603","8603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416185","2015-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of the National Living Wage on (a) local authority budgets and (b) home care services delivered by local authorities through private sector contracts.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8620","8620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416186","2015-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress his Department has made on the eight great technologies programme.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8621","8621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416187","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of farmers that have declared themselves bankrupt in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8641","8641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416188","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what change there has been in the level of farm subsidies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8642","8642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416189","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been spent on farm subsidies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8643","8643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416190","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will initiate a public inquiry into the collapse of Kids Company.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8644","8644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416191","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total cost to the NHS of temporary staff has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8645","8645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416192","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has held with (a) her ministerial colleagues and (b) her foreign counterparts on the culling of stray dogs in (i) Romania and (ii) India.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8651","8651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416193","2015-09-08","HM Treasury","2015-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he made of the market before setting out the timetable for the recent sale of Government shares in Royal Bank of Scotland; and what assessment he has made of the value for money to the public purse of that sale.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8668","8668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416194","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what criteria a charitable organisation must meet in order to be deemed viable in the long-term and eligible to receive Government funding.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8671","8671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416195","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish details of his Department's investigations into Kids Company which led to the formulation of Government's view on that charity's long-term viability.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8672","8672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416196","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Clinical Commissioning Groups incentive schemes.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8673","8673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416197","2015-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will review his policy on employers withholding gratuity payments under a tronc.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8675","8675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416198","2015-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to automatically increase on an annual basis the earnings limit for carer's allowance in line with annual increases in the national living wage.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8680","8680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416199","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on reducing the cost to the NHS of temporary staffing.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8681","8681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416200","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reasons are for the time taken in the procurement of NHS 111 and out-of-hours call handling services.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8682","8682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416201","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for the completion of the tendering and procurement process for NHS 111 and out-of-hours call handling services.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8683","8683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416202","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what implications the report of the unannounced visits by HM Chief Inspector of Prisons to HMP Wandsworth will have for his policies on (a) making prisons safer, (b) protecting minority groups in prisons, (c) addressing staff shortages in prisons and (d) providing educational and vocational opportunities in prison.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8689","8689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416203","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 8 June 2015 to Question 835, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Bangladesh about religious freedom in that country; and what support the UK is offering to the authorities in that country to protect secular campaigners from religious violence.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8692","8692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416204","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the recommendation of the King's Fund in its report published in July 2015, Making change possible, that a dedicated transformation fund for the NHS be established.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8693","8693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416205","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to implement the recommendations of the Interim Report of the Review of Operational Productivity in NHS Providers, published in June 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8694","8694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416206","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his permission was (a) sought and (b) granted for Sir Martin Narey's access to Rainsbrook Secure Training Centre.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8757","8757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416207","2015-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with Sir Martin Narey on (a) his access to Rainsbrook Secure Training Centre and (b) his subsequent report.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8758","8758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416208","2015-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will review the working of section 14 of the Animal Welfare Act 2006 and publish a new Code of Conduct relating to rabbits to bring the living space and welfare requirements for rabbits more in line with those in effect in other EU countries.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8721","8721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416209","2015-09-09","Home Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total cost to the public purse (a) was of the Gwent Police Authority in the financial year 2010-11 and (b) has been of the Gwent Police and Crime Commissioner in each year since 2012; and what assessment she has made of the value for money of the Police and Crime Commissioner in Gwent.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8785","8785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416210","2015-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will replace the earnings limit for Carer's Allowance with an earnings taper.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8807","8807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416211","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the prison population of the UK was in each year since 2010; and whether it is his policy to reduce the prison population over the course of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8815","8815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416212","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what account his Department took of the experience of attempting to exclude illegal drugs from prisons when formulating its ban on tobacco in prisons.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8816","8816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416213","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on prison and prisoner stability of banning tobacco in prisons.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8817","8817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416214","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the value of UK tea sales in the last financial year; what plans she has to return to China to promote British tea sales in that country; and if she will assess the value for money of previous such visits.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8805","8805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416215","2015-09-08","HM Treasury","2015-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many responses he has received to the letter sent by him to all public sector workers in August 2015 asking for ideas to reduce public sector expenditure to date.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8806","8806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416216","2015-09-08","Home Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what effect recent findings of the Crime Survey for England and Wales on ecstasy use among 16 to 24 years olds will have on her Department's drugs policy; and what steps she is taking to reduce ecstasy use among young people","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8916","8916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416217","2015-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in what ways the public can submit comments on the (a) National Security Strategy and (b) Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8857","8857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416218","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many instances of (a) suicide, (b) other death and (c) self-inflicted injuries there have been in Bullingdon Prison in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8508","8508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416219","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the prevalence rate of Hepatitis B was in (a) the London Borough of Ealing and (b) London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8577","8577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416220","2015-09-08","Cabinet Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Blaydon to his Department of 30 March 2015 regarding arranging a meeting between a Minister and representatives of the Shrewsbury 24 campaign.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9031","9031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416221","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will work with Amnesty International to make representations to the Indian government to prevent the punishment of the Kumari sisters.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9032","9032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416222","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, who was consulted by the person in his Department who took the decision to close Wallasey Jobcentre Plus before making that decision; and if he will make a statement on that decision.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9059","9059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416223","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much will be saved by the closure of the Wallasey Jobcentre Plus in Liscard; which other locations in the Wirral were considered for closure; what assessment his Department made of the economic effect on Liscard town centre of the closure; for what reason no consultation was undertaken prior to that decision; and what assessment he has made of the potential financial, time and other costs to (a) claimants and (b) staff of the planned closure.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8952","8952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416224","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what average time is taken to deal with appointments at (a) Birkenhead Jobcentre Plus and (b) Wallasey Jobcentre Plus; and how many claimants used services at the (i) Birkenhead and (ii) Wallasey location in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8953","8953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416225","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff who work at the Wallasey Jobcentre Plus in Liscard live within two miles of that office; and how many such staff will be (a) made redundant and (b) transferred as a result of the closure of that office.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8954","8954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416226","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, who within his Department took the decision to close the Wallasey Jobcentre Plus in Liscard; when that decision was taken; which criteria were employed in taking that decision; and when he will publish the business case for that decision.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8966","8966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416227","2015-09-08","HM Treasury","2015-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on continuing the existing ring-fence for investment in scientific research beyond 2015-16; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8853","8853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416228","2015-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much of the Government's 1.1 billion capital infrastructure fund for 2015-16 will be spent during 2015-16.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8854","8854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416229","2015-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much of the 1.1 billion capital infrastructure fund for 2015-16 has been (a) allocated for specific projects and (b) spent on delivering specific projects to date.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8855","8855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416230","2015-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether army apprenticeships at Level 2 require students to study towards Level 2 qualifications in English and mathematics.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8862","8862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416231","2015-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers who enlisted in the army aged (a) under 18 and (b) 18 years and above dropped out before completing Phase Two training in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8863","8863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416232","2015-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether army apprenticeships at Level 3 require students to have achieved Level 2 qualifications in (a) English and (b) mathematics in order to complete the Level 3 apprenticeship.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8797","8797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416233","2015-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2015 to Question 4788, why figures pertaining to the number of army and RAF visits to schools in the academic years from 2012 to 2015 are lower than figures for earlier years provided during the last Parliament by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8831","8831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416234","2015-09-08","HM Treasury","2015-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to reduce the time for which a parent or guardian can receive child benefit after a child has left their care.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8799","8799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416235","2015-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average time soldiers remained in the army after enlisting (a) under the age of 18 and (b) 18 or above was in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8796","8796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416236","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times the Israeli military have opened fire into Gaza since August 2014; and what steps his Department is taking to prevent future such incidents.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8503","8503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416237","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will estimate the number of Palestinian civilians killed by the Israeli military shooting into Gaza since August 2014; and what steps his Department is taking to prevent such fatalities.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8504","8504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416238","2015-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2015 to Question 4788, for what reasons figures pertaining to the number of RAF visits to schools is no longer collected in a disaggregated format for Scotland, Northern Ireland, Wales and England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8447","8447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416239","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received from (a) Israel, (b) Egypt, (c) the Palestinian Authority and (d) Hamas on the rebuilding of homes destroyed in Gaza during the conflict of January 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8530","8530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416240","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to implement UN Security Council Resolution 1860; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8532","8532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416241","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will estimate the number of Palestinian rockets fired into Israel from Gaza since August 2014; how many Israelis have been killed as a result of such attacks; and what steps his Department is taking to prevent such incidents.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8533","8533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416242","2015-09-08","Department for International Development","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will estimate the likely timetable for rebuilding infrastructure in Gaza following the July 2014 conflict.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8528","8528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416243","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the likely timetable for lifting the blockade of Gaza; and what steps he is taking with his counterparts in the EU and elsewhere to bring this about.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8529","8529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416244","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with counterparts in the EU and elsewhere on the obligations Israel has under UN Security Council Resolution 1860 and the Agreement on Movement and Access within it to open the Gaza crossings.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8531","8531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416245","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with counterparts in the EU and elsewhere on the number of incidents of the Israeli military shooting at fishing boats off Gaza and the number of fishermen so killed since August 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8454","8454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416246","2015-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many state school Combined Cadet Forces have been set up under the Cadet Expansion Programme in each year since 2012; and how many such forces are (a) new units and (b) partnerships with existing units.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8448","8448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416247","2015-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Local Education Authority areas are planned to host new Combined Cadet Force units; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8449","8449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416248","2015-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans for the one per cent reduction in social housing rents announced in the Summer Budget 2015 to apply to (a) supported accommodation claimed as specified accommodation under the Housing Benefit and Universal Credit (Supported Accommodation) (Amendment) Regulations 2014 and (b) other hostel accommodation for the single homeless.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9011","9011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416249","2015-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will conduct an assessment of the effect of online traders of second-hand cars on (a) the use of non-online second-hand car traders and (b) the second-hand car market.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9012","9012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416250","2015-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many car trading businesses have closed down in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9013","9013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416251","2015-09-08","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Budget Statement of 8 July 2015, Official Report, column 325,  what definition he plans to use of less affluent areas when prioritising expansion of cadet merits; and what estimate he has made of the number of (a) state and (b) independent schools in those areas.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9043","9043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416252","2015-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average response time for first appliance attendance by each UK fire and rescue service brigade was in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8502","8502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416253","2015-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the Darlington Filestores site has not been included in the re-tendering bid for the Document Management and Associated Services (document storage) contract; and what his Department plans to do with the files held at this facility.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8441","8441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416254","2015-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish his Department's (a) assessment of performance, (b) efficiency opportunities (c) savings market conditions, and (d) security risk management as a result of the most recent strategic management review with Capita on the Document Management and Associated Services (document storage) contract currently held by Capita Filestores in Darlington.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8442","8442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416255","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people aged 18 years old in each Young Offenders Institution have been transferred to adult prisons in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8686","8686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416256","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people aged 18 to 20 in each Young Offenders Institution have been transferred to adult prisons in each month since January 2010.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8687","8687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416257","2015-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what legal advice his Department has received on the tendering process for the Document Management and Associated Services (document storage) bid.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8849","8849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416258","2015-09-08","Department for Education","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what actions her Department is taking to promote a joined-up approach within and across Government departments to maintain and improve safeguarding for disabled children.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8808","8808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416259","2015-09-08","Department for Education","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department gathers on the safeguarding of children and the monitoring and review of safeguarding practice.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8574","8574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416260","2015-09-08","Department for Education","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) disabled and (b) non-disabled children were subject to (i) section 47 enquiries, (ii) child protection plans, (iii) care proceedings and (iv) serious case reviews in the last six months for which data is available.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8575","8575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416261","2015-09-08","Department for Education","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that Local Safeguarding Children Boards and local agencies are implementing the recommendations of the Ofsted 2012 thematic inspection on protecting disabled children.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8594","8594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416262","2015-09-08","Department for Education","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what data her Department routinely gathers about the safeguarding of disabled children from (a) inspection activity and (b) data returns; and how such information is analysed.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8602","8602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416263","2015-09-08","Department for Education","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to promote the safeguarding of disabled children.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9078","9078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416264","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the Gaza Reconstruction Mechanism allows the import of sufficient building materials.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9033","9033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416265","2015-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his Answer of 7 July 2015 to Question 4556, for what reason no financial assessment of the saving or cost to the Exchequer from the transfer of existing disability living allowance claimants to personal independence payments has been made.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8598","8598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416266","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July to Question 6166, whether all Clinical Commissioning Groups (CCGs) are to receive a funding increase in the next financial year; and whether the expectation in the National Health Service England planning document for 2015-16 that mental health spending will grow in real terms at least as fast as each CCG's overall allocation will be enforceable or a guideline.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8657","8657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416267","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure that wood or paper products from illegal or unsustainable timber sources are not being sold or used in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8658","8658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416268","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the ability and efficacy of alternative pest control methods to the use of neonicotinoids.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8652","8652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416269","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential change in the bee population of the decision to allow the use of neonicotinoid pesticides; and what assessment she has made of the effect of such a change on agricultural yields.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8653","8653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416270","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what basis the members of the stakeholder group for the study on cage-based breeding of game birds were chosen.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8428","8428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416271","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the two papers prepared for publication as part of the review into cage-based breeding systems have been submitted for review; and what the outcome of such a review was.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8427","8427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416272","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the cost was under each cost heading of the study to determine whether cage-based breeding can meet the needs of game birds.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8429","8429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416273","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to (a) back amendments to the EU Timber Regulation so that it covers all timber and wood products and (b) support at a European level proposals by the World Wild Fund for Nature to enable a market in 100 per cent sustainable timber by 2020.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8418","8418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416274","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the prevalence of medicated grit on grouse moors and its potential long-term effects.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8422","8422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416275","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons SAC Commercial Ltd were chosen to undertake the study on whether cage-based breeding can meet the needs of game birds.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8423","8423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416276","2015-09-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Indonesian counterpart on human rights violations, alleged killings carried out by the military and attempts to increase logging in West Papua.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8424","8424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416277","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what consultation was held with (a) animal welfare organisations, (b) farming organisations, (c) environmental groups and (d) shooting organisations as part of her Department's study into cage-based breeding of game birds.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8425","8425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416278","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reason her Department's study into cage-based breeding of game birds does not include a control group of birds living in a natural environment.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8426","8426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416279","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2015 to Question 1439, how the fund for advanced care in GP practices and community healthcare facilities will be (a) allocated and (b) used.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8846","8846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416280","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons his Department is not permitting Capita to provide dual-tape deck recorders for use by claimants of personal independence payments who want their assessment to be recorded.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8714","8714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416281","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when patient records will be made available to commercial pharmacies.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8722","8722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416282","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy not to introduce user charges or insurance-based funding or hold an inquiry into introducing such changes into the NHS during the course of this Parliament.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8723","8723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416283","2015-09-08","Department for International Development","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will respond to the Independent Commission for Aid Impact's Report on the Department for International Development's Contribution to Improving Nutrition published July 2014.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8670","8670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416284","2015-09-09","HM Treasury","2015-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July to Question 7590, what his timetable is for publishing updated guidance and advice on the implementation of changes to tax credit entitlement arising from the Summer Budget 2015; and if he will publish an online calculator incorporating those changes to tax credits.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8743","8743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416285","2015-09-08","HM Treasury","2015-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the recent effect on the public purse of the sale of public assets in the (a) Royal Bank of Scotland and (b) Royal Mail; and what steps he is taking to ensure the further sale of public assets does not result in a loss to the public purse.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8882","8882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416286","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to Objective 7 of the study to provide scientific evidence on cage-based breeding (a) whether and (b) how the best practice recommendations have been disseminated.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8883","8883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416287","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the diagnosis rate for dementia of people of each (a) age group and (b) gender in (i) Allerdale borough and (b) Copeland borough has been in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8755","8755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416288","2015-09-09","Department for Transport","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to prevent toxic fumes from aircraft engines entering the cabin and causing crew and passengers to fall ill.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8756","8756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416289","2015-09-09","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the rate of dementia among each (a) age group and (b) gender in (i) Allerdale borough and (ii) Copeland borough has been in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8771","8771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416290","2015-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to speed up the processing of benefit claims; what effect such measures are having on processing times in (a) the UK on (b) the smallest area that can be distinguished which includes Nottingham North constituency.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9028","9028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416291","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many clinical trials have been advertised to jobseekers through Jobcentre Plus as employment opportunities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9050","9050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416292","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on the advertising of clinical trials to jobseekers as employment opportunities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9051","9051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416293","2015-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the inclusion of the Postcode Address File in the sale of Royal Mail on (a) small businesses and (b) other users of formerly public postcode data.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9052","9052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416294","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for what reasons she is not implementing the recommendation of the Competition and Markets Authority that Ofgem should be the single provider of a switching and comparison website for energy.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8809","8809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416295","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has conducted research on one-stop-shop switching and comparison sites for energy in other advanced economies in order to inform its policies.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8810","8810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416296","2015-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the sale of the Government's majority stake in the Green Investment Bank on the level of investments made by that bank.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8811","8811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416297","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on strengthening the EU Emissions Trading Scheme.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8552","8552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416298","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she expects a fully functioning carbon market to be operational.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8553","8553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416299","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to make it easier for retail electricity consumers to negotiate distributed energy contracts with energy companies.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8554","8554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416300","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to ensure that the effect of existing green and social levies is more progressively distributed across the income scale.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8555","8555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416301","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make it her policy to require the provision to energy consumers of a breakdown of their energy consumption compared with similarly sized households or businesses.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8556","8556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416302","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the number of people in Greenwich and Woolwich constituency affected by fuel poverty in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8557","8557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416303","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the level of Government investment in renewable energy in Greenwich and Woolwich constituency since 2010.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8558","8558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416304","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will introduce an emissions performance standard applied to all UK power stations.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8559","8559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416305","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to ensure that all UK coal fire power stations will be offline by 2027.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8560","8560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416306","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to make the retail energy market more transparent and facilitate greater consumer choice.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8561","8561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416307","2015-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the increase of the minimum wage on small businesses which as a result of that increase will begin to operate above the VAT threshold.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8838","8838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416308","2015-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number of small businesses that will begin to operate over the VAT threshold as a result of complying with the new minimum wage.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8839","8839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416309","2015-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations have been made to his Department on the effect of the increase in the minimum wage on small businesses.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8840","8840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416310","2015-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the increase in the minimum wage on small businesses operating under the VAT threshold.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8886","8886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416311","2015-09-08","HM Treasury","2015-09-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of increasing the VAT threshold so that small businesses complying with the new national minimum wage can continue to operate below the VAT threshold.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8887","8887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416312","2015-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations have been made to his Department on the effect of the increase in minimum wage on small businesses.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8856","8856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416313","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what specialist training is given to employment and support allowance and personal independence payment assessors on handling claimants with mental health issues.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8742","8742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416314","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants have (a) participated in and (b) found work through Work Clubs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8750","8750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416315","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants have found work through a placement with a sector-based work academy in each year since such schemes have been available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8751","8751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416316","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance is issued by his Department on how long successful claimants of personal independence payment should wait before their first payment arrives once a decision has been made to award the claim.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8739","8739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416317","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new claims for (a) tax credits, (b) jobseeker's allowance, (c) employment and support allowance, (d) income support and (e) housing benefit have been made since April 2014.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8727","8727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416318","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many illegal immigrants have received free treatment in NHS hospitals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8407","8407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416319","2015-09-08","Department of Health","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much owed to the NHS by non-UK patients receiving treatment remains outstanding; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8408","8408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416320","2015-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people declaring themselves as a Company Director have applied for universal credit to date; whether their household income was considered before a decision was made on their application; and what proportion of such claims have been successful.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8417","8417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416321","2015-09-08","Department for Education","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, by what date she expects to confirm whether children of parents who claim universal credit while in employment will be entitled to free school meals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8636","8636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416322","2015-09-08","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in the cost of bringing a case to magistrates' courts on low income households' access to justice.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8674","8674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416323","2015-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many start-ups initiated by benefits claimants on the Work For Yourself programme were sustained beyond (a) six and (b) 12 months.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8624","8624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416324","2015-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many suspensions have been applied to jobseeker's allowance claims in each year since 2010; and how many such suspensions have resulted in the immediate withdrawal of benefit payments.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8618","8618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416325","2015-09-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the increase in affordable home starts between 2009-10 and 2013-14 was attributable to changing the definition of affordable from 70 to 80 per cent of local private rents.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9037","9037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416326","2015-09-09","Department for Transport","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers (a) local authorities and (b) the police have to enforce proper use of designated disabled parking spaces on public highways.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8762","8762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416327","2015-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his Department's policy to fund Standard disclosure and barring checks (DBS) for jobseekers' allowance claimants who have received a job offer conditional on obtaining a DBS certificate.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8763","8763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416328","2015-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria his Department applies to identify those people in receipt of Access to Work support.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8463","8463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416329","2015-09-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria his Department has set for claimants of Access to Work support to qualify for the maximum level of support.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8461","8461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/416330","2015-09-08","Department for International Development","2015-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make it her policy to make aid to Pakistan contingent on that country making progress on protecting religious and social minorities.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8462","8462"
