"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421446","2015-10-19","Department for International Development","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether it is an objective of the Health System Strengthening Framework to support partner governments to increase domestic funding for health services.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11951","11951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421447","2015-10-19","Department for International Development","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she plans to publish the new Health System Strengthening Framework.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11950","11950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421448","2015-10-19","Department for International Development","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what groups of people will be prioritised by the new Health System Strengthening Framework.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11953","11953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421449","2015-10-19","Department for International Development","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how the Health System Strengthening Framework will address the links between different health issues.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11952","11952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421450","2015-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the review which led the Government to decide not to proceed with a prisons training contract with Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11956","11956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421451","2015-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on external legal advice not from Queen's Counsel since 7 May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11957","11957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421452","2015-10-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps Community Rehabilitation Companies are taking to engage with local charities to prevent prisoners from reoffending.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11973","11973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421453","2015-10-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress his Department is making in arranging for the release of prisoners sentenced to imprisonment for public protection.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11905","11905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421454","2015-10-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on the Criminal Court Charge.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11877","11877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421455","2015-10-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has had on recruitment processes for vacancies in the College of Arms.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11803","11803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421456","2015-10-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make representations to Staffordshire and West Midlands Rehabilitation Company on ensuring jobs are not lost by the planned transfer of responsibilities for probation service administration staff to Derby.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11814","11814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421457","2015-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will issue a new impact assessment examining the economic and value for money consequences of Just Solutions international.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11806","11806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421458","2015-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to ensure that staff employed by HM Courts and Tribunals Service in the collection of court fines will have their employment transferred to the new provider of this service.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11795","11795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421459","2015-10-19","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to announce the outcome of the tendering process for the privatisation of the HM Courts and Tribunals Service fines collection service.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11796","11796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421460","2015-10-19","Northern Ireland Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether she has had discussions with Volkswagen and Renault car manufacturers regarding the recall of cars in Northern Ireland aged one to five years for refitting new computer and brake systems; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11933","11933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421461","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information she holds on surveillance of hon. Members' communications; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11966","11966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421462","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Wilson Doctrine has been consistently applied to the communications of the hon. Member for Brighton, Pavilion; and whether she has been subject to surveillance.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11965","11965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421463","2015-10-19","Cabinet Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Prime Minister's speech in Singapore of 28 July 2015, when he plans to initiate the consultation into making property ownership by foreign companies more transparent; what format he plans for that consultation to take; who he plans to invite to participate in that consultation; and when he plans for it to be concluded.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12011","12011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421464","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will increase the requirements placed on Network Rail to consult local communities on infrastructure planning.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11967","11967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421465","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for (a) Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs and (b) Defence on supporting international efforts to protect UK ships against pirates.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11798","11798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421466","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support her Department has given to recycling initiatives of spoil wastes from harbour dredging.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11799","11799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421467","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has had with the International Maritime Organisation on (a) disposal and (b) recycling of spoil waste from the dredging of harbours.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11800","11800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421468","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total cost was of London International Shipping Week (LISW) 2013; how much of that cost was borne by his Department; and what those costs were for LISW 2015.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11836","11836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421469","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many officials from the Maritime and Coastguard Agency (a) spoke at and (b) attended scheduled events during London International Shipping Week 2015.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11837","11837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421470","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many officials in his Department worked at events scheduled as part of London International Shipping Week 2015.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11838","11838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421471","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many officials in his Department were involved in preparatory work for London International Shipping Week 2015.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11839","11839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421472","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, by what criteria he judged the success of London International Shipping Week (LISW) 2013; and what criteria he used to judge the success of LISW 2015.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11840","11840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421473","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times officials from the Maritime and Coastguard Agency have visited overseas counterparts to discuss maritime policies since May 2010; and what the destinations were in each such case.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11841","11841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421474","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the objection in the Euston Area Plan on prioritising local people's needs adopted by the London Borough of Camden, the Mayor of London and Transport for London in January 2015 is not referred to in the Supplementary Environmental Statement for High Speed 2.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11843","11843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421475","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make provision for additional compensation schemes for people in (a) the London Borough of Camden and (b) other parts of London, supplementary to the existing High Speed 2 compensation scheme and similar to the additional support provided to people in rural areas affected by that project.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11844","11844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421476","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the proposed Crossrail 2 project; and what assessment he has made of the relationship between that project and the successful completion of work on High Speed 2 at Euston Station.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11845","11845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421477","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have visited overseas counterparts to discuss maritime policies since May 2010; and what the destinations were in each such case.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11842","11842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421478","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the provision of bike racks on buses on the number of people using public transport.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11881","11881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421479","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of extending the use of trams to increase low-carbon travel.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11875","11875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421480","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what geological assessment his Department has made to ensure the stability of (a) the sea wall at Dawlish, (b) the cliff at Teignmouth and (c) the line between Newton Abbott and Plymouth.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11904","11904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421481","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of free specialist legal advice available to new and expectant mothers who have been subjected to pregnancy, maternity or sex discrimination at work.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11914","11914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421482","2015-10-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2015 to Question 8870, whether the new life chances measures will monitor households where an adult is in work; and what steps he plans to take to measure the effects of welfare changes on child poverty for children in working households with low incomes.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11922","11922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421483","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support is available to people earning less than £110 per week net who are the principal carers for elderly relatives with a disability.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12001","12001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421484","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what effect the introduction of Universal Credit will have on funding for care available to older people with a disability whose principal carer is engaged in education for more than 21 hours per week.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12002","12002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421485","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support is available to people earning at least £111 per week net who are the principal carers for elderly relatives with a disability.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12003","12003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421486","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support to meet caring needs is available for older people with a disability whose principal carer has net earnings of at least £111 per week.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12004","12004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421487","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support is available to people spending more than 21 hours per week in education who are the principal carers for elderly relatives with a disability.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12005","12005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421488","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support to meet caring needs is available for older people with a disability whose principal carer is engaged in education for more than 21 hours per week.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12006","12006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421489","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support to meet caring needs is available for older people with a disability whose principal carer is engaged in education for less than 21 hours per week.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12007","12007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421490","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support to meet caring needs is available for older people with a disability whose principal carer has net earnings of less than £110 per week.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12008","12008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421491","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support is available for people spending up to 20 hours per week in education who are the principal carers for elderly relatives with a disability.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 12009","12009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421492","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2015 to Question 228756, when his Department plans to publish statistics on the performance of the Help to Work scheme.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11971","11971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421493","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were affected by the benefit cap between May 2015 and August 2015 normally carried out paid work between one hour and 16 hours per week during this period.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11853","11853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421494","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have been affected by the benefit cap at any point since September 2013, and are no longer affected, started a claim for working tax credit after becoming self-employed.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11854","11854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421495","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have been affected by the benefit cap at any point since September 2013, and are no longer affected, are in receipt of (a) disability living allowance, (b) personal independence payment and (c) the support component of employment support allowance.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11855","11855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421496","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were affected by the benefit cap in August 2015 have been affected by the benefit cap at any point since September 2013.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11856","11856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421497","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total number of hours worked by participants in (a) help to work and (b) mandatory work activity was in the most recent year for which figures are available; and what the average number of hours worked was by each such participant.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11851","11851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421498","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much time in total participants spent on (a) work choice, (b) help to work and (c) mandatory work activity in each year since the start of those programmes.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11852","11852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421499","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he plans to take to improve employment support for homeless people.","Biography information for Ben Howlett","Ben Howlett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11878","11878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421500","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people claiming (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) employment and support allowance and (c) income support who were sanctioned in the last 12 months moved into work within one month of being sanctioned.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11860","11860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421501","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people claiming income support (a) are pregnant and (b) gave birth within the last 15 weeks.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11861","11861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421502","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people claiming income support work between one and 16 hours per week.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11862","11862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421503","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to publish statistics on the number of sanctions made in relation to jobseekers claiming universal credit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11863","11863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421504","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people affected by the benefit cap are participants in the work programme.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11846","11846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421505","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were affected by the benefit cap in August 2015 were also affected by the benefit cap in September 2013.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11857","11857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421506","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many branches of Jobcentre Plus employed at least one full-time equivalent (a) disability employment adviser and (b) income support adviser in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11858","11858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421507","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many income support advisers were employed by Jobcentre Plus in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11859","11859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421508","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which employers who have provided work placements for participants in (a) help to work and (b) mandatory work activity since the start of programme in question.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11850","11850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421509","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of participants in (a) the work programme, (b) work choice and (c) help to work who started work during the course of their time on the programme in question were employed in the same job six months after their allotted time on the programme.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11849","11849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421510","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of participants in (a) the work programme, (b) work choice, (c) help to work and (d) mandatory work activity who started work while participating in those programmes became self-employed.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11847","11847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421511","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of participants in (a) the work programme, (b) work choice, (c) help to work and (d) mandatory work activity who started work during the course of their time on the programme in question claimed in-work benefits while in employment.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11848","11848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422391","2015-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking with foreign governments to counter ISIL propaganda online.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901665","901665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422392","2015-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on human rights violations in Jammu and Kashmir.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901664","901664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422393","2015-10-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help British citizens and the families of British citizens imprisoned abroad for minor offences.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901670","901670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420922","2015-10-15","Attorney General","2015-10-13","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with his Cabinet colleagues on the implementation of the UK's domestic and international legal obligations on human rights.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11542","11542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420923","2015-10-16","Attorney General","2015-10-13","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Oral Statement by the Prime Minister on 7 September 2015, Official Report, column 26, on what dates he was consulted on the legal basis for drone strikes in Syria.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11558","11558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420924","2015-10-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions there were in (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15 under Section 49 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 where the victims were (A) under 16 years old and (B) between 16 and 19 years old.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11743","11743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420925","2015-10-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions there were in (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14 and (iii) 2014-15 under Section 48 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 where the victims were (A) under 16 years old and (B) between 16 and 19 years old.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11744","11744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420926","2015-10-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions under Section 47 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 were made in (i) 2012 to 2013, (ii) 2013 to 2014 and (iii) to 2015 where the victim was (A) under 16 years old and (b) between 16 and 17 years old.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11750","11750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420927","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to better identify pyramid schemes involving UK nationals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11737","11737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420928","2015-10-15","Cabinet Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment the Government has made of the rates of productivity of young employed people in the UK.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11769","11769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420929","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the budget is for the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate in 2015-16.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11789","11789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420930","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with Volkswagen and Renault on the recall of cars in Northern Ireland aged one to five years for refitting new computer and brake systems; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11752","11752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420931","2015-10-15","Cabinet Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are employed in (a) the UK and (b) each region by companies (i) with headquarters in the EU and (ii) owned in the EU.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11563","11563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420932","2015-10-15","Cabinet Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are employed by non-British EU companies in (a) the UK and (b) each region.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11564","11564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420933","2015-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on students living or studying in areas where household income is below the national average of the announcement by the Chancellor of the Exchequer on 8 July 2015 that maintenance grants will be discontinued from 2016-17.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11570","11570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420934","2015-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of expenditure on UK Trade and Investment on the level of foreign direct investment in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Kilmarnock and Loudoun constituency between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11549","11549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420935","2015-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the schedule of comparable programme objects in HM Treasury's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, what projects were funded by the Research Establishments Major Capital funding; what the (a) projected and (b) actual cost was of each of those projects; and whether each of those projects has been completed.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11507","11507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420936","2015-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the schedule of comparable programme objects in HM Treasury's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, what the total expenditure was on UK Trade and Investment between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11508","11508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420937","2015-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the schedule of comparable programme objects in HM Treasury's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, what the total expenditure was on UKAEA-Decommissioning between 2010 and 2015; and what the forecast expenditure in which locations is on such decommissioning in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11509","11509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420938","2015-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of reduction in funding to English for Speakers of Other Languages Mandation Courses on the level of employment among people for whom English is an additional language.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11576","11576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420939","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a scheme for naming and shaming employers who fail to pay an employment tribunal award.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11618","11618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420940","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many financial penalties have been imposed on respondent employers under section 16 of the Enterprise and Regulatory Reform Act 2013 to date; and how many such penalties (a) have been paid and (b) remain unpaid.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11619","11619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420941","2015-10-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many days were taken to process and grant each application for readmission of employment tribunal fees that have been (a) granted and (b) partially granted since the introduction of those fees.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11620","11620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420942","2015-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect on productivity of increasing the minimum wage.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11770","11770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420943","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has been made of the effectiveness of the Government's credit union expansion programme; and what assessment he has made of the feasibility of extending that programme.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11604","11604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420944","2015-10-15","Cabinet Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much under each cost heading was spent on the House of Lords Appointments Commission between 2010 and 2015; and how many times that Commission met during that period.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11506","11506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420945","2015-10-16","Cabinet Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Department has responsibility for (a) data protection, (b) data sharing and (c) the Information Commissioner's Office.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11785","11785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420946","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to promote Pension Wise.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11777","11777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420947","2015-10-16","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to better regulate financial service providers working in the UK (a) in general and (b) specifically those selling off-shore services and investment opportunities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11736","11736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420948","2015-10-16","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Help to Buy mortgages have been refused by the Government despite being accepted by the participating bank.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11741","11741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420949","2015-10-16","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Help to Buy mortgages have been declined on the basis of a poor credit rating.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11739","11739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420950","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the (a) efficiency of the Valuation Office Agency (VOA) and (b) potential merits of providing emergency payments to councils who face budgeting difficulties due to the time taken by the VOA to re-assess business rates.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11512","11512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420951","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to principle 7 in paragraph 3.2 of his Department's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, which areas of self-financed expenditure of the Scottish Parliament are included in that principle.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11496","11496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420952","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.25 of his Department's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, when he expects the statement of funding policy to be next updated.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11497","11497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420953","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to principle 7 in paragraph 3.2 of his Department's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, whether he plans to include that principle in an updated statement of funding policy.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11498","11498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420954","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the schedule of comparable programme objects in his Department's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, what the total cost was of royal travel between May 2010 and May 2015.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11499","11499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420955","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the schedule of comparable programme objects in his Department's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, what projects were funded by the PFI Special Grant; and what the total capital cost was of each of those projects.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11500","11500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420956","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the schedule of comparable programme objects in his Department's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, what projects were funded by the revenue support grants; and what the total capital cost was of each of those projects.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11501","11501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420957","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to expenditure on (a) HMRC: Administration, (b) HMRC: Tax and rate collection, (c) HMRC: Valuation Office, and (d) HMRC: Treasury in the schedule of comparable programme objects in his Department's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, (i) how much of that expenditure in which locations was on (A) property and (B) personnel and (ii) how many people in which locations were employed through such expenditure between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11502","11502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420958","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect on local councils of the revaluation of business rates levied on GP surgeries.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11540","11540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420959","2015-10-16","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people under 25 years old in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK receive tax credits.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11553","11553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420960","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the work required to collect the revenue paid into the EU budget in each year since 1985.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11543","11543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420961","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the work required to collect the revenue paid into the EU budget each year.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11544","11544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420962","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on foreign direct investment of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11562","11562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420963","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on the future of the private sector home care industry of the implementation of the national living wage.","Biography information for Dr James Davies","Dr James Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11609","11609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420964","2015-10-16","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Minister for Finance in the Republic of Ireland; and what subjects were raised at those discussions.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11621","11621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420965","2015-10-16","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with the Ministers for Finance and Foreign Affairs in the Republic of Ireland; and what subjects were raised at those discussions.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11622","11622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420966","2015-10-16","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding the UK has been allocated from the (a) European Regional Development Fund, (b) European Social Funds, (c) European Agricultural Fund of Guarantee, (d) European Agricultural Fund for Rural Development, (e) European Territorial Cooperation, (f) Youth Employment Initiative and (g) European Maritime and Fisheries Fund for the period from 2014 to 2020; and what information his Department holds on how much funding has been allocated from each fund in each region.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11588","11588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420967","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding the UK was allocated from the (a) European Regional Development Fund, (b) European Social Funds, (c) European Agricultural Fund of Guarantee, (d) European Agricultural Fund for Rural Development, (e) European Territorial Cooperation, (f) Youth Employment Initiative and (g) European Maritime and Fisheries Fund in the period from 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11589","11589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420968","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the benefits to UK businesses in the (a) retail, (b) automobile, (c) construction, (d) ICT, (e) financial services and (f) defence sectors of reduced tariff barriers arising from UK membership of the World Trade Organisation.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11590","11590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420969","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the benefit to the UK economy of the preferential trade agreements the EU has negotiated with countries outside the EU.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11591","11591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420970","2015-10-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the benefits to the UK economy of (a) the absence of tariff barriers for intra-EU trade and (b)  other aspects of the single market.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11592","11592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420971","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to provide tax incentives for businesses seeking to enter the automotive and motor racing industries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11657","11657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420972","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the Financial Conduct Authority acts to prevent companies from fraudulently using capital raised from selling ring-fenced bonds to bail out poorly-performing parent companies.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11660","11660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420973","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the level of problem debt in the UK.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11776","11776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420974","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the most recent Global Financial Stability Report from the IMF.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11779","11779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420975","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the reasons are for the timing of his Department's sale of the remaining £2 billion of Lloyds' shares.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11718","11718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420976","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to improve Britain's economic ties with China.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11693","11693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420977","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities in phase two of the Troubled Families programme have made tackling (a) child sexual exploitation and (b) sexual abuse an outcome in their Troubled Families Outcome Plan.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11682","11682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420978","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with Derby City Council on the re-development of brownfield sites in the city with support from the grant announced on 28 January 2015 to help develop such sites following the announcement of a £4.4 million fund to help unlock potential sites.","Biography information for Amanda Solloway","Amanda Solloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11629","11629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420979","2015-10-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households occupy social housing in each London borough; and how many such households in each such borough have an annual income above £40,000.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11723","11723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420980","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of households in Worcester eligible to purchase their homes under (a) the right to buy, (b) the retained right to buy, (c) the right to purchase and (d) the new voluntary right to buy agreement with registered social landlords.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11667","11667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420981","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) Worcester and (b) Worcestershire have taken up a Help to Buy ISA.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11668","11668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420982","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to promote tenant management.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11634","11634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420983","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department differentiates between private sector landlords and housing associations in the manner in which it makes direct payments to landlords on behalf of tenants who receive universal credit.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11600","11600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420984","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will commission an independent inquiry into the practice of classifying people as intentionally homeless.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11579","11579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420985","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department provides to (a) the public and (b) councils on the definition and application of the classification of intentional homelessness.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11545","11545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420986","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to provide financial assistance to local authorities to deal with unforecastable shortfalls arising from the revaluation of business rates levied on GP surgeries.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11538","11538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420987","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take to help local councils with pooled funding tackle unpredicted revenue shortfalls due to the revaluation of the business rates levied on GP surgeries.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11539","11539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420988","2015-10-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to reduce barriers preventing tenants in shared ownership properties from staircasing up to increase the share of the property they own; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11756","11756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420989","2015-10-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to assist local authorities to safeguard the residential amenity of urban residential locales with high numbers of private sector lettings; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11749","11749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420990","2015-10-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2015 to Question 10535, what steps he is taking specifically to encourage the deployment of fibre to the premises in new build housing developments.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11787","11787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420991","2015-10-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold discussions with the FA about the affordability of tickets to Premier League matches for people on the national average wage.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11532","11532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420992","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse was of television licences for people over the age of 75 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11548","11548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420993","2015-10-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that payment of royalties is made by platform providers to broadcasters as well as to the rights-holders of programmes.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11547","11547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420994","2015-10-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) Connecting Cheshire and (b) other local authority partnerships provide timely and accurate advice to homes and businesses about when work will take place to connect them to superfast broadband.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11572","11572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420995","2015-10-16","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to promote competition in the telecommunications market.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11722","11722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420996","2015-10-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to promote the legacy of the 2015 Rugby World Cup.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11690","11690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420997","2015-10-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to increase participation in motor sport for young people from families with lower incomes.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11695","11695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420998","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what key policy aims he achieved during the recent visit to the UK by the US Secretary of Defense.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11714","11714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420999","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether UK Tornadoes flying missions over Iraq are armed with heat-seeking air-to-air missile systems.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11652","11652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421000","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information the British Defence Attaché to Russia has provided to the Russian government on measures taken to ensure accidental engagement with Russian military aircraft flying in Iraqi airspace does not lead to engagement in military confrontation.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11653","11653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421001","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will review the Army's rules of engagement in response to the court martial of Sergeant Blackman.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11683","11683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421002","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many regular soldiers he plans to maintain in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11699","11699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421003","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his (a) Russian and (b) US counterparts on the extension of British airstrikes to Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11701","11701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421004","2015-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans for Protector programme unmanned aerial vehicles, and each individual aircraft commissioned under that programme, to enter into service.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11595","11595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421005","2015-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Protector aircraft his Department plans to order.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11593","11593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421006","2015-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much he plans for the Protector programme to cost his Department in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11594","11594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421007","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the decision to order the Protector programme of aircraft was taken by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11603","11603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421008","2015-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of UK manufacturing jobs likely to be (a) created and (b) safeguarded by the commencement of the Protector programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11610","11610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421009","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of armed forces personnel originate from Commonwealth nations; and whether his Department plans to increase such numbers in future.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11661","11661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421010","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) nature and (b) purpose is of the deployment of UK armed forces to Somalia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11707","11707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421011","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with armed forces charities on the payment of lump sum compensation payments to veterans with mesothelioma; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11625","11625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421012","2015-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the value of the domestic supply chain for the Protector programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11596","11596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421013","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations he has received from his Russian counterpart on the deployment of UK troops to the Baltic states.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11665","11665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421014","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what future plans his Department has to co-ordinate with the armed forces of the Russian Federation in tackling ISIS.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11705","11705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421015","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons his Department applied a 1,500-character limit for individual submissions to his Department's consultation on the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11585","11585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421016","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many submissions his Department has received to date from (a) hon. Members, (b) academics, (c) industry, (d) think tanks, (e) allies and partners, (f) non-governmental organisations and (g) the public on the forthcoming National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review documents.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11584","11584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421017","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what capabilities he requires of Protector aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11582","11582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421018","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to lay a copy of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review before the House.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11583","11583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421019","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many minority ethnic service personnel were recruited to each service (a) nationally and (b) in Gloucester in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11529","11529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421020","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) men and (b) women were recruited to each service through the Armed Forces Careers Office in Gloucester in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11530","11530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421021","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made towards full disregard of military compensation payments for veterans in respect of their care costs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11758","11758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421022","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the potential for future UK airstrikes in Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11713","11713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421023","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the progress made by the Careers and Enterprise Company on (a) increasing employer output into schools and colleges and (b) managing its network of enterprise advisers to assist schools and colleges in choosing good careers and enterprise partner organisations.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11733","11733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421024","2015-10-15","Department for Education","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will implement the recommendations of the All-Party Group on a Fit and Healthy Childhood on encouraging play in childhood development and learning in school.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11571","11571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421025","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding was provided to each pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in Gloucestershire (A) in cash terms and (B) at 2015 prices in each financial year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11611","11611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421026","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding was provided to each pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in Essex (A) in cash terms and (B) at 2015 prices in each financial year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11612","11612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421027","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding was provided to each pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in Hampshire (A) in cash terms and (B) at 2015 prices in each financial year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11613","11613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421028","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding was provided to each pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in East Sussex (A) in cash terms and (B) at 2015 prices in each financial year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11614","11614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421029","2015-10-15","Department for Education","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding was provided to per pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in Devon (A) in cash terms and (B) at 2015 prices in each financial year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11605","11605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421030","2015-10-15","Department for Education","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve physical fitness standards in schools.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11719","11719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421031","2015-10-16","Department for Education","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to increase the number of former Armed Forces personnel who retrain as teachers through the Troops to Teachers programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11732","11732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421032","2015-10-15","Department for Education","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will publish the October 2015 census data for primary school reception class places for each school in the London Borough of Lambeth.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11677","11677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421033","2015-10-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which projects have been undertaken to date under the UK-China Memorandum and Understanding on Enhancing Cooperation in the Field of Civil Nuclear Industry Fuel Cycle Supply; and what the (a) location and (b) cost is of each such project.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11651","11651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421034","2015-10-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the annual budget is for the UK's Centre of Nuclear Excellence.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11656","11656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421035","2015-10-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the activities of the new UK-China joint research and innovation centre will be subject to oversight by (a) the Office for Nuclear Regulation and (b) her Department's national nuclear stakeholder forum.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11648","11648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421036","2015-10-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether all projects undertaken in the new UK-China joint research and innovation centre will be subject to the (a) Freedom of Information Act 2000 and (b) Environmental Information Regulations 2004.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11650","11650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421037","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on extracting potential oil reserves near the Falklands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11708","11708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421038","2015-10-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what new departmental resources have been committed to support the UK-China joint research and innovation centre; which UK personnel have been appointed to this work to date; what process was followed in making those appointments; and where each such post was advertised.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11649","11649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421039","2015-10-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the schedule of comparable programme objects in HM Treasury's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, what the total expenditure was on the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority between 2010 and 2015; and what the forecast expenditure is in each location on that authority in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11510","11510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421040","2015-10-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the announced reductions in feed-in tariff support will apply to existing contracts or new ones; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11742","11742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421041","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on (a) processing farmers' 2015 Basic Payment Scheme applications and (b) tackling the challenges of getting information supplied by farmers in paper form back onto an online validation process; and what resources have been committed to carry out this work to date.","Biography information for Nadhim Zahawi","Nadhim Zahawi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11734","11734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421042","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what effect the switch to a paper-based application system for the Basic Payment Scheme has had on (a) claim validation and the verification of claims and (b) the delivery of timely payments from 1 December.","Biography information for Nadhim Zahawi","Nadhim Zahawi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11735","11735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421043","2015-10-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the schedule of comparable programme objects in HM Treasury's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, what the total expenditure was on animal diseases between 2010 and 2015; and to what projects in which locations that funding was provided.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11511","11511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421044","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to introduce interim payments in cases in which there are delays in making payments under the Basic Payments Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11598","11598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421045","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the level of complexity of the Countryside Stewardship Scheme; if she will take steps to simplify that scheme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11599","11599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421046","2015-10-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will place in the Library a copy of the framework agreement between her Department and the Royal Botanic Gardens, Kew.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11566","11566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421047","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to ensure that (a) Seafish and (b) other bodies funded by fishing levies do not promote the fishing industries of other North Sea or Norwegian Sea countries.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11556","11556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421048","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the amount spent each year by (a) Seafish and (b) other bodies funded by fishing levies on promoting the fishing industries of other countries.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11557","11557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421049","2015-10-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the environmental effects of underground coal gasification.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11541","11541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421050","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish the results of the EU's recent tests on the likely harmful effects to bees of the use of neonicotinoids; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11724","11724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421051","2015-10-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the level of take-up of the Countryside Stewardship Scheme is; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11725","11725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421052","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to deter Russian forces from targeting non-IS targets in Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11702","11702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421053","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his US counterparts on the targeting of non-IS targets by Russian forces in Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11703","11703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421054","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent ISIL from destroying valuable historical sites in Palmyra and elsewhere.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11721","11721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421055","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Australian counterpart on the effect of Prime Minister Malcolm Turnbull coming into office on Australian-UK relations.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11717","11717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421056","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of progress on the (a) establishment of a national unity government in Libya and (b) ending of political instability in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11716","11716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421057","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to encourage a return to representative, democratic governance in Zimbabwe once Mr Mugabe ceases to hold the office of President.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11698","11698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421058","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's aims are for the state visit of President Xi Jinping in October 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11696","11696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421059","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterparts on recent outbreaks of violence in Israel and Palestine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11715","11715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421060","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effects of recent political instability in Turkey.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11662","11662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421061","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the current level of representation of the British Overseas Territories at Westminster; and whether his Department plans to increase such representation and adopt a model similar to that used in (a) France and (b) the Netherlands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11663","11663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421062","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of recent UK efforts to prevent people smuggling in the Mediterranean.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11684","11684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421063","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the attack on UK military vehicles in Kabul on 11 October 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11688","11688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421064","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Japanese counterparts on security reforms in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11685","11685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421065","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy of recent military defeats by Afghan forces; and what discussions he has had with his Afghan counterparts on the insurgency at Kunduz.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11697","11697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421066","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on the recent conflict at Temple Mount.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11686","11686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421067","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to prevent the export of illegal drugs from Afghanistan.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11687","11687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421068","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to encourage other nations in the Levant and Arabian peninsula to accept refugees from Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11658","11658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421069","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what policy aims his Department achieved at the 69th session of the UN General Assembly.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11706","11706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421070","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Spanish counterpart on incursions into Gibraltarian waters by Spanish ships in recent months.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11709","11709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421071","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Saudi Arabian counterpart against that country's policy of judicially-sanctioned capital punishment.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11655","11655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421072","2015-10-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the level of sexual violence (a) within Syria and (b) in camps for Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11597","11597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421073","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress was made during the recent visit of German Chancellor Angela Merkel on negotiations on the UK's relationship with the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11664","11664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421074","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Saudi Arabian counterpart on human rights abuses in that country.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11654","11654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421075","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Saudi Arabian authorities on pursuing a negotiated solution to the conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11624","11624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421076","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's chart of account.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11565","11565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421077","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on each international subscription in each financial year from 2000-01 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11567","11567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421078","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will place in the Library a copy of his Department's global asset management plan.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11568","11568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421079","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) locally engaged and (b) UK-based staff worked in each overseas post in financial years (i) 2000-01, (ii) 2005-06, (iii) 2010-11 and (iv) 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11569","11569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421080","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2015 to Question 6862 on Yemen: armed conflict, whether it remains the case that the UK Government has seen no credible evidence that the Saudi-led coalition has breached international humanitarian law in its campaign in Yemen.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11580","11580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421081","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of John Boehner's resignation as US Congress Speaker on US-UK relations.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11712","11712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421082","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients Lancashire Care have admitted to named NHS facilities at (a) Clatterbridge, (b) West Part, Darlington, (c) Hull (d) Birch Hill, Rochdale, (e) Brierley and (f) other named facilities between 1 January and 30 September 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11729","11729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421083","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust have admitted to named private facilities at (a) Cygnet, Bierley, (b) Cygnet, Bradford, (c) Cygnet, Harrogate, (d) Cygnet, Harrow, (e) Cygnet, Wyke, (f) The Priory, Cheadle Royal, (g) The Priory, Darlington, (h) The Priory, Glasgow, (i) The Priory, Altringham, (j) The Spinney, Manchester and (k) other facilities between 1 January and 30 September 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11730","11730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421084","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to establish a database of people suffering from secondary breast cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11731","11731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421085","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) proportion and (b) number of mental health providers have been inspected by the Care Quality Commission under its new inspection regime.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11780","11780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421086","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mental health providers have been inspected by the Care Quality Commission in each of the last five years; and what the longest period of time is that a mental health provider has been without inspection since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11781","11781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421087","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received from groups representing junior doctors on their current working conditions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11738","11738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421088","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hours of mental health training is required as part of the mandatory training course for (a) student doctors, (b) student nurses and (c) midwives.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11782","11782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421089","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to prepare for the implementation of waiting time standards for eating disorder services in April 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11783","11783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421090","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people referred for talking therapies received cognitive behaviour therapy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11784","11784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421091","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 September 2015 to Question 10120, what additional funding his Department plans to make available to facilitate diabetes care in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11760","11760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421092","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that the NHS Trust Development Authority collaborates with the NHS Future Fit process in Shropshire to make a decision regarding future emergency care for that county; and if he will take steps to ensure that population growth and the level of health inequality are taken into account in the process of making that decision.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11788","11788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421093","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what timetable NHS England has set for developing a commissioning policy for the Everolimus drug.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11615","11615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421094","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many medical students completed their studies in London medical schools in each year from 2006 to 2009.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11616","11616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421095","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many medical students completed their studies in London medical schools in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11617","11617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421096","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in Eddisbury constituency have been diagnosed with secondary breast cancer in the last three years.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11573","11573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421097","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps (a) his Department and (b) NHS England is taking to ensure that autism diagnosis waiting times for (i) children and (ii) adults in St Helens North constituency meet NICE guidance.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11602","11602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421098","2015-10-16","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to publish its final guidance on the Vimizim treatment.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11559","11559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421099","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations (a) NHS England and (b) NICE have received from (i) drug companies and (ii) patient groups on the treatment of uveitis.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11560","11560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421100","2015-10-19","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people with uveitis; and what treatment is available for that condition at what cost.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11561","11561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421101","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if Ministers or officials of his Department will meet Jeena International, Karma Nirvana and other organisations representing women who have been the victim of coerced sex-selective abortion to discuss the implications of his Department's assessment of the evidence of termination of pregnancy on grounds of gender.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11522","11522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421102","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the likely annual cost of health and social care provision for people aged over 65 during the present Parliament.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11513","11513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421103","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department next plans to publish an assessment of the incidence of sex-selective abortion in the UK.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11514","11514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421104","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of how widespread sex-selective abortion would have to be before it was detectable in nationally-compiled birth ratios.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11515","11515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421105","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has for future levels of provision of NHS-funded hospice care.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11516","11516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421106","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what strategy his Department has for ensuring that as many people as possible who wish to die at home are able to do so.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11517","11517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421107","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the level of unmet demand for palliative care beds for patients in the last six months of their lives.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11518","11518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421108","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether doctors performing surgical abortions are prohibited from altering the procedure (a) in order to maximise the amount or quality of fetal tissue obtained for research and (b) for other non-clinical reasons.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11519","11519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421109","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what procedures are in place to ensure that women agreeing to donate foetal tissue are not coerced, pressured or hurried into doing so and that they understand fully what it is that they are being asked to do.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11520","11520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421110","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve staff retention in NHS England.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11636","11636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421111","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Individual Funding Requests have been granted in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11637","11637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421112","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in devolved administrations on standardising the decision-making process for individual funding requests.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11608","11608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421113","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on securing funding for patients infected with contaminated blood and for their families.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11638","11638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421114","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of staff morale in NHS England.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11635","11635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421115","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what arrangements his Department has to ensure that financial grants made by his Department to Action on Smoking and Health are not used to fund activities intended to influence (a) Parliament, Government or political parties, (b) the awarding or renewal of Government contracts and grants and (c) legislative or regulatory action.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11587","11587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421116","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the recommendations in the publication entitled Achieving world-class cancer outcomes: a strategy for England 2015-2020 by the Independent Cancer Taskforce are implemented.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11704","11704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421117","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for its policy of the potential link between the HPV Vaccine and Postural Orthostatic Tachycardia Syndrome; and what assessment he has made of the effect of such a link on the progress of the Government's HPV vaccination programme.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11694","11694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421118","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what structures are in place for (a) staff in primary care settings and (b) other healthcare professionals to raise concerns about sex-selective abortions if they believe these are occurring.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11632","11632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421119","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether foetal tissue derived from abortions is used in medical research in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11631","11631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421120","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made in the arbitration dispute between the Barking, Havering and Redbridge University Trusts and Care UK, over which institution will deliver services from the King George Elective Care Centre, Redbridge, on behalf of the Barking/Dagenham, Havering and Redbridge Clinical Commissioning Groups; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that both parties receive a prompt decision by the arbitration tribunal.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11720","11720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421121","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which local authorities are receiving Prevent strategy funding; and if she will publish the formula used for allocating such funding.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11726","11726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421122","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to mark Anti-Slavery Day 2015; what steps she is taking to increase awareness of the growth of modern day slavery; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Field","Mark Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11727","11727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421123","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many individual investigations the National Crime Agency has conducted into County Line operations; and how many prosecutions have resulted from such investigations.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11679","11679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421124","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions the (a) National Crime Agency and (b) SOCA have declined a request by a police force to investigate a suspected County Line on grounds of the age of suspects.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11681","11681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421125","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many nominals in County Line investigations conducted or led by the National Crime Agency have been under 18; and what the age, gender and regional breakdown is of each such person.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11680","11680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421126","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that Syrian refugees coming to Britain do not have criminal records or connections to extremist groups.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11691","11691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421127","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to help Syrian refugees assimilate into British society.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11692","11692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421128","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the threat level of the group Britain First.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11628","11628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421129","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions for trafficking offences linked to County Line investigations there have been to date in cases where a child under the age of 18 was trafficked to another area to distribute drugs; and what the outcomes were of such prosecutions.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11678","11678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421130","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the ePassport gates at Stansted Airport were fully functional on the evening of Monday 12 October 2015.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11666","11666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421131","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in which prisons people are currently held solely under immigration powers; and if she will publish this information as part of the quarterly immigration statistics.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11644","11644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421132","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many days any of the ePassport gates at Stansted Airport were not fully functioning at any point during the months of June, July, August and September 2015.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11672","11672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421133","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many ePassport gates are in operation at (a) Heathrow, (b) Gatwick, (c) Luton and (d) Stansted airports.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11671","11671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421134","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many errors made by staff of her Department in recording details such as addresses and country of birth on applications for (a) naturalisation and (b) indefinite leave to remain forms have had to be corrected in the last month.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11577","11577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421135","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken was to respond to a new application for indefinite leave to remain in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11578","11578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421136","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2015 to Question 8380, how many burglaries were reported in each ward in Preston City Council in each of the first six months of 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11623","11623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421137","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers have been (a) allowed to continue on full duties, (b) placed on restricted duties and (c) suspended with figures following a death in custody and during an investigation for gross misconduct in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11626","11626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421138","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the prevalence of elder abuse by family members in England and Wales.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11521","11521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421139","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications made by Syrian nationals in each of the last three years were refused on the grounds that the applicant could be returned to a safe third country.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11523","11523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421140","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) shortest, (b) longest and (c) mean period of time was for deciding applications for family reunion in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11524","11524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421141","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for family reunion made by Syrian nationals have been (a) received, (b) decided, (c) granted and (d) refused in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11525","11525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421142","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrian nationals have been returned to third countries under the Dublin Regulations in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11526","11526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421143","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the number of people who do not receive a national insurance number within 28 days of being granted refugee status.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11528","11528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421144","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on amending the immigration system to increase the supply of non-domiciled seafarers to the UK shipping industry.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11535","11535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421145","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on amending the immigration system to increase the supply of non-domiciled shore-based workers to the UK maritime sector.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11536","11536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421146","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the national standards are for the training and guidance of police officers in deploying stinger devices.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11554","11554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421147","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the reasons are for the time taken to change regulations to allow mothers' names to be recorded on marriage certificates; what timetable is in place for that change to be made; whether she has made an assessment of the feasibility of allowing that change to be phased in as marriage registers are replaced; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11550","11550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421148","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an estimate of the potential (a) total and (b) average cost per register of allowing mothers names to be recorded on marriage certificates.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11551","11551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421149","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many transit visas for Syrian nationals have been (a) granted and (b) refused in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11527","11527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421150","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's consultation, Enabling closer working between the Emergency Services, whether firefighters employed by police and crime commissioners will retain the right to take part in industrial action; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11531","11531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421151","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will conduct a review into the efficiency and effectiveness of administrative handling of cases.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11574","11574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421152","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to clarify the administrative requirements on applicants for indefinite leave to remain (a) in general and (b) in respect of whether the date on a letter from her Department on the date on which it is received by an applicant dictates the period within which the applicant must respond.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11575","11575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421153","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons her Department did not renew the Choices contract in detention centres; and what assessment the Government has made of the effect of that decision on the number of people in detention taking up voluntary return and being removed from the UK.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11581","11581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421154","2015-10-16","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been resettled in the UK through the Mandate scheme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11740","11740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421155","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to amend the US-UK extradition treaty to make the legal requirements for extradition the same for US and UK citizens.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11710","11710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421156","2015-10-15","Department for International Development","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how UK aid has been used to assist refugees near the Syrian border to date; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11711","11711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421157","2015-10-15","Department for International Development","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the risk of famine in Yemen; and what assessment she has made of the possible humanitarian implications of famine in the Middle East and North Africa.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11645","11645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421158","2015-10-15","Department for International Development","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of the ongoing de facto blockade of Yemen by the government of Yemen and the Saudi-led coalition on (a) aid and (b) commercial supplies to that country.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11646","11646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421159","2015-10-15","Department for International Development","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to ensure that all parties involved in the conflict in Yemen allow unimpeded humanitarian access (a) into and (b) within the country to reach people in need.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11647","11647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421160","2015-10-15","Department for International Development","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of new HIV infections in sub-Saharan Africa.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11689","11689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421161","2015-10-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to complete the evaluation of the pilots of section 28 of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11778","11778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421163","2015-10-16","Leader of the House","2015-10-13","To ask the Leader of the House, what discussions he has had with Ministers or officials of HM Treasury on the effect of Government proposals for English votes for English laws on the future of the block grant for Scotland.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11757","11757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421164","2015-10-15","Northern Ireland Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress she has made in resolving the political situation in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11700","11700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421165","2015-10-15","Prime Minister","2015-10-13","To ask the Prime Minister, under which conditions he can order the killing of a UK citizen resident abroad.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11643","11643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421166","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will ensure that at least 1,000 Syrian children are brought to settle in the UK before Christmas 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11546","11546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421167","2015-10-16","Cabinet Office","2015-10-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much (a) fair price milk and (b) non-fair price milk was purchased for use in 10 Downing Street in August 2015; and what plans he has to ensure that only fair price milk is used at 10 Downing Street in future.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11728","11728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421168","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's letter of 11 April 2014 to the Chief Executive of HS2 Ltd, when he plans to publish the advice by HS2 Ltd and Network Rail on improving connections to European rail networks referred to in that letter.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11753","11753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421169","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's average spend on Bus Service Operators Grant was per capita in each English region in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11751","11751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421170","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to reduce the incidences of non-payment of wages to seafarers working in (a) UK and (b) Europe.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11747","11747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421171","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the total in unpaid wages owed to seafarers working in the UK shipping industry in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11748","11748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421172","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many temporary speed restrictions were in place on Network Rail infrastructure on (a) 1 April and (b) the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11755","11755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421173","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will raise with (a) his ministerial colleagues and (b) the International Labour Organisation the extent of non-compliance amongst open registers with the minimum standards for seafarers' rights established in the Maritime Labour Convention 2006.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11746","11746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421174","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings of the International Transport Workers Federation's Maritime Labour Convention compliance inspections on international shipping in 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11745","11745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421175","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the estimated cost is to (a) his Department and (b) Network Rail of unpausing electrification of the Midland Main Line and the North TransPennine route.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11754","11754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421176","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2015 to Question 9602, which external organisations received payments from his Department in connection with developing the policies referred to in that Answer; and what amount was paid to each such organisation.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11759","11759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421177","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase the supply of UK (a) domiciled and (b) trained seafarers to the shipping industry.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11534","11534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421178","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the current status is of the Shipping Strategic Plans for the (a) shipping, (b) ports and (c) business services sectors of the UK maritime industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11537","11537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421179","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings he has planned over the next six months with maritime training colleges to discuss the recommendations of the Maritime Growth Study.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11533","11533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421180","2015-10-16","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether officials in his Department were acting on his authority when they instructed Network Rail and the Office of Rail and Road on 26 March 2015 on how the further assessment of Control Period 5's cost estimates was to be carried out.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11601","11601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421181","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the National Atmospheric Emission Inventory results for the nitrogen dioxide levels at Pippins Primary School, Colnbrook, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the health of pupils and staff at that school of the proposals by the Davies Commission to expand Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11586","11586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421182","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff are employed by Network Rail to deal with contractual interface issues.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11669","11669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421183","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that automotive manufacturers have not falsified emissions data in the same manner as Volkswagen has done.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11659","11659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421184","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much it cost to reconstruct the railway at Dawlish; and from which budget that cost was met.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11670","11670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421185","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings he has had with airlines in which the administration charges for customers claiming back Air Passenger Duty were discussed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11607","11607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421186","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings he has planned over the next six months with maritime trades unions on the recommendations of his Department's Maritime Growth Study published in September 2015.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11606","11606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421187","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many lawyers are employed by Network Rail to work on delay attribution issues with the staff of train operating companies.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11676","11676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421188","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff are employed by Network Rail to deal with delay attribution issues with train operating staff.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11674","11674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421189","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many lawyers are employed by Network Rail to deal with contractual interface issues.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11675","11675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421190","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consultants have been used to advise the Government on the future structure of Network Rail; and what the cost to the public purse has been of engaging such consultants.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11673","11673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421191","2015-10-15","Department for Transport","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total cost was of his Department's Maritime Growth Study, published in September 2015; how many hours staff in his Department worked on that study; and when he plans to respond to its recommendations.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11630","11630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421192","2015-10-15","Women and Equalities","2015-10-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps the Government is taking to reduce the gender pay gap.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11633","11633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421193","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of anonymising job applications in tackling discrimination in the jobs market.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11627","11627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421194","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what specific guidance and advice his Department will be issuing to pensioners on the change in the Support for Mortgage Interest scheme from a benefit to an interest-bearing loan.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11764","11764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421195","2015-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to improve rates of pay for people aged under 25.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11768","11768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421196","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent on housing benefit between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11765","11765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421197","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pensioners will lose money as a result of changing the Support for Mortgage Interest scheme from a benefit to an interest-bearing loan; and what the average annual loss will be for such pensioners.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11761","11761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421198","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what processes and procedures are in place when benefit claimants report having suicidal thoughts.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11775","11775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421199","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of time is that pensioners currently in receipt of the Support for Mortgage Interest scheme have been claiming that benefit.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11762","11762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421200","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the level of administration fees and interest charges to pensioners under the Support for Mortgage Interest loan scheme.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11763","11763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421201","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he will respond to the Work and Pensions Committee Report on Benefit sanctions beyond the Oakley review, Fifth Report of Session 2014-15, HC 814.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11766","11766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421202","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of changes in the level of scam activity associated with pensions following the introduction of pensions freedoms.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11771","11771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421203","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in the number of people relying on temporary accommodation since 2010.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11767","11767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421204","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of pensioners who will not be exempt from the size criteria of universal credit.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11772","11772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421205","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many days were lost to sickness in his Department in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11773","11773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421206","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the morale of his Department's staff.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11774","11774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421207","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what effect the introduction of universal credit will have on the income of those working in a job from which they derive net earnings of less than £110 per week and who are the principal carers for elderly relatives with a disability.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11639","11639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421208","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what effect the introduction of universal credit will have on the income of those working in a job from which they derive net earnings of at least £111 per week and who are the principal carers for elderly relatives with a disability.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11640","11640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421209","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what effect the introduction of universal credit will have on the incomes of those spending more than 21 hours per week in education and who are the principal carers for elderly relatives with a disability.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11641","11641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421210","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what effect the introduction of universal credit will have on funding for care available to older people with a disability whose principal carer is engaged in education for no more than 20 hours per week.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11642","11642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421211","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to expenditure on (a) DWP Administration, (b) the Government Equalities Office, (c) the Health and Safety  Executive, (d) the Work Welfare and Equalities Group and (e) the Working Age Client Group in the schedule of comparable programme objects in HM Treasury's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, (i) how much of that expenditure in which locations was on (A) property and (B) personnel and (ii) how many people in which locations were employed through such expenditure between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11503","11503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421212","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the schedule of comparable programme objects in HM Treasury's publication, Funding the Scottish Parliament, National Assembly for Wales and Northern Ireland Assembly: Statement of Funding Policy, published in October 2010, what the total expenditure was on how many claims relating to pneumoconiosis in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Kilmarnock and Loudon constituency between 2010 and 2015; and how many such claims were unsuccessful.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11504","11504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421213","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time was for a decision to be made on a claim for pneumoconiosis between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11505","11505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421214","2015-10-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department is giving to people on low incomes who are unable to cover the costs of a funeral deposit.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11552","11552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421215","2015-10-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions her Department has had with the UK Miners Pension Scheme Association on the Miners Pension Scheme; and if she will review the provision that 50 per cent of any surplus made after 1994 will be paid to the Government.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11555","11555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/421216","2015-10-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2015 to Question 10360, how many sanctions have been applied due to claimants not ticking the appropriate box on NHS charges claims forms when claiming help with NHS health costs in cases where the claim forms do not include such a box.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11786","11786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422019","2015-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will consult Ministers in the Scottish Government on the Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901614","901614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/422020","2015-10-19","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian casualties were recorded as a result of drone strikes in 2014.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901611","901611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420580","2015-10-15","Attorney General","2015-10-12","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he is taking to reduce the time court cases take to reach a conclusion.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11423","11423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420581","2015-10-15","Attorney General","2015-10-12","To ask the Attorney General, how many Deferred Prosecution Agreements the Serious Fraud Office is currently negotiating; and what recent progress has been made in each of those negotiations.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11438","11438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420582","2015-10-15","Attorney General","2015-10-12","To ask the Attorney General, what the total value was of the proceeds of crime retained by the Serious Fraud Office (SFO) under the ARIS incentive scheme in each financial year since 2012-13; and what proportion of the annual SFO budget this formed in each case.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11439","11439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420583","2015-10-15","Attorney General","2015-10-12","To ask the Attorney General, how many requests for blockbuster funding were made by the Serious Fraud Office (SFO) in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15 and (f) 2015-16 to date; how much funding was requested on each such occasion for which investigations; what proportion of the SFO's annual budget such blockbuster funding represented in each of those years; and on how many occasions such funding requests were not approved in each of those years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11456","11456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420584","2015-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 22 September 2015 to Question 9932, what total amount of funding was not drawn down by beneficiaries by mutual agreement under each round of the Regional Growth Fund.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11490","11490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420585","2015-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department's target of three million apprenticeship starts by 2020 includes people starting more than one apprenticeship during that time period.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11443","11443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420586","2015-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices there were in the civil nuclear industry in each financial year between 2010-11 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11466","11466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420587","2015-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the terms of the forthcoming statutory review into the role of the Groceries Code Adjudicator will be; if the Government will consider a case for an extension of the remit of the Adjudicator in order to better protect primary producers as part of that review; and what steps the Government plans to take prior to the statutory review in order to give the Adjudicator more powers to deal with issues in the supply chain (a) in general and (b) in the dairy sector.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11457","11457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420588","2015-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the contribution of UK university satellite campuses in London to the economy.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11292","11292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420589","2015-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he has plans to regulate or limit the ability of UK universities to establish satellite campuses in London.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11293","11293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420590","2015-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of UK universities operating satellite campuses in London.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11294","11294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420591","2015-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that EU and US car safety regulations are compatible under the proposed Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership agreement.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11296","11296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420592","2015-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeship applications have been (a) made and (b) accepted in the last 12 months; and how many such applications were from people who have served a prison sentence.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11310","11310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420593","2015-10-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 14 September 2015 to Question 9138, what assessment he has made of whether payment by his Department to Royal Mail in respect of the Postcode Address File constitutes state aid to Royal Mail.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11315","11315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420594","2015-10-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that sufficient (a) skilled workers and (b) apprenticeships are available in the construction industry.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11347","11347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420595","2015-10-14","Cabinet Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will place restrictions on charities seeking annual contributions from supporters.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11328","11328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420596","2015-10-15","Cabinet Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2015 to Question 9924, whether he plans to implement the recommendation of the British Computing Society that personal data should remain the property of the individual unless they choose for it to be used.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11420","11420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420597","2015-10-15","Cabinet Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, who the acting Chief Data Officer is; and what plans are in place for a permanent appointment to that post.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11489","11489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420598","2015-10-15","HM Treasury","2015-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 September 2015, when he expects to publish 2014-15 data on families' tax credit awards within local authorities.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11419","11419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420599","2015-10-14","HM Treasury","2015-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the letter from the Exchequer Secretary of the Treasury to the Scottish Government's Minister for Business, Energy and Tourism, for what reasons his Department has concerns over the implementation of a CPS tax exemption on coal from land restoration sites and its compatibility with European requirements.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11469","11469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420600","2015-10-14","HM Treasury","2015-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department last reviewed the salaries of officers of arms.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11460","11460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420601","2015-10-14","HM Treasury","2015-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of buy-to-let mortgages authorised in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11350","11350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420602","2015-10-14","HM Treasury","2015-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many married couples with a single earner in each Office for National Statistics age group have received marriage allowance in (a) England, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11351","11351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420603","2015-10-14","HM Treasury","2015-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many married couples with a single earner in each Office for National Statistics age group have claimed marriage allowance in (a) England, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11352","11352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420604","2015-10-14","HM Treasury","2015-10-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to continue paying the homelessness prevention grant to local authorities when the local government grant is phased out.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11364","11364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420605","2015-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the homelessness prevention grant.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11365","11365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420606","2015-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people have been categorised as intentionally homeless in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11356","11356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420607","2015-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the likely level of government investment in right to buy schemes in the next five years.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11354","11354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420608","2015-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households have been placed in emergency temporary accommodation each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11355","11355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420609","2015-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of households evicted from council accommodation rented from private landlords at short notice have been provided with emergency accommodation on the night of eviction.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11353","11353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420610","2015-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with local authorities on their capacity to house refugees.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11272","11272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420611","2015-10-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what support his Department provides to finds liaison officers to ensure that detected archaeological finds are properly recorded in a speedier manner in order to encourage more finds to be declared to local authorities.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11287","11287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420612","2015-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding the Government plans to allocate to local authorities for housing Syrian refugees; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11283","11283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420613","2015-10-14","Home Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will provide information and data about the housing, health, and social needs of Syrian refugees to enable local authorities to plan for their arrival.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11284","11284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420614","2015-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many firefighters in each fire and rescue authority are qualified trauma technicians.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11465","11465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420615","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will require builders to submit infrastructure delivery plans prior to main planning applications.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11432","11432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420616","2015-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to further control the ability of private landlords to evict tenants at short notice.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11486","11486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420617","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the 30 September 2015 publication, English Indices of Deprivation, what plans his Department has to introduce specific measures to (a) improve the standard of housing, (b) improve the quality of life and (c) liberalise planning rules for house building in Jaywick.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11444","11444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420618","2015-10-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) council houses, (b) housing association properties and (c) affordable homes were built in the Lancaster City Council local authority area between (i) 1997 and 2001, (ii) 2001 and 2005, (iii) 2005 and 2010 and (iv) 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11473","11473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420619","2015-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment the Government has made of the potential for efficiencies from closer working between the ambulance and fire services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11494","11494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420620","2015-10-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will conduct a review of local government (a) procedures on and (b) requirements to provide housing to families who become intentionally homeless.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11495","11495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420621","2015-10-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how the final five per cent of superfast broadband coverage will be funded.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11471","11471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420622","2015-10-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has for the future regulation of television content royalty payments.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11413","11413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420623","2015-10-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions took place between the Government and the BBC on free television licences for people over 75 before the decision was made that the BBC would fund such licences; and when such discussions took place.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11406","11406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420624","2015-10-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with age-related third sector or charity organisations on the withdrawal of Government funding for free television licences for people over 75.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11407","11407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420625","2015-10-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to prevent illegal online sales of portable antiquities discovered at archaeological sites in the UK.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11288","11288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420626","2015-10-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold discussions with Camelot on steps they are taking to reverse the recent decline in national lottery sales.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11289","11289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420627","2015-10-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether requirements for religious content will be included in the new BBC Charter.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11308","11308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420628","2015-10-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold discussions with the Football Association about improved access for disabled people to Premier League football matches.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11290","11290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420629","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, under what circumstances RAF Tornado squadrons will be kept in service after 2017.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11346","11346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420630","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) target and (b) outturn was for (i) regular Army and (ii) Army Reserve recruitment in financial years 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11383","11383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420631","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the 2015-16 Army Demand Plan.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11384","11384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420632","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the interim performance regime for the Army Recruiting Partnership Project.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11385","11385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420633","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library an unredacted copy of Schedule 18 of the Army Recruiting Partnership Project contract with Capita.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11387","11387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420634","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list those armed forces units that have been relocated under the Army 2020 structure.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11379","11379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420635","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects the Army Recruiting Partnership Project to achieve full operating capacity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11386","11386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420636","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Air Force personnel of each (a) rank and (b) skill or trade left that service through (i) voluntary redundancy, (ii) involuntary redundancy, (iii) voluntary exit and (iv) involuntary exit in each financial year between 2010-11 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11380","11380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420637","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the target is for (a) regular Army and (b) Army Reserve recruitment in each financial year between 2015-16 and 2019-20.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11454","11454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420638","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many army personnel of each (a) rank and (b) skill or trade left that service through (i) voluntary redundancy, (ii) involuntary redundancy, (iii) voluntary exit and (iv) involuntary exit in each financial year between 2010-11 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11455","11455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420639","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) civilian and (b) military personnel of his Department are based in (a) Oman and (b) the Duqm Port facility.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11403","11403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420640","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where his Department plans to base (a) HMS Forth, (b) HMS Medway and (c) HMS Trent.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11404","11404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420641","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many naval personnel of each (a) rank and (b) skill or trade left that service through (i) voluntary redundancy, (ii) involuntary redundancy, (iii) voluntary exit and (d) involuntary exit in each financial year between 2010-11 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11381","11381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420642","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Army Reserve recruitment target for (a) new recruits and (b) trained entrants is in financial years between 2015-16 and 2019-20.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11382","11382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420643","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the anticipated personnel (a) inflow and (b) outflow in each (i) rank and (ii) skill or trade in the regular Army over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11453","11453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420644","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual budget is for running Queen Victoria School in Dunblane; and from what part of the Defence budget that funding is allocated.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11415","11415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420645","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent in Continuity of Education Allowance in independent schools in Scotland in financial year 2014-15; how many children were in receipt of Continuity of Education Allowance in Scottish schools in that year; and in which five schools had the highest Continuity of Education Allowance spend in Scotland in that year.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11401","11401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420646","2015-10-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the future of the Defence Storage and Distribution Agency at Ashchurch near Tewkesbury; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11418","11418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420647","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) assets and (b) personnel of his Department took part in NATO Exercise Northern Coasts.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11399","11399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420648","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the origin was of the steel cut for the hull of HMS Forth.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11400","11400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420649","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) assets and (b) personnel of his Department took part in Exercise Pearl Dagger in conjunction with the Bahraini armed forces.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11402","11402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420650","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2015 to Question 794, if he will place in the Library a copy of the report cited in paragraph 3 of document D/VCDS&2ndPUS/8/1/4 PR11.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11461","11461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420651","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people resident in Northern Ireland have been members of the reserve forces in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11478","11478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420652","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people resident in Northern Ireland have been recruited into the reserve forces in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11479","11479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420653","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason his Department has not proposed a reserve experience event for a location in Northern Ireland in 2015.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11480","11480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420654","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) planned and (b) actual savings to his Department were under the Army Recruiting Partnership Project in each financial year between 2012-13 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11481","11481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420655","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which armed forces units have been (a) disbanded and (b) created under the Army 2020 structure.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11482","11482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420656","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many army personnel of each (a) rank and (b) skill or trade transferred to the (i) Australian Defence Forces, (ii) Canadian Armed Forces, (iii) United States Army, (iv) New Zealand Army and (v) other overseas armed forces in each financial year between 1997-98 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11483","11483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420657","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) trained strength and (b) trained requirement was for the (i) Royal Scots Borderers, (ii) Royal Highland Fusiliers, (iii) Black Watch, (iv) Highlanders, (v) Balaklava Company, (vi) 52nd Lowland Battalion and (vii) 51st Highland Battalion in each financial year between 2004-05 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11484","11484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420658","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the planned savings are to his Department under the Army Recruiting Partnership Project in each financial year between 2015-16 and 2022-23.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11485","11485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420659","2015-10-15","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to (a) remove free school meals for children in primary school and (b) alter the provision of free school meals for children under the compulsory school age in England and Wales.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11445","11445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420660","2015-10-15","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of providing free school meals for Reception, Year 1 and Year 2 pupils since the launch of the free school meals scheme.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11448","11448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420661","2015-10-15","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the continued provision of free school meals for children in Reception, Year 1 and Year 2; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11449","11449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420662","2015-10-15","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of free school meals provided in each month since 2 September 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11452","11452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420663","2015-10-15","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many special schools were rebuilt between 2010 and 2014; and what the average cost was of each such construction excluding land.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11493","11493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420664","2015-10-14","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase the uptake of free school meals.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11372","11372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420665","2015-10-14","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of introducing automatic enrolment of children entitled to free school meals.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11371","11371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420666","2015-10-14","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has had with (a) headteachers, (b) teaching unions and (c) children's charities on the effect of universal infant free school meals on pupil wellbeing.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11370","11370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420667","2015-10-14","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to include food provision in its recently announced wraparound childcare policy during (a) term time and (b) non-term time.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11366","11366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420668","2015-10-14","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of the roll-out if the universal infant free school meals programme on the allocation of pupil premium money to schools.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11369","11369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420669","2015-10-14","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the correlation between levels of achievement at Level 4 in (a) reading and (b) mathematics and national average scores in those subjects at GCSE level.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11275","11275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420670","2015-10-14","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of including food provisions in the Government's recently announced wraparound childcare policy for children eligible for free school meals during (a) term time and (b) non-term time childcare.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11368","11368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420671","2015-10-14","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of new (a) kitchen and (b) other lunchtime staff who have been employed as a result of the roll-out of universal infant free school meals.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11367","11367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420672","2015-10-14","Department for Education","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of schools that have acquired (a) new kitchens and (b) new dining halls to provide universal infant free school meals since September 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11373","11373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420673","2015-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people were employed in the nuclear industry and its supply chain in each financial year between 2010-11 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11468","11468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420674","2015-10-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average age is of engineers in the civil nuclear industry.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11467","11467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420675","2015-10-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the effect of proposed changes to the feed-in-tariff on solar firms and small businesses in (a) Somerton and Frome constituency, (b) the South West and (c) the UK.","Biography information for David Warburton","David Warburton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11475","11475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420676","2015-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress the Government is making towards ensuring that 3,000 miles of the England Coast Path will be open by 2020.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11488","11488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420677","2015-10-14","Department for Transport","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people were killed due to fishing boats sinking in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11349","11349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420678","2015-10-14","Department for Transport","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many fishing boats were lost at sea in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11348","11348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420679","2015-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to implement the EU Water Framework Directive.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11378","11378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420680","2015-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to help implement United Utilities' proposed North-South water pipeline alongside the currently proposed High Speed 2 route.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11377","11377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420681","2015-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many CAP payment applications were submitted within the deadline in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11363","11363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420682","2015-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with the banking sector on support for farmers.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11362","11362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420683","2015-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the cost to date of the Government's CAP IT system.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11361","11361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420684","2015-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the European Commission on the relaxation of rules on farm checks required for the Basic Payment Scheme.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11358","11358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420685","2015-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what disallowance penalties her Department has incurred in relation to CAP payments in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11357","11357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420686","2015-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many farmers and other eligible businesses have (a) registered for and (b) completed the CAP payment application.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11359","11359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420687","2015-10-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to make CAP payments before the end of December 2015.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11360","11360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420688","2015-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions the Government has had with the Afghan government on the work of the Afghan Independent Human Rights Commission.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11338","11338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420689","2015-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions the Government has had with the Afghan government on improving the welfare and well-being of (a) women and girls and (b) other people in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11337","11337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420690","2015-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions the Government has had with the Afghan government on ensuring the protection of journalists and media organisations in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11339","11339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420691","2015-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the Nigerian government on the recent rescue of 178 people from Boko Haram; and what information his Department holds on the number of children so rescued who were kidnapped by Boko Haram in April 2014.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11345","11345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420692","2015-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with his French counterpart allegations that British tourists have been systematically overcharged at Disneyland, Paris.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11344","11344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420693","2015-10-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government reached an agreement with Afghan tribesmen for the person who made the bomb which killed Captain Lisa Head in April 2011 to be released from prison.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11342","11342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420694","2015-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Iranian government on the release from captivity of Jason Rezaian.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11343","11343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420695","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he is holding at the UN on a possible Security Council resolution on the establishment of safe zones in Syria.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11276","11276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420696","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he is holding at the UN on a possible Security Council resolution authorising the use of force against ISIL/Daesh in Syria.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11277","11277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420697","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of coalition air strikes on (a) the extent of the territory held by ISIL/Daesh and (b) that group's capacity to advance in (i) Iraq and (ii) Syria.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11279","11279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420698","2015-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the Pakistani government on persecution of Christians in that country.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11477","11477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420699","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the role played by access to natural resources across Iraq and Syria in the ongoing conflict in those countries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11451","11451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420700","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on the Gaza Reconstruction Mechanism.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11441","11441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420701","2015-10-15","Home Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government's overseas posts are taking to warn women applying for entry to the UK about the dangers of sex trafficking and exploitation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11424","11424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420702","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the aims and objectives are of the Government's policy towards Russia.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11433","11433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420703","2015-10-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to pages three and four of the United Kingdom Strategic Export Controls Annual Report 2014, whether the policy regarding Israel as of the end of 2014 remains in place.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11421","11421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420704","2015-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Israeli authorities in the aftermath of the deaths of Saad Riham and Ali Dawabsheh.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11410","11410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420705","2015-10-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department plans to distribute Syrian refugees amongst the British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11412","11412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420706","2015-10-14","Department of Health","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 27 July 2015 to Question 7775, how many times the Deputy Director, Tobacco Control in his Department met representatives from Action on Smoking and Health in each of the last five years; and what the reason, items discussed and outcome were of each such meeting.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11416","11416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420707","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prosecutions there have been following an investigation by NHS Protect in each of the past five years; and how many of those prosecutions have been for offences related to (a) fraud, (b) violence, (c) bribery, (d) corruption, (e) criminal damage, (f) theft, (g) market-fixing and (h) other unlawful action.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11428","11428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420708","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) doctors, (b) nurses, (c) other medical professionals, (d) directors of NHS trusts and (e) other NHS staff have been prosecuted following an investigation by NHS Protect in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11427","11427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420709","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether, under his Department's proposals for new junior doctor contracts, doctors will be prevented from receiving remuneration or other financial support for volunteering or working for the armed forces.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11437","11437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420710","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether, under his Department's proposals for new junior doctor contracts, doctors will be prevented from receiving financial remuneration or support as athletes or for playing competitive sport.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11434","11434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420711","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many investigations NHS Protect has undertaken relating to (a) fraud, (b) bribery, (c) corruption, (d) criminal damage, (e) theft, (f) violence, (g) market-fixing and (h) other unlawful action in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11426","11426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420712","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether, under his Department's proposals for new junior doctor contracts, doctors will be prevented from receiving remuneration or other financial support for time given to charitable causes.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11435","11435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420713","2015-10-15","Department of Health","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether, under his Department's proposals for new junior doctor contracts, doctors will be prevented from receiving remuneration or other financial support for time working for or volunteering for overseas medical organisations or charities.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11436","11436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/420714","2015-10-14","Department of Health","2015-10-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish an updated end of life care strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 11464","11464"
