"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65759","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were found guilty in a magistrates' court, consequent upon non-payment or contesting of a fixed penalty notice for graffiti, in each local authority area in each of the last three years; and what the total value was of fines levied for such offences in each local authority area in each such year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203993","203993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65760","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were found guilty in a magistrates' court, consequent upon non-payment or contesting of a fixed penalty notice, for failure to comply with a waste receptacles notice, in each local authority area in each of the last three years; and what the total value was of fines levied for such offences in each area in each such year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203990","203990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65761","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were found guilty in a magistrates' court, consequent upon non-payment or contesting of a fixed penalty notice, for failure to produce authority to transport waste, in each local authority area in each of the last three years; and what the total value was of fines levied for such offences in each area in each such year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203991","203991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65762","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has had with the Bar Standards Board on requiring advocates who handle sexual abuse cases to undertake appropriate specialist training.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203978","203978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65763","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were found guilty in a magistrates' court, consequent upon non-payment or contesting of a fixed penalty notice for failure to comply with a street litter clearing notice, in each local authority area in each of the last three years; and what the total value was of fines levied for such offences in each area in each such year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203992","203992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65764","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to increase the number and availability of remote sites for video conferencing with courtrooms.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203979","203979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65765","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were found guilty in a magistrates' court, consequent upon non-payment or contesting of a fixed penalty notice, for smoking in a smoke-free place, in each local authority area in each of the last three years; and what the total value was of fines levied for such offences in each area in each such year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203987","203987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65766","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were found guilty in a magistrates' court, consequent upon non-payment or contesting of a fixed penalty notice, for fly posting, in each local authority area in each of the last three years; and what the total value was of fines levied for such offences in each area in each such year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203988","203988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65767","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were found guilty in a magistrates' court, consequent upon non-payment or contesting of a fixed penalty notice, for unauthorised distribution of printed matter, in each local authority area in each of the last three years; and what the total value was of fines levied for such offences in each area in each such year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203989","203989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65768","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions were brought against people for distribution of explicit photographs when the permission of the photograph's subject had not been obtained in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204012","204012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65769","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were found guilty in a magistrates' court, consequent upon non-payment or contesting of a fixed penalty notice, for failure to remove dog faeces, in each local authority area in each of the last three years; and what the total value was of fines levied for such offences in each area in each such year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203986","203986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65770","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total (a) population and (b) number of foreign nationals of each nationality was in each jail in London on 1 July (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012, (iv) 2013 and (iv) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204035","204035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65771","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were found guilty in a magistrates' court, consequent upon non-payment or contesting of a fixed penalty notice for repairing vehicles on the road, in each local authority area in each of the last three years; and what the total value was of fines levied for such offences in each local authority area in each such year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203994","203994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65772","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what body is responsible for holding data on the number and availability of remote sites for video conferencing with courtrooms.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203981","203981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65773","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were found guilty in a magistrates' court, consequent upon non-payment or contesting of a fixed penalty notice for abandonment of a vehicle, in each local authority area in each of the last three years; and what the total value was of fines levied for such offences in each local authority area in each such year.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203995","203995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65774","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what statistics his Department holds on the use of fixed penalty notices in each local authority area and in each category.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203997","203997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65775","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign nationals of each nationality were deported from jails in London to complete their sentences in their home countries in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204039","204039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65776","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what crimes foreign nationals in jails in London on 1 July (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014 have been found guilty of committing.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204038","204038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65777","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign nationals in jails in London on 1 July (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014 (i) were on remand and (ii) have been found guilty of a criminal offence.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204037","204037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65778","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of (a) staff morale, (b) sickness rates, (c) turnover and (d) training in prisons; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203911","203911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65780","2014-07-07","Leader of the House","2014-07-03","To ask the Leader of the House, what guidance he has given to his ministerial colleagues about providing substantive answers to written questions.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203894","203894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65781","2014-07-07","Leader of the House","2014-07-03","To ask the Leader of the House, what his policy is on hon. Members of the Sinn Fein Party formally taking their seat in the House.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203966","203966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65782","2014-07-07","Scotland Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many (a) internal and (b) external complaints have been received by his Department about alleged breaches of the Civil Service Code of Conduct since 2010; and what actions his Department has taken in response to each such complaint.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203957","203957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65783","2014-07-08","Scotland Office","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what contribution his Department is making to the preparations for the 2014 Commonwealth Games in Glasgow.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203915","203915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65784","2014-07-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-03","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, if the Electoral Commission will produce a list of significant cases of electoral fraud resulting in custodial sentences since 1998; and what political party was involved in each case.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203973","203973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65785","2014-07-08","Department for Transport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many complaints have been received from members of the public about employees of (a) HS2 Ltd, (b) his Department or (c) any member of staff seconded to either HS2 Ltd or his Department in relation to the High Speed 2 project; what the grade was of the person against whom the complaint was made; and what the (i) substance and (ii) result was of each such complaint.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204010","204010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65786","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with his French counterpart on the effect of the EU Sulphur Directive on (a) the shipping industry, (b) jobs and (c) the environment; and what the outcome of the conversations has been.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203939","203939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65787","2014-07-10","Department for Transport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the economic and social contribution of airports to (a) the public purse and (b) local communities.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204033","204033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65788","2014-07-08","Department for Transport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 June 2014, Official Report, column 295W, on cycling: children, what criteria his Department uses to measure whether a mode of transport is safe and secure.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 204040","204040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65789","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what improvements to Coastway East and the Brighton-Ashford Line have been proposed in the TSGN franchise to improve services between Brighton and Ashford International; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203869","203869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65790","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received from Somerset County Council on the re-opening of railway stations in Somerset.","Biography information for Mr David Heath","Mr David Heath","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203864","203864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65791","2014-07-08","Department for Transport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Framework Agreement between his Department and Network Rail on the reclassification of Network Rail will ensure that the Freedom of Information Act 2000 applies to Network Rail.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203914","203914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65792","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether rolling stock to be delivered to Northern Rail and TransPennine Express over the next six years will be configured to allow the option of retaining the operational role of the guard.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203919","203919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65793","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has considered funding in the 2019 to 2024 spending review for the Brighton Mainline 2; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203873","203873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65794","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if it is his policy to retain the capping of rail fares at the rate of RPI + 1, beyond 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203880","203880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65795","2014-07-07","Women and Equalities","2014-07-03","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the contribution of women to the economy; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203923","203923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65796","2014-07-07","Women and Equalities","2014-07-03","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, on what dates she has met Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender mental health service providers.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203898","203898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65797","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether debt accrued by non-resident parents transfers automatically to the Child Maintenance Service for enforcement when the Child Support Agency is abolished.","Biography information for Natascha Engel","Natascha Engel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203899","203899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65798","2014-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time between claim and a decision on attendance allowance was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203926","203926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65799","2014-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time between claim and a decision on attendance disabled living allowance for parents of children aged under 16 years was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203927","203927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65800","2014-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the contracts for personal independence payment assessment providers include performance related incentives or penalties; whether such measures have been used; and what the financial value of those measure is.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203930","203930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65801","2014-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time between claim and a decision on carer's allowance was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203928","203928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65802","2014-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department has recorded as the main disabling condition of people under employment and support allowance and jobseekers' allowance benefit sanctions.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203929","203929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65803","2014-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in respect of Child Support Agency child maintenance owed to parents with care, how many arrears-only cases there are (a) where money is flowing and (b) where no money is flowing.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203881","203881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65804","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people whose main disability is cystic fibrosis are in receipt of the mobility award for personal independence payment at the (a) standard and (b) enhanced rate.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203884","203884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65805","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people whose main disability is cystic fibrosis are in receipt of the daily living award for personal independence payment at the (a) standard and (b) enhanced rate.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203885","203885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65806","2014-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress he has made in helping people with disabilities to access work through the employment and support allowance programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203908","203908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65807","2014-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the times taken to decide claims, measured by actual average clarance time, were for (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance, for the longest and shortest deciles of claims, processed in each financial year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203912","203912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65808","2014-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his contribution of 30 June 2014, Official Report, column 642, on DWP: performance, what level of service his Department expects to provide to meet his aim of providing a personal independence payment system that works for those most in need; and how he will measure success.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203900","203900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65809","2014-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his contribution of 30 June 2014, Official Report, column 647, on DWP: performance, how his Department will demonstrate that no claimant is waiting more than 16 weeks for their personal independence payment by the end of 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203901","203901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65810","2014-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the letter of 6 March 2014 from the Minister for Disabled People to Macmillan Cancer Support, for what reason his Department does not consider data on clearance times of personal independence payment normal and special rules claims to be robust enough to be included in the published quarterly statistics.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203902","203902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65811","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) internal and (b) external complaints have been received by his Department about alleged breaches of the Civil Service Code of Conduct since 2010; and what actions his Department has taken in response to each such complaint.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203959","203959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65812","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will review the rate for Social Fund funeral expenses payments.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203946","203946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65275","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the Government's policy is on whether holiday pay may be calculated without reference to bonus and overtime payment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203544","203544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65276","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department plans to intervene in the Neal v Freightliner proceedings in the Employment Appeal Tribunal in July.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203545","203545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65277","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department provides any guidance specifically for the creative industries.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203542","203542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65278","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the British Library's Business & IP Centre national network.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203556","203556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65279","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the contribution to the economy of the British Library's Business & IP Centre national network.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203557","203557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65280","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number of jobs created in partnership with the British Library's Business & IP Centre national network.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203558","203558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65281","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to (a) amend or repeal the Pedlars Acts 1871 and 1881 and (b) amend Schedule 4 to the Local Government (Miscellaneous Provisions) Act 1982 covering the street trading regime of England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dan Byles","Dan Byles","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203563","203563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65282","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding available through the disabled student's allowance was spent on non-medical help in the last year.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203586","203586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65283","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of manufacturing activity in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England in each of the last four years; and what assessment he has made of future capacity in that sector.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203598","203598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65284","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to prevent the postage by retailers of Second World War gas masks containing asbestos.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203584","203584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65285","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many current students in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) Cumbria and (d) South Lakeland have been awarded disabled students allowance.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203608","203608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65286","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the number of current students who have been awarded disabled student's allowance (DSA) who would fail to be awarded DSA under the proposed revised eligibility guidelines.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203609","203609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65287","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the cost of introducing, maintaining and updating a register of providers of disabled students' allowances (DSA) study needs assessments and DSA assistive technology service providers; and who will fund the introduction and maintenance of that register.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203625","203625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65288","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many men have been unemployed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203591","203591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65289","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been unemployed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203592","203592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65290","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many men have been employed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203593","203593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65291","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women have been employed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203594","203594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65292","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the unemployment rate in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK was in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203589","203589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65293","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women have been unemployed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203590","203590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65294","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have been employed in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203560","203560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65295","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Answer of 30 April 2014, Official Report, column 811, on cybercrime, whether the £860 million includes the £650 million in his Department's report The UK Cyber Security Strategy: Protecting and Promoting the UK in a Digital Age published in November 2011; and how much funding from the National Cyber Security Strategy has been allocated to the Ministry of Defence.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203539","203539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65296","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to lower air passenger duty.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203541","203541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65297","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203536","203536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65298","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the median gross weekly wage of employees in (a) Coventry North East constituency, (b) Coventry, (c) the West Midlands and (d) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203599","203599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65299","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the level of growth in the UK economy in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015; and what change in the level of public sector employment he anticipates will take place in each region and constituent part of the UK in that time.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203572","203572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65300","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the respondents to his Department's Review of Property conditions in the Private Rented Sector issued in February 2014 supported the mandatory installation of smoke alarms in privately rented housing.","Biography information for Mr Nick Raynsford","Mr Nick Raynsford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203564","203564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65301","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to tackle anti-semitic attacks (a) in Greater Manchester and (b) across the UK.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203568","203568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65302","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to make formal proposals to end the ongoing dispute on firefighters' pensions based on the alternative costed options within the proposed cost ceiling which were released on 12 June 2014; and if he will make a statement on progress towards resolving that dispute.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203610","203610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65303","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, at what level his Department values the reduction of risk of death per fatal casualty prevented; and if he will give an example of a policy intervention where this evaluation was made.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203611","203611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65304","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department gives on the weight to be given to areas of outstanding natural beauty when calculating housing need for the purpose of drawing up local plans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203607","203607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65305","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203523","203523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65306","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203524","203524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65307","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assistance his Department gives to community groups who wish to take over the running of museums and tourist attractions.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203559","203559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65309","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the decision not to proceed with a mast at Fownhope, if he will include the lack of mobile network coverage in that area in any future discussion he has with network operators.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203627","203627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65310","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the amount of foreign direct investment into the UK film industry in each year from 1997 to 2009.","Biography information for Tom Greatrex","Tom Greatrex","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203623","203623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65311","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made on Cornwall's additional European social funding.","Biography information for Sarah Newton","Sarah Newton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203605","203605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65312","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with Facebook about the experiment they conducted on users to influence their emotions in 2012.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203577","203577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65313","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the US administration about Facebook's experiment on users' emotions in 2012.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203578","203578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65314","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has sought legal advice on Facebook's experiment on users' emotions in 2012.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203579","203579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65315","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the regional distribution is of Arts Council England's Catalyst funds.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203580","203580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65316","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which media organisations in the UK have received funding from the European Parliament to promote coverage of EU-level decision-making in the last three years.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203566","203566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65317","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of UK citizens subject to Facebook's experiment on users' emotions in 2012.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203576","203576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65318","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding the UK has contributed to the European Parliament's House of European History Project to date.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203567","203567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65319","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203525","203525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65320","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203526","203526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65322","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the sponsor capacity funds awarded by his Department to the Third Millennium Education Trust were returned to his Department.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203554","203554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65323","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps his Department is taking to reduce levels of fuel poverty in (a) Coventry, (b) Coventry North East constituency and (c) England.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203596","203596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65324","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203527","203527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65325","2014-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203528","203528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65326","2014-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government's policy is on protecting migratory birds from the effects of offshore wind turbines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203543","203543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65327","2014-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, at what level his Department values the reduction of risk of death per fatal casualty prevented; and if he will give an example of policy intervention where this evaluation was made.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203612","203612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65328","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what system is in place to regularly review the number of Syrian resettlement places in the UK as part of the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme in order to ensure the scheme is responsive to need.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203565","203565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65329","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proposals the UK has put to the Permanent Five members of the UN Security Council (P5) on collective participation in the Conference on the Humanitarian Effects of Nuclear Weapons being hosted in Vienna in December 2014 by the Austrian government; and what discussions were held within the P5 on participation in the predecessor conferences held in Norway and Mexico.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203561","203561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65330","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures his Department has put in place to ensure that people with ovarian cancer and their families are aware of the right to request BRCA1/2 testing at the point of diagnosis; and what steps his Department is taking to encourage greater uptake of BRCA1/2 gene testing.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203562","203562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65331","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203529","203529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65332","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to maximise the use of donated organs.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203546","203546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65333","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of lungs retrieved from donors are transplanted into recipients.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203547","203547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65334","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of kidneys retrieved from donors are transplanted into recipients.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203548","203548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65335","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of hearts retrieved from donors are transplanted into recipients.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203549","203549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65336","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of livers retrieved from donors are transplanted into recipients.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203550","203550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65337","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places for general practice in each region were (a) commissioned and (b) filled in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203551","203551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65338","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what change there has been in the level of funding for diabetes research since 1 January 2012.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203555","203555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65339","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many diabetics have missed routine health checks since 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203575","203575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65340","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of adults (a) on the Care Programme Approach receiving secondary mental health services and (b) receiving secondary mental health services but who were not on the Care Programme Approach in (i) England, (ii) each mental health trust area (iii) each primary care trust area and (iv) each local authority area were in employment in 2013-14.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203600","203600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65341","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will institute a campaign to raise public awareness of the symptoms of a transient ischaemic attack and the need for urgent treatment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203602","203602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65342","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, at what level his Department values the reduction of risk of death per fatal casualty prevented; and if he will give an example of policy intervention where this evaluation was made.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203613","203613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65343","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that examples of good practice and better care pathways for the treatment of transient ischaemic attacks are disseminated throughout the NHS.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203604","203604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65344","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research he has commissioned into the effect of ensuring that patients receive urgent treatment following a transient ischaemic attack on (a) reducing the risk of stroke and (b) reducing the cost to the NHS of treating strokes.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203603","203603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65345","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to improve the diagnostic pathway for adults with autism in the autism statutory guidance.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203616","203616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65346","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of customers using the Passport Check and Send Service had their passport application rejected due to (a) completing the application form incorrectly, (b) providing incorrect supporting documents and (c) providing the incorrect fee in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203606","203606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65347","2014-07-09","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether requests from Syria for visitor visas are dealt with on merit on a case-by-case basis; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203626","203626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65348","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, at what level her Department values the reduction of risk of death per fatal casualty prevented; and if she will give an example of policy intervention where this evaluation was made.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203614","203614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65349","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203530","203530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65350","2014-07-07","Department for International Development","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203531","203531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65351","2014-07-07","Department for International Development","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent specifically to reduce the number of malnourished children in the developing world; and which 10 countries are the largest recipients of such funding.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203574","203574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65352","2014-07-07","Department for International Development","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much aid the UK has given to Yemen since 1 January 2012; and what comparative assessment she has made of the level of such spending in other EU countries.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203573","203573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65353","2014-07-07","Department for International Development","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which 10 countries will receive the highest amount of UK aid in the post-2015 development framework; and how much each such country will receive.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203571","203571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65354","2014-07-07","Department for International Development","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how UK aid money to India was allocated in (a) 2012, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203569","203569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65355","2014-07-07","Department for International Development","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much of the aid given by the UK to Yemen is spent on (a) food, (b) education, (c) housing, (d) healthcare and (e) employment.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203570","203570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65356","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people resident in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England received an award of legal aid in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203597","203597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65357","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer from Kevin Sadler to question 147 from the Work and Pensions Committee on 7 May 2014, what the predicted cost was of (a) employment and support allowance appeals, (b) such appeals borne by the Department for Work and Pensions and (c) such appeals borne by HM Treasury in the financial year 2009-10.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203617","203617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65358","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer from Kevin Sadler to question 147 from the Work and Pensions Committee on 7 May 2014, what the cost is of (a) employment and support allowance appeals, (b) such appeals borne by the Department for Work and Pensions and (c) such appeals borne by HM Treasury in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203618","203618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65359","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203532","203532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65361","2014-07-07","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans her Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203533","203533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65362","2014-07-07","Scotland Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203534","203534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65363","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the contribution of High Speed 2 to transport connectivity between communities in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203540","203540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65364","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203535","203535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65365","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, at what level his Department values the reduction of risk of death per fatal casualty prevented; and if he will give an example of policy intervention where this evaluation was made.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203615","203615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65366","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the use of telematics to reduce car insurance premiums.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203582","203582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65367","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to publish the Green Paper on young drivers safety.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203581","203581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65368","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential cost to the Strategic Highways Company of carrying full public liability and professional indemnity insurance as proposed in the Infrastructure Bill [Lords].","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203601","203601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65369","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received from groups supporting the development of the Brighton Mainline 2; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203588","203588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65370","2014-07-07","Wales Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203537","203537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65372","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to increase the number of replies sent electronically to letters from hon. Members.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203538","203538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65373","2014-07-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the proposed funding model for residential training colleges will be announced.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203587","203587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65374","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 25 November 2013, Official Report, column 126W, on gas masks, what progress he has made on preventing the continued on-line sale of Second World War gas masks containing asbestos.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203585","203585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65375","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to monitor the standards of asbestos management in schools (a) under and (b) outside of local authority control.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203583","203583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65376","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the universal credit system will accept claims from those who are self-employed.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203552","203552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65377","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants (a) received an overpayment of widowed parent's allowance and (b) were prosecuted for benefit fraud in respect of that allowance in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203553","203553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65378","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the risk of a link between the introduction of universal credit and levels of domestic violence.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203595","203595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65379","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many decisions based on work capability assessments were overturned during the completion of the mandatory reconsideration period in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2012-13.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203624","203624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65380","2014-07-07","Attorney General","2014-07-02","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Serious Fraud Office's incorrect reclamation of VAT on fees it paid to barristers and other contractors; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203779","203779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65381","2014-07-07","Attorney General","2014-07-02","To ask the Attorney General, what steps the Crown Prosecution Service is taking to prosecute successfully the offence of forced marriage in (a) Northamptonshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203838","203838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65382","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent steps he has taken to improve transparency in the procurement processes of university libraries.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203635","203635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65383","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to bring forward proposals to help the insurance industry to reduce the cost of car insurance for newly qualified drivers.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203643","203643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65384","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 649W, on disabled students' allowances, if he will publish a list of all stakeholders being consulted on the Equality Analysis and Disabled Students' Allowances Guidance for 2015-16.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203667","203667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65385","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in (a) the London Borough of Lewisham and (b) Lewisham East constituency are in receipt of disabled student's allowance.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203720","203720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65386","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people in (a) Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland, (b) Middlesbrough, (c) Stockton North, (d) Stockton South, (e) Hartlepool, (f) Redcar constituency and (g) the North East received disabled students' allowance in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203732","203732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65387","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects to conclude his Department's consultation on the proposed changes to the disabled students' allowance; and when he expects to publish the Equality Analysis and Disabled Students' Allowances Guidance for 2015-16.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203719","203719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65388","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many teenage pregnancies there have been in each ward in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203734","203734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65389","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants employed through the analytical graduate fast track schemes between June 2004 and June 2014 were educated at (a) private and (b) state schools.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203805","203805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65390","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what changes there have been in the claimant count for women in Ashfield constituency aged 25 and over claiming for over 24 months since May 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203808","203808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65391","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants employed through the Human Resources graduate fast track scheme between 1 June 2004 and 1 June 2014 were educated at (a) private and (b) state schools.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203800","203800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65392","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what changes there have been in the claimant count for women in Ashfield constituency aged between 18 and 24 years claiming for over 12 months since May 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203809","203809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65393","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants employed through the Technology in Business graduate fast track scheme between 1 June 2004 and 1 June 2014 were educated at (a) private and (b) state schools.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203801","203801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65394","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what changes there have been in the number of (a) female and (b) male part time workers in Ashfield constituency in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203810","203810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65395","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants employed through the generalist graduate fast track schemes between 1 June 2004 and 1 June 2014 were educated at (a) private and (b) state schools.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203802","203802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65396","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil servants employed through the European graduate fast track scheme between 1 June 2004 and 1 June 2014 were educated at (a) private and (b) state schools.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203804","203804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65397","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what changes there have been in the claimant count for women aged 25 years and over claiming for over 24 months since May 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203813","203813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65398","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what changes there have been in the claimant count for women aged between 18 and 24 years claiming for over 12 months since May 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203814","203814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65399","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance his Department provides to officials in the Northern Ireland Executive on personal security.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203620","203620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65400","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost of flexible resourcing within HM Revenue and Customs in terms of lost yield from staff being moved away from their normal duties to assist with call handling during the tax credit peak.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203798","203798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65401","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost to the public purse was of the Building Our Future workshops held for all HM Revenue and Customs staff.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203797","203797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65402","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) total operating cost and (b) staffing cost other than for staff not engaged in compliance work of Irvine tax office was in 2013-14.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203796","203796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65403","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the tax yield generated by compliance officers working in Irvine tax office in 2013-14.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203795","203795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65404","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many new claims were paid in April 2014 for (a) working tax credit and (b) child tax credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203727","203727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65405","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the reasons are for the proposed closure of Irvine Tax Office.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203767","203767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65406","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the sum was of unpaid wages involved in each of the cases where employers have been prosecuted for non-payment of the minimum wage since 1999.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203781","203781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65407","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many civil enforcement actions HM Revenue and Customs has taken against employers over non-payment of the minimum wage in the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203782","203782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65408","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria HM Revenue and Customs use to determine whether a case where an employer is paying one or more employees less than the minimum wage is pursued by the civil route or the criminal route.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203783","203783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65409","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-02","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the 10 largest amounts of unpaid arrears were that were imposed in the last five years against employers who paid one or more employees less than the minimum wage; and whether any of those employers were prosecuted.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203784","203784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65410","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) individuals, (b) couples and (c) families are registered in the UK as seeking accommodation.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203780","203780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65411","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of vacant residential properties in each region.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203818","203818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65412","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of vacant residential properties (a) awaiting occupation, (b) that are derelict, (c) that are for sale and (d) in other categories; and what estimate he has made of the proportion of current net additional housing demand that could be met through bringing vacant properites back into use.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203823","203823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65413","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the proportion of development land required to meet current net additional demand for housing that could come from brownfield sites.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203825","203825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65414","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many housing starts there were in 2013-14; and what recent forecast he has made of the likely number of housing starts in 2014-15.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203693","203693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65415","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 June 2014, Official Report, columns 151-2W, on Bellwin Scheme, which local authorities have made applications for Bellwin funding relating to flooding in winter 2013-14 since 11 June 2014; what amount each such local authority applied for; and what amount has been paid to each such local authority to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203680","203680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65416","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of (a) sites and (b) homes where building is yet to start which have full planning permission.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203668","203668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65417","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of individual respondents to his consultation on local authority parking agreed with the Government's proposal to abolish the use of closed circuit television cameras for parking enforcement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203639","203639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65418","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of organisations responding to his consultation on local authority parking agreed with the Government's intention to abolish the use of closed circuit television cameras for parking enforcement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203640","203640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65419","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold discussions with the sports ministers of the devolved administrations to ensure that following the 2014 Glasgow Commonwealth Games immediate preparations will begin to ensure greater participation by people in all four constituent parts of the UK in the run-up to the 2018 Gold Coast Commonwealth Games.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203703","203703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65420","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of primary pupils from each region have engaged with (a) theatre activities, (b) music activities, (c) dance and (d) other arts in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203662","203662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65421","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of primary pupils from (a) disadvantaged backgrounds and (b) non-disadvantaged backgrounds have engaged with (i) theatre activities, (ii) music activities, (iii) dance and (iv) other arts in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203663","203663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65422","2014-07-07","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many apprentices have been employed by contractors and sub-contractors to his Department in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion they make up of the workforce of those contractors and sub-contractors.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203859","203859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65423","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what total number of sponsored reserves were agreed as part of contracts signed by companies working for his Department in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203842","203842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65424","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department issues guidance on protocols relating to former armed forces' personnel using their rank as a title after they have left service.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203843","203843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65425","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on advertising for recruitment to the Reserves in the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Army and (c) Royal Air Force in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203844","203844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65426","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many apprentices have been employed by contractors and sub-contractors to his Department in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion such apprentices make up of the workforce of those contractors and sub-contractors.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203860","203860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65427","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what targets his Department had for the number of sponsored reserves in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203840","203840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65428","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the findings of Chavasse Report, published in spring 2014, what steps he is taking to ensure that injured soldiers receive the necessary specialist care to rebuild their lives.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203788","203788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65429","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he will answer Question 201291, tabled by the hon. Member for Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland on 18 June 2014.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203789","203789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65430","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to change funding for existing Combined Cadet Force detachments and to communicate those changes to schools.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203660","203660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65431","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will bring forward proposals to amend the rules governing the War Pension Scheme to allow all war widows a pension for life.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203702","203702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65432","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish the titles of all reports on the risks of the transport of nuclear warheads (a) within the UK and (b) from or to the UK from abroad produced for his Department by (i) his Department and (ii) the Atomic Weapons Establishment and its predecessor body in the last 30 years.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203638","203638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65433","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the contractor is financially liable for the delay in HMS Ocean returning to service from her refit; and what estimate he has made of the costs of that delay.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203709","203709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65434","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when HMS Illustrious will be deployed on Exercise Cougar 14; what estimate he has made of the cost of preparing that ship for the exercise; and when she will return to be decommissioned.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203708","203708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65435","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the RAF's Joint Strike Fighter 35-Bs have all been grounded following an on-board fire on another Joint Strike Fighter; when the grounded aircraft are expected to fly again; and whether those aircraft will make the transatlantic flight to the UK this July.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203707","203707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65436","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the document D/DDOR3(AIR)(IFF)12 dated 31 October 1994.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203689","203689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65437","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much was spent on a collision warning system for fast jets during the Technical Demonstration Programme between 1991 and 1998.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203690","203690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65438","2014-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish all (a) reports, (b) studies and (c) impact assessments held by Ministers in the Department for Energy and prepared or considered by Ministers or officials between July 1984 and January 1986 which detail (i) the potential economic benefits of oil exploration in the Firth of Clyde or (ii) the defence implications of granting applications for licences to drill oil in that sector.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203710","203710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65439","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what consideration was given to purchasing the RAIDS Collision Warning System software options after difficulties were encountered with the bespoke Collision Warning System.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203691","203691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65440","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the implementation of the tested bespoke Collision Warning System proposed by the Director of Operations Requirements (Air) in August 1998 was cancelled.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203692","203692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65441","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many apprentices have been employed by contractors and sub-contractors to his Department in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion such apprentices make up of the workforce of those contractors and sub-contractors.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203861","203861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65442","2014-07-07","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-02","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps he is taking to encourage the funding for and implementation of the strategic economic plans submitted by the Northamptonshire LEP and the South East Midlands LEP (a) generally and (b) in regard to junction 10A on the A14 near Kettering.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203839","203839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65443","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2014, Official Report, column 83W, on special educational needs, how many local authorities have provided extra funding to assist schools with a disproportionate number of pupils with special educational needs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203833","203833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65444","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2014, Official Report, column 83W, on special educational needs, how much local authorities have spent on providing extra funding for schools with a disproportionate number of pupils with special educational needs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203834","203834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65445","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2014, Official Report, column 83W, on special educational needs, how many schools in (a) England and (b) Birmingham have received extra funding from local authorities to assist them with disproportionate numbers of pupils with special educational needs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203835","203835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65446","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants administer medicine to children in local authority schools in England.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203826","203826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65447","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprentices have been employed by contractors and sub-contractors to his Department in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion such apprentices make up of the workforce of those contractors and sub-contractors.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203862","203862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65448","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) turnover and (b) wastage rate was for (i) full-time and (ii) part-time teachers in each school in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203736","203736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65449","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many requests for directions to admit a child to an academy were received by the Education Funding Agency in 2010; and how many such directions were issued.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203785","203785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65450","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were permanently excluded from (a) primary, (b) middle, (c) upper and (d) secondary schools in Staffordshire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203786","203786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65451","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils in (a) reception, (b) year 1 and (c) year 2 in each state-funded primary school had speech and language difficulties in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203737","203737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65452","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary, other than small primary and (b) secondary schools in each local authority area had more than three per cent of pupils in care in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203735","203735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65453","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) average, (b) shortest and (c) longest time taken was to issue a direction to admit a child to an academy by the Education Funding Agency, since the creation of that agency.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203729","203729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65454","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) primary school pupils and (b) infant school pupils in Ashfield constituency received free school meals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203811","203811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65455","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secondary school pupils in Ashfield constituency received free school meals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203812","203812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65456","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the capacity is of renewable energy projects that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 and received planning consent (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203746","203746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65457","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the capacity is of hydropower that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 and began construction (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203743","203743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65458","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many renewable energy projects that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 began construction (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203747","203747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65459","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many renewable energy projects that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 received planning consent (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203748","203748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65460","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the capacity is of renewable energy projects that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 and began construction (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203749","203749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65461","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many onshore wind projects that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 began construction (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203750","203750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65462","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the capacity is of offshore wind that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 and began construction (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203751","203751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65463","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many (a) new, (b) pending and (c) live non-domestic green deal plans there are.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203762","203762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65464","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many green deal assessments there have been in the non-domestic sector.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203763","203763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65465","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the capacity is of medium and large-scale solar PV that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 and received planning consent (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203744","203744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65466","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the capacity is of hydropower that started generation in May to December (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 and received planning consent (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203742","203742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65467","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will publish all (a) minutes, (b) memoranda and (c) correspondence held by his Department about contact with (i) the Ministry of Defence and (ii) the Scottish Office relating to the Department of Energy's consideration of the 1981 application by British Petroleum for a licence to drill in the Firth of Clyde.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203687","203687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65468","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which (a) government departments and (b) external stakeholders were consulted in the determination of the 1981 licence application made by British Petroleum to drill in the Firth of Clyde; and (i) on what date and (ii) for what reason the application was ruled unsuccessful.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203688","203688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65469","2014-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will publish all correspondence between his Department and (a) the Department for Energy and (b) the Scottish Office originating between July 1984 and January 1986 concerning applications for licences to drill for oil in the Firth of Clyde.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203712","203712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65470","2014-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what meetings took place between Ministers and officials of his Department and Ministers and officials of (a) the Department for Energy and (b) the Scottish Office between July 1984 and January 1986 at which oil exploration in the Firth of Clyde was discussed.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203711","203711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65471","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will publish all (a) minutes, (b) memoranda and (c) correspondence originating between July 1984 and January 1986 relating to contacts between the Department of Energy and the Ministry of Defence about applications for licences to drill for oil in the Firth of Clyde.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203686","203686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65472","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the capacity is of medium and large-scale solar PV that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 and began construction (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203745","203745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65473","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the capacity is of onshore wind that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 and began construction (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203755","203755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65474","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many hydropower projects that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 received planning consent (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203759","203759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65475","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many offshore wind projects that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 began construction (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203760","203760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65476","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many medium- and large-scale solar pv projects that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 began construction (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203756","203756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65477","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many medium- and large-scale solar pv projects that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 received planning consent (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203757","203757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65478","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many hydropower projects that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 began construction (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203758","203758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65479","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the capacity is of offshore wind that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 and received planning consent (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203752","203752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65480","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2014, Official Report, column 595W, on energy: prices, at which meetings with (a) EDF, (b) E-on, (c) Npower and (d) Scottish Power he asked them to pass on the savings from changes to green levies to customers on fixed-price deals.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203764","203764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65481","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many onshore wind projects started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 and received planning consent (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203753","203753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65482","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the capacity is of onshore wind that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 and received planning consent (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203754","203754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65483","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many offshore wind projects that started generation in (a) May to December 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) January to June 2014 received planning consent (i) before May 2010 or (ii) after May 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203761","203761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65484","2014-07-07","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many apprentices have been employed by contractors and sub-contractors to his Department in each year since 2010-11; and what proportion such apprentices make up of the workforce of those contractors and sub-contractors.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203863","203863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65485","2014-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's response is to the recommendations of the Elliott Review into the Integrity and Assurance of Food Supply Networks.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203701","203701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65486","2014-07-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when he expects the Elliot Report on food crime to be published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203636","203636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65487","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the imprisonment of ethnic Rohingya people for getting married.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203632","203632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65488","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he considers that the recent census in Burma meets international standards.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203633","203633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65489","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department took to help secure the release of Eyal Yifrah, Gilad Sha'ar and Naftali Frankel, who were abducted in the West Bank on 12 June 2014.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203659","203659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65490","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received about the imprisonment of the Bahrain 13.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203694","203694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65491","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received about the reasons for the imprisonment of the Bahrain 13.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203713","203713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65492","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with his Bahraini counterpart the release of the Bahrain 13.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203714","203714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65493","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many civil servants employed through his Department's graduate fast track scheme between 1 June 2004 and 1 June 2014 were educated at (a) private and (b) state schools.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203803","203803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65494","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the current political situation in Lesotho.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203738","203738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65495","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to prevent violence against women in the conflict-affected states of South Sudan.","Biography information for Sir Tony Baldry","Sir Tony Baldry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203766","203766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65496","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 29 October 2013, Official Report, column 411W, on Zimbabwe: pension payments, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that British nationals in Zimbabwe receive their pensions.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203821","203821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65497","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with Public Health England and NHS England on measures to ensure early diagnosis of rare cancers in the last (a) six and (b) 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203856","203856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65498","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the recommendations of the Bradley Report five years on, published in June 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203857","203857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65499","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the rate of obesity-related liver disease among adults was in the most recent period for which figures are available in each clinical commissioning group area.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203858","203858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65500","2014-07-08","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department has allocated to Public Health England and NHS England for promotion of early detection for rare cancers in the last (a) six and (b) 12 months.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203855","203855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65501","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the potential long-term costs to the NHS in England of un-managed (a) coeliac disease and (b) other nutritional disorders.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203846","203846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65502","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the potential cost savings to the NHS of pharmacy-led gluten-free prescribing schemes; and if his Department will issue guidance on such schemes.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203847","203847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65503","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to encourage the roll out of pharmacy-led gluten-free prescribing schemes in England.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203848","203848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65504","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will establish a national register of people with coeliac disease in England.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203849","203849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65505","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people of each gender, age bracket and household income bracket had diagnosed coeliac disease in England in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203850","203850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65506","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding per capita NHS England has allocated to each clinical commissioning group in Yorkshire and the Humber for 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203697","203697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65507","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which facilities patients of Winterborne View were transferred on that hospital's closure; and in which facilities those patients are now.","Biography information for Margot James","Margot James","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203622","203622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65508","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) non-patient egg donors and (b) egg-share donors were admitted to hospital for ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Mrs Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203642","203642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65509","2014-07-07","Department of Health","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any specialist trust hospitals currently have a deficit.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203705","203705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65510","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the minimum income threshold requirement on pensioners who wish to sponsor their partner's visa to settle in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Shaun Woodward","Mr Shaun Woodward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203685","203685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65511","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the change was in number of (a) part-time and (b) full-time staff in passport offices between 1 May 2014 and 1 July 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203704","203704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65512","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many failed asylum seekers have (a) been deported and (b) voluntarily returned to Somalia in each of the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203641","203641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65513","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department makes reasonable adjustments to require the needs of individuals with learning difficulties who want to apply for citizenship but are unable to pass the Life in the UK test.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203669","203669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65514","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the NSPCC's Order in Court Campaign seeking changes to the way the criminal justice system treats children.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203700","203700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65515","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of student visa applicants who illegally gained entry to the UK as a result of fraudulent language testing in the last 10 years; and how many of these applicants have now been removed from the UK.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203628","203628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65516","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the costs of identifying and removing student visa applicants who entered the country illegally as a result of fraudulent language testing.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203631","203631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65517","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what performance indicators for the renewal of existing passports were met by each passport office  administrative centre in (a) Scotland, (b) Wales, (c) Northern Ireland and (d) England in (i) 2009, (ii) 2010, (iii) 2011, (iv) 2012, (v) 2013 and (vi) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203716","203716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65518","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many female victims of (a) grevious bodily harm and (b) actual bodily harm there were (i) of each age and (ii) in each ward in the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203733","203733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65519","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to inform people whose entry clearance applications are on hold because of investigation into their Test of English for International Communication qualifications about (a) the fact that this is the case and (b) any action they can take to continue their entry clearance applications.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203778","203778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65520","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many illegal immigrants have been sent back from the UK to their country of origin in each calendar year since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203741","203741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65521","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in which countries her Department is investigating the Test of English for International Communication language test certificates from Educational Testing Service and the individuals who have provided them as part of the evidence in their visa applications.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203776","203776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65522","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that the Government regulates commercial companies providing evidence required in immigration applications and that such companies are not open to corruption.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203777","203777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65523","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have been returned for the UK to the last safe country they left under the Dublin II Regulation in each calendar year since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203740","203740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65524","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 30 April 2014, Official Report, column 717W, on human trafficking, whether the Salvation Army shares with her Department information on the town and shelter in which each victim is placed and whether the victim has a conclusive grounds decision.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203854","203854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65525","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people who have applied for entry clearance as (a) students and (b) family members of settled people including evidence of their knowledge of the English language through a Test of English for International Communication (TOEIC) certificate obtained through Educational Testing Service and whose applications are on hold while their right to hold that qualification is tested.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203775","203775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65526","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 30 April 2014, Official Report, column 717W, on human trafficking, how her Department gathers information to ensure that victims are safe once they have left the support service, if the town in which they have been placed is withheld on safety grounds.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203853","203853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65527","2014-07-07","Home Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applicants for a UK passport have paid an upgrade fee to fast-track their application after having submitted that application at a passport office at each such office and in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Shaun Woodward","Mr Shaun Woodward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203852","203852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65528","2014-07-07","Department for International Development","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure fair and efficient distribution of international aid in South Sudan.","Biography information for Sir Tony Baldry","Sir Tony Baldry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203765","203765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65529","2014-07-07","Department for International Development","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to promote the development of concentrated solar power in Iraq.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203819","203819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65530","2014-07-07","Department for International Development","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will take steps to promote collaboration between UK companies and the government of Iraq on development of solar technology to power desalination plants to provide clean drinking water to areas of shortage in that country.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203820","203820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65531","2014-07-07","Department for International Development","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2014, Official Report, column 416W, on Uganda, to which human rights organisations her Department is stepping up to support; and what form that support will take.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203718","203718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65532","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeals in social security tribunals in which the appellant was (a) represented and (b) not represented were successful in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203715","203715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65533","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people served as magistrates in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203730","203730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65534","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2014, Official Report, column 580W, on evidence in court, for what reason HM Courts and Tribunal Service (HMCTS) does not hold data on the number of child witnesses summoned to give evidence in court; and if he will request HMCTS to do so in future.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203723","203723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65535","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the savings from a residence test for claimants of legal aid.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203695","203695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65536","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for legal aid were made in cases relating to homicide in each of the last three years; and how many of those applications were successful.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203661","203661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65537","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when community rehabilitation companies are planned to begin providing post-release supervision to offenders serving sentences of under 12 months in prison.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203845","203845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65538","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training prison officers receive to enable them to detect incidents of sexual assault inside prison.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203841","203841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65539","2014-07-07","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times prison officers confiscated illegally brewed alcohol in each prison in England and Wales in each month in 2013.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203774","203774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65540","2014-07-07","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether her Department issues advice to officials on personal security; and when this advice was last updated.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203619","203619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65541","2014-07-07","Northern Ireland Office","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many civil servants employed through the Northern Ireland graduate fast track scheme between 1 June 2004 and 1 June 2014 were educated at (a) private and (b) state schools.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203799","203799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65542","2014-07-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recent assessment the Committee has made of the adequacy of the budget of the Electoral Commission for (a) advertising and (b) the functioning of the Commission.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203629","203629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65543","2014-07-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what role the Electoral Commission has in promoting political engagement; and what assessment the Commission has made of the contribution of ward level data or voter turnout at general elections to monitoring political engagement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203630","203630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65544","2014-07-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many electors have registered online since the introduction of online registration; and what steps the Electoral Commission is taking to encourage online registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203675","203675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65545","2014-07-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how much the Electoral Commission has spent on public awareness campaigns on the change from household to individual electoral registration; and what assessment the Commission has made of the effectiveness of those campaigns.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203676","203676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65546","2014-07-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of public awareness of the change from household to individual electoral registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203677","203677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65547","2014-07-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, for what reason the Electoral Commission first decided to undertake research into the completeness of the electoral register; and why further work on this issue has now been commissioned.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203678","203678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65548","2014-07-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the effect of the removal of electors who failed to register under individual electoral registration before 1 December 2015 on the next boundary review.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203679","203679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65549","2014-07-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2014, Official Report, column 613W, on electoral register: young people, what the EC's policy is on publishing data which it holds but has not commissioned.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203831","203831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65550","2014-07-07","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-07-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2014, Official Report, column 613W, on electoral register, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the accuracy of two separate pilot schemes which data mined Student Loans Company data.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203837","203837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65551","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to make the Fleet Driver Trainer register mandatory for paid vocational driver training.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203836","203836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65552","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to introduce mandatory regulation of B+E driving instructors.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203832","203832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65553","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what awareness activities the Maritime and Coastguard Agency has undertaken among (a) UK ship owners, (b) owners of UK flagged vessels and (c) the European shipping industry on regulations under Part 5 of the Equality Act 2010 to prevent differential pay rates for seafarers from countries in the European Economic Area since 1 August 2011.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203770","203770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65554","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the enforcement of the regulations under Part 5 of the Equality Act 2010 to prevent differential pay rates for seafarers from countries in the European Economic Area on vessels registered under Category 1 and Category 2 Red Ensign Group registries.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203773","203773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65555","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of vessels that have de-flagged from the Red Ensign Group where the shipowner cited the regulations under Part 5 of the Equality Act 2010 to prevent differential pay rates for seafarers from countries in the European Economic Area as the motivating factor in each year since 1 August 2011.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203772","203772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65556","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many contraventions of the regulations under Part 5 of the Equality Act 2010 preventing differential pay rates for seafarers from countries in the European Economic Area have been investigated by the Maritime and Coastguard Agency since 1 August 2011; and what the (a) outcome and (b) flag of each vessel was in each such investigation.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203768","203768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65557","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what enforcement activity the Maritime and Coastguard Agency has undertaken of the regulations under Part 5 of the Equality Act 2010 to prevent differential pay rates for seafarers from countries in the European Economic Area since 1 August 2011.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203769","203769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65558","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2014, Official Report, column 148W, to the hon. Member for Rochford and Southend East, on driving, when he plans to publish the findings from the focus groups with parents, young people and employers.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203851","203851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65559","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether levels of staffing and training at the Maritime and Coastguard Agency Maritime Operations Centre at Fareham are in line with the targets in the original proposals in the Coastguard Reform programme.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203794","203794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65560","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of staff currently employed at the Maritime and Coastguard Agency Maritime Operations Centre at Fareham have (a) received the amount of training required and (b) attained the level of qualification required in order to carry out their duties when the centre takes on its full operational responsibiliteis in December 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203791","203791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65561","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2014, Official Report, column 363W, on the Maritime and Coastguard Agency: Fareham, what discussions he has had in the last six months with external stakeholders on the staffing and training levels required for the Maritime and Coastguard Agency Maritime Operations Centre at Fareham to be fully operational.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203790","203790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65562","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what levels of staffing the Maritime and Coastguard Agency  expects to be in place at Martime and Coastguard Agency Maritime Operations Centre at Fareham in (a) September 2014, (b) November 2014, (c) January 2015 and (d) March 2015.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203792","203792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65563","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many coastguards have left the service since the Coastguard Reform programme began; and how many new entrants to the Coastguard service there have been in that period.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203793","203793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65564","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the three most recent (a) traffic counts, (b) speed measurements and (c) weight-of-vehicles measurements are from the B3006 Selborne Road between the A31 at Alton and the A3 Ham Barn roundabout.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203829","203829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65565","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish before the locus standi hearings the reasons for each challenge by HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203671","203671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65566","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he or any minister approved or commented on decisions to challenge the locus standi of any petitioner against the Hybrid Bill for Phase 1 of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203670","203670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65567","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which (a) Ministers in his Department, (b) officials in his Department and (c) HS2 Ltd personnel have attended meetings with the China Development Bank.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203674","203674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65568","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish all the responses to the petition response documents to petitions on High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203672","203672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65569","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish all documents exchanged between the Government and the China Development Bank mentioning or concerning High Speed 2 or associated development or works.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203673","203673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65570","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when discussions were held between PwC and the Law Society, Royal Institute of Chartered Surveyors, Council for Mortgages Lenders, National Association of Estate Agents and the Valuation Office Agency on the property bond prior to publication of the report, Analysis and advisory work on a potential property bond scheme for property owners affected by plans for HS2 dated March 2014 and published by HS2 Ltd as part of the response to the 2013 consultation on compensation.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203648","203648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65571","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many early access agreements have been issued in the High Speed 2 (Phase 1) process in each affected postcode and constituency since February 2014.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203650","203650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65572","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many blight notices have been (a) served on HS2 Ltd and (b) accepted in each affected postcode and constituency.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203649","203649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65573","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps his Department has taken to support regional air links with Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203621","203621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65574","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was paid to PwC for its report, Analysis and advisory work on a potential property bond scheme for property owners affected by plans for HS2 dated March 2014 and published by HS2 Ltd as part of the response to the 2013 consultation on compensation.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203647","203647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65575","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many requests for additional land have been served in each affected postcode and constituency by HS2 Ltd which require additional provision to the High Speed Rail (London-West Midlands) Bill to be deposited since February 2014.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203651","203651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65576","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what agricultural land in each affected postcode area and constituency has been purchased by HS2 Ltd in safeguarded areas on the route of Phase 1 or Phase 2 of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203652","203652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65577","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what records are kept of the concentrations of identified toxic chemicals in a fume event in each of the principal classes of civil aviation airliners operating within the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203637","203637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65578","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many additional seats his Department expects will be created on the West Coast Mainline by the conversion of one first class carriage to standard class following the award of the West Coast Mainline franchise to Virgin Trains.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203653","203653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65579","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any UK agencies or Departments conduct or have conducted research into the long-term consequences of repeated exposure of air crews to low levels of toxic fumes within civil aviation aircraft; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203644","203644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65580","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the additional capacity created by Virgin Trains converting one first class carriage to standard class on West Coast Mainline was factored into the HS2 business case issued in October 2013.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203654","203654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65581","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he or Ministers in his Department have had with (a) airlines and (b) organisations about fume events in UK airlines; and if he will take steps to improve the monitoring of the air quality in UK airliners.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203645","203645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65582","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many fume events were recorded in (a) UK civil aviation aircraft and (b) other aircraft using UK airports operating within the UK in the last 12 months; and which agency is responsible for recording these events.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203646","203646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65583","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions (a) Ministers in his Department and (b) representatives of High Speed 2 have had with the World Health Organisation on noise and High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203655","203655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65584","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the High Speed 2 Select Committee will have sight of the Major Project Authority's reports on High Speed 2 before it begins to hear petitions.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203656","203656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65585","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to respond further to the recommendations of the 138th Report of the Environmental Audit Committee, Session 2012-13, HC 1076, on HS2 and the Environment, so as to ensure that the Hybrid Bill process delivers the requirements of the Environment Impact Assessment Directive.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203657","203657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65586","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the development plans for Euston in the High Speed 2 (Phase 1) Hybrid Bill will be announced; and when the environmental statement consultation will be held.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203658","203658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65587","2014-07-07","Department for Transport","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what activities the Maritime and Coastguard Agency has undertaken among employers in the (a) UK, (b) European and (c) international shipping industry to ensure compliance with the regulations under Part 5 of the Equality Act 2010 to prevent differential pay rates for seafarers from countries in the European Economic Area since 1 August 2011.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203771","203771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65588","2014-07-07","Women and Equalities","2014-07-02","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, how much the Government has spent on the Think, Act, Report initiative.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203666","203666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65589","2014-07-07","Women and Equalities","2014-07-02","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what proportion of Named Day Written Questions were answered within the prescribed period in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203815","203815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65590","2014-07-07","Women and Equalities","2014-07-02","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what discussions the Government Equalities Office has had with LGBT mental health service providers in the last year.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203816","203816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65591","2014-07-07","Women and Equalities","2014-07-02","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, how many apprentices the Department has accepted as part of the Civil Service Fast Track Apprenticeship Scheme; and how many were (a) women and (b) men in each year since the scheme started.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203817","203817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65592","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) women and (b) men have applied for the new enterprise allowance.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203830","203830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65593","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many single parents have set up businesses using the new enterprise allowance scheme; and of these, what proportion are female.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203828","203828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65594","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of his Department's procurement expenditure was awarded to small and medium-sized enterprises in (a) direct procurement and (b) indirect procurement spend in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013; and what the projected proportion is for (A) 2014, (B) 2015 and (C) 2016.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203787","203787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65595","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effects of the introduction of the under-occupancy penalty on (a) the total housing benefit bill, (b) overcrowding, (c) homelessness and (d) housing mobility.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203739","203739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65596","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) women's and (b) men's business plans which were approved received a weekly allowance for 26 weeks of a total of £1,274 as part of the new enterprise allowance.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203824","203824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65597","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of the recipients of the new enterprise allowance who previously claimed (a) access to work benefits, (b) disability living allowance and (c) incapacity benefit were (i) male and (ii) female.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203822","203822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65598","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) women and (b) men are recipients of the new enterprise allowance.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203827","203827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65599","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what forecast his Department has made of the length of time each part of the claims process for personal independence payment (PIP) up to provision of accurate and targeted assessments will take; and what guidance his Department uses for a reasonable amount of time for an individual to wait for an accurate targeted assessment for PIP.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203706","203706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65600","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to deal with backlogs in personal independence payments.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203681","203681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65601","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects personal independence payment backlogs to be cleared.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203682","203682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65602","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will recruit additional staff to help clear personal independence payment backlogs.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203683","203683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65603","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent on housing benefit in (a) Cannock Chase and (b) Staffordshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Aidan Burley","Mr Aidan Burley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203634","203634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65604","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the written evidence from his Department to the Work and Pensions Committee of 20 October 2013 on child maintenance reform, when he will publish initial findings from the series of behaviour change trials undertaken by his Department to test different interventions aimed at addressing the barriers that prevent parents making regular payments of child maintenance.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203665","203665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65605","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he will bring into force section 40 of the Child Maintenance and Other Payments Act 2008.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203664","203664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65606","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what targets there are on increasing the number of women receiving the new enterprise allowance; and what progress has been made on these targets in the last year.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203807","203807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65607","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who received the new enterprise allowance have since reclaimed (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) income support as a lone parent and (c) employment and support allowance; and how many of these were (i) women and (ii) men.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203806","203806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65608","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to better identify personal independence payment claimaints who could be assessed solely on the basis of written evidence and without the need for face-to-face assessments.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203696","203696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65609","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2014, Official Report, column 431W, on jobseeker's allowance, how many jobseekers aged (a) between 18 and 21, (b) 22 and 24 and (c) 25 years and over were assessed for potential skills needs at the beginning of their claim to jobseeker's allowance in the most recent year for which data is available; and how many jobseekers in each category were assessed as having a skills need.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203725","203725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65610","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date he plans to publish the revised impact assessment for universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203726","203726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65611","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of his Department's contracts were awarded to small and medium- sized enterprises in (a) direct procurement spend and (b) indirect procurement spend in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013; and what the projected proportion is for (A) 2014, (B) 2015 and (C) 2016.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203717","203717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65612","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of the methods used to assess personal independence payment claims with the methods used to assess disability living allowance claims.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203684","203684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65613","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 June 2014, Official Report, column 282W, on universal credit, how much his Department spent on IT development and implementation for universal credit in 2013-14; and how much it expects to spend on such development and implementation in 2014-15.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203724","203724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65614","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether disabled people who go into debt because of long delays in processing their personal independence payment claims will be able to receive assistance from the Government to help pay off the interest on their debts.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203731","203731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65615","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how of his Department's contracts were awarded to small and medium sized enterprises in (a) direct procurement spend and (b) indirect procurement spend in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013; and what the projected number is for (A) 2014, (B) 2015 and (C) 2016.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203721","203721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65616","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many apprenticeships his Department and its agencies employed in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014; and how many he expects to employ in (i) 2015 and (ii) 2016.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203722","203722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65617","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment of the effects of the time taken to resolve claims for personal independence payments on claimants.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203698","203698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65618","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department took to reduce delays to personal independence payment (PIP) special rules claims; how long it took to resolve those delays; what steps he plans to take to reduce delays to PIP claims in the normal rules; and what estimate he has made of the time that will be taken to reduce those delays.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203699","203699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65619","2014-07-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new claims were paid in April 2014 for (a) jobseeker's allowance, (b) employment and support allowance, (c) income support, (d) housing benefit and (e) universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203728","203728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65623","2014-07-08","Attorney General","2014-07-02","To ask the Attorney General, what progress the Crown Prosecution Service has made in reducing costs.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904723","904723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/65779","2014-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2014-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to review sentences given for (a) murder and (b) manslaughter where the offence was a one-punch killing.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904724","904724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66226","2014-07-08","Attorney General","2014-07-02","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with the Director of the Services Prosecution Authority about its effectiveness in prosecuting rape and other sexual offences in the armed forces in the UK and overseas.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904727","904727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66227","2014-07-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-02","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues on further devolution of power from Westminster and Whitehall to the Humber region.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904720","904720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66228","2014-07-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-02","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what support the Government is giving to business growth opportunities in Medway.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904718","904718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66229","2014-07-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-02","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what discussions has he had with the Coventry and Warwickshire Local Enterprise Partnership on devolving powers and responsibilities from central government.","Biography information for Mark Pawsey","Mark Pawsey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904716","904716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66230","2014-07-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-02","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what recent assessment he has made of how City Deals are working.","Biography information for Chris White","Chris White","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904722","904722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66231","2014-07-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-02","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on the recall of hon. Members.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904715","904715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66232","2014-07-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-02","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what support the Government is giving to business growth opportunities in Newark.","Biography information for Robert Jenrick","Robert Jenrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904717","904717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/66233","2014-07-08","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-07-02","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what discussions he has had with the Leeds City Region Local Enterprise Partnership on devolving powers and responsibilities from central government.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 904719","904719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64871","2014-07-07","Attorney General","2014-07-01","To ask the Attorney General, what reports he has received of bribery of foreign officials in Tanzania by African Barrack Gold plc; and whether the SFO plans to investigate those reports.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203352","203352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64872","2014-07-07","Attorney General","2014-07-01","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2014, Official Report, column 389W, on the legal profession, what proportion of the money spent on consultancy fees by the Crown Prosecution Service was paid to which companies for what services in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014 to date.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203402","203402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64873","2014-07-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to create synergies with the European Alliance for Apprenticeships in improving work opportunities for young people.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203397","203397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64874","2014-07-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2014, Official Report, column 423W, on local enterprise partnerships, if he will make it his policy that his Department should record the gender composition of local enterprise partnerships boards for the purpose of strengthening equality impact assessments.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203386","203386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64875","2014-07-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2014, Official Report, column 461W, on asbestos, what training does the responsible person as a duty holder in line with Health and Safety Executive guidance receive in order to perform their duties.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203387","203387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64876","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2014, Official Report, columns 464W, on insolvency, how much the Insolvency Service's Redundancy Payments Service paid in relation to the collapse of Woolworths; and how much of that amount was paid in respect of protective awards.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203335","203335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64877","2014-07-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the statement of 7 April 2014, Official Report, columns 1-2WS, on higher education (student support), what new requirements will be put on higher education institutions; and what steps he is taking to ensure those institutions are prepared to fulfil these requirements.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203353","203353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64878","2014-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many complaints Trading Standards have received relating to the sale of unwell puppies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203196","203196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64879","2014-07-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to promote careers in the IT sector to young people.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203218","203218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64880","2014-07-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2014, Official Report, column 461W, on the British Business Bank, how many of the 44 people working in the Sheffield headquarters of the British Business Bank have been recruited since December 2013.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203232","203232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64881","2014-07-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, in light of the collapse of Comet and the recent industrial tribunal ruling on employee compensation, what plans he has to issue guidance on the law relating to the role of administrators in consulting employees regarding redundancy.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203234","203234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64882","2014-07-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the (a) average total debt, secured and unsecured, in debtor petition bankruptcies, (b)  average total debt, secured and unsecured, in creditor petition bankruptcies and (c) median unsecured debt in all bankruptcies was of individuals who filed for bankruptcy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203245","203245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64883","2014-07-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average total debt was of individuals who filed for a debt relief order in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203246","203246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64884","2014-07-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of ministerial replies sent to hon. Members in electronic form only.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203286","203286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64885","2014-07-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of research and development contracts undertaken by publicly-funded universities for private companies are covered by clauses that prohibit the publication of the research and development results on grounds of commercial confidentiality; and what proportion of such contracts are undertaken in facilities paid for by the public purse.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203269","203269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64886","2014-07-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2014, Official Report, column 461W, on asbestos, how often inspections for asbestos containing materials are carried out in buildings owned or managed by his Department.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203337","203337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64887","2014-07-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will estimate the total number of ministerial replies from his Department to hon. Members in a parliamentary session; and what proportion of such replies are sent (a) by letter and (b) by email.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203297","203297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64888","2014-07-03","Cabinet Office","2014-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of ministerial replies sent to hon. Members in electronic form only.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203285","203285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64889","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the difference is between standard security checks and developed vetting carried out in respect of officials employed in the Civil Service; how many officials in No. 10 Downing Street have been subject to (a) standard security clearance and (b) developed vetting; and what limitations are placed on officials in No. 10 Downing Street who have not undergone developed vetting.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203199","203199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64890","2014-07-03","Cabinet Office","2014-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the impact assessment for the Shared Services Connected Limited venture.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203200","203200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64892","2014-07-03","Cabinet Office","2014-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate the total number of ministerial replies from his Department to hon. Members in a parliamentary session; and what proportion of such replies are sent (a) by letter and (b) by email.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203298","203298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64893","2014-07-07","Cabinet Office","2014-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people over 50 years old are employed in each region and constituent part of the UK; and what proportion of people aged over 50 years old living in the region and constituent part do they represent in each such case.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203349","203349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64894","2014-07-03","HM Treasury","2014-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps HM Revenue and Customs is taking to ensure that public sector bodies do not underpay VAT.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203224","203224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64895","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to ensure that parents use their tax-free childcare accounts to pay for childcare; and what additional costs such checks will place on HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203316","203316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64896","2014-07-07","HM Treasury","2014-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what average value of tax credits were paid to claimants who were (a) out of work, (b) self-employed and (c) employed in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203325","203325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64897","2014-07-03","HM Treasury","2014-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Warrington North constituency were self-employed and in receipt of working tax credit in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203276","203276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64898","2014-07-03","HM Treasury","2014-07-01","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much Official Development Assistance was spent by each Government department in 2009-10 and in each year since (a) in cash terms, (b) at current prices and (c) as a proportion of Gross National Income.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203236","203236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64899","2014-07-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the potential effect of the Care Act 2014 on local authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203281","203281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64900","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects his Department to publish a consultation document on withdrawing permitted development rights for bookmakers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203326","203326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64901","2014-07-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the total number of ministerial replies from his Department to hon. Members in a parliamentary session; and what proportion of such replies are sent (a) by letter and (b) by email.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203299","203299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64902","2014-07-07","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many house purchases have been funded through the Help to Buy scheme in (a) Ribble Valley, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203332","203332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64903","2014-07-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons he reversed the appeal decision in Gateshead Borough, ref 2193211.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203360","203360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64904","2014-07-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what contact his officials have had with the European Parliament Working Group on Freedom of Religion or Belief in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203396","203396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64905","2014-07-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, by what process planning decisions can be reversed at the discretion of a court.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203429","203429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64906","2014-07-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to reduce bureaucratic obstacles to the flying of flags in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203415","203415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64907","2014-07-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate the total number of ministerial replies from his Department to hon. Members in a parliamentary session; and what proportion of such replies are sent (a) by letter and (b) by email.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203300","203300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64909","2014-07-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to introduce proposals for regulations or guidance to reduce the cost of the use of British mobile telephones roaming outside of the EU.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203267","203267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64910","2014-07-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Statistical Bulletin 6.02 on Accommodation will be published by the end of July 2014.","Biography information for Alison Seabeck","Alison Seabeck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203274","203274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64911","2014-07-07","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy formally to consult the residents of Marchwood, Hampshire, about the sale of the lease of land and facilities at the site of the military port; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203317","203317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64912","2014-07-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will estimate the total number of ministerial replies from his Department to hon. Members in a parliamentary session; and what proportion of such replies are sent (a) by letter and (b) by email.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203301","203301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64913","2014-07-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans his Department has to commemorate the 100th anniversary of the First Battle of the Marne between 5 and 12 September 2014.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203331","203331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64914","2014-07-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) sets of accounts will be audited and (b) value for money studies will be completed this calendar year by the International Board of Auditors of NATO; how many of these audits were completed in the first six months of the year; when NATO will publish these accounts and audit reports; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203405","203405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64915","2014-07-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State and Minister for International Security Strategy approved the proposals to limit contractor liability at HMNB Clyde to £100,000 despite the objection by the hon. Member for Newport West.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203416","203416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64916","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding was provided to each pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in Warrington in (A) cash terms and (B) at 2014 prices in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203329","203329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64917","2014-07-03","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will estimate the total number of ministerial replies from his Department to hon. Members in a parliamentary session; and what proportion of such replies are sent (a) by letter and (b) by email.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203302","203302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64918","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many meetings the Parliamentary Under-Secretary for Childcare and Early Years has had with parents of disabled children about improving access, affordability and quality of childcare for disabled children since he was appointed.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203388","203388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64919","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils who did not have a statement of special educational needs in each school achieved no qualifications by the end of key stage 4 in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203334","203334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64921","2014-07-03","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the time taken to adopt a child.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203216","203216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64922","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the UK's child protection legislation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Glenda Jackson","Glenda Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203198","203198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64923","2014-07-03","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment the Government has made of the impact on school budgets in 2016-17 of planned changes in pension and national insurance contributions.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203204","203204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64924","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the additional costs to (a) parents and (b) childcare providers of providing childcare for disabled children.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203315","203315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64925","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many nursery places were available in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203327","203327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64926","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the level of accessibility of childcare for disabled children; how many childcare settings of all types of provision provide places for disabled children; what proportion of disabled children are able to access early years provision; and how many disabled children access the free early years entitlement at (a) three and four years old and (b) two years old.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203321","203321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64927","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether all employees of his Department are required to return their departmental pass when they cease working for his Department.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203339","203339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64928","2014-07-03","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate he has made of the number of children in England starting primary school in September 2014 who have received a place at their first choice school.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203229","203229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64929","2014-07-03","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children are involved in the Challenge the Gap scheme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203230","203230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64930","2014-07-03","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary schools in (a) England and (b) Birmingham are taking part in the Challenge the Gap scheme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203231","203231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64931","2014-07-07","Department for Education","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in (a) Warrington and (b) Warrington North constituency received free school meals in each year since 1995-96.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203252","203252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64932","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the number of households who will receive assistance under (a) affordable warmth, (b) carbon savings community and (c) carbon saving target in (i) 2014-15, (ii) 2015-16 and (iii) 2016-17.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203283","203283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64933","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when his Department will publish its fuel poverty strategy.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203280","203280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64934","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the extent to which the UK's energy infrastructure was exposed to the recent Energetic Bear cyberattack.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203265","203265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64935","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of expenditure under (a) affordable warmth, (b) carbon savings community and (c) carbon saving target in (i) 2014-15, (ii) 2015-16 and (iii) 2016-17.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203284","203284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64936","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding his Department has allocated under the pioneer places programme.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203296","203296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64937","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which local authorities have received funding under the Green Deal Communities programme.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203290","203290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64938","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which local authorities have received funding under the pioneer places programme.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203293","203293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64939","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding has been allocated under the Green Deal Communities programme to date.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203291","203291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64940","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding has been allocated under the core cities energy efficiency programme.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203294","203294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64941","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which local authorities have received funding under the Core Cities Energy Efficiency programme.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203292","203292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64942","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the number of measures to be installed under (a) affordable warmth, (b) carbon savings community and (c) carbon saving target in (i) 2014-15, (ii) 2015-16 and (iii) 2016-17.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203282","203282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64943","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding has been (a) allocated and (b) spent on the Green Deal cashback incentive scheme to date.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203289","203289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64944","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 1247, on energy efficiency, what the evidential basis is for the statement that Green Deal assessments are stimulating action on energy efficiency.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203338","203338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64945","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 1252, on energy markets (competition), what estimate he has made of the level of fuel poverty under the low income high costs indicator in each year between 1997 and 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203336","203336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64946","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to reduce consumer energy prices in-line with changes in the wholesale market prices.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203217","203217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64947","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his contribution of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 1191, on energy prices, what the evidential basis is for his statement that the UK had the highest level of renewable investment in Europe in 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203381","203381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64948","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his contribution of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 1191, on energy prices, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Bloomberg new energy finance analysis.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203382","203382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64949","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his contribution of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 1191, on energy prices, what the evidential basis is for his statement that there was under-investment in the UK's energy infrastructure.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203383","203383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64950","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to his contribution of 18 June 2014, Official Report, column 1193, on energy prices, what assessment his Department has made of the rocket and feather effect in energy prices.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203384","203384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64951","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households have received free green deal assessments to date.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203361","203361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64952","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the number of landlords who have upgraded the energy efficiency of their properties to EPC rating E or higher in line with the Energy Act 2011 since the implementation of that Act.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203362","203362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64953","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the average annual saving to a household's energy bill from a (a) condensing gas boiler, (b) cavity wall insulation, (c) loft insulation, (d) solid wall insulation and (e) other forms of insulation.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203363","203363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64954","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the average saving on energy bills for households that have received measures under the Energy Company Obligation.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203366","203366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64955","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the average cost of a Green Deal assessment.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203367","203367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64956","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 1249, on low-carbon electricity projects, what the evidential basis is for the statement of the Minister of State for Energy and Climate Change that investment in low-carbon electricity projects has doubled during the current Parliament.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203376","203376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64957","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what financial support his Department has planned to allocate to (a) the Green Deal and (b) other domestic energy efficiency programmes for expenditure in (i) 2014-15, (ii) 2015-16, (iii) 2016-17 and (iv) any subsequent years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203368","203368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64958","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 1249, on low-carbon electricity projects, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Bloomberg analysis.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203377","203377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64959","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what financial support his Department allocated to (a) the Green Deal and (b) other domestic energy efficiency programmes in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203369","203369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64960","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households are forecast to be lifted from fuel poverty under the energy company obligation in each year between 2013 and 2017.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203356","203356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64961","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the number of households that have paid for a Green Deal assessment to date.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203370","203370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64962","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 1258, on energy security, on which process he calculated that there has been £45 billion of electricity investment since 2010.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203378","203378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64963","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department has spent on free Green Deal assessments for households to date.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203371","203371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64964","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what consumer research his Department has commissioned on (a) the Green Deal and (b) the Energy Company Obligation since 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203372","203372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64965","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 1258, on energy security, what the evidential basis is for his statement that the rate of investment in gas is increasing.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203379","203379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64966","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the evidential basis is for the statement in paragraph 2.1 of his Departmental annual report 2013-14, HC9, published on 26 June 2014, that investment in cleaner energy infrastructure will help support up to 250,000 jobs by 2020.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203357","203357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64967","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 1258, on energy security, what the evidential basis is for his statement that the rate of investment in renewables is increasing.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203380","203380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64968","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will estimate the total number of ministerial replies from his Department to hon. Members in a parliamentary session; and what proportion of such replies are sent (a) by letter and (b) by email.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203303","203303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/64969","2014-07-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to the Answer of 17 June 2013, Official Report, column 461W, on renewable energy, UIN 159722, if he will place in the Library a copy of the list of projects recorded on the renewable energy planning database since 1 January 2010 with the potential to generate 20MW or more cross-referenced with information provided by developers.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 203340","203340"
