"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175043","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department plans to fit Typhoon jets with the Brimstone missile; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221529","221529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175044","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2014 to Question 217205, if he will make it his Department's policy to collect and analyse data on the extent to which armed forces medical personnel are in breach of the single service harmony guidelines; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221530","221530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175045","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of Royal Navy personnel in each pinch point trade are exceeding their harmony guidelines.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221525","221525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175046","2015-01-26","Department for Education","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will list the top 20 local authority areas by proportion of pupils from maintained schools gaining admission to Russell Group universities, showing whether each authority is (a) selective (b) partially selective and (c) comprehensive for the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221664","221664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175047","2015-01-23","Department for Education","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of new childcare places that will be created through the Childcare Business Grant scheme in 2015-16.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221586","221586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175048","2015-01-23","Department for Education","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which organisations and individuals were consulted as part of her Department's review of asbestos policy in schools.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221608","221608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175049","2015-01-23","Department for Education","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's policy is on the use of asbestos in school buildings.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221609","221609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175050","2015-01-26","Department for Education","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will list all local authority areas in the (a) North West, (b) North East, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber, (d) West Midlands and (e) East Midlands from which 25 per cent or more of pupils from maintained schools secured admission to Russell Group universities, showing in each case whether the authority is (i) selective, (ii) partially selective and (iii) comprehensive for the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221665","221665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175051","2015-01-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require petrol wholesalers to publish the price at which they sell petrol; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221666","221666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175052","2015-01-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will take steps to ensure that both (a) Combined Heat and Power facilities where biogas production and combustion take place on the same site and (b) facilities that also produce biogas on the same site, but which generate their power from a combination of that biogas and some other energy source, receive equal treatment under the Government's proposal to amend the Renewable Heat Incentive Regulations.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221585","221585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175053","2015-01-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans he has to make provision for alternate means of electricity generation (a) to replace ageing nuclear power stations and (b) to meet the reduction in carbon emissions required by the Industrial Emissions Directive.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221520","221520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175054","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans the Government has to improve protection for ancient woodland in (a) England and (b) Staffordshire.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221541","221541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175055","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support her Department is giving to Natural England for its work to update the Ancient Woodland Inventory in (a) England and (b) Staffordshire.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221542","221542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175056","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to (a) return control of agricultural policy to member states and (b) reduce subsidies under the Common Agricultural Policy.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221523","221523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175057","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of milk sold in Britain comes from intensively farmed cows.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221564","221564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175058","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will take steps to ensure that all milk labelling clearly states the farming methods used in production of that milk.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221565","221565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175059","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to encourage more children to use national parks.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221567","221567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175060","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received from nature bodies about the introduction of a Nature and Well-Being Bill.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221568","221568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175061","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what targets the National Wildlife Crime Unit has been set for dealing with wildlife cybercrime.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221569","221569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175062","2015-01-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to support farmers in the Yorkshire and Humberside region.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221488","221488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175063","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page six of her Department's policy brief, How increased Connectivity is Boosting Prospects of Rural Areas, published in December 2014, what estimate she has made of the proportion of areas which will not be covered by superfast broadband by 2017 that are (a) rural and (b) coastal.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221620","221620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175064","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page seven of her Department's policy brief, How increased Connectivity is Boosting Prospects of Rural Areas, published in December 2014, what assessment she has made of the effect of UK RuralSkills on farmers' management and business skills to date.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221621","221621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175065","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of people who will (a) leave and (b) join the labour market in rural areas before 2025.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221619","221619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175066","2015-01-23","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page six of his Department's policy brief, How increased Connectivity is Boosting Prospects of Rural Areas, published in December 2014, how much of the £15 billion investment in road infrastructure will be used to promote rural connectivity.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221625","221625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175067","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page seven of her Department's policy brief, How increased Connectivity is Boosting Prospects of Rural Areas, published in December 2014, what assessment she has made of the effect of the Skills and Knowledge Transfer Programme on business people in rural areas to date.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221622","221622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175068","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page seven of her Department's policy brief, How increased Connectivity is Boosting Prospects of Rural Areas, published in December 2014, what assessment she has made of the effect of the International Food and Drink Action Plan on the level of (a) food and (b) drink exports to date.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221623","221623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175069","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page seven of her Department's policy brief, How increased Connectivity is Boosting Prospects of Rural Areas, published in December 2014, what assessment she has made of the effect of Visit England's marketing campaigns on tourism to rural areas to date.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221624","221624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175070","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the mandate of the UN Interim Security Force for Abyei to protect Ngok Dinka returnees while they gather grass to rebuild homes in that region.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221634","221634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175071","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has recieved about the imprisonment and welfare of (a) Dr Abduljalil Alsingace and (b) other political prisoners; and what discussions he has had with his counterparts in Bahrain about those matters.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221611","221611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175072","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many foreign UK-based and locally-engaged staff of his Department worked (a) part-time and (b) full-time on tackling the illegal wildlife trade in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14 and (v) 2014-15 to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221604","221604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175073","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on the implementation of commitments made by (a) the UK and (b) partner nations at the London Conference on the illegal wildlife trade in February 2014.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221605","221605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175074","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what funds his Department allocated to tackling the illegal wildlife trade in each financial year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221602","221602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175075","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which British embassies and high commissions include tackling the illegal wildlife trade in their business plans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221603","221603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175076","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of the illegal wildlife trade on UK national security.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221601","221601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175077","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of links between the illegal wildlife trade and (a) conflict and (b) terrorism in Africa; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221600","221600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175078","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department last raised human rights concerns at ministerial level with the government of Turkmenistan.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221573","221573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175079","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Turkmenistan remains a country of concern in relation to human rights; and when his Department's next annual Human Rights and Democracy Report will be published.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221574","221574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175080","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he next plans to convene his Human Rights Advisory Group.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221575","221575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175081","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to change the number of UK-based and locally-engaged staff of his Department working on tackling illegal wildlife trade; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221599","221599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175082","2015-01-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of prospects for bilateral ceasefires in the Colombian peace process.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221597","221597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175083","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of Bahrain on the detention and treatment of political prisoners.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221554","221554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175084","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the capacity of the Economic Community of West African States to tackle the threat from Boko Haram.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221551","221551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175085","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on ratification of the EU-Turkmenistan Partnership and Cooperation Agreement.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221571","221571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175086","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received about allegations of violence by Soco International in Virunga National Park.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221548","221548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175087","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on requiring benchmarks for human rights set by the European Parliament to be met by the government of Turkmenistan before the UK ratifies the EU-Turkmenistan Partnership and Cooperation Agreement.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221572","221572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175088","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will press the government of Turkmenistan to fulfil specific benchmarks set by the European Parliament as a condition of upgraded relations with the EU in the form of a Partnership and Cooperation Agreement.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221570","221570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175089","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to bring about reform of the two seat operation of the European Parliament.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221504","221504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175090","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote fundamental freedoms in Saudi Arabia and to dissuade the government of that country from misusing anti-terrorism laws.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221519","221519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175091","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the accession of the Palestinian Authority to the International Criminal Court on the prospects for further negotiations between Israel and that Authority.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221518","221518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175092","2015-01-23","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress has been made on securing an emergency brake for any member state on future EU legislation affecting financial services.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221522","221522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175093","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received on the effect on patients and NHS Trusts and foundation trusts of the 3.8 per cent efficiency factor proposed in the Monitor and NHS England document, 2015/16 National Tariff Payment System: a consultation notice.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221510","221510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175094","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many elected operations were cancelled by Warrington and Halton NHS Foundation Trust in (a) November and (b) December 2014.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221505","221505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175095","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with (a) the Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government about the effect of changes to local authority budgets on funding for adult social care.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221514","221514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175096","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on quality and access to care of failure by NHS providers and commissioners to achieve the 3.8 per cent efficiency factor proposed in 2015/16 National Tariff Payment System: a consultation notice.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221511","221511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175097","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many delayed discharges there were from (a) St Helens and Knowsley Hospitals Trust and (b) Warrington and Halton Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221512","221512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175098","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses have left the NHS before normal retirement age in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221513","221513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175099","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has discussed with Ministers in the devolved administrations the merits of extending to their jurisdictions the recently-announced programme to screen newborn babies in England for four rare genetic disorders.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221553","221553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175100","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department conducted its most recent study into the potency of skunk cannabis; and if he will commission a new potency study with respect to that drug.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221547","221547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175101","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2014 to Question 208139, when he expects the results of the Health Protection Agency findings on the health effects of emissions from municipal waste incinerators to be published.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221507","221507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175102","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to GPs about the prescription of anti-depressants and the need to reduce the risk of overdose.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221508","221508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175103","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which bodies his Department and NHS England consulted before deciding to remove specialised commissioned service status from dialysis and passing down the commissioning of that treatment to clinical commissioning group level.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221559","221559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175104","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what basis his Department and NHS England decided to remove the specialised commissioned service status from dialysis.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221560","221560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175105","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what parliamentary oversight there is of changes to the list of the specialised commissioned services within the NHS in England.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221561","221561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175106","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS paid translators in the last financial year.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221496","221496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175107","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with local authorities in Greater Manchester concerning changes to capacity in adult social care.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221479","221479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175108","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what contingency plans he has for hospitals in Greater Manchester failing to meet the Government's A&E target.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221480","221480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175109","2015-01-29","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on (a) all drugs, (b) cancer drugs and (c) drugs funded through the Cancer Drug Fund in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221615","221615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175110","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of potential financial loss to the NHS arising from failure to claim reimbursement from insurance companies.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221606","221606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175111","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that the NHS is maximising its entitlement to reimbursement from insurance companies.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221607","221607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175112","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS staff earn less than the living wage.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221640","221640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175113","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the medical questionnaire completed by Pauline Cafferkey on her return to the UK from Sierra Leone asked whether aspirin, paracetamol or ibuprofen had been taken prior to her temperature being tested.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221651","221651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175114","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether Ministers or officials in his Department has identified cause to refer for investigation the conduct of any UK medical staff returning from West Africa.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221652","221652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175115","2015-01-26","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on whether Pauline Cafferkey told any member of the medical team on the returning aeroplane from Sierra Leone that she felt unwell.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221650","221650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175116","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) acknowledgement and (b) information about action taken a victim receives following a report to Action Fraud.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221638","221638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175117","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many roles were added to the Tier 2 shortage occupation list in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013 and (e) 2014.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221579","221579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175118","2015-01-26","Home Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to publish the findings of the follow-up audit of reports made under Rule 35 of the Detention Centre Rules 2001.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221493","221493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175119","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to exercise a block opt-out from the 131 pre-Lisbon EU policing and criminal justice laws.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221552","221552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175120","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to enquiries emailed to her office by the constituent of the hon. Member for Chesterfield, Gillian Norman, on 28 September, 13 October, 21 October 2014 and 9 January 2015 concerning allegations of heavy-handed treatment by security officials at Manchester Airport.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221566","221566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175121","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will update the FRANK website to include information on skunk cannabis and links between that drug and psychosis.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221540","221540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175122","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers were returned to their country of origin in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221539","221539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175123","2015-01-26","Home Office","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the involvement of psychologists is in the Government's de-radicalisation programme.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221489","221489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175124","2015-01-23","Department for International Development","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make representations to the World Food Programme requesting it to consult South Sudanese members of AJOC and Dinka Ngok residents in Abyei about its report entitled, Abyei Integrated Rapid Food Security and Nutrition Assessment, and to revise the report and its recommendations in the light of their responses.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221583","221583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175125","2015-01-23","Department for International Development","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has funded any aid or development programmes in (a) Al Dayiri, (b) El Tashween, (c) Makenis, (d) Al Askar, (e) Um Kanshel, (f) El Ishlag, (g) Um Kheir, (h) El Magboul, (i) Faroug, (j) Dumboloya, (k) Antila and (l) Mukhtar locations in northern Abyei carried out or scheduled since July 2014.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221633","221633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175126","2015-01-23","Department for International Development","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether armed Misseriya or Twic militias have benefited from her Department's aid programmes targeted at northern areas of Abyei where Dinka Ngok are not present.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221632","221632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175127","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total value of fines was (a) issued by the courts and (b) collected in 2013-14 in each local criminal justice board area.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221639","221639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175128","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the future demand for prison places in the West Midlands; and what assessment he has made of the capacity of West Midlands prisons to meet that future demand.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221671","221671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175129","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drug seizures were made in each West Midlands prison in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221672","221672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175130","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the recidivism rate was of prisoners who were released from prisons in the (a) West Midlands and (b) UK in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221673","221673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175131","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers staffed prisons in the West Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221674","221674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175132","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to limit prisoners' access to (a) legal drugs and (b) other psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221487","221487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175133","2015-01-26","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review the powers of the Court of Protection; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221546","221546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175134","2015-01-26","Prime Minister","2015-01-21","To ask the Prime Minister, what provision was made in the arrangements for the Iraq Inquiry to deal with a situation arising from the incapacity of a member of the inquiry panel.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221598","221598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175135","2015-01-26","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy that motorists pay the same rate of vehicle tax whether or not they pay by direct debit in instalments.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221596","221596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175136","2015-01-23","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for how many months since 2010 the role of Chief Scientific Adviser for his Department has been vacant.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221582","221582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175137","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much the Government has provided to Surrey County Council to tackle potholes in each financial year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221595","221595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175138","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the terms and conditions for the newly-appointed HS2 Ltd Residents Commissioner.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221593","221593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175139","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the causes of train delays on the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises that are caused as a result of (a) driver shortages and (b) guards not being present.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221614","221614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175140","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings he has had with Network Rail since Christmas 2014 to discuss the quality of rail services in South London (a) in general and (b) relating to London Bridge and Victoria stations.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221644","221644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175141","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has had discussions with Transport for London in the last 12 months on that body taking a greater role in the operation of inner suburban train services.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221645","221645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175142","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Southern rail is complying with the terms of its franchise; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221643","221643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175143","2015-01-23","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many platforms at stations need further improvements to accommodate 12-carriage trains on the railway lines that run through (a) Eltham, (b) Plumstead and (c) New Eltham; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221618","221618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175144","2015-01-23","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many 12-carriage trains Southeastern rail has provided since work was completed to extend the platforms through (a) Eltham, (b) Plumstead and (c) New Eltham; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221617","221617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175145","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when and for what reasons the decision was made to remove Thameslink trains to Dartford via Lewisham from the timetable following the completion of the improvements at London Bridge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221653","221653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175146","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department holds on the performance of (a) the Southern rail franchise, (b) the Southeastern rail franchise and (c) services on the Thameslink route.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221642","221642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175147","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings he has had in the last 12 months with representatives of rail franchises operating in South London.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221641","221641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175148","2015-01-23","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 220504, if he will provide information equivalent to that in the Answer for the other 58 parliamentary constituencies within Scotland, for the period 1 January 2014 to 20 January 2015.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221635","221635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175149","2015-01-23","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 220504, what the average number of postponements of driving and motorcycle tests was in parliamentary constituencies in Scotland between 1 January 2014 and 20 January 2015; what the principal reasons for postponement were; and what average length of time it took for tests to be rescheduled.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221636","221636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175150","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost of alterations to the rail lines to enable Wimbledon trains from Brighton to pass through Blackfriars Station to Bedford and St Pancras was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221655","221655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175151","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consultation was held before the decision was made to remove Thameslink trains to Dartford via Lewisham from the timetable following the completion of the improvements at London Bridge; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221654","221654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175152","2015-01-23","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to integrate the London Gateway port with inland transport modes.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221626","221626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175153","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many train services were discontinued as a consequence of the decision to enable Wimbledon trains from Brighton to pass through Blackfriars Station to Bedford and St Pancras; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221669","221669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175154","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Thameslink trains will be formed of 12 carriages following the completion of improvements at London Bridge on services via (a) Wimbledon and (b) Lewisham; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221670","221670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175155","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of changes to revenue protection and collection on the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises in the last five years.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221500","221500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175156","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of changes in levels of anti-social behaviour and crime on the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises in the last five years.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221501","221501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175157","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the (a) number of women employed in the Merchant Navy and (b) positions they hold.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221497","221497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175158","2015-01-23","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2015 to Questions 219215 and 219414, what assessment he has made of (a) the comparative proportions of public and private sector investment in the railway, (b) the relationship between rail passenger journey growth and macroeconomic factors and (c) the proportion of revenue paid by private train companies to the public purse ultimately derived from passenger fares, since rail privatisation.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221531","221531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175159","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the use of interrupter devices to falsify driving records.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221498","221498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175160","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assistance the Government provides for freight operators who want to adapt their operations to low emissions restrictions.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221499","221499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175161","2015-01-23","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what instructions he has given to HS2 Ltd on minimising transport disruption in Buckinghamshire during the construction of High Speed 2 (a) affecting the emergency services and (b) generally; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221477","221477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175162","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on revenue protection and collection of the introduction of driver-only operation on the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221502","221502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175163","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on revenue protection and collection of station staffing proposals for the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221503","221503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175164","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the statement in his Department's strategy for the publication of information about the 2012 scheme administered by the Child Maintenence Service (CMS) that the strategic management information reporting capability of a new Data Warehouse would be available from 2014, what the latest timetable is for the managed process of the release of fully assured statistics on the performance of the CMS.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221675","221675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175165","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many deafblind recipients of Access to Work support have had a reduction in their support package in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221577","221577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175166","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how often his Department reviews the cost and availability of technologies that support deafblind people to work; and whether Access to Work applies a limit to the amount of funding available for assistance technologies in support packages.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221578","221578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175167","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government has taken to gain greater control over the type and amount of benefits paid to EU nationals who reside in the UK but are not in employment.","Biography information for Mike Weatherley","Mike Weatherley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221521","221521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175168","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it remains his estimate that the number of claimants of universal credit will reach 100,000 by May 2015, as forecast on page 30 of his Department's document Universal Credit at work, published in October 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221544","221544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175169","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what further plans he has to reduce youth unemployment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221545","221545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175170","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the number of people affected by the under-occupancy penalty in Halton Borough council area.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221506","221506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175171","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2015 to Question 220893, which aspects of the new closer working between jobcentres and Work Programme prime providers are improving relationships between them.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221549","221549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175172","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2015 to Question 220893, when the new closer working approach was introduced; and what figures he plans to use to measure that approach's effectiveness.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221550","221550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175173","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of Access to Work support packages are deafblind; and what the average cost to the public purse is of packages for those people.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221576","221576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175174","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will reduce the benefit cap further.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221478","221478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175837","2015-01-27","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of training available to staff at HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907254","907254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175838","2015-01-27","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of small business start-ups on the wider economy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907256","907256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175839","2015-01-27","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of recipients of tax credits are in employment.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907257","907257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175840","2015-01-27","HM Treasury","2015-01-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of falling oil prices on the rural economy.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907253","907253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174644","2015-01-22","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-20","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2015 to Question 219123, what proportion of people who initiated an online registration failed to finish that registration; and what information he holds on the main reason for failure to conclude the registration process.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221348","221348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174645","2015-01-22","Attorney General","2015-01-20","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 15 December 2014 to Question 218070, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in shoplifting between 2010 and 2014.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221402","221402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174646","2015-01-22","Attorney General","2015-01-20","To ask the Attorney General, how many and what proportion of the Law Officers Departments' executive board were educated at (a) private and (b) state school.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221403","221403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174647","2015-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will undertake a review of the use of the Enterprise Finance Guarantee scheme in response to the review announced by the Royal Bank of Scotland of its own practices relating to that scheme.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221411","221411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174648","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the Council of the European Union will act by unanimity or qualified majority when adopting decisions authorising the EU's (a) signature and, if relevant, provisional application and (b) conclusions of the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221468","221468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174649","2015-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what factors the Insolvency Service takes into account when reviewing the fees it charges.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221389","221389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174650","2015-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how regularly the Insolvency Service reviews its fees.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221391","221391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174651","2015-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to create jobs in Huddersfield.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221390","221390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174652","2015-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on what basis the Insolvency Service calculates the fees charged in cases of liquidation.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221371","221371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174653","2015-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much and what proportion of land was registered in Wales in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221369","221369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174654","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to replace the Ordnance Survey's aerial photography programme with the licensing of such photographs from other agencies and businesses; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Arbuthnot of Edrom","Mr James Arbuthnot","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221333","221333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174655","2015-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much research and development funding has been directed towards the oil and gas sector since 2010; and what proportion that is of all UK research and development funding in that period.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mr Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221347","221347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174656","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the Council of the European Union acted by unanimity or qualified majority when adopting the negotiating directives for the EU for the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221469","221469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174657","2015-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on funding for (a) University Centre Shrewsbury and (b) other new universities.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221294","221294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174658","2015-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the economic benefit of universities to the region in which they are located.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221295","221295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174659","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the cost was of the Ordnance Survey's aerial photography programme in each of the last five years; and if he will make an estimate of the potential annual cost of licensing such photographs from other agencies and businesses.","Biography information for Lord Arbuthnot of Edrom","Mr James Arbuthnot","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221332","221332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174660","2015-01-22","Cabinet Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he has taken to ensure that MyCSP tackles the reported backlog of problems and queries from individuals, and to ensure that payments to pensioners or their dependents will still be made promptly.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221438","221438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174661","2015-01-23","HM Treasury","2015-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to introduce a transferable tax allowance between married couples.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221471","221471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174662","2015-01-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the final recipient of Restoration Lump Sum was (a) private companies or (b) the public purse.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221386","221386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174663","2015-01-22","HM Treasury","2015-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many calls to HM Revenue and Customs helplines from numbers in (a) England and (b) the Bedford 01234 area were answered in (i) less than two minutes, (ii) between two and five minutes, (iii) between six and 10 minutes, (iv) between 10 and 20 minutes, (v) between 20 and 30 minutes, (vi) between 30 and 45 minutes, (vii) between 45 minutes and one hour, (viii) more than an hour after the start of the call in each of the last six months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221351","221351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174664","2015-01-22","HM Treasury","2015-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the savings to his Department arising from the closure of HM Revenue and Customs facilities in Rhyl.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221367","221367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174665","2015-01-22","HM Treasury","2015-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of personal allowance increases on those in work.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221327","221327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174666","2015-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress the Government has made on supporting businesses.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221326","221326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174667","2015-01-26","HM Treasury","2015-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that due weight is given to the position of Northern Ireland in respect of its (a) land border with the Republic of Ireland and (b) Section 75 equality-proofing requirements when decisions are taken on the future of HM Revenue and Customs offices and personnel under regional centres framework.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221448","221448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174668","2015-01-22","HM Treasury","2015-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to pursue a claim for costs against Rangers Football Club.","Biography information for Mr Brian H. Donohoe","Mr Brian H. Donohoe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221441","221441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174669","2015-01-22","HM Treasury","2015-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2014 to Question 205620, how his Department calculated the cost of providing the information requested.","Biography information for Mr Brian H. Donohoe","Mr Brian H. Donohoe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221440","221440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174670","2015-01-22","HM Treasury","2015-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria HM Revenue and Customs uses to assess the prudence of settling a tax case when costs of pursuing a case are compared to the settlement offer.","Biography information for Mr Brian H. Donohoe","Mr Brian H. Donohoe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221400","221400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174671","2015-01-22","HM Treasury","2015-01-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of HM Revenue and Customs' accounting procedures relating to assessing the cost of pursuing big value claims.","Biography information for Mr Brian H. Donohoe","Mr Brian H. Donohoe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221401","221401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174672","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what salary the directly elected city-region Mayor of Greater Manchester will be paid.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221428","221428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174673","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward proposals to amend the Building Approved Inspectors Regulations 2000 to ensure that building inspection is required to be independent.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221430","221430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174674","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether an equality impact assessment has been made of plans for a directly elected city-region Mayor for Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221419","221419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174675","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the cost of introducing a directly elected city-region Mayor for Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221420","221420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174676","2015-01-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will discuss with his counterparts in the devolved administrations the merits of a common formula for the Warm Home discount and grant schemes across all those administrations.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221330","221330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174677","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to promote tolerance of different minorities.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221305","221305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174678","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the performance of local authorities in issuing within 26 weeks a special educational needs final statement; and whether his Department (a) supplies information to and (b) receives information from the Department for Education on that matter.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221297","221297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174679","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his letter of 18 January 2015 to Muslim faith leaders, what recent discussions he has had with (a) LawWorks and (b) the Bar Pro Bono Unit on this matter.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221338","221338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174680","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his letter of 18 January 2015 to Muslim faith leaders, what assessment he has made of the capacity of (a) LawWorks and (b) the Bar Pro Bono Unit to provide free legal advice to organisations experiencing problems with preachers of hate.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221334","221334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174681","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the letter of 15 January 2015 from him and the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government to the local authorities concerning additional health funding, to which local authorities the letter was sent; and which local authorities have confirmed they will accept the offered funding.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221335","221335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174682","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the letter of 15 January 2015 from him and the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government to local authorities concerning additional health funding, what the total amount will be of additional funding made available to local authorities through the ring-fenced grant referred to in that letter.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221336","221336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174683","2015-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his letter of 18 January 2015 to Muslim faith leaders, what assessment he has made of whether all organisations that are at risk of experiencing problems with preachers of hate would meet the eligibility criteria applied by (a) LawWorks and (b) the Bar Pro Bono Unit for providing free legal advice.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221337","221337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174684","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, persuant to the Answer of 15 December 2014 to Question 906630, what the 117 projects funded by the Coastal Communities Fund are.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221354","221354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174685","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Building Approved Inspectors Regulations 2000 in providing independent and transparent assessment of building plans.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221431","221431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174686","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects to agree the share of the Apprenticeship Grant for employers for Greater Manchester as part of the Greater Manchester devolution deal.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221421","221421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174687","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many complaints he has received about a conflict of interest in assessments conducted by the National House Building Council in relation to Approved Document M.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221432","221432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174688","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals on the Greater Manchester devolution agreement and the election of a directly elected city-region Mayor.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221422","221422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174689","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the independence of building approved inspectors.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221433","221433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174690","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to ensure public scrutiny of a directly elected city-region Mayor for Greater Manchester other than at election time.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221426","221426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174691","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to bring forward amendments to the Greater Manchester Combined Authority Order 2011 to create an eleventh leader of Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221424","221424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174692","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how long the term of office will be for a directly elected city-region Mayor for Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221425","221425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174693","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what requirement there will be for public consultation as part of the evaluation of the Greater Manchester devolution agreement.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221423","221423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174694","2015-01-22","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress his Department has made on refurbishment projects and national events announced in 2012 to mark the centenary of the First World War.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221365","221365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174695","2015-01-22","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many members of his Department's executive board went to (a) private school, (b) state school and (c) the universities of Oxford or Cambridge.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221404","221404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174696","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2014 to Question 217721, whether personnel deployed on Operation Shader received hot meals at Crown expense before 4 December 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221449","221449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174697","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many suitably qualified and experienced personnel staff are currently required by his Department; and how many such positions for each role are vacant in (a) the Defence Support Group, (b) the Defence Science and Technology Laboratory, (c) the UK Hydrographic Office and (d) Defence Equipment and Support.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221406","221406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174698","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many nuclear-qualified and experienced personnel have been required by his Department in each of the last three years; and how many such posts were vacant at each location on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221405","221405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174699","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library the most recent version of the Defence Nuclear Executive Board's Risk Register for the Nuclear Programme.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221407","221407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174700","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2014 to Question 210783, what the issues were that required resolution; whether those issues they have been resolved; and if he will publish the revised TCAS embodiment programme for the Tornado GR4 fleet.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221408","221408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174701","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the section on Barrow Infrastructure in the United Kingdom's Future Nuclear Deterrent: 2014 Update to Parliament, how he calculated that £42 million would be saved by a different approach to financing the rebuild of new support facilites in the Central Yard at the Barrow shipyard; what the early implementation steel work to the New Assembly Shop consists of; and how the £55 million of planned expenditure for which no specific purpose is assigned will be used.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221394","221394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174702","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2015 to Question 219525, if he will place in the Library a copy of the document that has superseded Version 1.3 of the document 201110314 Collision Warning System Analysis.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221409","221409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174703","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects testing of the collision warning system for Typhoon jets to be completed; what estimate he has made of the time and cost of installing that system; and when he expects to take a decision on installing that system.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221410","221410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174704","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Royal Air Force and Royal Navy have sufficient submarine detection capabilities.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221307","221307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174705","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Questions 220492 and 220493, how many of the surveillance and monitoring activities resulted in (a) the withdrawal of a claim for compensation and (b) the disclosure of the monitoring and surveillance in court; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221328","221328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174706","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Questions 220492 and 220493, how many of the surveillance and monitoring activities involved claimants who had (a) sustained injuries on active service, (b) amputations, (c) mental health problems and (d) traumatic brain injuries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221324","221324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174707","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to offer support to veterans diagnosed with mesothelioma.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221387","221387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174708","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what cross-departmental work his Department is undertaking on veterans' welfare.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221427","221427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174709","2015-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many of his Department's Tornado jets (a) are in service, (b) are in the forward fleet and (c) have the Honeywell Traffic Collision Avoidance System II installed.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221470","221470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174710","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his statement of 20 January 2015, Official Report, column 105, on Trident renewal, that the UK has met its commitment to withdraw from deployment some of its nuclear weapons, whether an independent authority has been given access to verify that withdrawal of operational nuclear weapons; what his Department has done with those missiles withdrawn from deployment; what his Department has done with fissile material from those nuclear warheads withdrawn from deployment; and what international safeguards inspection measures have been applied to that fissile material.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221353","221353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174711","2015-01-23","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-20","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps his Department is taking to increase levels of individual electoral registration among (a) attainers and (b) students.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221341","221341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174712","2015-01-23","Department for Education","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of primary school teachers in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) Warrington have a degree in (i) English and (ii) mathematics.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221323","221323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174713","2015-01-23","Department for Education","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether there are circumstances in which, where parents have twins, each child is entitled to less than the standard allocation of 15 hours of free childcare per week for 38 weeks of the year.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221315","221315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174714","2015-01-23","Department for Education","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 128 of her Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC 745, what the reasons are for the increase in the cost of other office services since the previous financial year.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221344","221344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174715","2015-01-22","Department for Education","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many adoptions there were in (a) the North West, (b) Lancashire and (c) Pendle constituency in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221434","221434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174716","2015-01-23","Department for Education","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the reasons were for the cash losses, fruitless payments and write-offs worth more than £100,000 referred to on page 156 of her Department's Annual Report and Accounts, 2013-14, HC 745.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221472","221472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174717","2015-01-23","Department for Education","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding has been provided to each pupil in state (i) primary and (ii) secondary schools in Surrey (A) in cash terms  and (B) at 2015 prices in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221460","221460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174718","2015-01-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2015 to Question 220505, on coal: taxation what estimate he has made of the amount collected through that levy.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221412","221412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174719","2015-01-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department has spent on collective switching initiatives since 2010; and how many customers have switched specifically as part of those initiatives.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221398","221398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174720","2015-01-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with Ofgem on its change of interpretation of the Renewable Heat Incentive Scheme Regulations 2011, as amended by the Renewable Heat Incentive Scheme (Amendment) Regulations 2014, in respect of the definition of plant in relation to the eligibility criteria set out in Regulations 9, 11 and 12.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221296","221296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174721","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the cost of the Electricity Intensive Industries - Relief from the Cost of Renewables scheme.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221316","221316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174722","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on which industrial sectors reach the preliminary threshold of seven per cent electricity intensity, but in which a majority of businesses do not meet the added 20 per cent electricity intensity threshold.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Bailey","Mr Adrian Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221317","221317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174723","2015-01-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on what date his Department plans to publish its response to the Warm Homes Discount: Extension to the 2015-16 consultation.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221318","221318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174724","2015-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when her Department plans to announce emergency conservation measures to protect sea bass stocks.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221292","221292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174725","2015-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the use of the captive bolt gun for the destruction of dogs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221293","221293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174726","2015-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how long she plans that the consultation for the 2015 review of the Greyhound Regulations (England) 2010 will take.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221308","221308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174727","2015-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to control the pine marten population.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221381","221381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174728","2015-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what communication has been delivered to private veterinary practices and farmers regarding the recent changes to the UK's veterinary surveillance network; and what plans her Department has to ensure that surveillance data from veterinary practices and non-APHA sources is being centrally collated and shared at a national level.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221437","221437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174729","2015-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will discuss with the hon. Member for Strangford and Natural England the request for a licence to control buzzards by Mr Rodney McMorris.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221382","221382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174730","2015-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to extend the Animal Welfare Act 2006 to crustaceans and decapods.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221350","221350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174731","2015-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of waste collected has been recycled in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221413","221413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174732","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with Amnesty International on human rights in Colombia.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221442","221442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174733","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent support the Government has given to the authorities in the Democratic Republic of Congo.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221357","221357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174734","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on expansion of the sanctions regime on Russia.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221358","221358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174735","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the election in Sri Lanka and the prospects for an independent war crime inquiry in that country.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221359","221359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174736","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken in response to the decision of the General Court of the European Union on Hamas.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221360","221360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174737","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to help the Libyan government bring peace and stability to that country.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221361","221361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174738","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the human rights situation in Turkey.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221362","221362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174739","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Pakistani counterpart on the protection and maintenance of Jewish cemeteries in that country.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221385","221385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174740","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to promote (a) press freedom and (b) other human rights in Bahrain.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221298","221298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174741","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the recommendation on the NHS Choices website that all children are offered vision screening between the ages of four and five by an orthoptist-led service, if he will introduce a national vision screening programme for children.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221304","221304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174742","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce A&E waiting times in Huddersfield and Kirklees.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221388","221388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174743","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to provide care and respite funding for young adult amputees.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221374","221374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174744","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support patients with cirrhosis liver conditions.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221356","221356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174745","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the level of prescription drug-taking among women.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221379","221379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174746","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people underwent laser eye surgery in the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221380","221380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174747","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of long-term conditions which entitle patients to free prescriptions are curable.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221345","221345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174748","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for pain management in each region.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221346","221346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174749","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients with long-term health conditions which entitle them to free prescriptions have been fined for not renewing their certificates in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221372","221372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174750","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to publicise the fact that certificates of entitlement to free prescriptions for chronic and incurable conditions are time-limited.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221373","221373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174751","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to pages five and six of the summary of findings of the Hinchingbrooke Health Care NHS Trust Quality Report  of 9 January 2015, if he will publish the full list of organisations which were asked to share what they know about that hospital.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221375","221375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174752","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy that the NHS Business Unit should contact GPs when a certificate of entitlement to free prescriptions is due to expire.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221364","221364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174753","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has commissioned into complex regional pain syndrome.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221370","221370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174754","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been fined for falsely claiming free prescriptions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221363","221363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174755","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he takes to ensure that all patients assessed as requiring inpatient treatment for eating disorders are admitted; and what criteria are used to decide whether a patient requires inpatient treatment for such disorders.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221451","221451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174756","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England (a) currently and (b) since the establishment of that body has operated a moratorium on the commissioning of additional funded beds for inpatient eating disorder treatment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221452","221452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174757","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been treated with the gamma knife at University Hospital, Bristol, since it opened in October 2013; and whether NHS England approved those patients' treatment through individual funding requests.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221450","221450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174758","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to provide support to the NHS in assisting patients with breast cancer.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221399","221399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174759","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has commissioned into cholangiocarcinoma.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221396","221396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174760","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors and nurses, including agency staff and locums, are working in the NHS in England; and what the equivalent figure was in 2009-10.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221392","221392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174761","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made in treating pain since the Chief Medical Officer's annual report in 2008 called for the issue to receive greater priority.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221393","221393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174762","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what is the minimum number of annual procedures NHS England requires hospitals to deliver before they are allowed to treat cancer patients with stereotactic ablative radiotherapy.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221465","221465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174763","2015-01-23","Department of Health","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure that all stakeholder submissions to NHS England's review into stereotactic radiosurgery are made available to the public.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221466","221466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174764","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have (a) applied and (b) successfully resettled in the UK under the Vulnerable Persons Relocation Scheme to date; what the origin was of each applicant; which local authorities are participating in the scheme; and what the cost of the scheme has been to date.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221467","221467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174765","2015-01-26","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were apprehended when illegally entering the UK in Northern Ireland at the border with the Republic of Ireland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221443","221443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174766","2015-01-26","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps are being taken to increase surveillance and resources in Northern Ireland to prevent people from illegally entering the UK from the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221444","221444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174767","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the number of illegal firearms.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221415","221415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174768","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce criminal access to illegal firearms.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221416","221416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174769","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many illegal firearms were confiscated by police forces in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221418","221418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174770","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department last reviewed the effectiveness of Government policy aimed at reducing the number of illegal firearms.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221417","221417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174771","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer by Viscount Younger of Leckie on 25 February 2014, Official Report, House of Lords, column WA239, how many organisms of which species have been generated following pronuclear transfer by researchers at Newcastle in each year of the last decade according to records held by her Department.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221476","221476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174772","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of illegal firearms in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221414","221414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174773","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of naturalisation applications took (a) less than 6 months, (b) between 6 and 9 months, (c) between 9 and 12 months and (d) more than 12 months to be concluded in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221349","221349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174774","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department last reviewed the adequacy of the firearms unit provision made available to police forces in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221313","221313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174775","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce the incidence of hate crimes against religious minorities.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221306","221306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174776","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the average length of time each police force has taken to return Disclosure and Barring Service checks since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221314","221314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174777","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department last reviewed the adequacy of the response times of firearms units.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221311","221311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174778","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times armed police were deployed in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221312","221312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174779","2015-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is his policy to publish the names of people in England and Wales where the Royal Prerogative of Mercy has been used.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221301","221301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174780","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many illegal firearms were confiscated by UK customs officials at border checks in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221309","221309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174781","2015-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times the Royal Prerogative of Mercy has been used in England and Wales in the last 20 years for which information is available.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221302","221302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174782","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken for firearms units to arrive at crime scenes was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221310","221310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174783","2015-01-23","Department for International Development","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if her Department will ensure that Parliament is given adequate opportunity for effective scrutiny of the positions taken by the EU in the post-2015 sustainable development goals process.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221321","221321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174784","2015-01-23","Department for International Development","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what development issues and goal area she expects will be led by individual EU member states in the post-2015 sustainable development goals process; and whether the UK will lead on any of these development issues or goal areas.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221322","221322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174785","2015-01-23","Department for International Development","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many (a) female and (b) male burial operatives have been recruited (i) from the UK and (ii) from Sierra Leone to burial teams as part of her Department's response to the Ebola crisis in Sierra Leone.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221454","221454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174786","2015-01-23","Department for International Development","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has provided any financial support towards the opening of Médecins Sans Frontières' maternity clinic for Ebola sufferers.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221457","221457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174787","2015-01-23","Department for International Development","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to target the increased contraction rate of Ebola amongst women in Sierra Leone; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221458","221458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174788","2015-01-23","Department for International Development","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding from her Department has been assigned to Ebola vaccine candidate and safety testing; how much of that funding has been spent in (a) 2014 and (b) 2015 to date; and what steps she is taking to ensure that vaccine candidates funded by her Department are safe for use by pregnant women and nursing mothers.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221456","221456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174789","2015-01-23","Department for International Development","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many (a) female and (b) male patients have been treated for Ebola in each treatment centre funded by her Department.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221455","221455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174790","2015-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many books were received by his Department during December 2014 as part of the books for prisoners campaign; and where those books were distributed.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221459","221459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174791","2015-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure there is consistent, co-ordinated and efficient access to victim support services in the UK.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221319","221319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174792","2015-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations he has received on the future funding of victim support services.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221320","221320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174793","2015-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of defendants who represented themselves in court in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221303","221303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174794","2015-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the savings to his Department arising from the closure of (a) Rhyl family court and (b) Denbigh magistrates' court.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221368","221368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174795","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the savings to his Department arising from the closure of the army recruitment centre in Rhyl.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221366","221366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174796","2015-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which countries Just Solutions International (JSI) has worked with since it was established; what contracts it has with foreign companies; what visits Ministers in his Department have made relating to JSI; and what payments JSI has received from foreign contracts.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221378","221378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174797","2015-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what forecast his Department has made of the saving to the public purse from the relocation of the Crown Post Office in Rhyl.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221383","221383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174798","2015-01-23","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will discuss with the Secretary of State for the Home Department what changes would be needed to ensure that Northern Ireland citizens born in the Republic of Ireland are able to apply for UK passports on the same terms as those under which Northern Ireland citizens are able to apply for Irish passports.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221331","221331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174799","2015-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Special Representative on Preventing Sexual Violence in Conflict regarding sexual violence in Colombia; and what assistance the Government has offered to Colombia since the Global Summit to End Sexual Violence in Conflict.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221377","221377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174800","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which organisations have inspected mock-ups of Intercity Express Programme train sets.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221329","221329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174801","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to councils of damage caused by parking on the pavement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221435","221435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174802","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department provided to upgrade railway stations in Crawley constituency (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221384","221384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174803","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will conduct an impact assessment into the potential effects of the Pavement Parking Private Members' Bill; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221436","221436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174804","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made with the implementation of the European Rail Traffic Management System.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221429","221429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174805","2015-01-23","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of introducing Driver-Only Operation on delays and train dispatch times on the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221340","221340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174806","2015-01-23","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many stations at which Northern Rail services stop are currently (a) staffed and (b) unstaffed.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221325","221325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174807","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the specification was for (a) catering services, (b) guards' cabin and (c) catering staff accommodation in the mock-ups of Intercity Express Programme train sets.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221299","221299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174808","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which organisations his Department consulted on the design specifications used for mock-ups of Intercity Express Programme train sets.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221300","221300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174809","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many local authorities have implemented traffic regulation orders to tackle pavement parking in their area; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221439","221439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174810","2015-01-23","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to include in his Department's contract with the successful bidder for Northern Rail and Transpennine Express franchises a requirement that there is a second person on board the train in addition to the driver in the event of the introduction of driver-only operation.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221453","221453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174811","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the Highways Agency Digital Enforcement Camera System 3 cameras are not painted yellow in accordance with policy elsewhere; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221445","221445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174812","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what advice his Department gives to local Highways Authorities on how to decide which speed limits are appropriate in local areas.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221447","221447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174813","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will consider the issue of pavement parking as a barrier to safe walking within his Department's Cycling and Walking Delivery Plan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221395","221395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174814","2015-01-26","Department for Transport","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency has changed its policy on access to vehicle registration records from its archives and does not now make such records available to researchers and others seeking to collate vehicle histories for classic and historic vehicles.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221446","221446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174816","2015-01-23","Wales Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of cross-border water regulation in England and Wales as it relates to domestic and commercial properties in England supplied by Welsh Water; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221339","221339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174817","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to ensure that UK pensioners living in France receive winter fuel payments when the temperature where they live is below freezing.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221343","221343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174818","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether an external evaluator has been appointed to provide an independent assessment of the 17 Innovation Fund projects set up under the Help for Separated Families initiative to establish what works in assisting separated parents to co-operate in the interests of their children; when it is planned that that evaluation process will take place; and when it is planned that that evaluation report will be published.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221342","221342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174819","2015-01-23","Cabinet Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of recent trends in the number of workless households in (a) Northamptonshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221376","221376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174820","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer to Question 220107, if he will make it his policy to exclude French Overseas Departments in the calculation of average temperature for France for the purposes of determining eligibility for winter fuel payments to UK citizens.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221473","221473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174821","2015-01-22","Cabinet Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people left jobseeker's allowance because they reached the state pension age in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221355","221355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174822","2015-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in which areas of the UK personal independence payments natural reassessment has not yet been rolled-out.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221352","221352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174823","2015-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many requests for mandatory reconsideration on claims for Personal Independence Payments were made in the 12 months to October 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221397","221397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174824","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Youth Unemployment Innovation Fund.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221464","221464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174825","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the principal risks are which his Department has identified with respect to the national rollout of universal credit in 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221463","221463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174826","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has made an assessment of the consistency between different Work Programme providers of procedures on referrals for benefit sanctions.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221462","221462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174827","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that the approach of Work Programme providers to benefit sanctions referrals is consistent.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221461","221461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174828","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of (a) pension credit, (b) winter fuel allowance and (c) Christmas Bonus there were in each of the last five years up to the most recent period for which figures are available in (i) the UK, (ii) Scotland, (iii) England, (iv) Wales and (v) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221474","221474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174829","2015-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of (a) pension credit, (b) winter fuel allowance and (c) Christmas bonus there were in each of the last five years up to the most recent period for which figures are available in (i) Airdrie and Shotts constituency and (ii) North Lanarkshire.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221475","221475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175555","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of trends in youth unemployment.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907192","907192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175556","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent progress he has made on tackling fraud and error.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907186","907186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175557","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his Department's social security sanctions policy.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907174","907174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175558","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to ensure that the shared accommodation rate is representative of the real cost of renting shared accommodation.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907191","907191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176224","2015-01-28","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress she has made on implementation of the Stormont House Agreement; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907210","907210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/176225","2015-01-28","Northern Ireland Office","2015-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress she has made on implementation of the Stormont House Agreement; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Pat Glass","Pat Glass","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907211","907211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174351","2015-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans to publish the results of his call for evidence on the introduction of a pre-licensing register of arms brokers together with the Government's response in January 2015 at the latest.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221258","221258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174352","2015-01-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress the Government has made since 2010 in negotiating a revision of the Working Time Directive; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221280","221280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174353","2015-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total value was of the loans underpinned by the Enterprise Finance Guarantee scheme in each year since its inception; and what the value was of the loans underpinned by that scheme made by each financial institution in each of those years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221259","221259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174354","2015-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans to meet the Chairman and Chief Executive of the Royal Bank of Scotland to discuss the review announced by that bank of its practices relating to the Enterprise Finance Guarantee scheme.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221260","221260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174355","2015-01-21","Deputy Prime Minister","2015-01-19","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, whether the Electoral Commission has endorsed the inclusion of 17 year old attainers on the electoral register; and what assessment he has made of the effect of this inclusion on the number of 18 year olds registered to vote.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221159","221159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174356","2015-01-22","HM Treasury","2015-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue is protected by applying the EU VAT place of supply rules to micro businesses and sole traders which operate under the UK VAT threshold.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221289","221289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174357","2015-01-22","HM Treasury","2015-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make a comparative assessment of the level of administrative burden the EU VAT place of supply rules places on (a) micro businesses and sole traders and (b) large multinational companies.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221290","221290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174358","2015-01-22","HM Treasury","2015-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative assessment he has made of the way in which (a) the UK and (b) other EU member states have applied the EU VAT place of supply legislation to micro businesses and sole traders.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221287","221287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174359","2015-01-22","HM Treasury","2015-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to assist micro businesses and sole traders to comply with the EU VAT supply rules.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221288","221288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174360","2015-01-22","Cabinet Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of women earned less than two-thirds of the median hourly pay, excluding overtime, of all full and part-time female employees in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221252","221252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174361","2015-01-22","HM Treasury","2015-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will review the Government's policy on EU VAT place of supply legislation; and if he will suspend the EU VAT place of supply rules for the UK's micro businesses and sole traders.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221286","221286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174362","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to answer Question 219026, tabled on 16 December 2014 by the right hon. Member for Leeds Central.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221250","221250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174363","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to answer Question 219025, tabled on 16 December 2014 by the right hon. Member for Leeds Central.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221251","221251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174364","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on (a) recruitment agency fees, (b) outplacement agency fees for displaced or redundant staff and (c) staff training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221225","221225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174365","2015-01-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he has taken to ensure that the views of local residents are represented in decisions relating to drilling for shale gas.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221214","221214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174366","2015-01-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will take steps with the Department of Health to progress the commencement of powers for the Care Quality Commission to undertake inspections of how local authorities commission their care services where no specific complaints have been made.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221242","221242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174367","2015-01-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the commencement of wider powers for the Care Quality Commission to undertake inspections into local authorities' commissioning of care services.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221243","221243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174368","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to promote religious and ethnic tolerance and understanding.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221194","221194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174369","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the ability of claimants in North Staffordshire to access universal credit online.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221179","221179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174370","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the effect on the delivery of affordable housing of his Department's policy on section 106 affordable housing exemptions for small sites.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221278","221278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174371","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the letter dated 19 December 2014 from the Minister of State for Housing and Planning to the Planning Inspectorate concerning strategic housing market assessments, whether that letter represents a change in policy by his Department relating to the National Planning Policy Framework; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221284","221284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174372","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timetable is for inclusion of each of the wards in North Staffordshire in the next tranche of conversion to universal credit.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221176","221176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174373","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what budget he has allocated for promoting awareness of universal credit among claimants in North Staffordshire who will be required to make online applications.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221177","221177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174374","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department provides to support people in North Staffordshire making claims for universal benefit under the new procedures.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221178","221178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174375","2015-01-22","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2015 to Question 219653, on broadband, how much of the budget was spent in each local authority area; and where billboards have been used by the campaign in each local authority area.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221249","221249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174376","2015-01-22","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department spent on (a) recruitment agency fees, (b) outplacement agency fees for displaced or redundant staff and (c) staff training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221226","221226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174377","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 220486, how Royal Navy and Army personnel who served with the UN High Commissioner for Refugees detachment in Sarajevo can claim the UN Special Service Medal.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Robertson","Sir Hugh Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221266","221266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174378","2015-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many early service leavers from the Infantry enlisted (a) under and (b) over the age of 18 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221203","221203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174379","2015-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Scottish Government will participate in the One per cent Challenge for recruitment of reservists.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221237","221237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174380","2015-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it remains his policy to detain minors at the Military Correctional Training Centre (Colchester).","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221271","221271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174381","2015-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what research his Department has (a) commissioned, (b) funded and (c) undertaken on the mental health needs of service personnel and veterans since 2010; and what his most recent estimate is of the number of service personnel and veterans with such needs.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221166","221166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174382","2015-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average length of time taken by Veterans UK and its predecessors to deal with cases relating to (a) war disablement pensions and (b) compensation for injuries or illness incurred during service in the armed forces was in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221164","221164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174383","2015-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to provide support to female service personnel with mental health problems; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221165","221165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174384","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Incredible Years programme pilot in improving disruptive behaviour; and what plans she has to extend that programme.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221156","221156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174385","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the difference is in (a) attainment levels and (b) classroom behaviour in a child who has conduct disorder and has (i) been treated and (ii) not been treated for that disorder.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221158","221158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174386","2015-01-22","Department for Education","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of teachers and former teachers who have contracted mesothelioma from exposure to asbestos in schools.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221236","221236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174387","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Government's Nurse-Family Partnership pilot schemes.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221202","221202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174388","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary school teachers in each parliamentary constituency in the North West of England have a science degree.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221241","221241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174389","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the comparative recovery rates of children who have attention deficit hyperactivity disorder and have received (a) drug interventions, (b) psychological treatment and (c) no treatment.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221201","221201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174390","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what graded interventions are available to treat children with disruptive behaviour.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221200","221200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174391","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the estimated per-pupil cost was of GCSE re-sits in state schools for the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221204","221204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174392","2015-01-22","Department for Education","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent on (a) recruitment agency fees, (b) outplacement agency fees for displaced or redundant staff and (c) staff training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221229","221229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174393","2015-01-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the value and proportion of the UK content of each completed UK offshore wind farm is.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221257","221257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174394","2015-01-27","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the value and proportion of UK content of the forthcoming Race Bank offshore windfarm.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221256","221256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174395","2015-01-21","HM Treasury","2015-01-19","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Prime Minister's oral evidence to the Liaison Committee of 16 December 2014, HC 887, Question 4, whether the Government endorses the current guidelines on the use of revenues raised from the auctioning of carbon emissions allowances under the EU emissions trading system; if he will provide a breakdown of the UK's intended use of these revenues; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221240","221240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174396","2015-01-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which areas within Christchurch constituency are covered by existing Government licences permitting fracking.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221279","221279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174397","2015-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to protect farmers in the dairy industry from the economic consequences of the recent decision by supermarkets to significantly cut the price of a pint of milk.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221221","221221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174398","2015-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the merits of introducing an exemption for compostable plastic bags from the single use carrier bag charge; and if she will meet representatives from the compostable plastic bags industry to discuss such an exemption.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221191","221191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174399","2015-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in Ireland on the enforcement of the Balai Directive for racing greyhounds travelling to the UK; and how many racing greyhounds were recorded as having been moved from Ireland to the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221245","221245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174400","2015-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to assist the Nigerian and Cameroon governments in combating Boko Haram.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221198","221198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174401","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the government of Colombia urging action on recent death threats to former Colombian Senator, Piedad Cordoba.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221285","221285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174402","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of North Korea's nuclear activities.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221224","221224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174403","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to mark the seventieth anniversary of the liberation of Auschwitz-Birkenau.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221222","221222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174405","2015-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received on recent death threats to former Colombian Senator, Piedad Cordoba.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221234","221234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174406","2015-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is offering to Nigeria to tackle Boko Haram.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221218","221218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174407","2015-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Turkish government on freedom of speech.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221170","221170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174408","2015-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to address the activities of Boko Haram.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221171","221171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174409","2015-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to seek the release of Raif Badawi.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221172","221172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174411","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct his Department to collect information on (a) how many agency staff were employed and (b) what proportion of the total medical staff employed consisted of agency staff in NHS hospitals, by county, in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Mr David Ruffley","Mr David Ruffley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221175","221175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174412","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2015 to Question 219628, what penalties his Department can impose on pharmaceutical companies that fail to communicate drug shortages to GPs.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221168","221168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174413","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people scheduled to have a hip or knee replacement as a result of a musculoskeletal condition had their operation cancelled for non-clinical reasons in financial years (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221173","221173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174414","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make detailed data from the Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme available to researchers into mental health and employment.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221160","221160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174415","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the contribution of Improving Access to Psychological Therapies to improving mental health in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221162","221162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174416","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to provide employment advisers for Improving Access to Psychological Therapies clients; and what steps his Department is taking to implement those plans.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221153","221153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174417","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on co-ordinating pathways to work and volunteering for people who have undergone Improving Access to Psychological Therapies treatment.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221154","221154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174418","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the review by Professor Sir John Temple of the quality of training for doctors, published in May 2010, what progress has been made in negotiations between the NHS and the British Medical Association on changes to the national contract for junior doctors to better reflect the training needs of doctors.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221283","221283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174419","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Government publication, Sustaining Services, ensuring fairness: Government response to the consultation on migrant access and financial contribution to NHS provision in England, published on 30 December 2013, what steps his Department has taken to tackle the issues set out in that report; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221281","221281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174420","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the amount that his Department will spend on temporary staff in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221291","221291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174421","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the report of the independent taskforce on the implementation of the Working Time Directive under the chairmanship of Professor Norman Williams, published on 3 April 2014, what steps the Government has taken in response to that report.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221282","221282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174422","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average age of x-ray machines in use in hospitals.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221220","221220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174423","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients have been admitted to hospital after taking legal highs in (a) England and (b) each hospital in Kent in the last five years.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221216","221216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174424","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Question 220819, who appointed Tim Kelsey as Senior Responsible Owner (SRO) of the care.data programme; what the role of SRO involves; to whom Mr Kesley is accountable; and whether the composition of the programme board was decided by Mr Kesley.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221275","221275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174425","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of children who would have been eligible under the adult criteria for bariatric surgery in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221276","221276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174426","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in England are awaiting inpatient treatment for an eating disorder following a GP assessment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221253","221253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174427","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on (a) recruitment agency fees, (b) outplacement agency fees for displaced or redundant staff and (c) staff training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221228","221228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174428","2015-01-21","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost is of treating a child with conduct disorder.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221157","221157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174429","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the local hon. Member would ordinarily be one of the stakeholder consultees to a Care Quality Commission Quality Report.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221180","221180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174430","2015-01-22","Department of Health","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to require the Care Quality Commission to consult committees of (a) local district and (b) county councils when preparing Quality reports.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221181","221181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174431","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fresh applications for asylum have been (a) made and (b) accepted, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221183","221183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174432","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons her Department decided that further submissions on asylum and human rights cases must be made in person in Liverpool; with which bodies her Department consulted before making that decision; and what assistance her Department will provide to help individuals travel to Liverpool to make such submissions.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221184","221184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174433","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will offer asylum to Raif Badawi and his family.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221185","221185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174434","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to protect the well-being of animals once they have outlived their use in laboratories.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221189","221189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174435","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 220354, how many study visas were granted for each of the top 10 nationalities in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221190","221190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174436","2015-01-21","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum case work staff were employed in dealing with asylum claims in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221244","221244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174437","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on (a) recruitment agency fees, (b) outplacement agency fees for displaced or redundant staff and (c) staff training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221227","221227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174438","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many crimes of each category were perpetrated against Jewish people and recorded as being anti-Semitic in each police force area in each month since January 2014.","Biography information for Sir Alan Duncan","Sir Alan Duncan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221248","221248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174439","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for bail made under Schedules 2 and 3 of the Immigration Act 1971 or section 36(4) of the UK Borders Act 2007 were made to (a) an immigration officer, (b) the Secretary of State for the Home Department and (c) the First-Tier Tribunal, Immigration and Asylum Chamber in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221272","221272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174440","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of anti-Semitic assaults recorded in England since October 2014.","Biography information for Sir Alan Duncan","Sir Alan Duncan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221246","221246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174441","2015-01-22","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what statistical information her Department has used to establish the extent of, and any recent trends in, crimes against Jewish victims in England since October 2014.","Biography information for Sir Alan Duncan","Sir Alan Duncan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221247","221247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174442","2015-01-23","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the threat of far right radicalisation.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221195","221195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174443","2015-01-21","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have been waiting for an initial decision on their claim for (a) six months or more and (b) one year or more.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221261","221261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174444","2015-01-21","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total cost to her Department is of employing an Executive Officer asylum case worker.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221262","221262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174445","2015-01-21","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average weekly cost is of housing an asylum seeker under (a) section 95 and (b) section 4 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221270","221270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174446","2015-01-21","Home Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 220654, what indirect costs were incurred by her Department in connection with policing Black Friday.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221167","221167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174447","2015-01-22","Department for International Development","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to provide relief in those parts of Nigeria affected by the activities of Boko Haram.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221239","221239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174448","2015-01-22","Department for International Development","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Question 220652, what proportion of the target £1.8 billion has been allocated to date for 2015-16; and to what that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221277","221277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174449","2015-01-21","Department for International Development","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions officials in her Department have had with the governments of African states receiving aid from the UK on policy reforms relating to seeds and plants variety protections; and if she will publish correspondence and transcripts of meetings on those issues between her Department and (a) the governments of those African states, (b) the US administration, (c) representatives of agricultural companies and (d) representatives of seed companies.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221217","221217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174450","2015-01-22","Department for International Development","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to Question 220623, in what forms information on funding allocations of her Department's budget for the strategic framework for economic development is available.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221273","221273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174451","2015-01-21","Department for International Development","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department is offering to the Nigerian government in response to the recent actions of Boko Haram.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221199","221199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174452","2015-01-22","Department for International Development","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department takes to ensure that aid provided to Nigeria is not used by Boko Haram.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221193","221193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174453","2015-01-22","Department for International Development","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what monitoring of Private Infrastructure Development Group her Department undertakes to ensure value for money.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221186","221186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174454","2015-01-22","Department for International Development","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department provided to the Private Infrastructure Development Group in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221187","221187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174455","2015-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that the successful bidder for Compliance and Enforcement Service Project offers value for money.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221188","221188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174456","2015-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the next meeting between officials of his Department, Urban Vision and Stoke-on-Trent City Council to discuss Fenton Town Hall will take place.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221182","221182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174457","2015-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) number of convictions, (b) conviction rate as a percentage of prosecutions brought and (c) rate of convictions as a percentage of crimes reported was for (i) murder, (ii) grievous bodily harm, (iii) sexual offences, (iv) burglary, (v) robbery, (vi) theft, (vii) criminal damage, (viii) public order offences, (ix) drug offences, (x) driving offences and (xi) all offences in (A) Elmbridge, (B) Surrey, (C) the South East of England and (D) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221192","221192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174458","2015-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions officials from his Department have met (a) Urban Vision and (b) Stoke-on-Trent City Council to discuss Fenton Town Hall in the last three months.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221235","221235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174459","2015-01-21","Prime Minister","2015-01-19","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to his oral evidence to the Liaison Committee of 16 December 2014, what criteria he used to classify energy sources as (a) highly subsidised and (b) semi-subsidised; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221169","221169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174460","2015-01-21","Scotland Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps the Government is taking to protect the economies of Scottish cities linked to the North Sea oil and gas industry.","Biography information for Jim McGovern","Jim McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221215","221215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174461","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which train operators offer compensation to passengers travelling on services delayed by (a) 30 to 60 minutes and (b) 60 minutes or longer.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221209","221209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174462","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of likely passenger numbers on trains from Woking to London Waterloo in (a) 2019 to 2024 and (b) 2025 to 2043.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221210","221210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174463","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many seats are available on trains from Woking to London Waterloo during morning weekday peak hours.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221211","221211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174464","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the average daily number of passengers using morning peak weekday rail services from Woking to London Waterloo.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221212","221212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174465","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much was paid by Network Rail to South West Trains because of delays to train services of (a) 15 to 30, (b) 30 to 60 and (c) 60 minutes or more in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221213","221213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174466","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will require South West Trains to offer compensation to passengers delayed by more than 30 minutes whilst travelling on its trains.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221208","221208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174467","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many bridges are located over the Wessex Route rail line between (a) Basingstoke and Woking and (b) Woking and London Waterloo; and how many of those bridges are less than 16 feet clear from the ground.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221205","221205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174468","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many tunnels are located on the Wessex Route rail line between (a) Basingstoke and Woking and (b) Woking and London Waterloo; and how many of those tunnels are less than 16 feet in height.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221206","221206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174469","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 168 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, which were the 10 largest recipients of payments by the Departmental Group for Professional Services; and how much was paid to each such recipient.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221264","221264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174470","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of rail passengers are able to claim compensation for delays to rail journeys of 30 to 60 minutes.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221207","221207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174471","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to provide financial assistance to local authorities to repair potholes.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221223","221223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174472","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, by which date he expects the widening work between junctions 7 and 9 of the A14 around Kettering will have been completed.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221233","221233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174473","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to page 168 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2013-14, HC 12, what items constitute the other costs category of programme costs in that document.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221267","221267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174474","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which five companies were used most often to provide temporary workers for his Department in the last financial year; and how much was paid in agency fees to those companies in that period.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221219","221219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174475","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the proportion of biofuel added to road fuel which is sourced from overseas.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221238","221238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174476","2015-01-21","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 65 of the report of the Smith Commission, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to give the Scottish Government discretion to decide whether or not to tender for rail services for which it is responsible.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221174","221174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174477","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people on incapacity benefits suffer from mental health conditions; and what proportion of those people have undergone treatment for their mental health condition in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221155","221155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174478","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will guarantee a place on an Improving Access to Psychological Therapies course for people on incapacity benefit suffering from poor mental health.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221163","221163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174479","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of the employability of people on incapacity benefits suffering from poor mental health who have (a) received and (b) not received treatment for their condition.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221161","221161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174480","2015-01-21","Cabinet Office","2015-01-19","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the employment rate of people aged 16 to 29 in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221263","221263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174481","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have been sanctioned since January 2012 have received hardship payments in each year since then; and what the average level was of such hardship payments.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221197","221197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174482","2015-01-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many peer reviews his Department has carried out following the death of benefit claimants; how many such reviews involved the sanctioning of claimants; and in how many cases his Department's action was found to be inappropriate or incorrect.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221196","221196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174483","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of expenditure on unemployment-related benefits to people aged (a) 18 to 24 and (b) 24 to 29 in (i) the UK, (ii) Scotland, (iii) England, (iv) Wales and (v) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221268","221268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174484","2015-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate how much his Department has paid out to people aged 16 to 29 in unemployment-related benefits in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) England, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221269","221269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174485","2015-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any people claiming universal credit are subject to in-work conditionality.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221232","221232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174486","2015-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average weekly earnings were for self-employed women in each year since 2002-03.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221265","221265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174487","2015-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has prepared an equality statement on its decision to cease grant funding for local welfare provision from 2015-16.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221274","221274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174488","2015-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what basis the French Southern and Antarctic Lands, Saint Pierre and Miquelon, Saint Barthélemy, French Polynesia, Wallis and Futuna and New Caledonia are excluded from his calculations for the purposes of establishing the average mean winter temperature for France in connection with winter fuel payments.","Biography information for Sir Roger Gale","Sir Roger Gale","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221255","221255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174489","2015-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how much time per year self-employed workers spend on fulfilling regulatory health and safety obligations.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221230","221230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174490","2015-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects the Major Projects Authority to provide its next assessment of the universal credit project.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221231","221231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174491","2015-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2015 to Question 220704, how large the control group will be in the proposed randomised control trial for universal credit in work progression; for how long that trial is planned to run; how progression in the two groups will be measured; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221254","221254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174815","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of plans to continue the use of Pacer trains on the Northern franchise.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907138","907138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175181","2015-01-22","House of Commons Commission","2015-01-19","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what steps the Commission is taking to ensure that women authors are better represented in the books on sale in the House of Commons Bookshop.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907160","907160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175182","2015-01-22","House of Commons Commission","2015-01-19","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, when and by whom a decision will be made on whether to vacate the Palace of Westminster to allow complete restoration and refurbishment to commence.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907162","907162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175183","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on implementing the recommendations of the Leeds Bradford International Airport connectivity study, published in November 2014.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907145","907145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175184","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to increase levels of walking and cycling.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907151","907151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175185","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to tackle parking near schools.","Biography information for Mark Pawsey","Mark Pawsey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907149","907149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/175186","2015-01-22","Department for Transport","2015-01-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to relieve congestion on roads.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907150","907150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174156","2015-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2015 to Question 219396, on the Employee Ownership Fund, what estimate he has made of the amount of the £0.72 million that will be spent on training women engineers.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221085","221085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174157","2015-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 8 January 2014 from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State in his Department, Official Report, column 382, on mandatory origin marking, if he will place in the Library a list of the companies that have been consulted as part of the study of country of origin marking.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221080","221080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174158","2015-01-21","Cabinet Office","2015-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance he has issued to (a) businesses, (b) organisations and (c) individuals on methods of encryption to protect against malicious cyber-attacks while allowing the security services access to data.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221115","221115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174159","2015-01-21","HM Treasury","2015-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what involvement his Department has in monitoring the Enterprise Finance Guarantee scheme.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221142","221142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174160","2015-01-21","HM Treasury","2015-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department collects on the operation by lenders of the Enterprise Finance Guarantee scheme.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221143","221143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174161","2015-01-21","HM Treasury","2015-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department became aware of the allegations of misselling in relation to the Enterprise Finance Guarantee scheme.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221144","221144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174162","2015-01-21","HM Treasury","2015-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills about investigation of allegations of misselling to businesses by lenders relating to loans made under the Enterprise Finance Guarantee scheme.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221145","221145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174163","2015-01-21","HM Treasury","2015-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have had with (i) participating lenders (ii) business organisations at which allegations of misselling relating to the Enterprise Finance Guarantee scheme were discussed.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221146","221146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174164","2015-01-20","HM Treasury","2015-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many properties sold in (a) Woking constituency and (b) Surrey attracted stamp duty land tax in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221136","221136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174165","2015-01-20","HM Treasury","2015-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of how many people in (a) Woking constituency and (b) Surrey pay less income tax in 2014-15 than in 2009-10.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221138","221138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174166","2015-01-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2014 to Question 212813, what the cost to the public purse was of his Department's provision of its office space to the Big Society Network from 28 July 2010 to 26 November 2010.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221061","221061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174167","2015-01-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2014 to Question 212813, for what purpose the Big Society Network used the office space provided by his Department.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221062","221062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174168","2015-01-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of adults in (a) Woking constituency and (b) Surrey who have taken part in at least one sporting activity each week in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221139","221139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174169","2015-01-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the proportion of households with access to high speed broadband in (a) Woking constituency and (b) Surrey in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221137","221137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174170","2015-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to support veterans with industrial deafness.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221123","221123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174171","2015-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many veterans suffer from industrial deafness.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221124","221124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174172","2015-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people serving in the (a) Royal Navy, (b) Royal Marines, (c) Royal Air Force and (d) Army were convicted of (i) possession of and (ii) supplying illegal drugs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221064","221064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174173","2015-01-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 219665, how many (a) members of the Libyan General Purpose Force, (b) members of the UK training team and (c) Libyan trainees took part in each of the visits listed; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221056","221056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174174","2015-01-20","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 220450, who will assess whether improvement at the schools in question is adequate; and when that assessment will be made.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221054","221054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174175","2015-01-20","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 220450, whether her Department is considering new sponsorship, governance or partnership agreements with another Academy for any of the schools in question; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221050","221050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174176","2015-01-20","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 220450, what steps her Department can take in the case of adequate improvements not being made at one of the schools in question.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221051","221051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174177","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many independent careers advisers were employed by schools in academic years (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221057","221057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174178","2015-01-20","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 220450, how her Department can detail the input of challenging the schools in question.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221052","221052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174179","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people started the National Professional Qualification for Headship in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221058","221058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174180","2015-01-20","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2015 to Question 220450, for how long her Department expects to work closely with each of the schools in question.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221053","221053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174181","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people (a) applied for and (b) completed the National Professional Qualification for Headship in financial years (i) 2009-10, (ii) 2010-11, (iii) 2011-12, (iv) 2012-13 and (v) 2013-14.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221059","221059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/174182","2015-01-21","Department for Education","2015-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people applied for the National Professional Qualification for Headship in the first half of financial year 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 221060","221060"
