"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647180","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to prevent an increase in the sugar content of food and drink products after the EU sugar quotas are lifted in 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55157","55157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647181","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many admissions there were to the paediatric intensive care unit at the Royal Brompton Hospital in the last 12 months for which figures are available; what proportion of those admissions were cardiac cases; and what plans his Department has to replace elsewhere in London (a) paediatric intensive care beds and (b) the specialist children's lung disease service which will close at the Royal Brompton Hospital as a result of NHS proposals to decommission congenital heart disease services at that hospital.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55163","55163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647182","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many young people aged 17 years or under were admitted to mental health hospitals outside  their (a) clinical commissioning group and (b) area team area in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55164","55164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647183","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has made to Capita on the time taken by that body to send GP in-patient records to pay practices.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55183","55183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647184","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 40 of Implementing The Five Year Forward View for Mental Health, published by NHS England in July 2016, what progress has been made in the development of a five-year data plan; and whether he plans to ensure that professional organisations and charities have an opportunity to provide input into the development of that plan.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55242","55242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647185","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with blepharitis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55277","55277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647186","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with (a) knee, (b) ankle, (c) foot, (d) hand and (e) neck arthritis in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55278","55278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647187","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of proposals for NHS Pensions to charge fees for members requesting pension forecast information.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55252","55252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647188","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take to encourage increased consumption of vegetables.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55087","55087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647189","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage diversity in the workforce of ambulance services in England.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55088","55088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647190","2016-11-30","Department for Education","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 29 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, Cm 9301, published in July 2016, what the findings were of the study commissioned to ascertain the adequacy and consistency of knowledge on gender variance in initial social work training and continuous professional development.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55060","55060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647191","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 19 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, Cm 9301, published in July 2016, what steps NHS England has taken as part of its ongoing work to consider the uses of real-life experience for transgender people before genital surgery.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55059","55059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647192","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions between 1 April 2016 and 30 June 2016 (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his  Department have met representatives of (i) Boots, (ii) Lloyds Pharmacy and (iii) the National Pharmacy Association.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55009","55009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647193","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much missed or cancelled ophthalmology appointments in the Northern, Eastern and Western Devon Clinical Commissioning Group area cost the NHS in 2015-16.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55013","55013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647194","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions between 1 October 2016 and 21 October 2016 (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his  Department have met representatives of (i) Boots, (ii) Lloyds Pharmacy and (iii) the National Pharmacy Association.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55007","55007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647195","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions between 1 July 2016 and 30 September 2016 (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his  Department have met representatives of (i) Boots, (ii) Lloyds Pharmacy and (iii) the National Pharmacy Association.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55008","55008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647196","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 20 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, Cm 9301, published in July 2016, whether the final service specification for the children and young people's Gender Identity Development Service and the final clinical commissioning policy for prescribing cross-sex hormones to young people have been (a) agreed and (b) published.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55061","55061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647197","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 20 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, Cm 9301, published in July 2016, what progress has been made on the development of an action plan arising from the multi-agency symposium on a national and training plan in March 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55062","55062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647198","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to pages 18 and 19 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, Cm 9301, published in July 2016, what steps NHS England has taken to strengthen governance arrangements to review within six months NHS compliance with the Equality Act 2010 in respect of services for transgender people.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55063","55063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647199","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps NHS England is taking to increase bisphosphonates prescription for the prevention of secondary breast cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55067","55067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647200","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on the performance of the Pennine Acute Trust; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55028","55028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647201","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of prescriptions issued for bisphosphonates to prevent secondary breast cancer in each year that figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55068","55068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647202","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much in fees from overseas private patients was (a) collected by and (b) remain outstanding to NHS trusts in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55034","55034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647203","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential surplus or deficit in the NHS Provider sector in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55032","55032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647204","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many young people aged 17 or under of each age were treated in adult mental health wards in 2015-16.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55042","55042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647205","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to decrease the number of people missing or cancelling ophthalmology appointments.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55012","55012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647206","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what effect recent changes in the rate of sterling have had on the finances of the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55029","55029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647207","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of sustainability and transformation plans that he has received which will achieve the savings targets identified.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55035","55035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647208","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much in fees from private patients (a) was collected by and (b) remain outstanding to NHS trusts in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55033","55033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647209","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the introduction of accountable care organisations.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55081","55081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647210","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of accountable care organisations as a mechanism for improving efficiency.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55082","55082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647211","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the recent report from the all-party parliamentary group on occupational safety and health entitled Occupational medical workforce crisis, what steps he plans to take to ensure the occupational medicine workforce meets future demands for effective occupational health services.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55091","55091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647212","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish the number of NHS England's mental health workforce by nationality.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55113","55113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647213","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the extent of private sector involvement in accountable care organisations.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55083","55083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647214","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of the introduction of accountable care organisations on access to treatment.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55085","55085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647215","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has considered the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on delivering the required growth of the mental health workforce in England set out in the Five Year Forward View.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55098","55098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647216","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has funded into the potential relationship between bisphosphonates and instances of secondary breast cancer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55095","55095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647217","2016-12-01","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on how many children have been prescribed anti-depressants in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55140","55140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647218","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage clinical commissioning groups to commission psychological support for stroke survivors.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55134","55134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647219","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage better access to early supported discharge for stroke patients.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55135","55135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647220","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department is providing to clinical commissioning groups to improve provision for post-acute stroke care.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55136","55136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647221","2016-12-01","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's guidance, entitled implementation of section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016 in France, published on 14 November 2016, whether she plans to apply similar restrictions to those described in that document based on age or nationality to other children being considered for relocation to the UK under that section.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55180","55180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647222","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the merits of changing the eligibility criteria so that people aged over 80 years are entitled to apply for a free passport.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55133","55133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647223","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has conducted an assessment of the potential effect of reductions in housing payments for asylum seekers.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55110","55110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647224","2016-12-01","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the performance of VFS Global in providing visa services on behalf of UK Visas and Immigration in Iran.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55084","55084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647225","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Border Force operatives were deployed at (a) airports and (b) ports in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55051","55051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647226","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been to date of updating the warning index and Semaphore systems.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55052","55052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647227","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans that the warning index and Semaphore systems update will be completed.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55053","55053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647228","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of (a) flights, (b) sea transportation and (c) rail transportation has been risk-assessed when notified to the Border Force in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55054","55054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647229","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of Advanced Passenger Information checks has been completed by Border Force at primary check points on (a) scheduled flights, (b) unscheduled flights, (c) sea transportation and (d) rail transportation in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55055","55055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647230","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average waiting time at the UK border was for (a) British, European Economic Area (EEA) and Swiss passengers and (b) non-EEA passengers in (i) each year since 2010 and (ii) each month since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55058","55058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647231","2016-12-01","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the compatibility of her Department's guidance, entitled implementation of section 67 of the Immigration Act 2016 in France, published on 8 November 2016, with (a) the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child, (b) Article 2 of that convention and (c) the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55072","55072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647232","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2016 to Question 50110, whether her Department had made an assessment of the potential merits of requiring the collection of data on the presumed religion or belief or other key characteristics of alleged or suspected perpetrators of religiously or racially motivated attacks.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55265","55265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647233","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps  her  Department has taken to raise awareness of potential measures to reduce the risk of shoplifting and pick-pocketing in the Christmas period.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55272","55272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647234","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to improve (a) response times and (b) consistency across the UK in such times for the renewal of firearms licences.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55273","55273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647235","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of hate crime have been reported in each month of the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55224","55224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647236","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of hate crime were reported in each month of 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55203","55203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647237","2016-12-05","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects the Historic Child Abuse Inquiry to publish the review into its proceedings.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55202","55202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647238","2016-12-01","Department for International Development","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian aid needs of people in Aleppo.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55240","55240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647239","2016-12-01","Department for International Development","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, in relation to paragraph 5.22 of the Autumn Statement 2016, what assessment she has made of the effect of the planned reduction in her Department's budget; and whether any current projects are being considered for cancellation.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55212","55212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647240","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government has made an estimate of the number of refugee children awaiting entry to the UK who have gone missing in refugee camps.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55038","55038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647241","2016-12-01","Department for International Development","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 22 November 2016 to Question 53572, whether the UK made a financial contribution to the EU's Humanitarian Aid and Civil Protection Office (ECHO) in respect of the 180 structures funded by the ECHO and demolished by the Israeli government since 2009.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55142","55142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647242","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons it is not possible to make a (a) non-fixed monetary amount and (b) personal injury claim using the Money Claim Online website.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55131","55131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647243","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training is provided to magistrates and judges in Greater London on understanding the nature and effect of domestic abuse and of coercive and controlling behaviour.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55094","55094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647244","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the net income from employment tribunal fees was for the (a) first and (b) second quarter of 2016-17.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55092","55092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647245","2016-12-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers are predicted to leave the service in 2017 for reasons of (a) retirement, (b) reassignment, (c) dismissal and (d) redundancy.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55126","55126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647246","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the inquiries undertaken by (a) Hull City Council and (b) the NHS in Hull into issues arising from the loss of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North's constituent, Claire Clappison's son Hayden's ashes in 2003.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55099","55099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647247","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the inquiries undertaken by (a) Hull City Council and (b) the NHS in Hull into issues arising from the loss of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North's constituent, Tina Trowhill's son William's ashes in 1994.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55100","55100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647248","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have access to savings accounts for income earned from employment while they are in prison.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55056","55056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647249","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners are engaged in employment paying the living wage.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55057","55057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647250","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the inquiries undertaken by (a) Hull City Council and (b) the NHS in Hull into issues arising from the loss of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North's constituent, Linda Spring's son Raymond's ashes in 1996.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55101","55101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647251","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what account her Department plans to take of the findings of BIS Research Paper No. 235, on pregnancy and maternity-related discrimination and disadvantage, published in July 2015, in its review of employment tribunal fees.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55112","55112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647252","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the inquiries undertaken by (a) Hull City Council and (b) the NHS in Hull into issues arising from the loss of the constituent of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North Helen Dawson's son Jake's ashes in 2005.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55105","55105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647253","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the inquiries undertaken by (a) Hull City Council and (b) the NHS in Hull into issues arising from the loss of the constituent of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North Adele Thornton's daughter Chelsea's ashes in 2000.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55104","55104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647254","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the inquiries undertaken by (a) Hull City Council and (b) the NHS in Hull into issues arising from the loss of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North's constituent, Mandi Reeve's twins Scott and Sean's ashes in 1996.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55102","55102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647255","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the inquiries undertaken by (a) Hull City Council and (b) the NHS in Hull into issues arising from the loss of the constituent of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North Andrea Tarcey's triplets' ashes in 2006.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55103","55103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647256","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to support an inquiry by Hull City Council into the loss of the ashes of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North's constituent Andrea Tarcey's triplets in 2006.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55041","55041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647257","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to page 12 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, cm 9301, published in July 2016, what progress her Department has made on ascertaining why there have not been any prosecutions under section 22 of the Gender Recognition Act 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55064","55064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647258","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to page 24 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, cm 9301, published in July 2016, and page 3 of the Review on the care and management of transgender offenders, published in November 2016, what the timescale is for the introduction of a new NOMS-wide instruction on the management of transgender offenders.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55065","55065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647259","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to page 24 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, cm 9301, published in July 2016, what progress her Department has made in establishing an advisory group on transgender people in custody or subject to community supervision.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55066","55066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647260","2016-12-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment she has made of the reasons for high prison officer turnover; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55267","55267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647261","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timetable is for (a) recruitment and posting of the extra prison officers and (b) the special measures for vulnerable and mentally ill inmates announced in November 2016.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55241","55241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647262","2016-12-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the prison population.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55223","55223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647263","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of designating will writing as a reserved legal activity.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55155","55155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647264","2016-12-01","Scotland Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2016 to Question 54636, what the timetable is for completion of the Government's consideration of splitting competence; and whether the power to create new benefits in devolved areas and the power to top up reserved benefits will be capable of exercise before full executive competence has been transferred.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55233","55233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647265","2016-12-01","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what cost benefit analysis the Government has carried out on the potential financial risk for council taxpayers of powers being given to local authorities to reverse bus deregulation and replace it with bus franchising.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55234","55234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647266","2016-12-01","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to reduce the number of road accidents on the A595.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55147","55147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647267","2016-12-01","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many fatal accidents there have been on each A road in 2016.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55148","55148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647268","2016-12-01","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the exact date is of the change in the delayed repay threshold on the Southern Rail franchise.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55149","55149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647269","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2016 to Question 53656, how has the recruitment campaign been extended; whether those posts have been re-advertised; and how many people responded to the initial advertisement.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55165","55165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647270","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government has set a timetable for the electrification of the Mid-Cheshire railway line.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55169","55169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647271","2016-12-01","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2016 to Question 53180, which two individuals reported minor perceived conflicts of interest; and what was the perceived conflict reported in each such case.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55218","55218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647272","2016-12-01","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information he or officials of his Department hold on the number of delays or cancellations caused to Govia Thameslink Railway services by faulty rolling stock.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55217","55217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647273","2016-12-01","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding has been made available to his Department for redevelopment of rural rail stations in the Autumn Statement 2016.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55070","55070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647274","2016-12-01","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.18 of the Autumn Statement 2016, on electric vehicle charging points, what plans he has to ensure (a) greater compatibility between vehicles and charging points and (b) universal pricing systems for electric vehicle charging.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55073","55073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647275","2016-12-01","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Driver and Vehicle Agency posts there were in (a) Fermanagh and South Tyrone and (b) West Tyrone constituencies in (i) 2007-08 and (ii) the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55005","55005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647276","2016-12-01","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the level of planning by train operating companies of the availability of conductors or guards on train service delays and cancellations; and if he will place this information in the Library.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55010","55010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647277","2016-12-01","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether civil servants employed in his Department have been consultants to Govia Thameslink Railway in its bid for the Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern Franchise.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55011","55011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647278","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.17 of the Autumn Statement 2016, how the £1.1 billion investment in English local transport networks will be regionally allocated.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55049","55049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647279","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.17 of the Autumn Statement 2016, whether the £1.1 billion investment in local transport networks is in addition to the pothole action fund.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55048","55048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647280","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the DVLA's system for assessing older drivers.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55050","55050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647281","2016-11-30","HM Treasury","2016-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to review permissions for the use of red diesel in transport refrigeration units.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55128","55128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647282","2016-12-01","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on the application of the provisions of the Equality Act 2010 to driver only operation; and if he will place a copy of those representations in the Library.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55191","55191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647283","2016-12-01","Wales Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department has spent on ministerial travel in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55143","55143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647284","2016-12-01","Wales Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much tax revenue was collected from people in work in Wales in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55144","55144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647285","2016-12-01","Wales Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department has spent on alcoholic beverages in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55145","55145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647286","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the levels of customer satisfaction of passengers of the Wales and Border rail franchise.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55093","55093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647287","2016-12-01","Wales Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of the expected average wage level in Wales in 2020.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55014","55014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647288","2016-11-30","Wales Office","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the economy in Wales of restrictions to the free movement of people when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55019","55019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647289","2016-12-01","Women and Equalities","2016-11-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to page 11 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, column 9301, published in July 2016, what progress the Government has made on reviewing the Gender Recognition Act 2004 to determine whether changes can be made to streamline and de-medicalise the gender recognition process.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55074","55074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647290","2016-12-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to page 11 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, column 9301, published in July 2016, what steps the Government has taken since the publication of that response to monitor the possibility and incidence of victimisation of transgender people arising from the spousal consent provision of the Marriage (Same Sex Couples) Act 2013.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55075","55075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647291","2016-12-01","Women and Equalities","2016-11-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to page 8 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, column 9301, published in July 2016, and pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2016 to Question 45657, what progress the Government has made on (a) publishing update reports on the documents Working for Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Equality: Moving Forward and Advancing transgender equality: a plan for action, published in 2011 and (b) producing a new action plan on transgender equality.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55076","55076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647292","2016-12-01","Women and Equalities","2016-11-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to page 30 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, Cm 9301, published in July 2016, to which heads of profession she wrote highlighting the need for training on transgender issues for their profession and asking them to introduce training if not already available and to monitor the effectiveness of any training provided; and what information she holds on steps taken by heads of profession in response to those letters.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55077","55077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647293","2016-12-01","Women and Equalities","2016-11-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to page 22 of the Government response to the First Report from the Women and Equalities Committee, Session 2015-16, on Transgender Equality, Cm 9301, published in July 2016, what the outcomes have been of the Government's internal review of gender markers in official documents.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Mrs Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55078","55078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647294","2016-11-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appointments for claimants applying for personal independence payments have been rearranged or cancelled at the request of a person other than the claimant in (a) Plymouth and (b) the South West in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55127","55127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647295","2016-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) East Ham constituency, (b) the London Borough of Newham and (c) Greater London have been classified as under-occupying their homes in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55231","55231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647296","2016-12-01","HM Treasury","2016-11-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether under the proposed limitation of child tax credits to the first two children in a household, a third child in that household with a date of birth after April 2017 would be eligible for child tax credit payment, if the second child were cared for under kinship care arrangements or had been born as a result of non-consensual sex.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55214","55214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647297","2016-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2016 to Question 54256, what steps the Child Poverty Unit is taking to reduce poverty among children living in working households.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55237","55237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647298","2016-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have moved into work from receiving out-of-work benefits in each of the last five years; and how many such people have moved into work with a salary above 60 per cent of median household income in each of those years by year.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55249","55249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647299","2016-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have moved into work and earn above the national minimum wage from receiving out-of-work benefits in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55250","55250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647300","2016-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to enable people in low-paid professions to move into positions with a higher salary.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55251","55251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647301","2016-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many hardship payments have been issued by his Department to people living in (a) East Ham constituency, (b) the London Borough of Newham and (c) Greater London in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55268","55268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647302","2016-12-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 6.2 of the Autumn Statement 2016, what the reasons were for the error which resulted in families with disabled children not being in receipt of their full tax credit entitlement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55270","55270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647303","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support rural post offices.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55166","55166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647304","2016-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has for the future staffing of Innovate UK.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55186","55186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647305","2016-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much has been paid to McKinsey for its work on the BIS 2020 project; and what further such payments are due.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55185","55185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647306","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has for the future staffing of the Insolvency Service.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55153","55153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647308","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to establish an extended ministerial office.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55154","55154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647309","2016-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the BIS 2020 project is ongoing.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55184","55184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647310","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to identify, promote and develop innovations in (a) wind, (b) wave, (c) tidal and (d) riverflow cold renewables.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55151","55151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647311","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate the Government has made of the projected use of biomass fuels in each of the next 20 years.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55150","55150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647312","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish a consultation on changes to the Energy Efficiency (Private Rented Property) (England and Wales) Regulations 2015 required as a result of the end of the Green Deal.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55097","55097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647313","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of Warm Home Discount recipients who are (a) British Gas, (b) EON, (c) nPower, (d) Scottish Power, (e) SSE and (f) Big Six customers overall are on their supplier's variable tariff.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55108","55108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647314","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of Priority Service Register customers of (a) British Gas, (b) EON, (c) nPower, (d) Scottish Power, (e) SSE and (f) the Big Six energy companies on their supplier's standard variable tariff.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55109","55109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647315","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 7.5 of the Fuel Poverty Strategy, on what date the first annual fuel poverty debate in Parliament was held; and when the Government plans to timetable the next such debate.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55114","55114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647316","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many fuel poor households are living in properties that have been assessed for an energy performance certificate the result of which has been placed on the register.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55106","55106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647317","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of Priority Service Register customers of (a) British Gas, (b) EON, (c) nPower, (d) Scottish Power, (e) SSE and (f) the Big Six energy companies have been on their supplier's variable tariff for (i) three years or over, (ii) five years or over, (iii) 10 years or over and (iv) 15 years or over.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55107","55107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647318","2016-12-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 4.9 of the Government's Northern Powerhouse Strategy, published in November 2016, from which funding streams the £100 million spending to 2020-21 on incentivising university collaboration in tech transfer and working with business will be drawn; and how those funds will be distributed.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55071","55071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647319","2016-11-30","Department for International Trade","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether he has had any discussions with Cabinet colleagues on the potential for the EU having to pay compensation to countries with which it has trade deals as a result of the shrinking of the market when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55020","55020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647320","2016-12-01","Department for International Trade","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the value was of seafood exports from Northern Ireland in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2014-15 and (d) 2015-16.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55069","55069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647321","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he plans to take to ensure that businesses in the UK continue to benefit from the activities of the EU observatory on trademark protection after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55037","55037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647322","2016-11-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU Single Market on the UK shipping industry.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55046","55046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647323","2016-11-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will make time available for hon. Members to debate the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on health and social care.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55030","55030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647324","2016-11-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will take steps to ensure that negotiations on the UK's exit from the EU will support the UK's insurance industry so that it remains a significant UK export industry.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55039","55039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647325","2016-11-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his Department's budget is for hiring staff needed to facilitate the negotiations to leave the EU in 2016-17.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55266","55266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647326","2016-12-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether his policy is to trigger Article 50 by 31 March 2017.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55253","55253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647327","2016-12-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2016 to Question 47680, if he will list the consultancy firms that his Department has utilised the services of on a pro bono or nominal (£1) basis to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55210","55210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/647328","2016-12-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answers of 15 September and 13 October 2016 to Questions 45944 and 47680, if he will list the consultancy firms that his Department has utilised the services of not on a pro bono or nominal (£1) basis to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55211","55211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/648937","2016-12-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he plans to take during the UK's negotiations to leave the EU to ensure that (a) the financial and competitive position of UK agriculture is maintained and (b) UK agriculture can provide national food security after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907597","907597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644284","2016-11-29","Cabinet Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if the Government will bring forward legislative proposals to extend the franchise to 16 and 17 year olds for the next UK general election.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54916","54916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644285","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 4.13 of the Autumn Statement 2016, on the term convicted loan sharks, (a) what those offences were and (b) which agency has responsibility for prosecuting those offences.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54926","54926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644286","2016-11-30","HM Treasury","2016-11-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much Growth Deal funding he plans to make available to the Mayor of the West Midlands Combined Authority from May 2017.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54936","54936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644287","2016-11-29","Church Commissioners","2016-11-25","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, if the Church Commissioners will make it their policy that the next nominee for the Bishop of London will ordain both women and men as priests.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54965","54965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644288","2016-11-29","Church Commissioners","2016-11-25","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what assessment the Church of England has made of the appropriateness of procedures and practice relating to the Dean of Peterborough Cathedral standing down.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54985","54985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644289","2016-11-30","Church Commissioners","2016-11-25","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what the Church of England's policy is on erecting new war memorial plaques.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54987","54987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644290","2016-11-30","Church Commissioners","2016-11-25","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to support the commemoration of the contribution of the armed services by supporting veterans in establishing new war memorials in churches.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54988","54988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644291","2016-11-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 3.5 of Autumn Statement 2016, how many affordable homes to rent will be built in each year from 2017 to 2020; and how many of those homes will be built with a central government grant.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54973","54973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644292","2016-11-30","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many tenants in Greater Manchester were evicted through the courts in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54970","54970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644293","2016-11-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of powers available to community groups to appeal against housing development targets drawn up by local authorities.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54979","54979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644296","2016-11-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of new housing being developed in Worcestershire in the next three years which will be specifically reserved for first-time buyers.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54920","54920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644297","2016-11-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that new housing developments support economic growth and increase job creation in Worcestershire.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54921","54921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644298","2016-11-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will hold discussions with local authority leaders in Yorkshire on creating a post of Mayor of Yorkshire.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54910","54910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644299","2016-11-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to require planning permission before the use of a building is changed from Use Class A4 to A1.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54911","54911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644300","2016-11-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2016 to Question 52441, if he will take steps to promote the use of EU structural funds to support greater Roma involvement in the labour market.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54951","54951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644301","2016-11-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the comparative contribution of the UK, Europe and China to international standards development for the digital sector; and what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on that contribution and the development of those standards.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54990","54990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644302","2016-11-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has had discussions with the BBC Trust on proposals to tender 60 per cent of BBC radio production; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54968","54968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644303","2016-11-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what contribution the Government is making to the development of standards in the digital industry; and how many employees in her Department work on developing such standards.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54989","54989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644304","2016-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2016 to Questions 52667 and 52666, whether the £2.97 million paid to Red Snapper investigators for expenses is included in, or in addition to, the £20.8 million paid to Red Snapper since 2013.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54966","54966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644305","2016-11-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 45624, on war widows' pensions, what recent progress he has made with his Department's review of its policy on compensation for war widows who remarried between 1973 and 2005.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54955","54955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644306","2016-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with Fife Council on MoD Caledonia and the reallocation of land use in the Fife Plan to include housing on that site.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54928","54928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644307","2016-11-29","Department for Education","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the contribution to the UK economy of overseas students studying at (a) Russell Group, (b) University Alliance and (c) MillionPlus universities.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54929","54929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644308","2016-11-30","Department for Education","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 3 May 2016 to Question HL8119, what (a) her policy is on and (b) criteria will be used to allocate the £300 million for failing schools.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54969","54969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644309","2016-11-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to her oral contribution of 24 November 2016, Official Report, column 1004, whether that investment is in addition to the investment in flood defences announced in the March 2016 Budget.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54981","54981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644310","2016-11-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which postcodes in Leeds City Region her Department has identified as being vulnerable to potential winter flooding.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54931","54931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644311","2016-11-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether she has identified any existing flood defences in Leeds City Region as being inadequate to deal with potential winter flooding.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54932","54932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644312","2016-11-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the annual expenditure by farmers on pre-movement testing and other short interval tests.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54927","54927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644313","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that migrant worker rights are on the agenda for the next session of the UN Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54914","54914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644314","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that religious persecution is on the agenda for the next session of the UN Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54915","54915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644315","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to Egypt to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Egypt.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54949","54949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644316","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to Burkina Faso to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Burkina Faso.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54950","54950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644317","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to Kenya to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Kenya.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54948","54948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644318","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to Guinea Bissau to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Guinea Bissau.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54938","54938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644319","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, to which countries his Department has gifted equipment costing less than £300,000 per gift in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54908","54908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644320","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of his Department's Overseas Security and Justice Assistance guidance.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54909","54909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644321","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that arbitrary revocation of citizenship is on the agenda for the next session of the UN Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54912","54912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644322","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure that the juvenile death penalty is on the agenda for the next session of the UN Human Rights Council.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54913","54913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644323","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to Iraq to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Iraq.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54939","54939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644324","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to Togo to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Togo.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54940","54940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644325","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to Indonesia to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Indonesia.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54941","54941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644326","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to the Ivory Coast to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of the Ivory Coast.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54942","54942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644327","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to Nigeria to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Nigeria.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54943","54943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644328","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to Niger to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Niger.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54944","54944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644329","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to Benin to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Benin.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54945","54945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644330","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to the Central African Republic to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54946","54946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644331","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will urge the UK diplomatic representative to Yemen to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Yemen.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54947","54947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644332","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the implications are for his policies of the decision by the French parliament to establish a national compensation fund for people affected by the teratogenic effects of sodium valproate.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54957","54957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644333","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 53657, what the (a) planned and (b) budgeted spend was for mental health in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54958","54958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644334","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 53657, whether the figures provided in that Answer on mental health spending are adjusted for inflation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54959","54959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644335","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) outturn, (b) planned spend and (c) budgeted spend in programme allocation growth for specialist commissioning was in each category in 2014-15 and 2015-16 in (i) cash and (ii) real terms.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54960","54960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644336","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 53657, what the difference was between the total mental health spending for 2014-15 and 2015-16 provided in that Answer and the amount of such spending before it was revised to take into account NHS England's planning guidance to clinical commissioning groups on consistent reporting of mental health spending.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54961","54961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644337","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 53657, whether the revised baseline has been applied retrospectively to the mental health spending figure for 2014-15 to take into account NHS England's planning guidance to clinical commissioning groups on consistent reporting of mental health spending.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54962","54962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644338","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the officials from his Department who attended the seventh conference of the Parties of World Health Organisation Framework Convention on Tobacco Control met with representatives of the Group Action on Smoking and Health during that conference.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54974","54974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644339","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual budget for tobacco control was in each of the last five years; and how much of that budget was spent (a) internally within his Department, (b) on UK activities or grants and (c) on international activities or grants.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54978","54978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644340","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure GPs are added to the medical performers list in a timely fashion.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54982","54982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644341","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average time was for adding newly qualified GPs to the NHS England medical performers list in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54976","54976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644342","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding on tobacco control has been provided by his Department to (a) international governmental organisations and agencies and (b) international non-governmental organisations and agencies in each of the last five years; and if he will provide a list of those such organisations and agencies.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54977","54977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644343","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 22 November 2016 to Questions 53110, 53111 and 53107, how many pharmacies qualify for Pharmacy Access Scheme funding in each decile of the Indices of Multiple Deprivation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55000","55000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644344","2016-11-30","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answers of 22 November 2016 to Questions 53110, 53111 and 53107, how many pharmacies will qualify for funding from the Pharmacy Access Scheme in (a) the East Riding of Yorkshire, (b) South West Surrey constituency, (c) Ludlow constituency, (d) Oxford West and Abingdon constituency, (e) Warrington South constituency and (f) Maidenhead constituency.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 55001","55001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644345","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will take steps to ensure that (a) financially vulnerable and (b) less mobile members of society are not disadvantaged by any increase in journey times between points of (i) primary and (ii) acute health care services.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54925","54925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644346","2016-11-29","Home Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what checks are applied by the UK Border Agency to Heads of State and Heads of Government, and their staff, who visit the UK.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54953","54953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644347","2016-11-30","Home Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications for asylum seekers housed in Greater Manchester have been refused in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54964","54964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644348","2016-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department plans to take to (a) improve retention of and (b) reduce staff turnover among prison officers.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54923","54923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644349","2016-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average turnaround time was between receipt of a claim form by the County Court Money Claims Centre and that form being returned to the issuing solicitors in (a) October 2016, (b) September 2016 and (c) the 6 months to September 2016.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54902","54902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644350","2016-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons personal injury claims have to be sent to the County Court Money Claims Centre in Salford by post.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54903","54903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644351","2016-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the number of offenders (a) breached and (b) who have their orders terminated for good progess affects the amount paid in a contractual year to a community rehabilitation company.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54906","54906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644352","2016-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, to what extent contracts between her Department and community rehabilitation companies are dependent on offenders under supervision completing their orders.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54907","54907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644353","2016-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information her Department holds on the average number of applicants received for prison officer vacancies.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54924","54924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644354","2016-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the (a) estimated number of offenders to be allocated to community rehabilitation companies and (b) actual number of offenders so referred have an effect on the overall contract price.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54905","54905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644355","2016-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time district judges are appointed to sit in magistrates' courts on criminal cases.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54952","54952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644356","2016-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the number of offenders breached by a community rehabilitation company affects the total amount paid by her Department in a given financial year to that company.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54904","54904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644357","2016-11-30","Scotland Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to his oral contribution of 23 November 2016, Official Report, columns 879-880, what actions the Government has taken to enable opencast coal restoration within East Ayrshire; and where that restoration work has taken place.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54998","54998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644358","2016-11-30","Scotland Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to his oral contribution of 23 November 2016, Official Report, columns 879-80, how much the Government has spent on enabling open cast restoration works to be undertaken within (a) Scotland and (b) East Ayrshire.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54983","54983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644359","2016-11-30","Scotland Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to his oral contribution of 23 November 2016, Official Report, columns 879-880, and the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20538, how many meetings he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer to discuss assistance for opencast coal restoration works within East Ayrshire; and on what dates those meetings were held.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54999","54999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644360","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department has received from Govia Thameslink Railway on the effect on service levels of the shortage of train crew on the Govia Thameslink Railway franchise.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54992","54992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644361","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on driver-only operation from (a) the Disabled Persons Transport Advisory Committee and (b) any other organisations representing disabled people.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54991","54991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644362","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the amount of time it takes to despatch a train under (a) driver and (b) guard conductor dispatch.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54994","54994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644363","2016-11-29","Department for Transport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of rail connectivity to each of the UK's 20 busiest airports.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54980","54980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644364","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department has received from Govia Thameslink Railway on what the exceptional circumstances are that will allow trains to run without an on-board service supervisor.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54993","54993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644365","2016-11-29","Department for Transport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of High Speed 2 on the (a) speed and (b) efficiency of travel for people travelling within the Midlands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54922","54922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644366","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the Tram-Train pilot between Sheffield and Rotherham to start its passenger service.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54933","54933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644367","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has had discussions with Transport for the North on the roll-out of an Oyster card-type system for the North of England.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54934","54934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644368","2016-11-29","Department for Transport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on the consideration of the feasibility of a road tunnel between Sheffield and Manchester; and what the timetable is for future such consideration.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54918","54918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644369","2016-11-29","Department for Transport","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to ensure that all rolling stock on the Midland Mainline is compliant with disability legislation by 2020.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54917","54917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644370","2016-11-30","Wales Office","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many meetings he had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer specifically to discuss Welsh infrastructure projects between July 2016 and the Autumn Statement 2016.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54935","54935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644371","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when the Government plans to respond to the Independent Review of Tidal Lagoons, led by Charles Hendry.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54997","54997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644372","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the equality impact analysis published on 25 November 2016 by the Women's Budget Group and the Runnymeade Trust on the effect of the Autumn Statement 2016 on women and people from ethnic minority backgrounds; and what plans he has to respond to that publication.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54930","54930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644373","2016-11-29","Women and Equalities","2016-11-25","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if the Government will undertake a detailed analysis of (a) the pay gap between women of African, Caribbean, Asian and Minority Ethnic backgrounds and women of other backgrounds and (b) what steps can be taken to reduce that pay gap.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54954","54954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644374","2016-11-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of whether the premises used by Atos Healthcare to conduct personal independence payment (PIP) assessments at Queensbury House, Brighton (a) complies with relevant equalities legislation, (b) offers sufficient protection of confidentiality to those attending  assessments, (c) has toilets accessible on the same floor as assessments take place, (d) has sufficient space for wheelchairs in the waiting area and (e) is a suitable premises for PIP assessments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54919","54919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644375","2016-11-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many hardship payments have been issued by his Department to people living in Greater Manchester in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54971","54971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644376","2016-11-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Greater Manchester have been classified as under occupying their homes in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54972","54972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644377","2016-11-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseeker's allowance claimants in Greater Manchester have had their benefits suspended in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54963","54963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644378","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, for what reasons the UK was not a signatory to the Joint Statement issued by the High Ambition Coalition ministers on 11 November 2016 during the 22nd Conference of the Parties to the UN Framework Convention on Climate Change.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54996","54996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644379","2016-11-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the letter from the Committee on Climate Change to his Department, of 22 November 2016, if he will make it his policy that final approval of additional capacity at Heathrow Airport is contingent on the UK meeting its carbon budgets in 2050 without international offsets or additional emissions reductions being required in other sectors of the economy.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54937","54937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644380","2016-12-01","Department for International Trade","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what export licences have been granted for the sale of British-made policing equipment in the last 12 months; and to which countries each of those licenses was granted for.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54956","54956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644381","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what research his Department has commissioned on the effect on the UK's future trade balance of the UK leaving the customs union.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54967","54967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644382","2016-11-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the cost to UK businesses of resolving future cross-border trademark and patent disputes through court action after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54984","54984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644383","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment the Government has made of the potential for additional costs or complexities for medicines manufacturers in securing separate regulatory approval for products for the UK and the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54975","54975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644384","2016-11-29","Department for International Trade","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment his Department has made of which countries offer potential markets for UK-based defence small and medium-sized enterprises to export armoured fighting vehicles or associated equipment and services; and what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Defence and the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Climate Change on such markets.","Biography information for Dr James Davies","Dr James Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54986","54986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644385","2016-11-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many full-time equivalent civil servants employed by his Department are working exclusively on issues arising for Wales as a result of the UK voting to leave the EU; and what the civil service grade is of each of those officials.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54995","54995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643811","2016-11-28","Attorney General","2016-11-24","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the implementation of the UK's domestic and international legal obligations on human rights.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54676","54676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643812","2016-11-28","Cabinet Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many internships currently exist in all government departments.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54796","54796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643813","2016-11-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent estimate she has made of the number of households capable of receiving 30 megabits a second.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54820","54820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643814","2016-11-28","Cabinet Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people employed in human resources roles in the civil service have (a) prior experience and (b) qualifications in human resources.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54840","54840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643815","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the full analysis undertaken by his Department's tax and benefit microsimulation model on the Autumn Statement 2016.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54874","54874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643816","2016-11-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much grant funding West Midlands Combined Authority will receive in financial year 2017-18 for (a) adult education, (b) transport, (c) the Work and Health Programme, (d) business support and (e) any other sources of funding by grant.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54823","54823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643817","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to publish the Midlands Engine strategy.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54824","54824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643818","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the amount of funding the Greater Birmingham and Solihull Local Enterprise Partnership will receive under the Growth Deal announced in paragraph 3.49 of the Autumn Statement 2016.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54826","54826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643819","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on reforming the reporting of air passenger duty to attribute that duty to each airport.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54789","54789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643820","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.25 of the Autumn Statement 2016, whether that investment in flood defence and resilience measures is in addition to the investment in flood defences announced in the March 2016 Budget.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54791","54791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643821","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the full terms of his planned Investment Guaranteed Growth Bonds.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54792","54792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643822","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of participants in the Employee Shareholder Status scheme in (a) Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54693","54693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643823","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking as part of the negotiations for the UK to leave the EU to improve the competitiveness of the UK insurance industry.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54847","54847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643824","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with external organisations on the effect of the Autumn Statement 2016 on child poverty.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54871","54871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643825","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Autumn Statement 2016 on child poverty.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54872","54872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643826","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Autumn Statement 2016 on excess winter deaths.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54873","54873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643827","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many criminal prosecutions there were against illegal consumer credit providers by the Financial Conduct Authority in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54860","54860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643828","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he next plans to visit Copeland constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54674","54674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643829","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the London and South Coast Rail Corridor Study; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54670","54670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643830","2016-11-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an estimate of the number of pubs that will benefit from the extension of rural rates relief.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54675","54675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643831","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many P800 adjustments were issued to individual taxpayers to correct for an over or under-payment of income tax in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54672","54672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643832","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the West Midlands Combined Authority on granting that Authority power to fund non-transport infrastructure projects.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54685","54685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643833","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Statement 2016, Table 2.1, line 32, what proportion of that total spend is subject to Barnett consequentials; and what the subsequent value is of Barnett consequential funding allocated to Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54717","54717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643834","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Statement 2016, table 2.1, line 10, what proportion of that total spend is subject to Barnett consequentials; and what the subsequent value is of Barnett consequential funding allocated to Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54735","54735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643835","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Statement 2016, table 2.1, line 9, what proportion of that total spend is subject to Barnett consequentials; and what the subsequent value is of Barnett consequential funding allocated to Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54736","54736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643836","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Statement 2016, table 2.1, line 8, what proportion of that total spend is subject to Barnett consequentials; and what the subsequent value is of Barnett consequential funding allocated to Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54737","54737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643837","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Statement 2016, table 2.1, line 16, what proportion of that total spend is subject to Barnett consequentials; and what the subsequent value is of Barnett consequential funding allocated to Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54738","54738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643838","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Statement 2016, table 2.1, line 31, what proportion of that total spend is subject to Barnett consequentials; and what the subsequent value is of Barnett consequential funding allocated to Scotland.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54739","54739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643839","2016-11-29","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Ministerial Statement of 18 November 2016, HCWS 269, if he will ensure that the £53.9 million due to policy holders who could not be paid will be allocated and distributed among other former Equitable Life policy holders.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54772","54772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643840","2016-11-28","Church Commissioners","2016-11-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, whether a Bishop of London has ordained a woman as a priest.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54893","54893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643841","2016-11-28","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of regulation of long-term leasehold properties.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54776","54776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643842","2016-11-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish funding allocations for Birmingham City Council.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54822","54822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643843","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the level of dementia training provided to homecare workers delivering care to people with dementia.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54720","54720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643844","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all homecare workers receive dementia-specific training in every local authority.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54721","54721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643845","2016-11-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what comparative assessment she has made of trends in levels of television programming by and for BME groups in the US and UK.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54773","54773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643846","2016-11-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent estimate she has made of the number of households consistently receiving speeds of 30 megabits a second or above.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54835","54835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643847","2016-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to extend the criteria for the use of the HM Forces railcard to veterans.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54837","54837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643848","2016-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to publish the National Shipbuilding Strategy.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54838","54838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643849","2016-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to replace the GWS 60/Harpoon Block 1C anti-ship missiles when they are withdrawn from Royal Navy service at the end of 2016.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54839","54839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643850","2016-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons publication of the National Shipbuilding Strategy has been delayed.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54821","54821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643851","2016-11-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will investigate for what reasons military helicopters flying over Manchester on 27 October 2016 did so without running lights; and what communications were made between the Royal Air Force and Manchester City Council on that exercise.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54891","54891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643852","2016-11-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many helicopters flew over properties in Manchester on 26 October 2016 as part of a military exercise.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54892","54892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643853","2016-11-30","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department plans to give the Crown Estate notice that it will be releasing its tenancy of the Citadel.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54901","54901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643854","2016-11-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's report, a Better Defence Estate, published in November 2016, what the annual running costs were for MoD Caledonia in each financial year from 2011-12 to 2015-16.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54853","54853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643855","2016-11-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with Fife Council on the disposal of MoD Caledonia.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54854","54854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643856","2016-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to establish a separate railcard for armed forces veterans as part of his policy initiatives arising from the Armed Forces Covenant.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54836","54836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643857","2016-11-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the issuing of compensation of ex gratia payments to civilians killed or injured by UK airstrikes.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54689","54689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643858","2016-11-28","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many RAF crews have been embedded in the Canadian military on maritime patrol duties in each year since 2010; and how many of those crew members no longer serve in the UK armed forces.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54682","54682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643859","2016-11-29","Department for Education","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that Newham Borough Council is fully funded to implement the Government's educational reforms on provision for children and young people with special needs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54671","54671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643860","2016-11-28","Department for Education","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to bring forward the legislative proposals that will be required as a consequence of the planned removal of the Education Services Grant to local authorities.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54716","54716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643861","2016-11-28","Department for Education","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to promote arts subjects in schools.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54740","54740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643862","2016-11-29","Department for Education","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools have been judged by Ofsted to not provide the necessary level of support to children with medical conditions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54885","54885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643863","2016-11-29","Department for Education","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will provide funding for the rebuilding of the Whitehaven Academy.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54886","54886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643864","2016-11-29","Department for Education","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's target number for new entrants to early years initial teacher training programme has been for each academic year since that programme was established; and what that target is for each of the next three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54831","54831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643865","2016-11-29","Department for Education","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new entrants of the early years initial teacher training programme received a bursary and subsequently withdrew or failed to complete the course in each year since that programme was established.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54830","54830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643866","2016-11-28","Department for Education","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Northern Powerhouse Schools Strategy, published on 23 November 2016, what estimate she has made of the level of underfunding of schools in the north of England.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54788","54788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643867","2016-11-28","Department for Education","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of mathematics teachers who teach pupils at key stage (a) 1, (b) 2, (c) 3 and (d) 4 have a mathematics degree.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54841","54841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643868","2016-11-29","Department for Education","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many entrants to the early years initial teacher training programme received a government bursary of what amount in each year since 2013-14.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54828","54828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643869","2016-11-29","Department for Education","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many entrants to the early years initial teacher training programme have (a) completed, (b) withdrawn from and (c) failed to finish that programme in (i) 2013-14, (ii) 2015-16 and (iii) 2016-17.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54829","54829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643870","2016-11-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much has been spent from the public purse on flood (a) defence and (b) prevention schemes in Cumbria in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54825","54825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643871","2016-11-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many farmers have been underpaid under the 2015 Basic Payments Scheme.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54834","54834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643872","2016-11-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to paragraph 3.25 of the Autumn Statement 2016, which schemes will receive the £20 million of investment in new flood defences.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54833","54833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643873","2016-11-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her plans are for replacing the EU Blue Flag Scheme to ensure the cleanliness of beaches, protection of wildlife and the enforcement of sea regulations after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54862","54862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643874","2016-11-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Government spent on annual testing of cattle in the high risk, edge and low risk areas in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54844","54844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643875","2016-11-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) average, (b) minimum and (c) longest time between an animal testing positive for TB at a farm test and being collected from that farm for destruction has been in the last 12 months.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54845","54845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643876","2016-11-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many abattoirs in the UK process TB reactor cattle.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54846","54846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643877","2016-11-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on how many of the flood defence and prevention schemes that were announced in Budget 2016 construction has begun.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54898","54898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643878","2016-11-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many abattoirs in the UK processed TB reactor cattle in 2016.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54741","54741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643879","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many TB reactor cattle were taken to each abattoir in the last 12 months.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54742","54742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643880","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many abattoirs have adequate lairage for cattle kept overnight.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54743","54743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643881","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the Government's welfare standards are for adequate lairage for TB reactor cattle which are kept overnight.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54744","54744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643882","2016-11-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the furthest distance is in (a) time and (b) mileage that a TB reactor cow has travelled to a UK abattoir which processed TB reactor cattle in the last three years.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54745","54745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643883","2016-11-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the annual value is, excluding testing costs on farm or in a laboratory, of TB reactor salvage to the Government.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54747","54747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643884","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the longest time is that a TB reactor cow has spent in lairage before its destruction.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54748","54748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643885","2016-11-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the total cost of transport and lairage is for TB reactor cattle travelling the furthest distance.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54746","54746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643886","2016-11-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to paragraph 3.25 of the Autumn Statement 2016, which flood defence schemes in Lancashire have been granted funding.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54667","54667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643887","2016-11-28","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether mechanisms to reducing the UK's international footprint outside the UK and in the UK's Overseas Territories will be included in her Department's planned 25 year environment plan.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54668","54668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643888","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 52971, if he will instruct the UK Ambassador with responsibility for Djibouti to make representations on the practice of female genital mutilation to the government of Djibouti.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54686","54686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643889","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Malaysian counterpart on the (a) use of the Security Offences (Special Measures) Act 2012 in that country to arrest and detain Maria Chin Abdullah and other peaceful demonstrators and campaigners and (b) release of those demonstrators detained under that Act.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54680","54680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643890","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Government last made an assessment of the safety and stability of manmade structures of the outer islands of the British Indian Ocean Territory; and when the Government next plans to make such an assessment.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54666","54666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643891","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many customers have used the British Indian Ocean Territories post office (a) in person and (b) online in each year for which records are available.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54665","54665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643892","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Sudanese counterpart on the trial of members and affiliates of the Centre for Training and Human Development.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54661","54661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643893","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the fairness of the trial relating to members and affiliates of the Centre for Training and Human Development in Sudan.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54662","54662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643894","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Sudanese counterpart on the six-month detention of Khalafalla Al-Afif Mukhtar, Midhat Afif Al-Deen Hamdan and Mustafa Adam on charges relating to their work and affiliation with the Centre for Training and Human Development.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54663","54663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643895","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what arrangements are in place for the ownership and management of the British Indian Ocean Territories post office.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54664","54664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643896","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to visit Burma to discuss the (a) promotion of human rights, (b) strengthening of democratic process and (c) protection of ethnic, religious and sexual minorities.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54758","54758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643897","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security and human rights situation in Rakhine, Burma.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54759","54759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643898","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with (a) his Burmese counterpart, (b) Htin Kyaw, (c) elected officials of the National League for Democracy and (d) Aung San Suu Kyi on transitioning from the former military government to the current government in that country.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54760","54760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643899","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Burmese counterpart on the recently reported attacks on (a) Yekai Chaung Gwasone, (b) Dar Gyi Sar and (c) Myaw Taung.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54757","54757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643900","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his US counterpart on international co-operation to tackle climate change.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54730","54730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643901","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Minister of State for Climate Change and Industry on the Government's approach to tackling climate change.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54731","54731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643902","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department takes to monitor the (a) number and (b) behaviour of private visitors to the British Indian Ocean territory.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54702","54702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643903","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for how many years the Government has been issuing mooring permits for yachts visiting the British Indian Ocean territory; and how many such permits have been issued in each year for which records are available.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54701","54701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643904","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to retain the role of Special Representative for Climate Change within his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54732","54732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643905","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to appoint a new Special Representative for Climate Change.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54733","54733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643906","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Indian government on ensuring that demonetised 500 and 1,000 rupee notes can be exchanged in the UK before the end of 2016.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54889","54889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643907","2016-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has undertaken any evaluation of how training the Burmese military has led to improvements in human rights.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54899","54899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643908","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the alleged incident of rape of Rohingya women by security forces in Rakhine State, Burma, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54815","54815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643909","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has raised with Burma State Counsellor Daw Aung San Suu Kyi  (a) the banning of media from areas of Rakhine State, (b) government blocking of humanitarian aid to Rohingya in Rakhine State and (c) the sacking of Myanmar Times journalist Fiona MacGregor for reporting on the mass rape of ethnic Rohingya women.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54864","54864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643910","2016-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has undertaken a review of offering further training to the Burmese military to take account of recent serious human rights violations by the Burmese military against Rohingya civilians in Rakhine State and against ethnic Kachin civilians in Kachin State and northern Shan State, Burma.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54867","54867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643911","2016-11-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on whether any Burmese Army soldiers who have received training from the UK are involved in military operations against the Rohingya in Rakhine State.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54868","54868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643912","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Egypt on the imprisonment of journalists and curtailment of the free press in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54851","54851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643913","2016-11-28","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Turkey on the imprisonment of journalists and curtailment of the free press in that country.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54852","54852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643914","2016-11-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the decision by President Kabila of the Democratic Republic of Congo to delay elections due to take place in November 2016 until April 2018; and whether he has made an assessment of the adequacy of the funding made available by the EU for those elections.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54774","54774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643915","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the potential merits of issuing qualifying patients with medical identification cards as part of his Department's policy on health tourism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54780","54780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643916","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate how many proposals for new medical technologies the NICE Technology Appraisal Committee has discussed in the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54777","54777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643917","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the number of people requiring social care who do not receive such care.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54787","54787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643918","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Local Government Association press release, entitled £2.6 billion could be needed to fix social care, published on 13 October 2016, what steps he is taking to reduce the funding gap in social care.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54790","54790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643919","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on future death reports that have been issued in relation to NHS trusts in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54875","54875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643920","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the proposals for changes to the arrangements for evaluating and funding drugs and other health technologies appraised through NICE's technology appraisal and highly specialised programmes, published on 13 October 2016, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of proposals for the introduction of a budget impact threshold on the level of inward investment into the UK life sciences sector.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54855","54855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643921","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many referrals to the Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme ended after (a) entering treatment and (b) completing treatment without receiving an assessment in each clinical commissioning group in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54877","54877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643922","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were prescribed vitamin B12 treatment for a mental health condition in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54878","54878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643923","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions for antidepressants were dispensed in each month of each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54879","54879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643924","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 November 2016 to Question 53657, whether the figures given on mental health spending for 2014-15 and 2015-16 include specialist commissioning by NHS England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54876","54876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643925","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the effect of NICE technology appraisal recommendations on the level of uptake of new medical technologies among NHS healthcare providers.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54858","54858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643926","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the proposals for changes to the arrangements for evaluating and funding drugs and other health technologies appraised through NICE's technology appraisal and highly specialised programmes, published on 13 October 2016, what international evidence was taken into account when setting out the proposals for the (a) implementation and (b) level of the budget impact threshold.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54859","54859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643927","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to support terminally ill children and their families.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54687","54687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643928","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to encourage local authorities to contribute more funding to palliative care organisations.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54688","54688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643929","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital bed days were lost in (a) St Helens, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK due to delays in discharging patients in each year from 2010 to 2016.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54770","54770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643930","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish all correspondence between NHS England and (a) St Helens City Council, (b) St Helens Clinical Commissioning Group and (c) St Helens and Knowsley Teaching Hospitals NHS Trust on sustainability and transformation plans.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54769","54769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643931","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital bed days were lost in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK due to a lack of social care provision available for people being discharged from hospital in each year from 2010 to 2016.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54768","54768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643932","2016-11-29","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in (a) St Helens North constituency, (b) Merseyside and (c) the UK that waited longer than 18 weeks between GP referral and beginning hospital treatment.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54767","54767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643933","2016-11-28","Department of Health","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings in the Clinical Commissioning Group (CCG) Improvement and Assessment Framework data, published in September 2016, which showed that over two-thirds of CCGs have been rated as either needs improvement or greatest need for improvement in diabetes services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54681","54681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643934","2016-11-30","Department for Transport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what support his Department provides to serving officers in the British Transport Police with post-traumatic stress disorder.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54713","54713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643935","2016-11-28","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2016 to Question 41770, what proportion of the funding raised by the Immigration Health Surcharge in 2015-16 was paid by people resident in the UK and eligible to pay national insurance.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54677","54677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643936","2016-11-28","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which external groups her Department plans to consult on its review of the Scrap Metal Dealers Act 2013 under section 18 of that Act.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54678","54678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643937","2016-11-29","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to assess the safety of the Democratic Republic of Congo for the purposes of removing people from the UK to that country.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54771","54771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643938","2016-11-29","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been removed to the Democratic Republic of Congo in 2016.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54734","54734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643939","2016-11-28","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will collect and publish data on performance in processing firearm and shotgun certificate applications which includes the time taken to process (a) initial firearm and shotgun licence grants and (b) firearm and shotgun licence renewals in England and Wales.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54884","54884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643940","2016-11-28","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 4.13 of the Autumn Statement 2016 policy paper, published on 23 November 2016, how much has been recovered pursuant to confiscation orders made under the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 from people convicted of loan sharking offences in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54897","54897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643941","2016-11-28","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 4.13 of the Autumn Statement 2016 policy paper, published on 23 November 2016, what the total value of confiscation orders made under the Proceeds of Crime Act 2002 against people convicted of loan sharking offences has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54896","54896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643942","2016-11-28","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many section 7 temporary firearm and shotgun permits were issued in the last year for which figures are available in England and Wales.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54883","54883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643943","2016-11-28","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what mechanisms there are to measure the performance of police forces when  dealing with firearm and shotgun certificate applications.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54882","54882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643944","2016-11-28","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 51923, if she will place a copy of her Department's guidance on (a) the genuine student rule and (b) interviewing in support of making final decisions on Points Based System Tier 4 cases in the Library.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54786","54786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643945","2016-11-28","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 52095, on how many occasions in the last 12 months reviews and the exercise of the specialist assurance function in relation to tier 4 decision making have resulted in a reversal of a decision.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54782","54782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643946","2016-11-28","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2016 to Question 51921, who is given responsibility to carry out the specialist international assurance function in relation to tier 4 decisions; and what steps she has taken to guarantee the independence of that function.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54783","54783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643947","2016-11-28","Home Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 21 November 2016 to Question 51921, what the average time taken is to process an administrative review of a tier 4 application.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54784","54784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643948","2016-11-28","Department for International Development","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to undertake a stocktake review of her Department's work on HIV to assess its comparative performance with other countries (a) in general and (b) on Sustainable Development Goal 3.3.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54888","54888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643949","2016-11-28","Department for International Development","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of its integration of HIV and AIDS prevention programmes into (a) the wider health system and (b) her Department's programmes; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54890","54890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643950","2016-11-28","Department for International Development","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what reports she has received on (a) a proposed revision to the 2009 NGO Policy Regulations by the government of Sierra Leone and (b) the views of civil society organisations on that proposed revision.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54679","54679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643951","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when her Department plans to publish its response to its consultation, Enhancing the quality of criminal advocacy which closed on 27 November 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54715","54715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643952","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will meet with the constituent of the hon. member for Kingston Upon Hull North, Linda Spring, to discuss the loss of the ashes of her son, Raymond, in 1996.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54722","54722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643953","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to support an inquiry by Hull City Council into the loss of the ashes of Tina Trowhill's son, William, in 1994.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54724","54724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643954","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will ensure that the National Cremation Working Group assesses the potential merits of changes to policy arising from the loss of the ashes of William, the son of Tina Trowhill, in 1994.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54723","54723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643955","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will ensure that the National Cremation Working Group assesses the potential merits of changes to policy arising from the loss of the ashes of the triplets of Andrea Tracey in 2006.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54725","54725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643956","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will meet the constituent of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North, Andrea Tracey, to discuss the loss of the ashes of her triplets in 2006.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54726","54726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643957","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will ensure that the National Cremation Working Group assesses the potential merits of changes to policy arising from the loss of the ashes of Raymond, the son of Linda Spring, in 1996.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54727","54727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643958","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to support an inquiry by Hull City Council into the loss of the ashes of Linda Spring's son, Raymond, in 1996.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54728","54728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643959","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeals to Tier 4 visa decisions were (a) received and (b) upheld by the appellant's country of origin in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54749","54749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643960","2016-11-29","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment she has made of the prevalence of the use of the psychoactive substance, spice, in prisons.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54880","54880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643961","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 November 2016 to Question 51925, what the average time taken for processing appeals to tier 4 visa decisions was in the last 12 months; what time targets or limits she has set in relation to processing such appeals; on how many occasions the length of time taken to process such an appeal has prevented a successful applicant from taking up a place at a UK higher education institution in the last 12 months; and what the country of origin of each such applicant was.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54785","54785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643962","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to support an inquiry by Hull City Council into the loss of the ashes of Emma Whitley's son, Connor, in 1996.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54812","54812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643963","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to support an inquiry by Hull City Council into the loss of the ashes of Jenni Murray's son, Jake, in 2002.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54804","54804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643964","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will meet the constituent of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull East, Emma Whitley, to discuss the loss of the ashes of her son, Connor, in 1996.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54811","54811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643965","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will ensure that the National Cremation Working Group assesses the potential merits of changes to policy arising from the  loss of the ashes of Jake, the son of Jenni Murray in 2002.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54805","54805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643966","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will meet the constituent of the hon. Member for Kingston Upon Hull East, Judith Drury, to discuss the loss of the ashes of her son, Benjamin, in 1994.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54808","54808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643967","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will ensure that the National Cremation Working Group assesses the potential merits of changes to policy arising from the loss of the ashes of Connor, the son of Emma Whitley, in 1996.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54816","54816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643968","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will meet with the constituent of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull East, Joanne Dix, to discuss the loss of the ashes of her son, Michael, in 1994.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54817","54817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643969","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to support an inquiry by Hull City Council into the loss of the ashes of Judith Drury's son, Benjamin, in 1994.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54809","54809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643970","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to support an inquiry by Hull City Council into the loss of the ashes of Joanne Dix's son, Michael, in 1994.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54818","54818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643971","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will ensure that the National Cremation Working Group assesses the potential merits of changes to policy arising from the loss of the ashes of Michael, the son of Joanne Dix, in 1994.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54819","54819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643972","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will ensure that the National Cremation Working Group assesses the potential merits of changes to policy arising from the loss of the ashes of Benjamin, the son of Judith Drury, in 1994.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54810","54810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643973","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will meet the constituent of the hon. Member for  Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle, Jenni Murray, to discuss the loss of the ashes of her son, Jake, in 2002.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54799","54799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643974","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will meet the constituent of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle, Louise Medlam, to discuss the loss of the ashes of her daughter, Chloe, in 1996.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54801","54801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643975","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will ensure that the National Cremation Working Group assesses the potential merits of changes to policy arising from the loss of the ashes of Chloe, the daughter of Louise Medlam, in 1996.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54806","54806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643976","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will meet the constituent of the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull West and Hessle, Angela Hughes, to discuss the loss of the ashes of her son, Reece, in 1996.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54803","54803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643977","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will ensure that the National Cremation Working Group assesses the potential merits of changes to policy arising from the loss of the ashes of Reece, the son of Angela Hughes, in 1996.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54807","54807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643978","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to support an inquiry by Hull City Council into the loss of the ashes of Louise Medlam's daughter, Chloe, in 1996.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54802","54802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643979","2016-11-28","Ministry of Justice","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will take steps to support an inquiry by Hull City Council into the loss of the ashes of Angela Hughes' son, Reece, in 1996.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54800","54800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643980","2016-11-28","Northern Ireland Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many projects in operation in his Department are related to the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54756","54756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643981","2016-11-28","Northern Ireland Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits to Northern Ireland energy consumers of maintaining an all-island single electricity market and arrangements for gas.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54719","54719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643982","2016-11-28","Northern Ireland Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps his Department is taking to maintain security of supply for consumers in Northern Ireland by retaining the ability to access and trade with European electricity and gas markets.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54718","54718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643983","2016-11-28","Cabinet Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many projects in operation in 10 Downing Street are related to the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54755","54755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643984","2016-11-28","Scotland Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many projects in operation in his Department are related to the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54754","54754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643985","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many projects in operation in his Department are related to the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54753","54753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643986","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 April 2016 to Question 34680, what his Department's current involvement is with the European Aviation Safety Agency's development of EU-wide safety rules for drones.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54690","54690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643987","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with (a) the British Airline Pilots' Association, (b) the Civil Aviation Authority, (c) the Metropolitan Police and (d) other relevant stakeholders on the near-miss incident between a drone and a passenger plane on 18 July 2016.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54775","54775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643988","2016-11-29","Department for Transport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with Highways England on its policy of contraflow and reducing lane size during maintenance or other work on motorways; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54779","54779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643989","2016-11-29","Department for Transport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.25 of the Autumn Statement 2016, on which schemes the £100 million of investment in road resilience projects referred to will be spent.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54832","54832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643990","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the main elements are in the cost-benefit analysis conducted on alternative proposals for the A27 road in and around Worthing.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54798","54798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643991","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make available online the 1996-97 conclusions of the inspector's report stemming from the inquiry on the A27 road proposals for Worthing and District.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54797","54797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643992","2016-11-29","Department for Transport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 4.8 of the Autumn Statement 2016, which projects will receive funding for rail resilience.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54881","54881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643993","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the longer semi-trailer trial on residents in small villages.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54861","54861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643994","2016-11-28","Wales Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many projects in operation in his Department are related to the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54752","54752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643995","2016-11-29","Wales Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department has spent on agency staff in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54763","54763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643996","2016-11-29","Wales Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many staff of his Department at each civil service grade are employed in a press or communications role.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54765","54765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643997","2016-11-29","Wales Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many staff of his Department are employed in its (a) press and (b) communications department.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54766","54766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643998","2016-11-29","Wales Office","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many full-time equivalent civil servants in his Department are working exclusively on issues arising as a result of the UK voting to leave the EU; and what the civil service grade is of each of those officials.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54764","54764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/643999","2016-11-28","Women and Equalities","2016-11-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many projects in operation in her Department are related to the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54751","54751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644000","2016-11-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people will lose entitlement to carer's allowance as a result of increases to the national minimum wage taking their income over the earning limit for that allowance.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54762","54762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644001","2016-11-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many projects in operation in his Department are related to the UK's exit of the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54750","54750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644002","2016-11-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) parents with care and (b) non-resident parents there are in Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency with a Child Support Agency case.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54695","54695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644003","2016-11-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total amount of child maintenance arrears is in (a) Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency and (b) Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54696","54696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644004","2016-11-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many older people champions are employed in job centres.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54707","54707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644005","2016-11-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the role is of older people champions in job centres.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54708","54708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644006","2016-11-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to make an estimate of the number of customers of his Department in Scotland who are using the services of food banks.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54669","54669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644007","2016-11-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent from the public purse through the Work Choice programme on employment support in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54673","54673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644008","2016-11-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Welfare Reform of 27 January 2016, Official Report, HL1315, on the Welfare Reform and Work Bill, whether he plans for spending on employment support for disabled people to be greater or less after the implementation of the policies in his Department's recent Green Paper on work, health and disability.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54866","54866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644009","2016-11-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to improve the child maintenance system to ensure payments due are received.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54863","54863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644010","2016-11-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the oral contribution by the Minister of State for Welfare Reform of  27 January 2016, in the House of Lords, Official Report, column 1315, on the Welfare Reform and Work Bill, whether the £60 to £100 million per year proposed under his Department's Green Paper on work, health and disability to be spent on supporting employment and support allowance claimants into work is in addition to or instead of funding currently being spent in the Work Programme and in Work Choice.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54869","54869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644011","2016-11-29","Department for Education","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many full-time equivalent staff worked in the Social Mobility Commission in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54870","54870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644012","2016-11-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Child Support Agency (a) arrears-only and (b) arrears cases involving a current liability for a child there are in Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54694","54694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644013","2016-11-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Disabled People, Health and Work of 17 November 2016, Official Report, columns 462 to 464, whether the hardship fund, flexible support fund and other third-party deals will compensate new claimants in full for the loss of the work-related activity group payments.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54827","54827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644014","2016-11-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of the British Business Bank's investment portfolio is invested in life science businesses.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54813","54813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644015","2016-11-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post office branches are located in off-licences; where each of those branches is located; and on what date each of those branches was opened.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54795","54795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644016","2016-11-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many and what proportion of pub tenants are protected pub tenants.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54778","54778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644017","2016-11-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many Petroleum Exploration and Development Licences have been granted where the Local Plan does not include development land for such purposes.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54856","54856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644018","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to tackle bogus self-employment.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54857","54857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644019","2016-11-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his oral contribution of 8 November 2016, Official Report, column 1395, on the Royal Bank of Scotland, when he plans to write to the right hon. Member for Delyn.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54814","54814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644020","2016-11-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much the British Business Bank has invested in life science businesses since it was established.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54848","54848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644021","2016-11-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps he has taken to encourage retailers to stock more Fairtrade products and adopt Fairtrade principles.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54698","54698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644022","2016-11-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the oral contribution by his predecessor of 28 June 2016, Official Report, column 130, when the Government plans to publish a National Innovation Plan.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54709","54709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644023","2016-11-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what research the Government is conducting on carbon capture and the energy-making process.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54710","54710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644024","2016-11-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure the continued recognition of UK firms' existing trademarks and patents in the EU after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54683","54683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644025","2016-11-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support micro enterprises in Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54697","54697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644026","2016-11-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post offices are in Bargain Booze shops; where each of those post offices are located; and in what branches was each of those post offices has opened.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54761","54761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644027","2016-11-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the average proportion of household expenditure on energy bills was in Rutherglen and Hamilton West constituency in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54699","54699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644028","2016-11-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on the potential effect of the Government's policy on fracking on local communities.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54711","54711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644029","2016-11-28","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will commission research on the reasons for the unseasonably high temperatures being recorded in the Arctic.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54700","54700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644030","2016-11-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the total value is of the Industrial Strategy Challenge Fund.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54712","54712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644031","2016-11-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 7 December 2015 to Question 18473, whether the Government plans to publish a response to the Dowling Review of Business-University Research Collaborations.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54729","54729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644032","2016-11-28","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of potential merits of the proposal by Tony Abbot for a free trade deal between the UK and Australia that abolishes tariffs and quotas on all goods, gives mutual recognition of industry standards and qualifications and allows people to move freely between the two countries.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54691","54691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644033","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has commissioned cost-benefit analysis of the potential effect of the UK leaving the single market and the customs union on the UK's balance of trade.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54692","54692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644034","2016-11-28","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans the Government has to embed the precautionary principle in UK domestic law as a basis for future bilateral trade agreements.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54714","54714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644035","2016-11-28","Department for Transport","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to maintain the UK's participation in the European Air Safety Agency's work on certifying aircraft, aircraft engines and other related products for safety to exports after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54684","54684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644036","2016-11-29","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what meetings he and Ministers of his Department have had with members of the Mexican government in (a) Mexico and (b) London in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54706","54706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644037","2016-11-29","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what preparation work is being conducted on negotiating a trade deal with Mexico after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54705","54705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644038","2016-11-29","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to increase trade with Mexico.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54704","54704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644039","2016-11-29","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to his Department's press release entitled, Global ambitions for British food and drink could boost economy by nearly £3 billion, if he will publish the methodology used to calculate that the International Action Plan for Food and Drink could benefit the UK economy by £2.9 billion over five years.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54703","54703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644040","2016-11-28","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the Answer of 26 July 2016 to Question 43064, when he plans to publish a list of his special advisers.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54849","54849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644041","2016-11-29","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether in his meeting with Heritage Foundation staff during his trip to the US in July 2016, he discussed (a) climate change and (b) pharmaceuticals.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54865","54865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644042","2016-11-28","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what engagement he has had with trade unions on negotiating priorities for the UK's new trading arrangements.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54850","54850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644043","2016-11-28","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department has generated any updated estimates of the administrative and compliance costs for British firms linked to rules of origin since the estimates in research published alongside the Balance of Competences Review were produced.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54894","54894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644044","2016-11-29","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many officials his Department employs; and what proportion of those officials worked in the Civil Service prior to July 2016.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54794","54794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644045","2016-11-29","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Government agreed to the provisional application in spring 2017 of provisions under exclusive EU competence for the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement during discussions with EU counterparts in October 2016.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54781","54781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644046","2016-11-29","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which Government Minister represented the UK during EU discussions on its negotiating lines relating to geographical indications on the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54793","54793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644047","2016-11-28","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2016 to Question 43019, how many civil servants in his Department primarily working on trade policy had prior experience of trade negotiations.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54843","54843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644048","2016-11-28","Department for International Trade","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2016 to Question 906161, how many of the priority global high-value export campaigns and campaigns for foreign direct investment are planned to begin before 31 March 2017; and if he will make it his policy to publish regular summaries of the effect of those campaigns.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54842","54842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/644049","2016-11-28","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-11-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he plans to take to ensure the Common Travel Area is maintained after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54887","54887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642945","2016-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many meetings Ministers and officials of his Department have had with Ministers and officials of the (a) Ministry of Defence, (b) Foreign and Commonwealth Office and (c) Department for International Development to discuss negotiations on the new scheme for BBC monitoring services and the closure of Caversham Park.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54427","54427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642946","2016-11-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what risk assessments government departments have carried out of the proposed restructuring of BBC monitoring services and the closure of Caversham Park; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54451","54451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642947","2016-11-28","Cabinet Office","2016-11-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times the Childcare Implementation Taskforce has met since its creation; what the full attendance was at each such meeting; and on what dates those meetings were held.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54555","54555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642949","2016-11-25","Cabinet Office","2016-11-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will estimate the value of savings accrued from government land and property by the Government Property Unit since 2010; and what the running costs of the Government Property Unit have been since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54596","54596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642950","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of spending from the National Productivity Investment Fund in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54558","54558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642951","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of predicted changes in the rate of inflation on consumer spending power over the next 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54559","54559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642952","2016-11-25","HM Treasury","2016-11-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what support his Department is offering to combined authorities to help fund non-transport infrastructure projects.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54538","54538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642953","2016-11-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-11-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect of pausing planned reductions in the employment and support allowance work-related activity group rates on the rate of employment for disabled people.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54543","54543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642954","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) minimum and (b) maximum compensation payment paid to a claimant for maladministration of tax credits was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54563","54563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642955","2016-11-28","HM Treasury","2016-11-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish in full the criteria used formally to determine the level of compensation paid to claimants for maladministration of their tax credits.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54564","54564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642956","2016-11-25","HM Treasury","2016-11-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.29 of the Autumn Statement 2016, how much of the additional £4.7 billion for research and development will be spent in each region.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54570","54570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/642957","2016-11-25","HM Treasury","2016-11-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.36 of the Autumn Statement 2016, if he will take steps to ensure that the £400 million Patient capital funding supports new ventures in Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 54571","54571"
