"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426764","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many faults have been found aboard HMS (a) Astute, (b) Ambush and (c) Artful since it left dry dock.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15291","15291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426765","2015-11-10","Department for Education","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of her Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps she has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments that have been carried out; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15332","15332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426766","2015-11-10","Department for Education","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15342","15342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426767","2015-11-16","Department for Education","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2015 to Question 14021, how many new teachers were trained in each of the last 10 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15281","15281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426768","2015-11-10","Department for Education","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an estimate of the number of additional teachers that will be needed to accommodate the predicted population rise over the next 25 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15260","15260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426769","2015-11-10","Department for Education","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to improve health literacy among children; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15252","15252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426770","2015-11-10","Department for Education","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an estimate of the number of additional schools that will be needed to accommodate the predicted population rise over the next 25 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15261","15261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426771","2015-11-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the likely market size of the UK solar industry in 2016.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15189","15189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426772","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she plans to close the feed-in tariff scheme in January 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15202","15202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426773","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many responses her Department received to the recent consultation on a review of the feed-in tariff scheme.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15203","15203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426774","2015-11-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether she plans to bring forward legislative proposals that hydraulic fracturing cannot be conducted from wells that are drilled at the surface of sensitive areas.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15221","15221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426775","2015-11-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will establish an examination of objections to her departmental minute of 21 October 2015 including the entering into contracts regarding the Hinkley Point C power station that could give rise to liabilities.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15222","15222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426776","2015-11-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether it is Government policy to phase out coal.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15246","15246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426777","2015-11-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15343","15343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426778","2015-11-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many of her Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps she has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments that have been carried out; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15333","15333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426779","2015-11-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she plans to publish the Government's response to the consultation on a review of the feed-in tariff scheme.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15321","15321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426780","2015-11-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many of her Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps she has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments that have been carried out; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15334","15334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426781","2015-11-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15344","15344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426782","2015-11-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she intends to answer the letter of the hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton, dated 29 June, on Mr I Boddison.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15234","15234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426783","2015-11-16","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November to Question 14627, what estimate her Department has made of the total funding that will be available to the Waste and Resources Action Programme in each of the next five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15266","15266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426784","2015-11-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to extend the provisions of the Dangerous Wild Animals Act 1976 to include pet shops.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15210","15210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426785","2015-11-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to amend the licensing schedule under the Pet Animals Act 1951 to make it species specific.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15209","15209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426786","2015-11-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to respond to recommendation 2015/105 from the Marine Accident Investigation Branch in its 2/2015 Investigation Report, on adoption of the Boat Safety Scheme by the Lake District National Park Authority.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15208","15208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426787","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to (a) increase the provision of humanitarian aid in Yemen and (b) ensure that that aid gets to where it is most needed.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15195","15195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426788","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of Bermuda's progress in introducing a public register of beneficial ownership since June 2013.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15218","15218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426789","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take in response to Bermuda's decision to (a) reject the Prime Minister's request to introduce a public register of beneficial ownership and (b) reject the Prime Minister's request to hold a consultation on adopting such a register.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15219","15219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426790","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what efforts are being made through the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Scheme to assist refugees in (a) the Yazidi, Druze or Christian communities or (b) other communities who do not reside in the main refugee camps because of fears of religious persecution.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15220","15220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426791","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contact his Department has had with the US Atrocity Prevention Board.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15242","15242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426792","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many named people from which countries have been subject to UK targeted sanctions in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15231","15231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426793","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15345","15345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426794","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many of his Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps he has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments that have been carried out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15335","15335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426795","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on (a) temporary agency staff, (b) consultants, (c) non-payroll staff, (d) administration and (e) marketing and advertising in real terms in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15317","15317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426796","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many of his Department's policies have been assessed against the family test; what steps he has taken to publish the outcome of such assessments that have been carried out; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15336","15336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426797","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were referred by the NHS England Liaison and Diversion Service for support or treatment in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15323","15323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426798","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been screened by the NHS England Liaison and Diversion Service to see if they have mental health issues, learning disabilities, substance misuse or other vulnerabilities in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15322","15322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426799","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mental health places of safety for detention under section 136 of the Mental Health Act 1983 accept under 18 year olds; and what that figure is as a proportion of that total number of places.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15324","15324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426800","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to implement the family test.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15346","15346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426801","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of increased use of temporary doctors and nurses on the (a) quality of the healthcare provision and (b) cost of that provision.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15236","15236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426802","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2015 to Question 12902, what policies for improvement he is developing as a result of the Care Quality Commission's Community Mental Health Survey 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15250","15250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426803","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that providers of care are funded at a sustainable rate; and if he will make it his policy to implement the recommendations relating to care funding in the report by the Homecare Association, entitled the Homecare Deficit, published in March 2015.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15247","15247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426804","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of national programmes which provide naloxone for at-risk prisoners on their release.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15244","15244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426805","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisons provide naloxone for prisoners upon release in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15245","15245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426806","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support and promote Self Care Week; and what promotional materials he is disseminating in the NHS to support that campaign.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15253","15253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426807","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the density of physicians was in (a) 1985-86, (b) 1995-96, (c) 2005-06 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15256","15256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426808","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the density of dentistry personnel was in (a) 1985-86, (b) 1995-96, (c) 2005-06 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15257","15257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426809","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the training programme fill rates were for doctors entering core and further speciality training in each (a) speciality and (b) training region or deanery in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15268","15268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426810","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the density of nursing and midwifery personnel was in (a) 1985-86, (b) 1995-96, (c) 2005-06 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15258","15258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426811","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors entered core and further speciality training in each (a) speciality and (b) training region or deanery in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15269","15269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426812","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an estimate of the number of additional (a) doctors and (b) nurses that will be needed to accommodate the predicted population rise over the next 25 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15259","15259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426813","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many delayed discharges in West Sussex related to people with brain injuries in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15280","15280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426814","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to update the Cardiovascular Disease Outcome Strategy, published in March 2013.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15277","15277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426815","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to make access to liver transplantation services more equitable.","Biography information for Dr Phillip Lee","Dr Phillip Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15191","15191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426816","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the amount of choice and quality of care people available to those with terminal illnesses, their families and carers; and what steps his Department is taking to increase the amount of choice for high quality care.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15206","15206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426817","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to (a) reduce the effects of and (b) improve outcomes for (i) coronary heart disease and (ii) cardiovascular disease.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15193","15193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426818","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the change in the number of police officers in Hammersmith and Fulham as a result of her proposed changes to the Metropolitan Police.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15198","15198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426819","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to provide (a) humanitarian visas, (b) facilitated refugee family reunion and (c) other safe legal routes for migrants to enter the UK.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15227","15227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426820","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will make an assessment of the implications for its policies of the report by Transparency International UK entitled, Gold Rush, published 15 October 2015; if her Department will retrospectively examine what transparency declarations can be required of existing investors who entered the UK on Tier 1 visas; what steps her Department takes to assess whether funds coming into the UK via those visas have been gained illicitly; and if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of strengthening those measures to address that issue.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15200","15200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426821","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has spent on (a) temporary agency staff, (b) consultants, (c) non-payroll staff, (d) administration and (e) marketing and advertising in real terms in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15305","15305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426822","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what (a) the amount of any underspend expected against departmental expenditure limits in the current fiscal year and (b) her Department's latest forecast of total AME spend for this year are; and what the forecasts were for those two sums at the time of the Summer Budget 2015 and March Budget 2015.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15315","15315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426823","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to ascertain the extent of human trafficking into the fishing industry; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15311","15311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426824","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential financial effect of proposals to deny refused asylum seekers access to financial support will have on (a) local authorities and (b) (i) homelessness, (ii) health and (iii) mental health service providers,","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15296","15296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426825","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people renounced British citizenship in each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15273","15273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426826","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people subsequently resumed British citizenship after renouncing it in each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15274","15274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426827","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people had British citizenship revoked in each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15275","15275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426828","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many nationals aged (a) between 15 and 64 and (b) over 65 from each EEA country were granted British citizenship in each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15276","15276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426829","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which countries' citizens (a) may and (b) may not enter the UK without a visa.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15270","15270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426830","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times the UK has been asked to use the discretionary powers in Article 17 of the Dublin Regulation EC No 604/2013 since that regulation came into force; and how many of those requests resulted in the UK taking charge of an applicant under that Article.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15249","15249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426831","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many nationals aged (a) between 15 and 64 and (b) over 65 from each non-EEA country were granted British citizenship in each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15264","15264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426832","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many nationals aged (a) between 15 and 64 and (b) over 65 from each non-EEA country were granted indefinite leave to stay in the UK in each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15262","15262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426833","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many nationals aged (a) between 15 and 64 and (b) over 65 from each EEA country were granted permanent residence in each year from 1997-98 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15263","15263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426834","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to answer the letter of the hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton, dated 28 September 2015, with regard to Mr Ammar Baadj.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15233","15233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426835","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many taxi and private hire drivers have been fined for refusing to take an assistance dog in each quarter of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15319","15319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426836","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of individuals currently living in (a) camps in Calais and (b) hotspots in Greece and Italy who may be eligible to have their asylum case determined in the UK under articles within the Dublin III Regulation.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15283","15283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426837","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have sought asylum in the UK through the Dublin III regulation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15325","15325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426838","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason the publicly available version of Chapter 28 of the Enforcement and Instructions Guidance refers to EC No 343/2003 and not EC No 604/2013.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15300","15300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426839","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason the publically available guidance entitled, Third Country cases: Referring and Handling refers to EC No 343/2003 and not EC No 604/2013.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15299","15299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426840","2015-11-16","Home Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has conducted an investigation into how Demie Omol was able to travel through the UK to the Republic of Ireland; and what steps she is taking to prevent further victims of trafficking being similarly transported by the same agents and through the same routes.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15312","15312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426841","2015-11-10","Department for International Development","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she intends to answer the letter of the hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton, dated 28 September 2015, on John Rooke.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15235","15235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426842","2015-11-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2015 to Question 13950, what the estimated annual shortfall is in the payment of pensions to former employees of the Southern Rhodesian government.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15237","15237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426843","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the reasons why only 37 per cent of the millennium development goals in the UK's 28 priority countries have been marked as met or will be met in her Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2014-15.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15243","15243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426844","2015-11-16","Department for International Development","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance and support her Department is providing to food sovereignty movements in developing countries; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15267","15267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426845","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on (a) temporary agency staff, (b) consultants, (c) non-payroll staff, (d) administration and (e) marketing and advertising in real terms in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15306","15306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426846","2015-11-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what (a) the amount of any underspend expected against departmental expenditure limits in the current fiscal year and (b) his Department's latest forecast of total AME spend for this year are; and what the forecasts were for those two sums at the time of the Summer Budget 2015 and March Budget 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15316","15316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426847","2015-11-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2015 to Question 9384, on Reoffenders, if he will list the offences committed by those people numbered in the violence against the person category.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15303","15303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426848","2015-11-10","Prime Minister","2015-11-06","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he plans to attend the COP21 climate talks in Paris.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15217","15217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426849","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the safety and speed of evacuation from Virgin (a) Pendolino and (b) Voyager trains in the event of an emergency.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15212","15212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426850","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he will publish a timetable for the refurbishment of Wolverhampton train station.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15213","15213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426851","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect that the decision of the Quality Contract Scheme board on the Quality Contract proposed to be run by Nexus for Tyne and Wear will have on city devolution deals.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15214","15214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426852","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will discuss with Virgin Trains its replacing the ageing Voyager fleet rolling stock.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15211","15211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426853","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many deaths occurred on rural roads in 2014 to 2015.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15215","15215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426854","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has had discussions with the car insurance sector regarding (a) the cost of premiums and (b) the variations in that cost around the UK.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15216","15216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426855","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the airport security at Hurghada and Safaga airports in Egypt.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15192","15192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426856","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the recent legal decision on the Quality Contract for NEXUS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15190","15190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426857","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) the amount of any underspend expected against departmental expenditure limits in the current fiscal year and (b) his Department's latest forecast of total AME spend for this year are; and what the forecasts were for those two sums at the time of the Summer Budget 2015 and March Budget 2015.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15314","15314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426858","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the likely effect on (a) passenger and (b) freight traffic on the West Coast Mainline following completion of Phase 1 of High Speed 2; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15248","15248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426859","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the type approval regime is for (a) aircraft used at UK airports and (b) ships used at UK ports; and whether there are any emissions standard components to either of those regimes.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15284","15284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426860","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to respond to the report by the Law Commission on tax; and private hire services, published in May 2014.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15301","15301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426861","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on funding the independent review on the future of the Manston airfield.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15318","15318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426862","2015-11-16","Department for Transport","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spent on (a) temporary agency staff, (b) consultants, (c) non-payroll staff, (d) administration and (e) marketing and advertising in real terms in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15313","15313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426863","2015-11-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how changes made as a result of the Pension Act 2011 were communicated to people affected.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15254","15254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426864","2015-11-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) men and (b) women were affected by the changes made in the Pension Act 2011.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15255","15255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426865","2015-11-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what impact assessment his Department carried out on women directly affected by the Pension Act 2011 before those changes came into effect.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15278","15278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426866","2015-11-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average change in income for a woman born in 1952 is as a result of the provisions of the Pension Act 2011.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15279","15279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426867","2015-11-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what facilities are available to enable staff based at the Carer's Allowance Unit in Preston to pay money from their wages into the Guild Money credit union.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15229","15229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426447","2015-11-09","Attorney General","2015-11-05","To ask the Attorney General, which regulations his Office introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Office expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15038","15038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426448","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which regulations his Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15037","15037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426449","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps (a) he and (b) his Department made to secure a buyer for Redcar coke ovens and blast furnace before the Official Receiver called for a hard closure.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14993","14993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426450","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure of Redcar coke ovens and blast furnace on the local economy.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14994","14994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426451","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on how many bids were received by the Official Receiver to buy or operate any element of the former SSI site in Redcar prior to the Receiver's decision on hard closure.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14995","14995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426452","2015-11-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that consumers' personal and private data is not gathered, bought and sold by third parties.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15051","15051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426453","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received on the Open University's plans to close regional centres across England.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15064","15064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426454","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS trusts and NHS employers on proposals to allow Ministers to cap union facility time contained in the Trade Union Bill.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15104","15104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426455","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to promote the development of healthcare assistants in primary care by means of apprenticeships.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15146","15146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426456","2015-11-10","Department for Education","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department intends to take to reduce the number of children who do not attend school due to bullying.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15147","15147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426457","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposals to allow Ministers to cap union facility time contained in the Trade Union Bill on (a) staff morale, (b) productivity and (c) patient safety in the NHS.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15105","15105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426458","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to NHS trusts of nursing staff turnover as a result of proposals to cap union facility time in the Trade Union Bill.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15106","15106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426459","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what correspondence his Department has had with PwC regarding SSI Redcar in the last three years; and how many meetings his Department has had with PwC in that period.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15159","15159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426460","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to prevent the loss of skilled manufacturing jobs to other countries in the EU.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15171","15171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426461","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the assistance that could best be offered to help prevent the loss of highly-skilled manufacturing jobs at MAHLE in Kilmarnock.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15183","15183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426462","2015-11-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Government's report, Fixing the Foundations; creating a more prosperous nation, Cm 9098, published in July 2015, what assessment he has made of the effect on productivity of allowing education providers to offer degrees independently of universities.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15184","15184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426463","2015-11-10","Cabinet Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Civil Service Commission was consulted on changes to the Code of Conduct for Special Advisers, published in October 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15182","15182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426464","2015-11-10","Cabinet Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with whom he consulted on recent changes to the ministerial code.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15170","15170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426465","2015-11-09","Cabinet Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths in (a) Wales and (b) Scotland were caused by people taking legal highs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14981","14981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426466","2015-11-10","Cabinet Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the likely cost of establishing and running his extended ministerial office.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15019","15019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426467","2015-11-10","Cabinet Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to publish details of his Department's expenditure over 25,000 from September 2014 to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15020","15020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426468","2015-11-09","Cabinet Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which regulations his Office introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Office expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15034","15034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426469","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people who have been granted refugee leave have claimed backdated tax credits in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15008","15008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426470","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been paid from the public purse in backdated tax credits to people who have been granted refugee leave in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15009","15009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426471","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people who have been granted refugee leave have claimed backdated child benefit in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15010","15010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426472","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been paid from the public purse in backdated child benefit to people who have been granted refugee leave in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15011","15011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426473","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which regulations his Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15029","15029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426474","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of families who will have marginal deduction rates over (a) 50, (b) 60, (c) 70, (d) 80 and (e) 90 per cent in 2015-16; and what his projections of those figures are for each year to 2020-21.","Biography information for Edward Miliband","Edward Miliband","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15002","15002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426475","2015-11-10","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether under any Act arising from the Scotland Bill the Scottish Government will be enabled to pay tax credits.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14980","14980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426476","2015-11-10","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his Answer of 23 October 2015 to Question 12551, if he will invite the hon. Member for Preston to visit the tax credit office in that constituency.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14988","14988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426477","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that people eligible to join the Class 3A voluntary contribution scheme are made aware of it.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14986","14986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426478","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the time taken by the Cayman Islands government to respond to its consultation on a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15158","15158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426479","2015-11-10","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of proposed changes to (a) the student loans system and (b) maintenance grants on productivity.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15186","15186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426480","2015-11-10","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 5 of his Department's document Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, Cm9098, published in July 2015, what analysis his Department has made of the effects of changes to vehicle excise duty and the creation of a roads fund on UK productivity.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15180","15180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426481","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will ensure that any agreement on a central registry of beneficial ownership in Anguilla will include access for the public with legitimate reason.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15153","15153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426482","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will ensure that any agreement on a central registry of beneficial ownership in the Cayman Islands will include access for the public with legitimate reason.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15154","15154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426483","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress made by Anguilla since June 2013 in meeting the Prime Minister's ambition for a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15156","15156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426484","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress made by the Cayman Islands since June 2013 in meeting the Prime Minister's ambition for a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15157","15157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426485","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of people eligible for the Class 3A Voluntary National Insurance Contribution Scheme that have signed up to that scheme.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15099","15099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426486","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have signed up to the Class 3A Voluntary National Insurance Contribution Scheme in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) Pendle constituency.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15091","15091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426487","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of eligible policyholders in (a) St Albans, (b) Hertfordshire, (c) the east of England and (d) the UK have received funds from the Equitable Life Payment Scheme; what proportion of funds owed to those people has been so received; and what steps he is taking to ensure that people are tracked down and compensated before that scheme's closure.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15097","15097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426488","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in the number of people sleeping rough since 2010.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15123","15123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426489","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how the extension of office to residential permitted development rights will be set out in legislative proposals.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15112","15112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426490","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which regulations his Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15035","15035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426491","2015-11-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which regulations his Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15036","15036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426492","2015-11-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many television licenses were purchased in each region and constituent part of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15163","15163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426493","2015-11-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of Ofcom's programme to monitor and enforce the cancellation and termination arrangements of different providers; and what steps he is taking to ensure that consumers can easily leave their communications contracts in future.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15150","15150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426494","2015-11-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the FTE equivalent headcount figures are for Ofcom for each year for which data is available since 2009.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15139","15139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426495","2015-11-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will introduce for the rest of the UK equivalent powers as those proposed in the Scotland Bill on fixed odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15056","15056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426496","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in what conditions the 114 Syrian refugees are being held at RAF Dhekelia in Cyprus; and if he will undertake to ensure that these conditions are inspected as to their appropriateness.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15067","15067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426497","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his most recent estimate is of the number of UK military personnel currently involved in military operations in (a) Iraq and (b) Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15165","15165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426498","2015-11-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which regulations his Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15032","15032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426499","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the reasons were for the Ministry of Defence Police withholding a Special Investigation Branch report of Lt. Col. Jolleys' circumstances from a fraud trial in which he was convicted of failing to declare changes to his circumstances.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15053","15053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426500","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the reasons were for the Ministry of Defence Police denying Lt. Col. Jolley his own military records for him to use at his trial in 2013.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15054","15054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426501","2015-11-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the reasons were for the Ministry of Defence Police failing to disclose army doctors', chaplains', commanding officers' and Lt. Col. Jolleys' own statement of his circumstances.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15055","15055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426502","2015-11-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what account his Department plans to take of the closure of steel plants in 2015 in the strategic defence and security review process.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14985","14985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426503","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which regulations her Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations her Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate she has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15033","15033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426504","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to address the relative low educational attainment in coastal communities; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14979","14979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426505","2015-11-10","Department for Education","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of supply teacher recruitment in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15167","15167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426506","2015-11-10","Department for Education","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has conducted a review into the adequacy of the service provided by agencies supplying supply teachers to school; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15164","15164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426507","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 1 December 2014 to Question 216015, what criteria her Department sets for eligibility for free school meals for households in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15125","15125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426508","2015-11-10","Department for Education","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to the public purse of private agency supply teacher services in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15166","15166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426509","2015-11-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her policy is on the Global Goal on Adaption.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15107","15107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426510","2015-11-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to chart 4.2 of the Annual Fuel Poverty Statistics Report 2015, published by her Department on 28 May 2015, what proportion of the (a) local authority, (b) owner-occupied, (c) private rented and (d) housing association households are in fuel poverty.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15089","15089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426511","2015-11-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to identify locations for potential electricity storage schemes that would best supplement the existing National Grid system.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15113","15113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426512","2015-11-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the comparative merits of electricity storage and transmission network upgrades.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15114","15114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426513","2015-11-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of Green Deal Home Improvement funding that was allocated to deprived areas.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15162","15162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426514","2015-11-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to support poor communities overseas to tackle the effects of climate change.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15108","15108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426515","2015-11-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the likely effect on household electricity bills of the agreement of a 92.50 MWh rate for the proposed Hinkley Point C nuclear power station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15115","15115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426516","2015-11-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the merits of exempting operators of electricity storage from Balanced Services Use of System charges.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15116","15116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426517","2015-11-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what comparative cost-benefit analyses her Department has made of electricity storage and constraint payments.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15117","15117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426518","2015-11-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the likely annual cost to electricity customers of the proposed Hinkley Point C power station (a) in total and (b) per customer.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15121","15121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426519","2015-11-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what comparative assessment she has made of the cost of generating electricity from (a) conventional hydro-electric sources and (b) gas fired plants.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14978","14978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426520","2015-11-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which regulations her Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations her Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate she has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15031","15031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426521","2015-11-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of changes to support for the solar power sector on the market share of the global solar industry that will be held by UK firms by 2020.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14997","14997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426522","2015-11-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which regulations her Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations her Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate she has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15030","15030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426523","2015-11-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will set out the costs and benefits to the UK of the EU Air Quality Framework Directive, and of the first, second, third and fourth daughter directives.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15044","15044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426524","2015-11-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to increase the level of competition among milk processors.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15168","15168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426525","2015-11-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to encourage more retailers to sell milk brands that best support the domestic dairy industry.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15169","15169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426526","2015-11-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to implement a strategy to tackle invasive non-native species at the European level; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15181","15181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426527","2015-11-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the effect on consumer demand of increases in the price of milk.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15188","15188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426528","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received about the threatened demolition of the village of Khan Al Ahmer in the West Bank and the effects of Israeli settlement activity in the vicinity.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15135","15135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426529","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will (a) discuss with the Moroccan ambassador to the UK and (b) instruct the British Ambassador in Rabat to investigate reports of intimidation, harassment and kidnapping of human rights defenders in the Occupied Territories of Western Sahara coinciding with the visit of King Mohamed VI.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15120","15120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426530","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the elections to the Mexican Supreme Court.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15138","15138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426531","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to address the political dimensions of the situation in Syria.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15061","15061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426532","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to meet the UK's international obligations to refugees fleeing the conflict in Syria, other than by supporting countries in that region.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15062","15062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426533","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he plans to take to use the UK's position on the UN Security Council to help facilitate diplomatic negotiations on protecting civilians in Syria.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15057","15057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426534","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to assist the Syrian people in putting in place stable political and diplomatic foundations on which to rebuild that country once the conflict there has ended.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15058","15058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426535","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how the Government plans to develop a more comprehensive strategy to combat ISIL that prioritises protecting civilians in Syria.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15059","15059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426536","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what conclusions he wants the Vienna talks on the Syria crisis to reach.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15060","15060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426537","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the outcome was of his Department's visit to Um-il-Hiran and Ateer; whether he plans to visit that region; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15102","15102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426538","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on implementing the recommendations set out in the Bahrain Independent Commission of Inquiry report.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15045","15045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426539","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) staff of which grades and (b) desk teams were working on Russia in his Department in (i) 2011, (ii) 2012, (iii) 2013, (iv) 2014 and (v) the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15052","15052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426540","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to reduce the international dog meat trade.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15012","15012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426541","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Department has had with its counterparts in countries where trading dog meat is legal about that trade.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15013","15013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426542","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received on incidents of sexual violence committed by the Burmese army; and what representations he has made to the Burmese government on that matter.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15024","15024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426543","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of reported irregularities in the run-up to the Burmese election.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15025","15025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426544","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government is providing to the Women's League of Burma.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15026","15026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426545","2015-11-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Russian counterpart on recent Russian military action in Syria.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15027","15027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426546","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which regulations his Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15047","15047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426547","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many applications for warrants for electronic surveillance he rejected last year.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15000","15000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426548","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the surplus of deficit was for all acute trusts and foundation trusts in (a) the South West and (b) England on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15018","15018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426549","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the projected surplus or deficit is for all acute trusts and foundation trusts in (a) the South West and (b) England for 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15017","15017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426550","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve access to specialist health facilities for children with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15022","15022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426551","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to develop a national register for people with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15021","15021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426552","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of support for people with cerebral palsy.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15023","15023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426553","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which regulations his Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15048","15048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426554","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ask the Care Quality Commission to investigate the project run by South East Coast Ambulance Service NHS Foundation Trust between December 2014 and February 2015 on the treatment of emergency calls to NHS 111.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15028","15028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426555","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department gives to NHS trusts on hiring temporary doctors and nurses.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14984","14984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426556","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he has any plans to inform NHS users of the actual costs of visits, treatments and prescriptions.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14976","14976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426557","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues to hospital trusts on the account they should take of the availability of transport links when making decisions on reconfiguring services across two sites; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14977","14977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426558","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he Department has made of the effect of the availability of different cancer drugs being available in Scotland and Wales to those in England on the treatment of cancer in England.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15063","15063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426559","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve children and young people's mental health services.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15092","15092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426560","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2015 to Question 13135, if he will place in the Library a copy of the review described at section A7 of Schedule One of the contract for the provision of tobacco control legislation enforcement undertaken by the contractor.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15088","15088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426561","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) contracts and (b) grants have been awarded by the tobacco policy team in his Department in each of the last five years; what the (i) name of the recipient, (ii) purpose of the contract or grant, (iii) financial value, (iv) job title of the lead official overseeing the procurement process was in each such case; and whether ministerial approval was required or given in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15096","15096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426562","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many secondments have taken place between his Department and the Chartered Institute of Trading Standards in the last 15 years; and in what capacity each such secondment was undertaken.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15094","15094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426563","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many organisations submitted applications for his Department's tender for the provision of the tobacco control legislation enforcement contract awarded in 2013.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15095","15095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426564","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of total NHS expenditure spending on maternity services represented in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15041","15041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426565","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to improve awareness, diagnosis and treatment of heart valve disease.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15149","15149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426566","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential efficacy of introducing restrictions on the advertising of foods high in saturated fats, sugars and salts on television before 9pm in reducing rates of childhood obesity.","Biography information for Dr Phillip Lee","Dr Phillip Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15119","15119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426567","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to reduce the exposure of children to alcohol marketing.","Biography information for Dr Phillip Lee","Dr Phillip Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15118","15118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426568","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the number of NHS patients with Crohn's disease and ulcerative colitis who have not had a gastroenterology appointment in the last six months and who have had an appointment cancelled or postponed by their NHS provider during the last six months.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15176","15176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426569","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the number of NHS patients with Crohn's disease and ulcerative colitis who have not had a gastroenterology appointment in the last six months.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15177","15177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426570","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts on measures to tackle avoidable winter deaths.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15111","15111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426571","2015-11-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2015 to Question 14466, if he will publish the minutes of the 21 October 2015 meeting of the Ministerial Board on Deaths in Custody.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15174","15174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426572","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2015 to Question 12901, on mental health services, whether the figures in that Answer include children and young people.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15173","15173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426573","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what additional funding his Department is making available to local authorities to support implementation of interventions to reduce excess winter deaths.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15109","15109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426574","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consultation the NHS England Vanguard programme has undertaken with mental health clinicians in order to ensure that there is integrated care for the pilot sites' registered populations.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15172","15172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426575","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether clinical commissioning groups have received real terms increases in mental health care funding in 2015-16; and if he will publish information on changes to mental health core funding in that year.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15134","15134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426576","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on the number of gastroenterology appointments specifically related to Crohn's disease and ulcerative colitis that have been cancelled or postponed at the request of the Grimsby and Goole Hospital Trust in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15178","15178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426577","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the shortage of doctors and nurses in the NHS.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15124","15124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426578","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to set additional access and waiting time standards for NHS mental health services following the introduction of standards for adult IAPT and Early Intervention in Psychosis services.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15132","15132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426579","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the number of gastroenterology appointments specifically related to Crohn's disease and ulcerative colitis that have been cancelled or postponed at the request of an NHS provider in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15179","15179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426580","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Chief Executive of NHS England on introducing new access and waiting time standards for mental health services.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15133","15133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426581","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many scientists and engineers have been refused a Tier 2 (General) Certificate of Sponsorship because the annual cap had been reached since May 2010; which Standard Occupational Classification codes have been affected by that cap; and how many applications have been refused for each such code to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15141","15141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426582","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) arrests and (b) safeguarding interventions arose from Operation Notarise.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15136","15136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426583","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of refugees and migrants living in Calais in each month of 2015; and how many refugees and migrants have had contact with the command and control centre the Government has established in Calais in each month of 2015.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15100","15100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426584","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many verified images are currently on the National Hash Set Database; and how many police forces have direct access to that database.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15137","15137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426585","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the requirements of the community sponsorship route to Britain for refugees are; and when she plans to establish that route.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15101","15101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426586","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the efficiency of the work visa system in enabling UK businesses to have speedy access to the language skills they need for new markets.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15161","15161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426587","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department takes to help protect 16 and 17 year olds who are victims of child sexual exploitation.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15155","15155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426588","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of standard passport applications made in the last six months were processed within three weeks.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15066","15066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426589","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) standard and (b) fast-track passport applications were made in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15065","15065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426590","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the current guidance is on how data required to be retained by communications companies for investigations undertaken or authorised by the Government is to be stored.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15069","15069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426591","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Government will process as a matter of urgency the asylum applications of the 114 Syrian refugees currently being held at RAF Dhekelia in Cyprus.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15068","15068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426592","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been referred by the National Crime Agency to regional police forces in (a) 2014 and (b) so far in 2015; and how many of those people are under suspicion of involvement in crimes of child abuse.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15071","15071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426593","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of recent trends in the use of legal highs.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14975","14975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426594","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrian refugees selected for resettlement from UN camps to the UK had previously been selected for resettlement in the US.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15042","15042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426595","2015-11-10","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrian refugees from each UN camp she expects to be resettled in the UK in 2015.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15043","15043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426596","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which regulations her Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations her Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate she has made of the cost of such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15049","15049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426597","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for judicial review against decisions on asylum applications made by UK Visas and Immigration have been brought in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15007","15007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426598","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for warrants for electronic surveillance she rejected last year.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15001","15001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426599","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugee families she expects to be relocated to Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross constituency; where such families will be housed; and what steps the Government is taking to ensure that such families have access to education for their children.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14983","14983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426600","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to relax immigration rules on the reunification of families and allow members of a refugee's extended family to join them in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14982","14982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426601","2015-11-09","Department for International Development","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which regulations her Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations her Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate she has made of the cost of such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15050","15050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426602","2015-11-09","Department for International Development","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department is providing to remote communities in Nepal affected by the earthquakes to prepare for and cope with winter.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15122","15122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426603","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of unmet need for locked rehabilitation units offering intense psychology and substance misuse support to patients with personality disorders and drug or alcohol problems in the Humber area.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15175","15175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426604","2015-11-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will introduce new sentencing guidelines recommending strict penalties to assist magistrates in prosecuting caces under the Equality Act 2010 where a private hire or taxi driver has refused to provide transport to a visually impaired passenger and their guide dog.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15110","15110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426605","2015-11-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to his oral Answer to the hon. Member for Hampstead and Kilburn of 3 November 2015, Official Report, column 866, how much revenue the criminal courts charge has generated since its introduction.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15143","15143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426606","2015-11-10","Department of Health","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to help establish an international agreement on surrogacy arrangements and harmonisation of the law and practice on surrogacy overseas.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15148","15148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426607","2015-11-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which regulations his Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15039","15039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426608","2015-11-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the quality of the evidence presented by the Association of British Insurers on the continuing increases to motor insurance premiums being a result of fraudulent personal injury claims; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14996","14996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426609","2015-11-09","Northern Ireland Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which regulations her Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations her Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate she has made of the cost of each such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15040","15040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426610","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have entered the UK as a result of successful family reunion applications in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15006","15006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426611","2015-11-09","Scotland Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which regulations his Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15126","15126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426612","2015-11-09","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which regulations his Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15127","15127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426613","2015-11-09","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will require Heathrow Airport Limited to respond publicly to the recommendations of the Airport Commission that, in order to mitigate the effects of a third runway at Heathrow, (a) there should be a commitment in Parliament not to build a fourth runway, (b) there should be a ban on all scheduled night flights in the period 11.30pm to 6.00am, (c) a third runway should allow periods of predictable respite to be more reliably maintained and (d) additional operations at an expanded Heathrow Airport must be contingent on acceptable performance on air quality.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15131","15131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426614","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Government's report, Fixing the Foundations; creating a more prosperous nation, Cm 9098, published in July 2015, what assessment he has made of the effect of (a) proposed changes to the rail industry and (b) the rail investment programme on productivity.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15185","15185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426615","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what safeguards are in place to avoid mistakenly withdrawing motor tax following erroneous or malicious notification of cars being exported or going off road.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15142","15142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426616","2015-11-09","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons Network Rail has not yet published a timetable to close 73 dangerous level crossings on the East Cost Main Line; and what recent discussions he has had with Network Rail over the East Coast Main Line level crossing closure programme.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15098","15098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426617","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much compensation the Government is liable for in its contract with Agility Trains in the event that the new IEP fleet cannot be introduced according to its planned timescales due to delays to either (a) the Great Western Mainline electrification programme or (b) East Coat Mainline IEP enabling works.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15160","15160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426618","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of children have (a) walked and (b) cycled to school in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15152","15152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426619","2015-11-09","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what take-up there has been of the cycle to work salary sacrifice scheme since it started.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15103","15103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426620","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will name the people in his Department who are entitled to use the Government Car Service.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15015","15015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426621","2015-11-09","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the estimated value of Network Rail was on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14987","14987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426622","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of his road investment strategy on productivity.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14992","14992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426623","2015-11-10","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people in his Department have been entitled to use the Government Car Service in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15016","15016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426624","2015-11-09","Department for Transport","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Traffic Regulation Orders have been introduced by local authorities to tackle pavement parking since 2011.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15003","15003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426625","2015-11-10","Wales Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how the Government plans to monitor and enforce clause 2 of the draft Wales Bill.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14991","14991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426626","2015-11-10","Wales Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, for what reasons the draft Wales Bill would seek to change the criteria on which the Assembly could legislate outside its normal competence, as set out in section 108(5) of the Government of Wales Act 2006.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14989","14989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426627","2015-11-10","Wales Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the draft Wales Bill, for what reason it is his policy to remove the wording of the Government of Wales Act 2006 which states that an Act of the Assembly may make any provision that could be made by an Act of Parliament.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14990","14990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426628","2015-11-09","Wales Office","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which regulations his Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15128","15128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426629","2015-11-09","Women and Equalities","2015-11-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, which regulations the Government Equalities Office introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations her Office expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate she has made of the cost of such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15129","15129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426630","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which regulations his Department introduced as a result of EU legislation in (a) 2013, (b) 2014 and (c) 2015 to date; which regulations his Department expects to implement as a result of EU legislation in (i) 2016 and (ii) 2017; and what estimate he has made of the cost of such regulation to the (A) public purse and (B) private sector.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15130","15130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426631","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average reduction in entitlement to universal credit was which resulted from a claimant taking up paid work in the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15077","15077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426632","2015-11-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of his Department's expected DEL underspend in 2015-16; what his Department's current forecast for AME expenditure is in 2015-16; and what that forecast was at the time of (a) the Summer Budget 2015 and (b) the March Budget 2015.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15187","15187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426633","2015-11-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the under-occupancy penalty on people with disabilities.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15144","15144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426634","2015-11-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the number of people who have been affected by the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15145","15145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426635","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many self-employed people in receipt of universal credit reported earnings lower than the minimum income floor in the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15075","15075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426636","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of households in receipt of universal credit qualify for (a) free school meals and (b) free NHS prescriptions; and how many such qualifying households are in receipt of those benefits.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15087","15087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426637","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people in receipt of universal credit had their entitlement reduced as a result of taking up paid work in the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15076","15076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426638","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Universal Credit (Work Allowance) Amendment Regulations 2015 (S.I., 2015, No. 1649) on work incentives for single parents in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15084","15084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426639","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of households that will move into work as a result of moving onto universal credit by 2020.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15073","15073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426640","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to fund additional support for disabled people who might require assistance to fill in job applications and to attend job interviews.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15093","15093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426641","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who are self-employed made a successful claim for universal credit in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15074","15074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426642","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of households in receipt of universal credit in the four pathfinder areas have alternative payment arrangements in place to allow for the housing costs element to be paid directly to their landlord.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15085","15085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426643","2015-11-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he will respond to the Review of Survivor Benefits in Occupational Pension Schemes, published in June 2014.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15070","15070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426644","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many social housing providers in the four pathfinder areas for universal credit have applied for trusted partner status to allow for direct payment of the housing costs element in certain circumstances.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15086","15086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426645","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average amount paid for the reimbursement of childcare costs to claimants in receipt of the childcare element of universal credit was in the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15082","15082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426646","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of universal credit are self-employed.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15072","15072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426647","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who will be in receipt of legacy benefits and awaiting transfer to universal credit in May 2020.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15083","15083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426648","2015-11-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on (a) temporary agency staff, (b) consultants, (c) non-payroll staff, (d) administration and (e) marketing and advertising in real terms in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15151","15151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426649","2015-11-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of the independent living fund have had that funding reduced following the transfer of that fund to local authorities.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15140","15140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426650","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average reduction in entitlement to universal credit was which resulted from a claimant who was already in work increasing the number of hours they worked in the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15078","15078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426651","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of universal credit lost their entire entitlement as a result of (a) taking up paid work and (b) increasing the number of hours they worked in the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15079","15079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426652","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average number of hours of childcare was for which claimants in receipt of the childcare element of universal credit made a claim for reimbursement of their costs in the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15081","15081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426653","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department holds on the average hourly earnings of working people in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15080","15080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426654","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the cost associated with the introduction of universal credit to date.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15090","15090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426655","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been paid from the public purse in backdated guardian's allowance to people who have been granted leave in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15005","15005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426656","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people who have been granted refugee leave claimed backdated guardian's allowance in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15004","15004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426657","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people currently claiming legacy benefits he expects to have transferred to universal credit by the end of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14998","14998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426658","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people in receipt of universal credit who were already in work had their entitlement reduced as a result of increasing the number of hours they worked in the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14999","14999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426659","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what total amount has been spent by his Department to date on the (a) design and (b) implementation of universal credit.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15014","15014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426660","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people aged 18 to 21 in receipt of housing benefit also received tax credits in the most recent period for which figures are available; and what assessment he has made of the effect on those people of planned reforms to tax credit.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 15046","15046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426070","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2015 to Question 10790, who (a) the chair and (b) other members of the National Infant Feeding Steering Group are.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14864","14864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426071","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2015 to Question 10790, if he will place in the Library the minutes of meetings of the National Infant Feeding Steering Group in the last two years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14865","14865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426072","2015-11-06","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK nuclear weapons have been withdrawn from operational service as a result of (a) multilateral negotiation and (b) unilateral action since 1985.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14817","14817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426073","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2015 to Question 13044, what the (a) technical, (b) regulatory and (c) contractual reasons were for delays at (i) Olkiluoto 3 and (ii) Flamanville 3 reactors.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14863","14863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426074","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS (a) standalone midwife-led units, (b) midwife-led units situated alongside consultant-led units and (c) consultant-led maternity units there are in each region of England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14850","14850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426075","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the length of time it is taking the British Virgin Island government to respond to its consultation on a public register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14757","14757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426076","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the steps taken by the British Virgin Islands to meet the Prime Minister's ambition for a public register of beneficial ownership since June 2013.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14756","14756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426077","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions patients were refused access to their mental health records in 2014.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14972","14972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426078","2015-11-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will hold discussions with the devolved administrations on establishing best practice in reducing re-offending rates throughout the UK.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14973","14973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426079","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will raise with the Prime Minister of India during his forthcoming visit the welfare of elephants being trained to work in the tourism industry in that country.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14718","14718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426080","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of electric charging points in air quality management areas, (b) number of such points needed to have an effect on air quality and (c) associated costs of upgrading the necessary grid infrastructure.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14855","14855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426081","2015-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the role of LPG autogas in helping to improve urban air quality.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14856","14856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426082","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has assessed the necessary financial support required by local authorities to deliver a charging network for electric vehicles of the scale required to have an effect on local air quality.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14767","14767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426083","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has assessed the potential of liquid petroleum gas as a replacement for diesel in (a) passenger cars, (b) taxis, (c) HGVs, (d) vans and (e) public sector fleets.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14766","14766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426084","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support the development of biopropane for transport fuel.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14692","14692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426085","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has met vehicle manufacturers to discuss the availability of liquid petroleum gas vehicle models in the UK market and their potential effect on air quality.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14693","14693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426086","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what support his Department has provided to local authorities to improve air quality using liquid petroleum gas; and what further such support his Department has planned.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14696","14696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426087","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to prevent carbon emissions outside the UK.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14808","14808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426088","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to support the sustainable management of forests outside the UK.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14809","14809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426089","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will take steps in support of the African Group's agreement on a Global Goal for Adaptation at the Paris Climate Conference in December.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14810","14810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426090","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to support the creation of jobs through low carbon growth (a) within and (b) outside the UK.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14956","14956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426091","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on responding to correspondence from hon. Members by email rather than by letter.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14891","14891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426092","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many replies to constituent correspondence from hon. Members her Department sent by (a) email and (b) letter in each of the last three years; and what the cost of using each method was in each such year.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14880","14880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426093","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many replies to constituent correspondence from hon. Members his Department sent by (a) email and (b) letter in each of the last three years; and what the cost breakdown of each method was in each such year.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14881","14881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426094","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received on responding to correspondence from hon. Members by email rather than by letter.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14890","14890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426095","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 October 2015 to Question 11792, which grants made under section 64 of the Health Services and Public Health Act 1964 are awarded on a non-competed basis; and if he will ensure that all future section 64 grants are awarded on a competed basis.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14761","14761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426096","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2015 to Question 12657, if he will commission an independent review into the procedures followed by the Tobacco Control policy team within his Department when awarding section 64 grants to Action on Smoking and Health.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14760","14760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426097","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department received from Action on Smoking and Health about its grant application for the 2015-16 financial year since receipt of that application.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14762","14762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426098","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people over 100 years old living (a) in the UK and (b) overseas received the state pension in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14680","14680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426099","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Royal Prerogative of Mercy has been granted to Moussa Koussa; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14895","14895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426100","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Moussa Koussa's arrival in the UK by aeroplane at Farnborough in March 2011 was by prior agreement with the UK Government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14953","14953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426101","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what evidence the Government holds of involvement in the Lockerbie bombing of Moussa Koussa; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14952","14952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426102","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when Jonathan Dart commenced his duties as head of the Libyan Reconciliation Unit; when lawyers representing victims of terrorist attacks committed using Semtex supplied by Libya were advised of his appointment; on what dates Mr Dart met those lawyers (a) first and (b) subsequently; and what other contact Mr Dart has had with those lawyers.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14951","14951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426103","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contact there has been between Government officials and Moussa Koussa since his departure from the UK in 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14947","14947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426104","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which (a) retired civil servants and (b) former Ministers travelled to Libya at public expense between 2002 and October 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14948","14948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426105","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which (a) retired civil servants and (b) former Ministers have travelled to Libya at public expense since October 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14949","14949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426106","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what was discussed at the meeting between Sir John Scarlett and Moussa Koussa in the UK in 2001.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14950","14950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426107","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what (a) ex gratia and (b) other payments were made to Moussa Koussa by the UK Government in 2011; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14954","14954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426108","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what costs relating to the relocation of Moussa Koussa to Qatar in 2011 were met by the UK Government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14955","14955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426109","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government has taken to (a) improve destination data for school leavers and (b) develop online portals to help advise school leavers of all post-16 learning options.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14828","14828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426110","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what evidential basis there is for there being a link between enabling students from low and middle income backgrounds to attend university and improving UK productivity set out in his report, Fixing the foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation, published in July 2015.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14827","14827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426111","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how the introduction of a faster route to degree-awarding powers set out in the HM Treasury report, Fixing the foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation, published in July 2015, will improve UK productivity.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14829","14829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426112","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans the Government has to move away from the funding per qualification model for adult learners as set out in the HM Treasury report, Fixing the foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation, published in July 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14826","14826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426113","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2015 to Question 11315, whether local authorities (a) retain intellectual property rights over the postal addresses they have helped to create and (b) benefit financially from those rights from Royal Mail.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14730","14730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426114","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of annual funding cycles on the ability of further education and sixth form colleges to undertake financial planning; what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on that matter; what plans the Government has to change those funding cycles to reflect Government spending review cycles; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14932","14932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426115","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of English and mathematics teachers in further education and sixth form colleges; and what effect those steps have had.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14933","14933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426116","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received on increasing the number of English and mathematics teachers in further education and sixth form colleges.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14934","14934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426117","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect on the financial sustainability of sixth form colleges of (a) VAT and (b) pension costs; and if she will estimate the average proportion of a sixth form college's budget which is spent on those costs.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14892","14892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426118","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS charges claim forms include a box for universal credit.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14935","14935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426119","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will support the establishment of a full, international, independent investigation by the UN into claims of genocide against the Rohingya in Burma.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14857","14857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426120","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will take steps to promote the use of British welded steel instead of imported seamless steel in the shale gas exploration industry.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14676","14676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426121","2015-11-06","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many former service personnel are in receipt of Armed Forces Independence Payments.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14797","14797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426122","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to update guidance to Jobcentre Plus staff on claimants that report suicidal thoughts; and how such existing guidance is made available to those staff.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14716","14716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426123","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average number of personal independence payment assessments undertaken each week was in September and October 2015.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14734","14734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426124","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent contact the Government has had with the Free Syrian Army.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14765","14765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426125","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of Syrian children in Europe who are (a) vulnerable to trafficking and (b) unaccompanied.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14772","14772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426126","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the creation of 28 states in South Sudan on the prospects for peace in that region.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14773","14773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426127","2015-11-09","Department for International Development","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the financial contribution made by (a) the UK and (b) other nations to the UN World Food Programme to meet demand on that programme (i) in 2015 and (ii) from January 2016.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14770","14770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426128","2015-11-09","Department for International Development","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her objectives are for the World Humanitarian Summit in May 2016.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14771","14771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426129","2015-11-09","Department for International Development","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect on Syrian refugees of fluctuations in the value of food vouchers provided by the World Food Programme.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14843","14843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426130","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure schools in rural Suffolk receive an allocation of funding based on need.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14777","14777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426131","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the President of Egypt on that country's protest and counter-terrorism laws.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14837","14837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426132","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what human rights concerns he plans to raise with President Abdel Fatah al-Sisi of Egypt during his forthcoming visit.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14968","14968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426133","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he made to the President Abdel Fatah al-Sisi of Egypt about the case of Israa Al-Taweel.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14913","14913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426134","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he raised with the President Abdel Fatah al-Sisi of Egypt the case of Mahmoud Mohamed Ahmed Hussein.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14914","14914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426135","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to secure a fair contribution from offshore digital betting operators to the 55th levy scheme.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14851","14851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426136","2015-11-06","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress he has made on and what the timescale is for implementation of a Horserace Betting Right as a replacement for the Horserace Betting Levy.","Biography information for George Kerevan","George Kerevan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14852","14852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426137","2015-11-09","Wales Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the Written Statement by the Secretary of State for Scotland, HCWS282 whether he plans to bring forward proposals to amend the draft Wales Bill to include a requirement that the National Assembly for Wales and the Welsh Government should not be abolished except on the basis of a decision of the people of Wales.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14775","14775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426138","2015-11-06","Wales Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will publish the minutes of all the meetings held during the St David's Day process.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14798","14798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426139","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2015 to Question 13279, for what reason his Department has not estimated or calculated the number of families whose income will be reduced as a result of proposed changes to tax credits.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14749","14749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426140","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many men in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency aged (i) 60, (ii) 61, (iii) 62, (iv) 63, (v) 64, (vi) 65, (vii) 66 and (viii) 67 are in receipt of the carer addition element of pension credit.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14737","14737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426141","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency aged (i) 60, (ii) 61, (iii) 62, (iv) 63, (v) 64, (vi) 65, (vii) 66 and (viii) 67 are in receipt of the carer addition element of pension credit.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14738","14738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426142","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency who had claimed carer's allowance immediately prior to attaining state pension age have ceased to be eligible to claim that allowance upon their receipt of the state pension since (i) January 2015, (ii) January 2014, (iii) January 2013, (iv) January 2012, (v) January 2011, (vi) May 2010 and (vii) January 2010.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14803","14803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426143","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency who are aged (i) 60, (ii) 61, (iii) 62, (iv) 63, (v) 64, (vi) 65, (vii) 66, and (viii) 67 are in receipt of the state pension in the 2015-16  financial year.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14804","14804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426144","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many men in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency who are aged (i) 60, (ii) 61, (iii) 62, (iv) 63, (v) 64, (vi) 65, (vii) 66, and (viii) 67 are in receipt of the state pension in the 2015-16 financial year.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14805","14805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426145","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency who are aged (i) 60, (ii) 61, (iii) 62, (iv) 63, (v) 64, (vi) 65, (vii) 66, and (viii) 67 are in receipt of pension credit in the 2015-16 financial year.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14806","14806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426146","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many men in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency who are aged (i) 60, (ii) 61, (iii) 62, (iv) 63, (v) 64, (vi) 65, (vii) 66, and (viii) 67 are in receipt of pension credit in the 2015-16 financial year.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14807","14807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426147","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost of providing carer's allowance was to people in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14711","14711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426148","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost of providing pension credit was to people in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14712","14712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426149","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimates he has made of expenditure on the state pension for people in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14713","14713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426150","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were in receipt of the carer addition element of pension credit in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14714","14714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426151","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many women aged (a) 60, (b) 61, (c) 62, (d) 63, (e) 64, (f) 65, (g) 66 and (h) 67 were in receipt of carer's allowance in (i) the UK, (ii) Scotland, (iii) Glasgow and (iv) Glasgow East constituency in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14715","14715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426152","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency are in receipt of both the state pension and carer's allowance in the 2015-16  financial year.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14801","14801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426153","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of Government expenditure on the carer addition element of pension credit in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency in the 2015-16 financial year.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14799","14799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426154","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he he has made of the proportion of Government expenditure on pension credit which falls within the carer addition element of that credit in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency in the 2015-16  financial year.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14802","14802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426155","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many men in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Glasgow and (d) Glasgow East constituency who are aged (i) 60, (ii) 61, (iii) 62, (iv) 63, (v) 64, (vi) 65, (vii) 66, and (viii) 67 are in receipt of carers' allowance in the 2015-16 financial year.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14800","14800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426156","2015-11-06","Women and Equalities","2015-11-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what plans she has to improve the representation of women among (a) hon. Members and (b) local councillors.","Biography information for Natalie McGarry","Natalie McGarry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14882","14882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426157","2015-11-06","Cabinet Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many cyclists have been (a) killed and (b) seriously injured in the last year.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14815","14815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426158","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the market size of the UK solar industry in 2016.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14859","14859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426159","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many responses have been received to the feed-in tariff consultation; and what account she will take of those responses in making her final decision on the feed-in tariff support scheme.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14858","14858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426160","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in the amount paid in road user compensation claims by local authorities in England outside London from 2012-13 to 2013-14.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14709","14709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426161","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the contribution made by bus commuters to economic output in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14679","14679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426162","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many roads were resurfaced in 2014-15.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14816","14816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426163","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of progress on Total Transport pilots.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14814","14814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426164","2015-11-09","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress he has made in respect of the introduction of regulations for international seafarers in the fishing industry.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14876","14876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426165","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to clause 1 of the Childcare Bill, what categories of childcare provider she plans to include in an independent review of the free childcare entitlement funding system.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14818","14818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426166","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of increasing free childcare provision to 30 hours per week on the number of nurseries which offer free childcare.","Biography information for Caroline Nokes","Caroline Nokes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14811","14811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426167","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2015 to Question 13325, how many bursaries his Department offered people to become mathematics teachers in the further education sector in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15; and how many such bursaries he estimates his Department will offer in 2015-16.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14936","14936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426168","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2015 to Question 13325, how many mathematics enhancement programmes his Department offered people in the further education sector  in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15; and how many such programmes he estimates his Department will offer in 2015-16.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14937","14937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426169","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of his Department's policies of providing bursaries and mathematics enhancement programmes to teaching staff in the further education sector on the total number of mathematics teachers in that sector; and on what evidential basis he made the decision to offer bursaries and mathematics enhancement programmes to teaching staff in the further education sector.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14938","14938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426170","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) discussions he has had and (b) consultations he has undertaken with sector stakeholders on potential changes to earning repayment thresholds for 24+ Advanced Learner Loans.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14944","14944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426171","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has to apply the freeze of the student loan repayment threshold on which his Department has recently consulted to the repayment of 24+ Advanced Learner Loans.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14943","14943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426172","2015-11-06","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of Innovate UK's effectiveness in securing (a) jobs and (b) growth for UK businesses.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14854","14854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426173","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the retesting of Volkswagen vehicles being carried out by the Vehicle Certification Agency includes testing for carbon dioxide emissions.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14759","14759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426174","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Volkswagen on irregularities in the levels of carbon dioxide emissions from cars manufactured by that firm; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14778","14778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426175","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions, on what dates and by what medium he has had with Volkswagen about the reliability of carbon dioxide emissions data for its vehicles; and what response he has received from Volkswagen in those discussions.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14846","14846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426176","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Volkswagen vehicles have been retested for emissions by the Vehicle Certification Agency to date; what the outcome of those retests has been; how many vehicles are still to be retested; and when he expects all retests to be completed.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14847","14847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426177","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of Innovate UK's contribution to the development of technologies in (a) aviation, (b) road transport and (c) ports and shipping.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14853","14853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426178","2015-11-09","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to increase productivity in 2015-16.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14682","14682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426179","2015-11-09","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he plans to take to improve broadband services in urban areas (a) generally and (b) for small and medium-sized businesses in 2015-16.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14681","14681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426180","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the outcome was of the investigation by his Department's Finance Group Internal Audit and Investigations team into allegations made in December 2013 of inappropriate use of the Flexible Support Fund at Plaistow Jobcentre.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14920","14920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426181","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, who authorised the payment from the Flexible Support Fund which led to the dismissal of two staff from Plaistow Jobcentre in May 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14921","14921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426182","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions were held with the two Jobcentre Plus staff dismissed from Plaistow Jobcentre in May 2014 after a complaint about misuse of the Flexible Support Fund on (a) whether that misuse was part of a pattern of malpractice and (b) by whom it was authorised.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14866","14866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426183","2015-11-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints were made by jobseekers about advisers at Plaistow Jobcentre between 1 June 2013 and 31 May 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14871","14871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426184","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on how many occasions between 1 June 2013 and 31 May 2014 the officer at Plaistow Jobcentre responsible for authorising payments from the Flexible Support Fund queried the use of that fund to pay for Zone 1 to 4 travelcards.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14911","14911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426185","2015-11-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department plans to take steps to ensure that water and sewerage charges for schools reflect actual costs incurred by the water company.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14776","14776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426186","2015-11-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the proposals on the provision of court and tribunal estate in England and Wales published by his Department on 16 July 2015, when the decision was taken to include Ormskirk Magistrates' Court and Family Court in the list of courts to be considered for closure.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14929","14929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426187","2015-11-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, why HM Courts and Tribunals Service officials based in Lancashire were not informed that courts in that county were to be considered for closure before the consultation on the proposal for a single local justice area for Lancashire.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14930","14930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426188","2015-11-09","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when HM Courts and Tribunals Service Delivery Director for the North West region was informed of the inclusion of courts in Lancashire on the list of courts being considered for closure under the proposals announced on 23 June 2015.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14931","14931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426189","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of additional teachers needed in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19, (d) 2019-20 and (e) 2020-21.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14872","14872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426190","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of additional teachers need in (a) mathematics, (b) English, (c) science, (d) physics, (e) computer science, (f) modern languages, (g) geography and (h) history in (i) 2016-17, (ii) 2017-18, (iii) 2018-19, (iv) 2019-20 and (v) 2020-21.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14873","14873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426191","2015-11-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will ensure that any agreement on a central registry of beneficial ownership in Bermuda includes access for the public with legitimate reason.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14836","14836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426192","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2015 to Question 5430, whether similarly effective systems for central registries of beneficial ownership in the Overseas Territories includes legitimate public access in line with the Fourth EU Anti Money Laundering Directive.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14755","14755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426193","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 11080, on Deportation: Appeals, how many of the 426 cases referred to have been heard in court.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14834","14834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426194","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people deported under the deport first, appeal later measures have successfully appealed against their deportation; how many of those people have returned to the UK; and of those people that have returned, what the length of time was that each such person spent outside the UK between their deportation and return.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14743","14743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426195","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the length of time was that each person who successfully appealed against their deportation under the deport first, appeal later measures spent outside the UK.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14744","14744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426196","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of foreign national offenders deported between July 2014 and August 2015 who returned to a country other than their country of nationality.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14745","14745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426197","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to her Department has been of (a) deporting and (b) returning deported people following a successful appeal under the deport first, appeal later measures.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14751","14751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426198","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 11080, on deportation: appeals, how many appellants (a) had a legal representative at their panel and (b) gave evidence at the appeal via video link.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14788","14788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426199","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 11080, on deportation: appeals, how many of the 426 cases referred to are pending to be heard before the Upper Tribunal.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14791","14791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426200","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 11080, on deportation: appeals in, how many of the 426 cases which were appealed were the appeals later discontinued by the appellant.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14792","14792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426201","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 11080, on deportation: appeals, in how many of the 426 cases which were appealed were those appeals dismissed by the relevant tribunal.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14793","14793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426202","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 11080, on deportation: appeals, to which countries the 1,780 foreign national offenders referred to have been deported.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14794","14794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426203","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 11080, on deportation: appeals, in how many of the 426 cases referred to was certification withdrawn.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14789","14789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426204","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 11080, on deportation: appeals, how many of the 426 appeals referred to have been certified under Regulation 24AA.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14790","14790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426205","2015-11-09","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether home educators are permitted under her Department's guidance to receive help from education authorities (a) through the SEN budget and (b) for looked after children, through the pupil premium; and what financial help is available to guardians who wish to home educate children with SEN.","Biography information for Sir Oliver Heald","Sir Oliver Heald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14927","14927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426206","2015-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with the fisheries Minister in the Northern Ireland Executive on the level of cod stocks in the Irish Sea.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14753","14753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426207","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Egypt.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14741","14741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426208","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Indian government on its steps to hold to account and prosecute state officials and other people who violate the safeguard for religious freedom in that country's constitution.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14677","14677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426209","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government had with the Chinese government during the state visit to London in October 2015 on reducing restrictions on the Christian minority in China.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14678","14678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426210","2015-11-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Kenyan counterpart on steps to control terrorism in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14752","14752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426211","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that people receive sufficient vitamin D each day.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14683","14683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426212","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of suicides by men aged 18 to 45.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14684","14684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426213","2015-11-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2015 to Question 8120, what the sensor capability is of the C-130 Hercules; and what the full extent is of its search and rescue resources.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14940","14940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426214","2015-11-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2015 to Question 8120, what the range is of the RAF Sea King helicopter resource in its coverage of Atlantic waters.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14941","14941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426215","2015-11-09","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2015 to Question 8118, what the Atlantic coverage is of the Sentry airbourne warning MK1 aircraft.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14942","14942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426216","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2015 to Question 11306, what the cost of commissioning NHS Employers to help trusts improve staff mental health and wellbeing was in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14945","14945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426217","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2015 to Question 12672, how many specialist midwives have been trained since November 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14946","14946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426218","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much of the 15 million new funding allocated to perinatal mental health for 2015-16 has been spent to date; and what that funding has been spent on.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14919","14919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426219","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2015 to Question 11305, if he will ask NICE to undertake a technical appraisal of psychological therapies.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14939","14939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426220","2015-11-09","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the report of the Mental Health Taskforce commissioned by NHS England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14912","14912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426221","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the names are of the in-patient mother and baby units specialising in caring for women during the perinatal period that were open in 2010.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14739","14739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426222","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many in-patient mother and baby units specialising in caring for women during the perinatal period closed between 2010 and 2015; and how many such units are open.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14740","14740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426223","2015-11-09","Cabinet Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what change there has been in median gross weekly pay for (a) men and (b) women in Ashfield constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14868","14868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426224","2015-11-09","Cabinet Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of (a) men and (b) women have been paid the minimum wage in (i) Ashfield constituency, (ii) each constituency in Nottinghamshire and (iii) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14869","14869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426225","2015-11-09","Cabinet Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of (a) men and (b) women were paid the living wage in (i) Ashfield constituency, (ii) each constituency in Nottinghamshire and (iii) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14870","14870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426226","2015-11-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many families with children living in bed and breakfast have been so accommodated for more than six weeks; and how many families with children were living in bed and breakfast accommodation in (a) each local authority in the East Midlands and (b) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14867","14867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426227","2015-11-06","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will (a) consider legal action to recover tax due from Volkswagen as a consequence of carbon dioxide outputs and nitrogen dioxide levels and (b) commit to not reassessing tax payments for an additional benefit in kind as a result of higher carbon dioxide outputting vehicles.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14888","14888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426228","2015-11-06","Department of Health","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings in the report of the Office for National Statistics, Decennial Child Dental Health Survey that (a) 46 per cent of 15 year olds and 34 per cent of 12 year olds had obvious decay experience in their permanent teeth and (b) children eligible for free school meals are significantly less likely to be in good overall oral health than those not eligible.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14889","14889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426229","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pensioners who were living in countries where their pensions were frozen have moved back to the UK in each year since 2009.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14780","14780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426230","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many foreign vehicles that had overstayed the permitted six months in the UK were identified as a result of the information sharing trial between the police service and HM Revenue and Customs that ran from November 2014 to February 2015; how many such vehicles were impounded; how much was raised in fines in that trial; and what plans his Department has to introduce such a scheme permanently.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14779","14779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426231","2015-11-06","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans the Government has for the effective and efficient oversight of strategic fuel stocks.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14877","14877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426232","2015-11-06","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Council of Europe Convention on preventing and combating violence against women and domestic violence.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14717","14717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426233","2015-11-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on developing energy policy.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14721","14721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426234","2015-11-09","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the planned date for the (a) start and (b) finish of the A509 Isham bypass is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14695","14695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426235","2015-11-06","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the economy of reductions in the level of the Bus Service Operators Grant that were made in 2012; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14782","14782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426236","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to (a) regulate freelance tutors and (b) ensure that such tutors have an enhanced DBS check in order to safeguard children.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14878","14878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426237","2015-11-06","Department for Education","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to (a) regulate freelance sports coaches (b) ensure that such coaches have an enhanced DBS check in order to safeguard children.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14879","14879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426238","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training and experience advisers who received calls to the NSPCC human trafficking and modern slavery helpline between July 2014 and June 2015 had; and what the cost to the public purse was of providing such training.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14821","14821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426239","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the nature of enquiries received by the NSPCC human trafficking and modern slavery helpline between July 2014 and June 2015; and how many such calls were from survivors of human trafficking.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14822","14822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426240","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of the referrals made by the NSPCC human trafficking and modern slavery helpline between July 2014 and June 2015 were made to the police.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14823","14823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426241","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of calls to the NSPCC human trafficking and modern slavery helpline between July 2014 and June 2015 that were referred to that helpline by (a) the police and (b) other agencies were referred back to those agencies.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14824","14824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426242","2015-11-09","Home Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what grant her Department made available to the NSPCC for running the modern slavery human trafficking helpline between July 2014 to June 2015.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14820","14820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426243","2015-11-06","Department for Transport","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce the finalised route phase two of the High Speed 2 rail line; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14735","14735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426244","2015-11-06","Ministry of Defence","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the cost of using external agencies for recruitment to senior Civil Service posts in his Department in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14894","14894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426245","2015-11-06","HM Treasury","2015-11-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost of using external agencies for recruitment to senior Civil Service posts in his Department in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14893","14893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426246","2015-11-06","Cabinet Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what average time his Department took to respond to freedom of information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14898","14898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426247","2015-11-09","Cabinet Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many organisations considered in-scope under the Public Contracts Regulations 2015 have provided Certificates of Performance in each Department in 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14831","14831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426248","2015-11-09","Cabinet Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether organisations considered in-scope under the Public Contracts Regulations 2015 have submitted Certificates of Performance to the Crown Commercial Service for each in-scope stand-alone public contract as required under those Regulations.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14832","14832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426249","2015-11-09","Cabinet Office","2015-11-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which suppliers have provided Certificates of Performance under the Public Contracts Regulations 2015 for each Department in 2015.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14830","14830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426250","2015-11-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the implementation of the greenhouse gas reporting regulation.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14813","14813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426251","2015-11-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to amend the Investment Regulations for Occupational Pensions Funds to require them to set out within their Statement of Investment Principles their approach to considering environmental, social and governance risks and to stewardship.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14812","14812"
