"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222641","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with bidders for the Northern Rail franchise covering the Colne to Blackpool South service via Preston on the replacement of Pacer trains with rolling stock that has not previously been used on London Underground.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224765","224765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222642","2015-02-25","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what input Rail North will have into formulating the response to the consultation for the Northern Rail and TransPennine express franchise; and whether this response will be a joint response with his Department.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224735","224735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222643","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what operational regulations or arrangements are in place to ensure that Northern Rail and TransPennine Express services always have another member of staff on board the train in addition to the driver.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224711","224711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222644","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers he has to vary, suspend and terminate the current tendering process for Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224712","224712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222645","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for how long Pacer trains will continue to operate on Northern Rail services; and when all Pacer trains will be retired.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224713","224713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222646","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on how many occasions representatives of his Department have met Rail North since the close of the consultation for the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises; and who represented Rail North at each such meeting.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224714","224714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222647","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether each local authority comprising Rail North will be asked to approve that body's response to the consultation for the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224715","224715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222648","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the existing Rail North board will be asked to assist in formulating the response to the consultation for the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224716","224716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222649","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which staff of Rail North will be involved in formulating the response to the consultation for the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224717","224717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222650","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many complaints the DVLA has received about delays in completing a review of an individual's medical information in relation to a driving licence in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224704","224704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222651","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many complaints the DVLA has received about delays in people receiving driving licences in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224703","224703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222652","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many applications the DVLA has received relating to a review of medical information in relation to a driver's licence in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224702","224702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222653","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what arrangements are in place in his Department to manage potential conflicts of interest of civil servants in relation to their previous employment.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224678","224678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222654","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether representatives from each local authority comprising Rail North will be asked to approve Rail North's response to the consultation for the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224708","224708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222655","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many approvals his Department has given to (a) close and (b) change hours for ticket offices in the last five years.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224709","224709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222656","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps in the invitation to tender for the Northern Rail and TransPennine Express franchises to ensure that there is always a second person on the train in addition to the driver.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224710","224710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222657","2015-02-24","Department for Transport","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recruitment process was used when hiring Simon Baugh, Group Director of Communications for his Department; and what role Mr Baugh will have in his Department after the Airports Commission has made its recommendation on airport expansion in the South East.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224679","224679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222658","2015-02-24","Wales Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the total value of contracts his Department has with private sector providers was in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224669","224669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222659","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the proportion of people expected to claim universal credit who have never previously used the internet.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224637","224637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222660","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) number, (b) value and (c) proportion is of incorrect payments made to claimants of universal credit since the scheme was introduced.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224638","224638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222661","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many challenges to benefits sanctions have been overturned as a result of tribunal interventions where his Department has not made reasonable adjustments under disability equality law; how his Department takes into account information from social services or health service staff before imposing such sanctions; and what processes ensure that adjustments are made before such sanctions are imposed on disabled claimants.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224641","224641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222662","2015-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of increasing the other funeral expenses category of the social fund funeral payments scheme in line with inflation since the level was set at £700 in 2003.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224546","224546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222663","2015-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department provides on (a) the average cost of a funeral and (b) potential sources of financial support for a funeral to families of the recently deceased who are in receipt of state benefits.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224548","224548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222664","2015-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people aged 18 to 24 years are subject to sanctions for (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance in (i) Preston, (ii) Lancashire and (iii) the North West.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224597","224597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222665","2015-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding has been provided to the Rapid Response Service in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland in each of the last five years; and what the staffing level of that service was in each of those areas in those years.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224589","224589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222666","2015-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons the Universal Credit IT system in Leigh, Greater Manchester, was out of action for three consecutive days in the first week of February 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224690","224690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222667","2015-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received from local authorities in Tranche 1 for universal credit roll-out about his Department's implementation plans for universal credit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224688","224688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222668","2015-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many local authorities are in the Tranche 1 group for the roll out of universal credit; and how many such authorities have signed a delivery partnership agreement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224689","224689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222669","2015-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many sanctions were imposed on employment and support allowance claimants in each month between January 2013 and June 2014; and how many such sanctions were imposed on claimants whose primary condition was (a) mental and behavioural disorders, (b) diseases of the nervous system, (c) diseases of the circulatory or respiratory system, (d) diseases of the musculoskeletal system and connective tissue, (e) injury, poisoining and certain other consequences of external causes and (f) other.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224691","224691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222670","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will place in the Library copies of the letter he wrote to the Rt hon. Member for East Ham on Universal Credit in January 2015.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224724","224724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222671","2015-02-25","Cabinet Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) men and (b) women were earning the minimum wage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224730","224730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222672","2015-02-25","Cabinet Office","2015-02-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of people were earning the minimum wage in each ethnic group in each of the last five years; and what proportion of people earning the minimum wage were in each ethnic group in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224753","224753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222673","2015-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which Ministers in his Department visited departmental buildings in Preston in 2014; which buildings were so visited and on what dates; who was met on each such visit; and what was discussed on each such occasion at those meetings.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224791","224791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222674","2015-02-24","HM Treasury","2015-02-20","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are currently employed at the Tax Credit Office in Preston; and what the projected staffing level at that office is for (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224792","224792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222675","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the number of people in Glasgow South West constituency who have found work after having had their benefits sanctioned in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Ian Davidson","Mr Ian Davidson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224807","224807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222676","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many calls were made to (a) The Pension Service, 08456060265, (b) Personal Independence Payment, 08458503322, (c) Carer's Allowance Unit, 08456084321, and (d) Bereavement benefits, 08456088601, in each of the last five financial years; how much revenue was generated from calls to each of those numbers; and when he plans to end the use of those numbers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224822","224822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222677","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the European Social Fund Operational Programme for 2014-20 has been agreed with the European Commission; and when he expects funding from that programme to be released to local enterprise partnerships.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224799","224799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222678","2015-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what arrangements his Department has put in place for situations where application forms requesting an increase in local housing allowance (LHA) to cover an increase in rent applied to an eligible LHA claimant are lost by his Department and the applicant consequently faces eviction.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224845","224845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222679","2015-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseeker's allowance applications processed by (a) Maryhill Job Centre and (b) Partick Job Centre were subject to monetary sanctions in (i) 2011, (ii) 2012, (iii) 2013 and (iv) 2014; and what the average length of such sanctions was in each such year.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224818","224818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179514","2015-02-23","Attorney General","2015-02-12","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 3 September 2014 to Question 207315, whether a Shawcross exercise has been conducted in relation to Serious Fraud Office investigations since the date of that Answer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224413","224413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179515","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking through the Fairer Deal to support local businesses in Thirsk and Malton.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224373","224373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179516","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people with limited or discretionary leave to remain have had applications for students loans or grants rejected in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224394","224394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179517","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224419","224419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179518","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224468","224468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179519","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224487","224487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179520","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224506","224506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179521","2015-02-23","Cabinet Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224420","224420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179522","2015-02-23","Cabinet Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224469","224469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179523","2015-02-23","Cabinet Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224488","224488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179524","2015-02-23","Cabinet Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224507","224507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179525","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224522","224522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179526","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224503","224503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179527","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224484","224484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179528","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224435","224435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179529","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the notional value of derivatives held by banks regulated by the UK authorities is; and what information his Department holds on the maturity and exposure of such derivatives.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224397","224397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179530","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the derivatives exposure is of each bank regulated by the UK authorities.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224398","224398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179531","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the contribution of the spirits industry to economic activity in the wider economy.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224341","224341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179532","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of how much consumers of spirits paid in duty, tax and VAT in the latest period for which figures are avaiable.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224342","224342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179533","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many jobs are supported by the spirits industry in the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224343","224343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179534","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the financial contribution of the spirits industry to the UK economy.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224340","224340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179535","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value of tax reductions for companies under the patent box legislation has been since April 2013.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224364","224364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179536","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the capital value is of each PFI contract formed since the inception of that policy; and what amount the Government is contracted to repay in each such case.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224365","224365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179537","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies have applied the lower rate of corporation tax associated with patent box legislation.","Biography information for Austin Mitchell","Austin Mitchell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224366","224366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179538","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on which dates he discussed with senior officials at HM Revenue and Customs whether maximisation of recovery of unpaid tax liabilities from UK residents holding private unregistered accounts offshore should be prioritised ahead of prosecuting alleged offenders.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224368","224368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179539","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224470","224470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179540","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224421","224421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179541","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224489","224489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179542","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224508","224508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179543","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of minor developments which will be built in the next five years; and what assessment he has made of in which towns and cities the greatest numbers of such developments will be built.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224544","224544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179544","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224509","224509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179545","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224490","224490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179546","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224422","224422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179547","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224471","224471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179548","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the BBC about the funding of the BBC and its regional programming.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224378","224378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179549","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 7 January 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester Gorton with regards to Mrs J Heron.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224383","224383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179550","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to commemorate the 200th anniversary of the first recruitment of Gurkha soldiers into the British Army.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224349","224349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179551","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what criteria he is using to decide the future location of the Household Cavalry Regiment.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224393","224393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179552","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on strengthening the Armed Forces Covenant.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224372","224372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179553","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224472","224472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179554","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance the Atomic Weapons Establishment is receiving from the US authorities on Project Pegasus.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224442","224442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179555","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when construction work on Box A of Project Pegasus at the Atomic Weapons Establishment started.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224441","224441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179556","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224423","224423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179557","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the decision to review the scope and delivery schedule for Project Pegasus at the Atomic Weapons Establishment was taken; and when he expects a revised scope and delivery schedule to be approved.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224443","224443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179558","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224491","224491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179559","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224510","224510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179560","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Strategic Defence and Security Review will address the issues identified in Joint Doctrinal Note 2/11, the UK Approach to Unmanned Aircraft Systems.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224466","224466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179561","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the expected operational dates are for Project Pegasus and Project Mensa at the Atomic Weapons Establishment.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224444","224444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179562","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the expected out-turn expenditure is on (a) Project Pegasus and (b) Project Mensa at the Atomic Weapons Establishment.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224445","224445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179563","2015-02-23","Department for Education","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224511","224511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179564","2015-02-23","Department for Education","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224492","224492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179565","2015-02-23","Department for Education","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in her Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224473","224473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179566","2015-02-23","Department for Education","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224424","224424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179567","2015-02-24","Department for Education","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to announce funding for music hubs in 2016-17.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224416","224416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179568","2015-02-23","Department for Education","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to collect information on waiting times for students referred to educational psychologists.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224359","224359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179569","2015-02-23","Department for Education","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what background checks are carried out when a qualified teacher from (a) outside and (b) inside the EU applies to teach in England.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224360","224360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179570","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of how many families with children are currently in debt to their energy companies.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224345","224345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179571","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if the Government will take steps to prioritise support for families with children when they fall behind on their bills to energy companies.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224346","224346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179572","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information energy suppliers are required to provide (a) his Department and (b) Ofgem to assist with monitoring the roll-out of smart meters to vulnerable, low income and pre-payment meter customers.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224399","224399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179573","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the resources needed by local authorities to enforce a minimum energy efficiency standard for the private rented sector.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224400","224400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179574","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many households that have had a smart meter installed in their property have also had one or more unique energy efficiency measures installed in their property under the Energy Companies Obligation scheme.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224401","224401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179575","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many vouchers from the first round of the Green Deal Home Improvement Fund have been cashed.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224402","224402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179576","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224425","224425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179577","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many Green Deal providers, assessors and installers have broken the Green Deal Code of Practice since the start of the Green Deal.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224408","224408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179578","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224474","224474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179579","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224493","224493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179580","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224512","224512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179581","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 222816, what estimate he has made of (a) the total number of hours, (b) full-time equivalent staff employed and (c) costs of reachback support in 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224534","224534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179582","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2015 to Question 220911, how much the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority expects to award Nuclear Management Partners in efficiency fees in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224535","224535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179583","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the cost to the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority of termination of its contract with Nuclear Management Partners.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224536","224536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179584","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 222816, what estimate he has made of (a) the total number of hours, (b) full-time equivalent staff employed and (c) costs of reachback support in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224533","224533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179585","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 222829, how much of the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority's expenditure on support costs was for (a) research and technology, (b) IT, (c) security, (d) facilities, (e) programme management, (f) procurement, (g) human resources, (h) finance, (i) head-office costs, (j) environment, health safety and quality, (k) regulatory engagement and (l) communications in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224537","224537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179586","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 222829, what the (a) research and technology, (b) IT, (c) security, (d) facilities, (e) programme management, (f) procurement, (g) human resources, (h) finance, (i) head-office costs, (j) environment, health safety and quality, (k) regulatory engagement and (l) communications support costs were for each of the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority's site licence companies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224538","224538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179587","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 222816, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed under reachback contracts in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224539","224539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179588","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much Nuclear Management Partners has received in executive staff costs in each year since it became the parent body organisation for Sellafield Ltd.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224540","224540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179589","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) time taken and (b) cost of dredging operations undertaken by the Environment Agency was in the (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14 financial years in each operational area; and what the expected benefits of such operations were.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224541","224541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179590","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on how many occasions the Environment Agency has (a) issued warnings and (b) brought prosecutions as a result of dredging or channel maintenance activities in each of the last three years; on how many occasions referrals were made to the police following such activities; and which rivers were affected in each such case.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224542","224542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179591","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the comparative costs of (a) connecting new minor developments to surface water main drainage and (b) utilising sustainable drainage systems for such developments in the next five years.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224543","224543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179592","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224513","224513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179593","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224494","224494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179594","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in her Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224475","224475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179595","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to introduce biodiversity offsetting; and whether ancient woodland will be exempt.","Biography information for Joan Walley","Joan Walley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224406","224406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179596","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance her Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224426","224426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179597","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which towns and cities in England and Wales have been most affected by flooding caused by urban surface run-off following heavy rain events in the last five years.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224439","224439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179598","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons his Department will not be flying the Commonwealth Flag on Commonwealth Day; and by whom that decision was taken.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224417","224417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179599","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the government of Democratic Republic of Congo on the arrest and incommunicado detention of 12 activists after protests in January 2015 against revision of the electoral law.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224415","224415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179600","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224427","224427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179601","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Libyan government on the campaign for equitable compensation for victims of IRA terrorism sponsored by Colonel Gaddafi's government and the decision by the Libyan Parliament to revoke a law banning officials from that government from re-entering the political realm.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224377","224377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179602","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Malaysian government regarding (a) the imprisonment of opposition leader Anwar Ibrahim, (b) Malaysia's sodomy laws and (c) sedition laws.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224348","224348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179603","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the conviction and imprisonment of opposition leader Anwar Ibrahim in Malaysia.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224347","224347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179604","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to commemorate the 200th anniversary of the UK establishing diplomatic relations with Nepal.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224350","224350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179605","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Chinese authorities on religious freedoms in Zhejiang province.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224381","224381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179606","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to encourage respect for freedoms of religion, association and speech in Niger.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224382","224382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179607","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224476","224476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179608","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224495","224495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179609","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224514","224514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179610","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224515","224515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179611","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of cataract surgery procedures that were carried out by West Midlands NHS trusts in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224454","224454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179612","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of IVF cycle procedures that were carried out by West Midlands NHS trusts in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224453","224453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179613","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to lay before Parliament regulations on the standardisation of packaging of tobacco products.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224464","224464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179614","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many block contracts are in place for mental health services in England; and what the aggregate value is of those contracts.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224465","224465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179615","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of knee replacement operations that were carried out by West Midlands NHS trusts in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224456","224456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179616","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of varicose vein surgery procedures that were carried out by West Midlands NHS trusts in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224457","224457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179617","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of breast reduction operations that were carried out by West Midlands NHS trusts in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224458","224458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179618","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of hip replacement operations that were carried out by West Midlands NHS trusts in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224455","224455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179619","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224496","224496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179620","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224477","224477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179621","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many private prescriptions for (a) benzodiazepines, (b) z drugs and (c) antidepressants were issued in 2013; and whether such private prescriptions are included in the analysis by the NHS of prescription costs.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224371","224371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179622","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the total amount spent from government sources on research into (a) stroke, (b) cancer and (c) coronary heart disease.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224370","224370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179623","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what analysis and research her Department has undertaken into the potential risk to human health of the transportation of animal carcasses and animal products in unsealed and unrefrigerated vehicles to rendering facilities.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224369","224369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179624","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent representations he has received on the proportion of Government funding which is allocated to health and social care.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224374","224374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179625","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of trends in levels of eligibility for social care set by councils between 2005 and 2010.","Biography information for Sir George Hollingbery","George Hollingbery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224385","224385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179626","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues to NHS trusts on the effective diagnosis and treatment of postural tachycardia syndrome.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224403","224403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179627","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has undertaken into the effective diagnosis and treatment of postural tachycardia syndrome.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224404","224404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179628","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many operations were performed by the Kettering General Hospital NHS Trust in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224409","224409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179629","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will delay the commencement of regulations on the standardised packaging of tobacco products for 12 months or until any legal challenges have been concluded.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224396","224396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179630","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress NICE has made on establishing Quality Standards on adult hearing loss.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224407","224407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179631","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224428","224428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179632","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2014, Official Report, column 710W, on pharmacy, what progress his Department has made on the introduction of data-sharing between GPs and pharmacists.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224438","224438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179633","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received from patients' groups about postural tachycardia syndrome.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224405","224405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179634","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224429","224429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179635","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what rules apply to the entry into the UK of diplomatic personnel from countries identified by the Government on countries of concern in relation to human rights violations and corruption.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224379","224379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179636","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse was of the Salvation Army shelters for victims of human trafficking in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013; whether the Government's funding of those shelters is dependant on the number of victims identified or the length of time they stay in the shelter; and for what average number of days victims have stayed in such shelters in 2014.","Biography information for Lord Randall of Uxbridge","Sir John Randall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224411","224411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179637","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with the government of Ethiopia the possible return of Mr Tsige to its jurisdiction since 2004.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224414","224414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179638","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any organisations contracted to provide specialist support and accommodation to victims of modern slavery are accommodating victims in hotels or bed and breakfast lodgings for (a) 24 hours or less, (b) one to five days and (c) more than five days; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Randall of Uxbridge","Sir John Randall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224412","224412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179639","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been identified in each of the last five years as having been referred to the National Referral Mechanism more than once.","Biography information for Lord Randall of Uxbridge","Sir John Randall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224410","224410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179640","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Mayor of London on the level of violent crime in London.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224375","224375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179641","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department offers on compensation available when police officers force entry into residential properties.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224362","224362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179642","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued on the use of reasonable force in the execution of a search warrant.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224363","224363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179643","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many awards of damages have been awarded in respect of cases in which police officers from each police force caused substantial damage during the execution of a police raid or warrant in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224361","224361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179644","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in her Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224478","224478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179645","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224497","224497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179646","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224516","224516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179647","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224517","224517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179648","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224498","224498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179649","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in her Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224479","224479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179650","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will meet the Religious Liberty Commission to discuss placing respect for religious freedoms at the heart of development policy.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224376","224376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179651","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the UN World Food Programme in Syria in ensuring that food parcels reach their intended recipients.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224380","224380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179652","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what guidance her Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224430","224430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179653","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224431","224431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179654","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what procedures are in place to inform victims of the reasons for any delays in criminal matters being listed for court.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224440","224440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179655","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victims were granted compensation by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224448","224448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179656","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people applied for compensation from the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224449","224449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179657","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224480","224480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179658","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many forms or documents need to be completed by people applying for compensation from the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224450","224450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179659","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average age was of a magistrate on 1 April (a) 1989, (b) 1994, (c) 2000, (d) 2005, (e) 2010 and (f) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224459","224459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179660","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what government funds are available for victims' support organisations in England and Wales.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224451","224451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179661","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224499","224499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179662","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of magistrates were aged (a) over 65, (b) 55 to 65, (c) 45 to 55, (d) 35 to 45, (e) 25 to 35 and (f) under 25 on 1 April (i) 1989, (ii) 1994, (iii) 2000, (iv) 2005, (v) 2010 and (vi) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224461","224461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179663","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what costs may be incurred by a victim when applying for compensation from the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224452","224452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179664","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of magistrates were (a) female, (b) male and (c) of BAME origin on 1 April (i) 1989, (ii) 1994, (iii) 2000, (iv) 2005, (v) 2010 and (vi) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224460","224460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179665","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224518","224518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179666","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many magistrates there were on 1 April (a) 1989, (b) 1994, (c) 2000, (d) 2005, (e) 2010 and (f) 2014.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224462","224462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179667","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers who have received severance or redundancy packages since May 2010, have subsequently been re-employed as prison officers.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224463","224463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179668","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the delays in criminal proceedings in courts in England and Wales.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224446","224446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179669","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in how many cases in which a suspect had been charged for offences committed in (a) 2013 and (b) 2014 a trial had not commenced after (i) six and (ii) 12 months had elapsed.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224447","224447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179670","2015-02-23","Northern Ireland Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what guidance her Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224432","224432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179671","2015-02-23","Northern Ireland Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much her Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224519","224519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179672","2015-02-23","Northern Ireland Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what her Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224500","224500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179673","2015-02-23","Northern Ireland Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in her Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224481","224481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179674","2015-02-23","Scotland Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224433","224433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179675","2015-02-23","Scotland Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224482","224482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179676","2015-02-23","Scotland Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224501","224501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179677","2015-02-23","Scotland Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224520","224520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179678","2015-02-23","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-12","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what information the Committee holds on what income local authorities receive from the sale of electoral registers to the private sector.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224367","224367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179679","2015-02-23","Department for Transport","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will conduct or commission an investigation into the knock-on effects of current engineering works at London Bridge.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224418","224418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179680","2015-02-23","Department for Transport","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224434","224434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179681","2015-02-23","Department for Transport","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224521","224521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179682","2015-02-23","Department for Transport","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224502","224502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179683","2015-02-23","Department for Transport","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224483","224483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179684","2015-02-23","Wales Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224485","224485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179685","2015-02-23","Wales Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224504","224504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179686","2015-02-23","Wales Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224523","224523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179687","2015-02-23","Wales Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224436","224436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179688","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department provides to its managers on how many days training should be made available to staff.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224437","224437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179689","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Government has loaned to the insurance industry to assist with the costs of the Diffuse Mesothelioma Payment Scheme in the first year of its operation.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224387","224387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179690","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the value is of (a) awards under the Diffuse Mesothelioma Payment Scheme and (b) benefits recovered from payments made under that Scheme by the Compensation Recoveries Unit in the period from the commencement of that Scheme to 11 February 2015.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224388","224388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179691","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance the Government issues on health and safety protection for workers administering (a) chemicals and (b) poisons used in pest control.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224395","224395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179692","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many individual cold weather payments were made to recipients in the UK in winter 2013-14.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224386","224386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179693","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what targets his Department has is place for processing customer claims for (a) income support, (b) jobseeker's allowance, (c) employment and support allowance and (d) universal credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224391","224391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179694","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of raising the participation age on the take up of apprenticeships by 16 to 19 year olds.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224392","224392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179695","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of raising the participation age on the level of youth unemployment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224390","224390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179696","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 10 February 2015, HCWS 269, on Diffuse Mesothelioma Payment Scheme, what the additional administrative safeguards referred to in that statement are.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224352","224352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179697","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 10 February 2015, HCWS 269, on Diffuse Mesothelioma Payment Scheme, what estimate he has made of the (a) additional and (b) total cost of paying awards at 100 per cent of average civil damages in the first year of operation of the Diffuse Mesothelioma Payment Scheme.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224353","224353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179698","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 10 February 2015, HCWS 269, on Diffuse Mesothelioma Payment Scheme, whether there will be any change in the amount of the levy on the insurance industry which was announced in the Written Statement of 28 November 2014, column 58WS, on Diffuse Mesothelioma Payment Scheme levy.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224354","224354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179699","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) applications and (b) awards he estimates will be made by the Diffuse Mesothelioma Payment Scheme in (i) the first year of the scheme and (ii) each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224355","224355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179700","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his estimate is of the (a) cost of awards and (b) administration costs of the Diffuse Mesothelioma Payment Scheme in (i) the first year of the scheme and (ii) each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224356","224356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179701","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of UK state pension reside in the French overseas department of (a) Guiana, (b) Martinique, (c) Guadeloupe and (d) Reunion.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224357","224357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179702","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of UK state pension reside in metropolitan France.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224358","224358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179703","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received from local authorities engaged in the accelerated rollout of universal credit to their areas from February 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224389","224389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179704","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 2 January 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester Gorton with regards to Mr Marwan Saleh.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224384","224384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179705","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensures that in cases where jobseeker's allowance claimants are sanctioned, local authorities suspend housing benefit only in cases where it is appropriate to do so.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224351","224351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179706","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2015 to Question 221729, how many former Incapacity Benefit claimants that were transferred to either jobseeker's allowance or employment and support allowance had participated in a Work Programme in (a) Edinburgh, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK up to September 2014; and how many of those have found work as a result of that programme.","Biography information for Mark Lazarowicz","Mark Lazarowicz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224344","224344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179707","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what criteria his Department compiled the list of people and organisations to whom his Department's consultation, Universal Credit data sharing between his Department and local support providers, published on 10 December 2014, was initially sent.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224467","224467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179708","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on training in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224524","224524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179709","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's training budget was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224505","224505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179710","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average number of days training of full-time equivalent staff employed in his Department was in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224486","224486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222463","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to assist people affected by the Ebola outbbreak.","Biography information for Stephen Mosley","Stephen Mosley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907685","907685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222695","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what terms and conditions the contract of the Chief of Defence Materiel has been extended.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907691","907691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222696","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects that a final decision will be made on the final pension age for the Ministry of Defence Police and Defence Fire and Rescue Services.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907684","907684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/222697","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress he has made on recruitment to the Army Reserve.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907689","907689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223025","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of savings related to PFI contracts in the NHS since 2010.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907651","907651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223474","2015-02-25","Scotland Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what progress has been made on implementation of the Smith Commission recommendations.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907640","907640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223475","2015-02-25","Scotland Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the change in the level of real wages in Scotland since May 2010.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907638","907638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/223476","2015-02-25","Scotland Office","2015-02-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the change in the level of real wages in Scotland since May 2010.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 907641","907641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179106","2015-02-23","Attorney General","2015-02-11","To ask the Attorney General, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the criteria used to determine whether or not a prosecution is in the public interest.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224213","224213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179107","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether it is his policy that the Ordnance Survey will remain the only official national mapping agency for the UK.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224214","224214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179108","2015-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which new higher education institutions designated under section 129 of the Education Reform Act 1988 received funding for (a) capital works and (b) specific designated courses in the last five years for which data are available.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224149","224149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179109","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many passport applications and renewals were administered by post offices in each year since 1985.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224171","224171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179110","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many post offices in which public funds were invested to convert them to a (a) main or (b) local post office have (i) temporarily or (ii) permanently closed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224172","224172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179111","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many external ATMs have been installed at (a) Crown, (b) main and (c) local post offices in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224173","224173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179112","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) Crown and (b) sub-post offices have been (i) temporarily and (ii) permanently closed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224174","224174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179113","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the shortest period was between the date on which a post office branch received public funding for improvement and the date on which it closed.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224217","224217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179114","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he held with the National Federation of SubPostmasters on the abolition of road tax discs.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224218","224218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179115","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) 18-25 year olds going to university from each West Midlands constituency and (b) higher education students who fell into the top 20 per cent for attainment nationally from each West Midlands constituency in the most recent year for which both figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224143","224143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179117","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what qualifications are required of Pension Wise staff providing (a) telephone and (b) face-to-face advice.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224153","224153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179118","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what certificated training Pension Wise staff providing (a) telephone and (b) face-to-face advice will require prior to the launch of that scheme.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224154","224154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179119","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff have been recruited to deliver the Pension Wise scheme; and what the salary bands are to which those staff have been appointed.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224155","224155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179120","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much has been spent on (a) advertising and (b) recruitment of staff to provide telephone and face-to-face contact for the Pension Wise service since the introduction of that service was announced.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224156","224156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179121","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding has been provided to the (a) Pension Advisory Service and (b) Citizens Advice Bureaux for providing the Pension Wise service since the introduction of that service was announced.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224157","224157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179122","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which HM Revenue and Customs officials saw the list of bank accounts held at the HSBC private bank in Geneva, known as the Falciani list, as passed to the Government by the French financial authorities; what evaluation was conducted of that list on its receipt; and when Ministers in his Department were first made aware of the information on that list.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224162","224162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179123","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what communications he has had with Mr David Hartnett, the former head of tax collection at HM Revenue and Customs, since he left that post to advise HSBC in 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224163","224163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179124","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs which are supported by the Scotch whisky industry in (a) Barnsley and (b) each nation and region of the UK.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224222","224222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179125","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the total annual economic contribution of the Scotch whisky industry to the economy.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224223","224223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179126","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2015 to Question 222233, if he will place in the Library the grant agreements for integration projects and activities funded by his Department since 2010.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224231","224231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179127","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what procedures are in place to ensure applicants to the Right to Buy scheme meet that scheme's eligibility criteria.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224201","224201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179128","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reason he decided to amend section 106 agreements in respect of small and medium sized builders and rural areas not covered by section 157 of the Housing Act 1985.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224212","224212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179129","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the (a) social and (b) environmental impacts of the housing opportunities for inadequately housed people arising from his decision to change section 106 agreements for (i) builders and (ii) rural areas not covered by section 157 of the Housing Act 1985; and what further steps he will take to monitor such impacts and opportunities in the future.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224211","224211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179130","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2015 to Question 222144, if he will take steps to prevent Gateshead Council from proceeding with proposals to build on green belt land in Blaydon constituency until after the publication of Household Projections 2012 to 2037; and when he expects those projections to be published.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224150","224150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179131","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to better enforce building regulation inspections to ensure quality housing builds.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224167","224167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179132","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons spending data for his Department for most months of 2014 has been published later than such data for the previous three years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224158","224158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179133","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, for what reasons ministerial returns for his Department for quarters two and three of 2014 have not yet been published.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224159","224159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179134","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the reasons were for the change in his Department's performance in meeting deadlines for responding to Freedom of Information requests between 2010 and quarter three of 2014.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224160","224160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179135","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold discussions with the English Premier League on increased investment in grassroots football, in response to the recent sale of broadcasting rights.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224169","224169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179136","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to arrange for licensing of the Wycombe Sound radio station to be expedited.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224161","224161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179137","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make it his policy to encourage the English Premier League to increase its investment in grassroots football in line with the increase in revenue arising from the recent sale of broadcast rights.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224178","224178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179138","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on issues arising from the measures contained in the Football Governance Bill.","Biography information for Cathy Jamieson","Cathy Jamieson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224215","224215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179139","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the European Commission on the Digital Single Market.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224226","224226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179140","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to promote UK creative industries in Europe.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224227","224227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179141","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the press notice issued by the Ministry of Defence of Ukraine on its website on 9 February 2015, whether the proposed Memorandum of Understanding between the UK and Ukrainian governments will entail the UK Government guaranteeing any possible assistance in the pursuit of Ukrainian independence.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224184","224184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179142","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether lethal targeting by UK armed forces in Iraq is limited to ISIL combatants.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224142","224142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179143","2015-02-23","Department for Education","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 12 July 2010, Official Report, columns 577-8W, on teachers: Hartlepool, what the teacher to pupil ratio was in each school in Hartlepool constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224146","224146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179144","2015-02-23","Department for Education","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the average number of hours children spent exercising in schools each week in (a) the UK and (b) each region of the UK in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224219","224219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179145","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much land is currently held by NDA Properties Limited; and what the use, value and location is of that land.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224187","224187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179146","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much land has been sold by NDA Properties Limited in each of the last five years; and how much has been raised as a result of those sales.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224188","224188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179147","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the amount of land that will be sold by NDA Properties Limited in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16; and what estimate he has made of the revenue likely to be raised by those sales.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224189","224189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179148","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much NDA Properties Limited receive in income from its land and property holdings in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224190","224190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179149","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking to bring the ETSU-R-97 assessment methodology for calculating the noise impact of wind turbine generators in line with current World Health Organisation guidelines.","Biography information for Sir James Paice","Sir James Paice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224179","224179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179150","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the annual staff costs and other operating expenditure of NDA Properties Limited, including through third-party management fees, was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224209","224209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179151","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the staff costs and other operating expenditure of NDA Properties Limited in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16, including through third-party management fees.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224210","224210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179152","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much land required for (a) nuclear licensed sites, (b) operational purposes, (c) NDA offices and (d) other purposes is currently owned by the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority (i) directly and (ii) through subsidiaries including NDA Properties Limited.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224186","224186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179153","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much he estimates that NDA Properties Limited will receive in income from its holdings in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224206","224206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179154","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 223360, what proportion of the 1,000 skilled people he expects to be UK-based; and whether he expects these people to be subject to a collective bargaining agreement.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224216","224216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179155","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the (a) value and (b) amount is of land property holdings held by NDA Properties Limited, by function.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224207","224207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179156","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many holdings are owned by NDA Properties Limited; and what the value is of those holdings.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224208","224208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179157","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the full reports by KPMG he commissioned into the health economies of (a) Staffordshire, (b) Eastern Cheshire, (c) South West London, (d) North East London, (e) Cumbria, (f) Mid Essex, (g) Cambridge and Peterborough, (h) Leicestershire, (i) Northamptonshire, (j) East Sussex and (k) Devon.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224148","224148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179158","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in (a) Hartlepool and (b) the North East had to wait on trolleys for more than 12 hours to be admitted to a hospital ward in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224144","224144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179159","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 132 of the judgment of the European Court of Justice in the case C-491/01 - British American Tobacco (Investments) and Imperial Tobacco, 10 December 2002, if he will ensure that legislative proposals he plans to bring forward on the standardised packaging of tobacco will meet the standard set down in that judgment for sufficient space to be provided on that packaging to affix other material, in particular concerning trademarks.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224180","224180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179160","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policy on the effects of mitochondrial donation techniques on the characteristics of children born as a result of those techniques of research by (a) Woolf et al, Mitonuclear interactions: evolutionary consequences over multiple biological scales, published in the Philosophical Transactions of the Royal Society B: Biological Sciences 369, 20130443, 2014 and (b) Løvlie, et al, The influence of mitonuclear genetic variation on personality in seed beetles, published in Proceedings of the Royal Society B: Biological Sciences.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224152","224152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179161","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Health on 23 October 2014, Official Report, column 1142, what progress he has made on establishing the independent review of papers and evidence relating to oral hormone pregnancy tests; and when he plans to appoint a panel alongside the chair for that review.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Mr Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224183","224183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179162","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for mental health talking therapies in (a) Hartlepool constituency and (b) the North East.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224147","224147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179163","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to review the regulatory framework for the dental profession.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224168","224168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179164","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to address the effect of the time taken to obtain continence products on the quality of life of patients with continence problems.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224175","224175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179165","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library copies of the full reports by KPMG he has commissioned into the health economies of (a) Staffordshire, (b) Eastern Cheshire, (c) South West London, (d) North East London, (e) Cumbria, (f) Mid-Essex, (g) Cambridge and Peterborough, (h) Leicestershire, (i) Northamptonshire, (j) East Sussex and (k) Devon.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224177","224177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179166","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration he gave to owners and other beneficiaries of intellectual property rights relating to tobacco products in deciding to bring forward legislative proposals for standardised packaging.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224176","224176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179167","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2015 to Question 221511, what estimate he has made of the level of efficiency savings that NHS providers and commissioners can make in 2015-16 without affecting (a) the quality of, or access to, services, (b) staffing levels and (c) organisational financial performance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224191","224191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179168","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential (a) benefits for and (b) risks to patient care of NHS foundation trusts and trusts being financially penalised for failing to meet performance targets in 2015-16; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224192","224192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179169","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the oral Answer of 13 January 2015, Official Report, column 718, over what timescale he expects NHS foundation trusts and trusts to move to new and more preventative models of care as envisaged in NHS England's Five Year Forward View; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224193","224193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179170","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has conducted a study on the viability of a New Medicines Fund for England.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224200","224200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179171","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cumulative efficiency factor for NHS foundation trusts and trusts in 2015-16, taking into account (a) the proposed 3.8 per cent efficiency factor, (b) the proposed marginal rate for specialised services, (c) the marginal rate for urgent and emergency care and (d) other cost pressures; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224194","224194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179172","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost was to the NHS of paying doctors who had been excluded from practice on full pay in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224202","224202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179173","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many exclusions of doctors under the Maintaining High Professional Standards framework have been for reasons relating to their non-clinical behaviour.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224203","224203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179174","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS doctors are excluded from practice under the Maintaining High Professional Standards framework.","Biography information for John Howell","John Howell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224204","224204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179175","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding is provided from government sources for research into (a) intracerebral haemorrhage and (b) subarachnoid haemorrhage.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224224","224224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179176","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many commissioning fact sheets have been produced by NHS England since 2013; and what plans NHS England has to produce a commissioning fact sheet for dermatology services.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224232","224232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179177","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what stroke research projects receive funding from (a) his Department and (b) other government sources.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224225","224225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179178","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her modern day slavery strategy will contain plans to prevent victims of modern day slavery being retrafficked (a) within the UK, (b) within the EU and (c) elsewhere.","Biography information for Lord Randall of Uxbridge","Sir John Randall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224195","224195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179179","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the 449 potential victims of trafficking from Albania referred to in the National Crime Agency's National Referral Mechanism Statistics 2014 have received a (a) positive Reasonable Grounds decision, (b) positive Conclusive Grounds decision, (c) negative Reasonable Grounds decision and (d) negative Conclusive Grounds decision on their immigration status; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Randall of Uxbridge","Sir John Randall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224199","224199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179180","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the risks of retrafficking within the UK once a victim of trafficking has completed his or her period of reflection in a government-funded shelter and is no longer permitted to remain in the shelter accommodation.","Biography information for Lord Randall of Uxbridge","Sir John Randall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224198","224198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179181","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of how many suspected victims of modern slavery were subsequently retrafficked after being referred to the National Referral Mechanism in each of the last three years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Randall of Uxbridge","Sir John Randall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224197","224197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179182","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many calls have been logged in total since the government-funded trafficking helpline run by the NSPCC was established; and how many confirmed victims of human trafficking have been identified as a result of such calls.","Biography information for Lord Randall of Uxbridge","Sir John Randall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224196","224196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179183","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time taken for the determination of applications for Tier 4 visas Confirmation of Acceptance for Studies certificates was in the last period for which figures are available; and what the average time taken for applications equivalent to those applications was in the period before that period.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224185","224185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179184","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to determine the application by CTC Aviation, dated 10 October 2014, for an allocation of Tier 4 (General) Confirmation of Acceptance for Studies visas for pilot training; and if she will direct officials to make an interim allocation to enable the needs of that body's current clients to be met.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224181","224181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179185","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to determine the application by CTC Aviation, dated 18 November 2014, for Highly Trusted Sponsor status for pilot training; and what the reason is for the time taken to determine that application.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224182","224182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179186","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 22 November 2012, Official Report, columns 566-7W, on police: Cleveland, what estimate she has made of the number of police officers allocated to Hartlepool constituency for frontline duties in each year since the basic command unit was abolished; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224145","224145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179187","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2015 to Question 222395, what proportion of UK Official Development Assistance was allocated to fragile and conflict-affected states in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2012-13 and (c) 2011-12.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224151","224151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179188","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of prisoners were released without accommodation from each private prison in England and Wales in the most recent 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224165","224165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179189","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many punishments of removal from wing were given to prisoners in each private prison in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224166","224166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179190","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress has been made in implementing each of the recommendations of the review into the needs of families bereaved by homicide, published by his Department in July 2011.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224220","224220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179191","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the average number of days taken by coroners to release the body of a homicide victim back to the family for burial in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224221","224221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179192","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 223157, how many times (a) aggravated damages and (b) exemplary damages have been awarded following a civil claim brought by (i) victims of trafficking for sexual exploitation and (ii) victims of trafficking for labour exploitation or forced labour.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224205","224205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179193","2015-02-23","Ministry of Justice","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent progress he has made on proposals to privatise the criminal fine enforcement service.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224230","224230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179194","2015-02-23","Prime Minister","2015-02-11","To ask the Prime Minister, what due diligence he undertook on the background of Lord Green of Hurstpierpoint before his appointment as a Minister of State in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills and the Foreign and Commonwealth Office; and what communications he has had with Lord Green in respect of the accounts of British residents and nationals held by HSBC in Switzerland since 2005 since 7 February 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224164","224164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179195","2015-02-23","Department for Transport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department plans to provide to Surrey County Council for (a) road maintenance and (b) fixing potholes in (i) 2015-16, (ii) 2016-17 and (iii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224229","224229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179196","2015-02-23","Department for Transport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to announce the direct contract awards to (a) First Great Western and (b) East Midlands Trains.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224233","224233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179197","2015-02-23","Cabinet Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new jobs have been created in (a) Elmbridge and (b) Esher and Walton constituency since May 2010; and what the effect of such job creation has been on the level of unemployment in each of those areas.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224170","224170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179256","2015-02-23","Attorney General","2015-02-11","To ask the Attorney General, whether he has issued a direction under 4(b) of the Protocol Between the Attorney General and the Prosecuting Departments to the Serious Fraud Office on a case under investigation by that office in the last four months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224228","224228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179257","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the declaration by the African Union that the Crans Montana Forum in Dakhla, occupied Western Sahara, should be cancelled.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224247","224247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179258","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether any former officials his Department have taken employment with Rio Tinto plc in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224271","224271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179259","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether any employees of Rio Tinto plc has been seconded to his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224274","224274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179260","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the EU Commission on the UK's implementation of the Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224307","224307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179261","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the provision of superfast broadband to rural businesses in all parts of the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224292","224292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179262","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has sought a meeting with Hervé Falciani to discuss the details of unregistered bank accounts held by UK citizens in HSBC Private Bank in Switzerland.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224285","224285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179264","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the consequences for the UK economy of a Greek exit from the Eurozone.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224328","224328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179265","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2014 to Question 215333, what the estimated cost to the Exchequer in the calendar year 2015 will be of raising Transport for London bus fares in line with the retail price index.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224318","224318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179266","2015-02-23","Department for Transport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2015 to Question 223589, what the value was of the support provided by Network Rail to the National Task Force in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224319","224319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179267","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the future prospects for the UK's credit rating.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224321","224321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179268","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what incentives he is providing to encourage investment from Commonwealth countries in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224322","224322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179269","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with Scottish Ministers on the sharing of Scottish NHS data with HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224311","224311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179270","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether (a) his Department and (b) HM Revenue and Customs has asked the (i) Panorama programme or (ii) Guardian for the documents reporting on the use by UK citizens of unregistered accounts in jurisdictions abroad to evade paying tax in the UK was based.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224286","224286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179271","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what safeguards he plans to put in place to ensure the security of Scottish NHS data shared with HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224312","224312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179272","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect he expects the judgement in Edenred (UK Group) v HM Treasury & Ors to have on the timescale for roll-out for the tax free childcare scheme contract.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224305","224305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179273","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of debt owed to HM Revenue and Customs in unpaid taxes.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224290","224290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179274","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with (a) the Crown Prosecution Service, (b) the Attorney General, (c) HM Revenue and Customs and (d) the Financial Conduct Authority on the use by UK residents of the provisions of the European Savings Directive to avoid paying UK tax by opening anonymous bank accounts in jurisdictions abroad since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224284","224284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179275","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to permit publication of data by banks in the UK on the aggregate bank holdings of residents in other jurisdictions using the structure developed by the Bank for International Settlements for banking data collection.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224283","224283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179276","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any employees of Rio Tinto plc were seconded to his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224273","224273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179277","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with the US (a) Treasury and (b) Justice Department on HSBC's licence to operate in the US since HSBC's prosecution by the US authorities for facilitating money laundering in 2012.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224282","224282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179278","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any former officials of his Department have taken employment with Rio Tinto plc in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224276","224276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179279","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether UK Export Finance has provided (a) loan guarantees and (b) low interest loans to Rio Tinto plc to support any of its investments or operations overseas in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224280","224280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179280","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-11","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department provides tax relief to encourage multinational mining corporations to maintain their headquarters in the UK.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224281","224281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179281","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much Bradford Metropolitan District Council received from central government in grants in (a) 2009-10 and (b) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224253","224253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179282","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the potential (a) number of job losses at and (b) redundancy costs to local authorities as a result of the proposed takeover of responsibility for LLC1 searches by the Land Registry.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224289","224289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179283","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support market towns.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224325","224325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179284","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to publish the Government's response to the review of gambling advertising before the General Election.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224313","224313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179285","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership on UK creative industries.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224306","224306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179286","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the Regular Forces were stationed in Northern Ireland in 2014.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224264","224264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179287","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many women are employed full-time in the Royal Navy.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224268","224268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179288","2015-02-23","Ministry of Defence","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the value is of each of the golf courses owned by his Department.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224335","224335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179289","2015-02-23","Department for Education","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what comparative assessment she has made of the effects of compulsory school starting ages in Sweden and the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224262","224262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179290","2015-02-23","Department for Education","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the budget for schools in Bradford was in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Ward","Mr David Ward","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224308","224308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179291","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether any employees of Rio Tinto plc has been seconded to his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224272","224272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179292","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether any former officials of his Department have taken employment with Rio Tinto plc in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224270","224270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179293","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many electricity customers switched to an independent supplier in each month of 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224257","224257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179294","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of regional differences in the cost of electricity to domestic consumers.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224331","224331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179295","2015-02-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the average cost of connecting community hydro-electric schemes to the National Grid in the last five years.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224337","224337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179296","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had on the inclusion of proposals to introduce direct elections to National Park authorities through the draft Governance of National Parks (England) and the Broads Bill; and with which people or organisations those discussions have taken place.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224250","224250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179297","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the draft Governance of National Parks (England) and the Broads Bill will be published.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224249","224249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179298","2015-02-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the declaration by the African Union that the Crans Montana Forum in Dakhla, occupied Western Sahara, should be cancelled.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224248","224248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179299","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any former officials of his Department have taken employment with Rio Tinto plc in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224275","224275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179300","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any employees of Rio Tinto plc have been seconded to his Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224278","224278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179301","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress British military forces have made on defeating the ISIL threat in Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224326","224326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179302","2015-02-23","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the flag of the Commonwealth nations will fly on public buildings on Commonwealth Day 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224329","224329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179303","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the government of Germany on financial contributions for British victims of thalidomide.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224295","224295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179304","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his NATO counterparts on supplying arms to Ukraine's military; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224323","224323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179305","2015-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Jordanian counterpart on tackling ISIL.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224324","224324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179306","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals have not met their staffing requirements for registered nurse day hours in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224316","224316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179307","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent meetings he and other Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the food industry.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224296","224296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179308","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether Public Health England plans to publish its analysis of how the public health grant has been spent by each local authority.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224317","224317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179309","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 December 2014 to Question 218412, how much was spent on NHS smoking cessation services in 2013-14.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224315","224315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179310","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 Febraury 2015 to Question 223094, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings by the Pernicious Anaemia Society members' survey, published in the British Journal of Nursing in April 2014, that over 60 per cent of people with pernicious anaemia are unhappy with their treatment and that many such people self-medicate to reduce their pain; and if he will consider the potential merits of revising the relevant guidelines to recommend more regular treatment.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224293","224293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179311","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what scope joint committees of NHS England and clinical commissioning groups will have to deviate from national service specifications for specialised services in (a) 2015-16 and (b) future years.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224333","224333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179312","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what change there has been in the productivity of the NHS in England in each of the last three years for which information is available.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224314","224314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179313","2015-02-24","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England will remain the sole budget-holder and accountable commissioner for all specialised services in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) future years.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224332","224332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179314","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what change there has been in access to colon cancer treatments since 2012.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224267","224267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179315","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has conducted into the effect on public health of alcohol advertising in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224303","224303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179316","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost of treating alcohol-related illnesses in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224304","224304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179317","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the effect of the regulation of alcohol (a) packaging and (b) advertising on public health.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224302","224302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179318","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the adoption of standardised packaging for alcohol.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224301","224301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179319","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were newly diagnosed with diabetes in 2013-14.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224291","224291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179320","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what change there has been in access to prostate cancer treatments since 2012.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224266","224266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179321","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a National Clinical Director for Dermatology.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224258","224258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179322","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NHS England to publish the third quarter figures for Cancer Drugs Fund notifications and individual Cancer Drugs Fund requests for 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224255","224255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179323","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with Ewing sarcoma in 2014.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224263","224263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179324","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received from NHS trusts on difficulties experienced in recruiting breast radiologists.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224235","224235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179325","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of breast radiologists employed by NHS trusts.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224236","224236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179326","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of people with diabetes receiving regular checks of their blood pressure, blood glucose and cholesterol levels.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224243","224243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179327","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when there have been discussions since 12 January 2015 between members of the Chemotherapy Clinical Reference Group and clinicians on the breast cancer drugs that are to be removed on 12 March 2015 from the Cancer Drugs Fund list; and what the content of those discussions was.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224241","224241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179328","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed for the first time as obese in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224244","224244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179329","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of his Department's expenditure on diabetes is spent on complications arising from diabetes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224245","224245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179330","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps NHS North West London took to consult residents of Ealing local authority area whose first language is not English when drawing up its Shaping a Healthier Future plan.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224254","224254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179331","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of his Department's expenditure on diabetes is spent on regular treatment of that condition.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224246","224246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179332","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the next review of strategic clinical networks will be undertaken; and if he will consider the merits of creating a dermatology-focused strategic clinical network.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224234","224234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179333","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review the capacity of NHS trusts to provide specialist mammography services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224237","224237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179334","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of clinical radiologists specialising in mammography and diagnostic breast cancer procedures employed by NHS trusts.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224238","224238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179335","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of radiologists entering into training in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224239","224239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179336","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with NHS England on the future re-evaluation of the Cancer Drugs Fund list.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224240","224240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179337","2015-02-23","Department of Health","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of his Department's diabetes spending is on prevention.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224242","224242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179338","2015-02-23","Home Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the success of efforts to reduce the potential radicalisation of British Muslims in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224320","224320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179339","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department disbursed to projects in (a) Pakistan and (b) Azad Kashmir in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224256","224256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179340","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what additional support her Department is providing for Royal Navy personnel assisting with the aftermath of the Caribbean tsunami.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224265","224265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179341","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether any staff of her Department are engaged in considering the effects of drone strikes on civilian populations as part of her Department's work in the Middle East and North Africa.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224260","224260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179342","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department will assess (a) the effect of drone strikes on civilian populations and (b) access to civilian compensation schemes as part of its humanitarian mission in Iraq and Syria.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224261","224261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179343","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department provides to religious minorities affected by the activities of ISIL in Iraq and Syria.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224287","224287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179344","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what research her Department has undertaken on access of civilian victims of drone strikes in Afghanistan to civilian compensation schemes administered by troop contributing nations.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224259","224259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179345","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether any employees of Rio Tinto plc have been seconded to her Department in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224279","224279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179346","2015-02-23","Department for International Development","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether any former officials in her Department have taken employment with Rio Tinto plc in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224277","224277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179347","2015-02-23","Northern Ireland Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the outcomes were of her visit to New York and Washington in February 2015 to brief US administration representatives on the progress of the Stormont House Agreement.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224269","224269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179348","2015-02-23","Scotland Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with (a) Ministers of the Scottish Government and (b) his ministerial colleagues on the sharing of Scottish NHS data with HM Revenue and Customs in relation to implementation of the Scottish rate of income tax.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224309","224309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179349","2015-02-23","Scotland Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many children in Scotland are living in (a) relative and (b) absolute poverty.","Biography information for Margaret Curran","Margaret Curran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224310","224310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179350","2015-02-23","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what guidance the Electoral Commission issues on the sale of electoral registration details of electors who (a) are on the open register and (b) have opted not to be included on the central register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224251","224251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179351","2015-02-23","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-02-11","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what steps the Electoral Commission has taken on local authorities who have improperly sold on the details of electors who have opted out of the open register.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224252","224252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179352","2015-02-23","Department for Transport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many traffic enforcement cameras for special limits were in force on (a) 6 May 2010 and (b) the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr James Clappison","Mr James Clappison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224288","224288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179353","2015-02-23","Department for Transport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to ensure that cases before the Transport Commissioner originating from Wales are heard in Wales.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224339","224339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179354","2015-02-23","Department for Transport","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 223358, how many UK-based (a) ratings and (b) officers will be employed on the re-named Allseas vessel contracted by Shell to carry out major decommissioning work in the Brent Field.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame M. Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224294","224294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179355","2015-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many vaccine damage payments have been awarded in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Mr Russell Brown","Mr Russell Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224334","224334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179356","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to share information on personal independence payment claimants between his Department and social services departments in local authorities.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224338","224338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179357","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of apprenticeships to be created over each of the next five years and (b) the cost of those apprenticeships.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224336","224336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179358","2015-02-23","Cabinet Office","2015-02-11","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were in full-time employment in Havering in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224327","224327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179359","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants he expects to return to work as a consequence of the revised benefit cap.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224330","224330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179360","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons his Department and the Skills Funding Agency have not agreed a data sharing protocol with the Work Programme contractors delivering the Skills Support for Work Programme participants in employment project in partnership with Newham College of Further Education.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224300","224300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179361","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received from Jobcentre Plus staff, working on Universal Credit in jobcentres where it has been rolled out, about technical and communications problems associated with Universal Credit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224297","224297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179362","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the withdrawal of the Youth Contract Wage Incentive Scheme on youth unemployment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224298","224298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/179363","2015-02-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in youth unemployment between June to August and September to November 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224299","224299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178787","2015-02-23","Attorney General","2015-02-10","To ask the Attorney General, what recent steps he has taken to promote awareness of the laws on contempt of court among social media users.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224010","224010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178788","2015-02-12","Attorney General","2015-02-10","To ask the Attorney General, what discussions he has had with the Crown Prosecution Service in respect of the possibility of prosecuting HSBC Bank for conspiracy to assist some of its customers to evade paying tax.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224063","224063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178789","2015-02-12","Attorney General","2015-02-10","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the application of the EU Charter of Fundamental Rights, Article 3, Part 2 and the Convention on Human Rights and Biomedicine to interventions aimed at modifying the genome of the recipient's descendants.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224112","224112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178790","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 222938, regarding the standard individual export licence for equipment employing cryptography and software for equipment employing cryptography to the value of £7.7 billion approved by his Department for export to Israel and the Occupied Palestinian Territories, what the reasons were for the surrender of that licence by the exporter in August 2014; what role was played by his Department in the surrender of that licence; and what the reasons were for his Department's approval of that licence in the first quarter of 2013 when it was then surrendered unused by the exporter 18 months later.","Biography information for Sir John Stanley","Sir John Stanley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224113","224113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178791","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department has taken to enforce prompt payments to small and medium-sized enterprises by large companies.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224107","224107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178792","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what advice his Department provides to pensioners on how to invest their money.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224108","224108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178793","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to page 10 of the Government's publication entitled UK Oil and Gas Industrial Strategy, what revisions have been (a) made or (b) planned to the UK's Supply Chain Code of Practice in the offshore oil and gas industry since July 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224029","224029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178794","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to page 11 of the UK Government's publication entitled, Oil and Gas Industrial Strategy, what funding has been allocated to date to companies in the offshore industry supply chain through the Advanced Manufacturing Supply Chain Initiative during the current period of low oil prices.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224030","224030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178798","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 223458, what the current (a) employment protections and (b) collective bargaining rights are for contractors working in the offshore oil and gas sector.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224044","224044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178799","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding had been drawn down by successful bidders to the Regional Growth Fund by 31 December 2014; and what proportion of the overall allocation for each round that funding represents.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224047","224047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178800","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps have been taken since July 2014 to revise the UK Oil and Gas Industrial Strategy: government and industry in partnership; and when that Strategy is next due for review.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224046","224046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178801","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on the number of people (a) qualified and (b) qualified at level 3 as hairdressers and barbers.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224048","224048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178802","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the staff of the Ordnance Survey being transferred into a government company will have their terms and conditions protected by TUPE.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224120","224120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178803","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding was awarded by the (a) Arts and Humanities Research Council, (b) Biotechnology and Biological Sciences Research Council, (c) Engineering and Physical Sciences Research Council, (d) Economic and Social Research Council, (e) Medical Research Council, (f) Natural Environment Research Council and (g) Science and Technology Facilities Council to institutions and Reseach Organisations in (i) Scotland, (ii) Wales, (iii) Northern Ireland and (iv) each government office region in England in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224049","224049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178804","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding was awarded by the (a) Arts and Humanities Research Council, (b) Biotechnology and Biological Sciences Research Council, (c) Engineering and Physical Sciences Research Council, (d) Economic and Social Research Council, (e) Medical Research Council, (f) Natural Environment Research Council and (g) Science and Technology Facilities Council to each university in the UK in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14 and (v) 2014-15.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224050","224050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178805","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward proposals to extend the powers of the Groceries Code Adjudicator to consider complaints from primary producers.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224085","224085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178806","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding BAFTA receives from his Department and its agencies; and what diversity guidance and requirements accompany that funding.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224087","224087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178807","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure policy coherence between trade policy and international poverty reduction with reference to the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224086","224086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178808","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much capital and revenue research funding was awarded by the Higher Education Funding Council for England to institutions in each government office region in England in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224051","224051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178809","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what briefing his Department provided on (a) the promotion and sale of arms and military equipment and (b) human rights to HRH the Prince of Wales before his trip to the Middle East; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224053","224053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178810","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he has received an invitation to the Crans Montana forum in Dakhla, occupied Western Sahara; and whether he plans to send a representative to that forum.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224137","224137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178811","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many young people living in Preston entered higher education in each of the last 20 years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223982","223982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178812","2015-02-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what meetings he and Ministers in his Department had with the Prospect and Public and Commercial Services trades unions before taking the decision to change Ordnance Survey from a trading fund to a Government-owned company; and whether he plans further such meetings.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223970","223970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178813","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent progress he has made on UK participation in the Mumbai/Bangalore Economic Corridor; and if he will place in the Library the feasibility report for that project and other related studies.","Biography information for Lord Barker of Battle","Gregory Barker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224015","224015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178815","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on consumers of decisions by utility companies to introduce charges for receiving information and bills in paper format.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223938","223938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178816","2015-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department plans a full or part privatisation of the Ordnance Survey to result from the change of operating model for that organisation.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223975","223975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178817","2015-02-12","Cabinet Office","2015-02-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will ensure that the change in definition of ambulance in Government Amendment 43 of the House of Lords Committee stage of the Deregulation Bill will continue to permit private ambulance and medical providers to operate (a) conventional ambulances and (b) fast response cars and motorbikes under blue lights.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223991","223991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178818","2015-02-12","Women and Equalities","2015-02-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many people have applied for the Access to Elected Office for Disabled People Fund in each year since its establishment; and what estimate she has made of the total grants from that date to May 2015.","Biography information for Alison McGovern","Alison McGovern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223992","223992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178819","2015-02-12","Cabinet Office","2015-02-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of commissioners from local government have attended the Commissioning Academy; and by which local authorities those commissioners are employed.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224134","224134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178820","2015-02-12","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2015 to Question 221932, what estimate he has made of the number of redundancies in the offshore drilling sector since the introduction of the Investment Allowance.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224045","224045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178821","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to comments by the Minister of State for Care and Support in the Daily Telegraph on 7 February 2015, on investigations into minimum wage payment in the social care sector, when HM Revenue and Customs will complete its investigations into the six companies; how the companies to be investigated were identified; and if he will take steps to ensure that workers are compensated when breaches of the minimum wage are found to have taken place.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224081","224081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178822","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimates his Department has made of the amount that would be raised from hedge funds, or similar financial institutions, by closing tax loopholes arising from the use of mixed membership partnerships.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224082","224082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178823","2015-02-12","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the names of individuals with whom HM Revenue and Customs has reached an out of court agreement to settle cases of tax evasion that came to light as a result of information from HSBC's Swiss branch; and what the amount of tax evaded was in each case.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224064","224064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178824","2015-02-12","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 221932, when the Joint Oil and Gas Industrial Strategy was published; what discussions he has had regarding the Strategy with his ministerial colleagues in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills since the fall in international oil prices; and what updates his Department has proposed to the Strategy since July 2014.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224043","224043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178825","2015-02-12","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 221932, what estimate he has made of the effect of the reduction in the rate of Supplementary Charge on levels of (a) employment, (b) exploration activity, (c) infrastructure maintenance and (d) decommissioning in the offshore oil and gas industry to date.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224042","224042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178826","2015-02-12","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the number of employees at Eurostar International Limited who receive more than 50 days' paid holiday per year.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224040","224040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178827","2015-02-12","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the possible risk of Greek sovereign default and subsequent effects on the UK banking sector.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224031","224031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178828","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking in addition to the Film Tax Relief scheme to promote the production of independent British films.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224103","224103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178829","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what total amount was paid out in Film Tax Relief in each of the last five years; and how many productions qualified for that tax relief in each such year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224099","224099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178830","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Film Tax Relief scheme in promoting the production of culturally British films.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224100","224100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178831","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations his Department has received from the creative industries on Film Tax Relief.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224101","224101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178832","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the number of creative productions which have been refused Film Tax Relief in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224102","224102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178833","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has received on Equitable Life compensation packages; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224013","224013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178834","2015-02-12","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward proposals to increase the island fuel rebate.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223964","223964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178835","2015-02-12","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he last reviewed the level of the island fuel rebate.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223966","223966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178836","2015-02-12","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to review the level of compensation paid to Equitable Life policy holders; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223969","223969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178837","2015-02-12","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the potential revenues to the Exchequer arising from an EU financial transaction tax.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223995","223995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178838","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on which occasions his Department has received representations on the introduction of special tax arrangements to support a major sporting event since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223937","223937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178839","2015-02-23","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on consumer indebtedness of decisions by banks to (a) charge consumers to receive information about their accounts online and (b) encourage consumers to receive information online.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223939","223939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178840","2015-02-12","HM Treasury","2015-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the potential savings to the public purse of abolishing higher rate tax relief on private pension contributions.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223929","223929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178841","2015-02-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 223119, how many times the Minister-led working group set up to identify evidence of poor practice in the park homes sector has met to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223952","223952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178842","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government of 15 January 2015, Official Report, Public Bill Committee, column 386, when and in what ways part M of the building regulations have been strengthened as a baseline accessibility standard since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 223976","223976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178843","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to publish a response to its consultation entitled Planning and travellers: proposed changes to planning policy and guidance, published on 14 September 2014.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224018","224018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178844","2015-02-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether it is his policy that his Department's proposed Mayoral Development Orders will be subject to the same guidance under the National Planning Practice Guidance as Local Development Orders.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224139","224139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178845","2015-02-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to lay regulations before the House to make the provision of smoke alarms in private rented property compulsory; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224062","224062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178846","2015-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people living in council and housing association properties in each local authority in Lancashire have been subject to the underoccupancy penalty since its introduction.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224135","224135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178847","2015-02-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes were purchased under Help to Buy in each local authority ward in each district and unitary council in Lancashire in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224136","224136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/178848","2015-02-12","Cabinet Office","2015-02-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the implementation by local authorities of the Public Services (Social Value) Act 2012.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 224130","224130"
