"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454113","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on the Gateway Project for armed forces veterans; and what plans he has to include Northern Ireland within the scope of that project.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28165","28165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454114","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much and what proportion of his Department's overseas development assistance budget his Department spent was subject to the International Development Act 2002 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28140","28140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454115","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether further authorisation from him will be necessary for any future airstrikes in Libya carried out by US forces from UK bases.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28099","28099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454116","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of email MA/DGMAA to Min(DPWV) private office 3 Dec 13 16:32.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28104","28104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454117","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of EC-01-19-01/20130205-Mil Cap Air Safety Management Plan 2103.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28105","28105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454118","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK (a) military and (b) civilian personnel are deployed on UN peacekeeping operations in each operational theatre.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28161","28161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454119","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK (a) military and (b) civilian personnel have been deployed on UN peacekeeping operations in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28162","28162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454120","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) funding the Government will provide to the Joint Security Fund, (b) funding his Department will receive from that fund, (c) funding Defence Intelligence will receive from that fund and (d) proportion of the funding his Department will so receive will be passed onto the armed forces.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28040","28040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454121","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people in receipt of a war disablement pension are also in receipt of the (a) age-related tax allowance, (b) allowance for lowered standard of occupation and (c) unemployability supplement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28038","28038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454122","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Chinooks, (b) Sea King and (c) Lynx helicopters HMS Ocean carried on her most recent deployment.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28039","28039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454123","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects each of the Royal Navy's Type 23 frigates to be withdrawn from service.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28004","28004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454124","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.92 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015, Cm 9161, what additional funding the Government intends to provide for investment in the Special Forces; and when that funding will be provided.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28005","28005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454125","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25153, on which Type 45 Destroyers all 16 recommendations of the Independent Power and Propulsion System Performance Review have been implemented in full; when he expects the implementation of all 16 recommendations to be completed across the class; and if he will publish the recommendations made by the review.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28036","28036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454126","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the amount spent was from the public purse was on decommissioning and disposal of (a) HMS Ark Royal and (b) HMS Illustrious.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28037","28037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454127","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.47 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence Review 2015, Cm 9161, which of the two Queen Elizabeth class aircraft carriers will be adapted to support amphibious capability.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28006","28006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454128","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence Review 2015, when he expects to announce further details of the Government's proposed armed forces families strategy.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28007","28007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454129","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.45 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence Review 2015, when he expects to announce further details of the Government's proposed new armed forces offer.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28008","28008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454130","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release, UK to step up NATO maritime commitment, published on 10 February 2016, which Type 45 Destroyer will be deployed to NATO's Standing Maritime Group 1 in October 2016.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28003","28003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454131","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2016 to Question 24278, how much has been set aside in his Department's budget for potential costs associated with the decommissioning and disposal of HMS Ocean.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28002","28002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454132","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.46 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence Review 2015, how much additional funding the Government plans to provide for investment in (a) equipment and (b) training for the reserves; and when he expects such funding to be provided.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28009","28009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454133","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27928","27928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454134","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27949","27949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454135","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2016 to Question 25590, whether his Department has received a request from the Kurdistan Regional Government for replacement ammunition rounds for British-gifted heavy machine guns; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27922","27922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454136","2016-02-26","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the reasons are for the time taken to supply the Kurdistan Regional Government with new rounds for British machine guns.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27907","27907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454137","2016-02-25","Department for Education","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in her Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27950","27950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454138","2016-02-25","Department for Education","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27929","27929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454139","2016-02-25","Department for Education","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has discussed the study, The impact of classroom design on pupils' learning, by Professor Barrett of Salford University, with her counterparts in the devolved administrations; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27897","27897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454140","2016-02-25","Department for Education","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's consultation on out-of-school education settings, launched on 26 November 2015, whether proposals to register out-of-school settings will require Ofsted inspectors to travel to Scotland, Wales or Northern Ireland to inspect tuition, training or instruction given outside of England by English-based institutions.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28027","28027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454141","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the total number of students enrolled in the English Baccalaureate in each year since its inception; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28053","28053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454142","2016-02-26","Department for Education","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 February 2016 to Question 26625, on the Twynham Learning Federation, for what reason it is not possible to place the documents in the Library prior to publication on the Department's website in May.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28136","28136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454143","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many smart (a) electric and (b) gas meters have been installed in Calderdale since the smart meter programme started; and what estimate she has made of the total savings achieved by consumers as a result of the smart meter programme to date.","Biography information for Craig Whittaker","Craig Whittaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28114","28114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454144","2016-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much and what proportion of her Department's overseas development assistance budget her Department spent was subject to the International Development Act 2002 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28138","28138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454145","2016-02-26","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has undertaken a value-for-money assessment for gas absorption heat pumps for inclusion within the Renewable Heat Incentive; and if she will place in the Library a copy of such an assessment.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28128","28128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454146","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she plans to open her Department's consultation on changes to the Warm Home Discount scheme.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27980","27980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454147","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will publish an updated set of Levy Control Framework projections.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27990","27990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454148","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what evidential basis was used when calculating the latest forecasts for the Levy Control Framework.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27991","27991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454149","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she will publish the findings of the Frontier Economics analysis commissioned by her Department in 2014 with the aim of further systematising her Department's understanding of the whole system impacts of electricity generation technologies.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27992","27992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454150","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27930","27930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454151","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in her Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27951","27951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454152","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information her Department holds on the number of people employed in the (a) wind and (b) solar energy sector in Yorkshire and the Humber in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27879","27879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454153","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the level of installed capacity was for (a) wind and (b) solar energy in Yorkshire and the Humber in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27883","27883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454154","2016-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26611, whether the Clean Growth Committee has met to discuss air quality.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27911","27911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454155","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her Department's policy is on the future development of tidal lagoons in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27842","27842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454156","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in her Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27952","27952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454157","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27931","27931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454158","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dogs on the restricted breed list were destroyed in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27984","27984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454159","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many dogs were destroyed following violent behaviour in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27985","27985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454160","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans her Department has for the UK to participate in the revised European School Milk Scheme due to be implemented from August 2017.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28042","28042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454161","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department is making on helping implement the European School Milk Scheme.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28043","28043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454162","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to promote collaboration between farmers by setting up producer organisations in the dairy sector.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28022","28022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454163","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to help dairy farmers better manage market volatility.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28023","28023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454164","2016-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to support the growth of the red squirrel population.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28075","28075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454165","2016-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to encourage more milk processors to comply with the voluntary code on milk contracts.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28070","28070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454166","2016-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to facilitate the development of an improved labelling code in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28071","28071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454167","2016-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will carry out a review of UK dairy processing capacity.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28069","28069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454168","2016-02-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps she has taken to support and develop the export potential of UK dairy through the Dairy Exports Strategy.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28072","28072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454169","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 June 2015 to Question 1205, how many UK nationals are currently employed by the European Commission; and what proportion of the total number of Commission employees they represent.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28126","28126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454170","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK nationals work at administrator grade staff level in the General Secretariat of the European Council; and what proportion of the total number of General Secretariat employees they represent.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28124","28124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454171","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many full-time equivalent officials are (a) budgeted for and (b) actually employed in each African country in which the UK has an Embassy or High Commission.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28132","28132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454172","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK nationals work for the European External Action Service; and what proportion of the total number of employees in that service they represent.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28123","28123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454173","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effect on national security of members of al-Qaeda (a) in Saudi Arabia, (b) in refugee camps near the Syrian border and (c) among migrants traveling to Europe.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28154","28154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454174","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much and what proportion of his Department's overseas development assistance budget his Department spent was subject to the International Development Act 2002 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28139","28139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454175","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the European Council on the use of EU funds to support travel by candidates for the post of the UN Secretary General in connection with that candidacy.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28155","28155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454176","2016-02-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK nationals work at administrator grade staff level in the European Parliament; and what proportion of the total number of that parliament's employees they represent.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28125","28125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454177","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the extent of Israeli settlement-building in the occupied territories since the cessation of Operation Protective Edge.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28111","28111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454178","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Indonesian counterpart on freedom of access by journalists to West Papua.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28024","28024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454179","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with his Indonesian counterpart the restriction on non-governmental organisations working in West Papua.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28025","28025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454180","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to publish the next quarterly progress report to the House on Syria.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28046","28046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454181","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department's guidance to overseas missions on hospitality for senior UK figures was last reviewed.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27994","27994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454182","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27932","27932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454183","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27953","27953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454184","2016-02-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on (a) geopolitical stability and (b) the UK's influence in the world.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27971","27971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454185","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Israel on the extension of the Separation Barrier in the Cremisan Valley.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27849","27849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454186","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Israel on the international delegation of Bishops which was recently refused access to the Cremisan Valley by Israeli security forces during a visit to the construction site of the Separation Barrier.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27850","27850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454187","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the government of Israel concerning recent anti-Christian vandalism at the Dormition Abbey.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27851","27851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454188","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the effect of a result in favour of leaving the EU at the EU referendum would be on the UK's membership of the (a) European Economic Area and (b) European Free Trade Area.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27866","27866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454189","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) children and (b) adolescent patients in (i) England and (ii) London were admitted to mental health hospitals outside of their home local authority area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27918","27918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454190","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much compensation the former Chairman of East Midlands Ambulance Service NHS Trust will receive as a result of her resignation from that post.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27867","27867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454191","2016-02-29","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has allocated funding to defend a legal challenge against his decision to impose a new junior doctors contract.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27923","27923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454192","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual rent paid by his Department is on 39 Victoria Street.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27972","27972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454193","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made by his Department or NHS England of the effect of minor ailments services provided by community pharmacies on demand for the services of GP practices and other parts of the NHS; and what assessment he has made of the effect of planned reductions in funding for pharmacies on those services.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27895","27895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454194","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is from referral to the commencement of a talking therapy course in (a) the North West and (b) Warrington.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27905","27905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454195","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what budget he plans to allocate to each clinical commissioning group in England to support the effective transfer of obesity surgery in April in a manner consistent with NICE's clinical guidelines.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27869","27869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454196","2016-02-26","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many women have died from primary cervical cancer at the age of (a) 20, (b) 21, (c) 22, (d) 23, (e) 24 and (f) 25 in each year since 2003.","Biography information for Ms Nadine Dorries","Nadine Dorries","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27910","27910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454197","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials of his Department have had with representatives of the Pharmaceutical Services Negotiating Committee since May 2015.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27912","27912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454198","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the ability of ambulance trusts to meet targets for (a) Red 1 and (b) Red 2 category emergency callouts.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27913","27913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454199","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 December 2015 to Question 18621, what further assessment he has made of levels of preparedness among clinical commissioning groups (CCGs) for the planned transfer of obesity surgery commissioning responsibilities to CCGs in April 2016.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27844","27844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454200","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27954","27954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454201","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27933","27933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454202","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on NHS (a) services and (b) governance of NHS England's decision to discontinue the role of national clinical director for neurology services from March 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27966","27966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454203","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of changes in the number of registrations of care home residents at GP surgeries since the end of retainer fees in 2015.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27998","27998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454204","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many community hospitals have closed in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27999","27999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454205","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) more cases of chronic lyme disease are correctly diagnosed and (b) more people with chronic lyme disease receive the appropriate treatment.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27987","27987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454206","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many grants of what value were made by his Department for meningitis research programmes in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27974","27974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454207","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on meningitis vaccine stocks in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27975","27975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454208","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the National Screening Committee next plans to meet to review its recommendations on group B streptococcus screening for pregnant mothers.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27968","27968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454209","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department expects hospitals to catch up with any backlog caused by the junior doctors' strike on 12 January 2016.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27993","27993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454210","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to review the efficacy of the 111 service in ensuring that 999 is not used in medical non-emergencies.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28017","28017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454211","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the announcement in paragraph 1.233 of Budget 2015, HC 1093, of additional funding for children and young people's mental health services, how much of this funding has been spent by NHS England to date; how such funding has been spent; and how much in total he anticipates NHS England will have spent by the end of the current financial year.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27979","27979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454212","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2015 to Question 14463, what the timetable for the equality impact assessment referred to will be.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28048","28048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454213","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much the Government expects to accrue to the public purse from the planned annual charge on Australian and New Zealand citizens for use of the NHS.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28049","28049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454214","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions the Government has had with the governments of Australia and New Zealand on the proposed introduction of an annual change to Australian and New Zealand citizens for use of the NHS.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28050","28050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454215","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding from NHS England General Practices under (a) General Medical Services and (b) Personal Medical Services contracts in Hampstead and Kilburn (i) was allocated in 2014-15, (ii) has been allocated in 2015-16 and (iii) is forecast to be allocated for each financial year to 2021-22.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28055","28055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454216","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will carry out an assessment of the effect of changes in funding for community pharmacies on patient safety.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28077","28077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454217","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of Personal Medical Services contracts by general practices in (a) Hampstead and Kilburn, (b) London and (c) England have been reviewed by NHS England; and in how many such cases have the surgeries been advised of the future funding arrangements to financial year 2021-22.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28056","28056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454218","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Government will reverse its decision to impose an annual charge to Australian and New Zealand citizens for use of the NHS.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28052","28052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454219","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if the Government will provide additional financial support to providers in the care industry to support such providers affected by the introduction of the living wage; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28150","28150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454220","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings he or other Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of Care UK, BUPA, Virgin Care, The Practice, United Health/Optum, Serco, Nestor Primecare, General Healthcare (BMI Netcare), Spire/Classic, HCA International, Ramsay and Capio in each month of (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014, (f) 2015 and (g) 2016 to date.","Biography information for John Cryer","John Cryer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28170","28170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454221","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support NHS England plans to provide clinical commissioning groups relating to the transfer of obesity surgery commissioning responsibilities from NHS England after that transfer.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28115","28115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454222","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings he or other Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the British Medical Association in each month of (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014, (f) 2015 and (g) 2016 to date.","Biography information for John Cryer","John Cryer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28169","28169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454223","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people vaccinated against meningitis in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28135","28135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454224","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who will be consulted during the review of blood donations by the Advisory Committee on the Safety of Blood, Tissues and Organs.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28058","28058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454225","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether (a) ex-intravenous drug users and (b) former-sex workers will be included in the review of blood donations by the Advisory Committee on the Safety of Blood, Tissues and Organs.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28059","28059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454226","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how long the review on blood donations by the Advisory Committee on the Safety of Blood, Tissues and Organs is expected to take.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28060","28060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454227","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the terms of reference for the blood donations review will be approved by the Advisory Committee on the Safety of Blood, Tissues and Organs.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28061","28061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454228","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the expansion of parenting programmes will be integrated with local transformation plans for children and young people's mental health services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28083","28083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454229","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure NHS England is working with (a) clinical commissioning groups, (b) local authorities and (c) other partners to develop and trial a new model of acute in-patient care for young adults aged 16 to 25.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28084","28084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454230","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to increase public awareness of personal health budgets.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28147","28147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454231","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on the care industry of the implementation of the living wage.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28145","28145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454232","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 1.233 of the March Budget 2015, how much of the 1.25 billion investment in mental health services has been allocated to children and young people's mental health in each clinical commissioning group in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28160","28160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454233","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2016 to Questions 24490 and 24491, on right of abode, what the process is for her Department's assessment on granting the right of abode to former British-Hong Kong servicemen.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28144","28144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454234","2016-02-26","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2016 to Question 19716 and 18 February 2016 to Question 26688, what estimate her Department has made of the (a) average and (b) total cost to the public purse of (i) appeals heard in the First-Tier Tribunal (Immigration and Asylum) which have a Home Office representative and (ii) appeals heard in the First-Tier Tribunal (Immigration and Asylum) which do not have a Home Office representative in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28057","28057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454235","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2016 to Questions 24490 and 24491, when her Department expects to have made a decision on whether to grant the right of abode to former British-Hong Kong servicemen.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28086","28086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454236","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking with university vice chancellors to encourage action to prevent threats of physical violence against Jewish students and connected parties.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28093","28093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454237","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information police forces hold on the (a) nationality and (b) ethnicity of those (i) arrested for (ii) convicted of sexual assaults against women.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28000","28000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454238","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people arrested in (a) England and Wales, (b) London and (c) each London borough were diverted to mental health services after an assessment by liaison and diversion workers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27917","27917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454239","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to provide certified copies of identity documents to visa applicants to support their applications to undertake an approved English language test.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28011","28011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454240","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were imprisoned for non-violent drug offences in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28001","28001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454241","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27934","27934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454242","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in her Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27955","27955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454243","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that failed asylum claimants who have spoken out against the government of their country of origin are not deported in such a way as to draw the case to the attention of immigration officials in the destination country.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27893","27893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454244","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of her Department's policy of providing information on failed asylum claims to the government of their country of origin on the safety of those claimants on their return to that country.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27894","27894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454245","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2015 to Question 3343, if she will commission an independent review of the reasons for the refusal of visa applications by people from the Kurdistan region of Iraq over the last three years.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27896","27896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454246","2016-02-26","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the custody nurse vacancy rate was in (a) total and (b) each London borough in the Metropolitan Police area on 1 January of each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27921","27921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454247","2016-02-26","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many crimes in (a) England and Wales, (b) London and (c) each London borough were related to or caused by some kind of mental health issue in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27920","27920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454248","2016-02-26","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many recorded incidents there were of no custody nurses being available in police stations when required in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27919","27919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454249","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made in standardising the border control queue measurement system across airports, ferry ports and rail terminals.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27868","27868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454250","2016-02-26","Department for International Development","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of donations to the Global Alliance for Vaccines and Immunisations she expects the UK's share to be at the end of the 2016 to 2020 funding period.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27856","27856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454251","2016-02-26","Department for International Development","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will increase Government funding for emergency food aid to Ethiopia.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27899","27899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454252","2016-02-25","Department for International Development","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in her Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27956","27956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454253","2016-02-25","Department for International Development","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27935","27935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454254","2016-02-25","Department for International Development","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what metrics she uses in monitoring human rights abuse (a) by governments and (b) in countries in receipt of UK aid.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27995","27995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454255","2016-02-25","Department for International Development","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has made representations to the EU on its funding of aid and development projects in Eritrea.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27978","27978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454256","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish details of the Global Challenges research fund announced in the Government strategy paper, UK aid: tackling global challenges in the national interest, published on 23 November 2015.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28035","28035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454257","2016-02-25","Department for International Development","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department has allocated to projects which are primarily aimed at Eritrean nationals in the last three years; and in which countries such projects are based.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28092","28092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454258","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect on children whose refugee shelters in Calais are due to be demolished by the French government.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28108","28108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454259","2016-02-26","Department for International Development","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which Departments other than her Department, the Ministry of Defence, the Foreign and Commonwealth Office and the Department for Energy and Climate Change have responsibility for Overseas Development Assistance (ODA) spending under the terms of the International Development Act 2002; and what proportion of those Departments' ODA spending was subject to the Act in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28137","28137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454260","2016-02-25","Department for International Development","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the effect on poverty reduction in West Papua, Indonesia, of the reported ban on non-governmental organisations working in that area.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28156","28156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454261","2016-02-26","Department for International Development","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff leaving employment at her Department in the last three years have subsequently been rehired within 12 months by the (a) Foreign and Commonwealth Office, (b) Ministry of Defence, (c) Department for Energy and Climate Change, (d) Department for Culture, Media and Sport, (e) Cabinet Office and (f) HM Treasury.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28141","28141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454262","2016-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many injuries were sustained by children during restraint in each custodial institution in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28142","28142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454263","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many concerted indiscipline incidents of each type have occurred in each prison establishment in each month since May 2005.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28151","28151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454264","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hostage incidents in which a (a) prison officer and (b) prisoner was taken hostage have taken place in each prison establishment since January 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28152","28152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454265","2016-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many responses to his Department's consultation on the closure of Hammersmith Court were (a) in favour of and (b) against the closure.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28129","28129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454266","2016-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average amount of time is a prisoner spends on education or work-related activities at Feltham Young Offenders Institution.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28130","28130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454267","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if the Government will bring forward proposals for legislation to establish guardianship provisions to assist families in managing the affairs of missing persons.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28047","28047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454268","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many pathologists qualified to conduct post-mortems there were in (a) 2010 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28044","28044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454269","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27936","27936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454270","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27957","27957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454271","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time between application to initial decision was for awards issued by the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27970","27970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454272","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many compensation claims against prison staff were made by prisoners in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27892","27892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454273","2016-02-26","Department of Health","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many Legionnaires' disease incidents have been reported in each prison since May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27914","27914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454274","2016-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many loss of tool incidents have occurred in each prison establishment since May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27915","27915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454275","2016-02-26","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many rape incidents have occurred in each prison establishment in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27916","27916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454277","2016-02-25","Leader of the House","2016-02-23","To ask the Leader of the House, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Office.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27958","27958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454278","2016-02-25","Leader of the House","2016-02-23","To ask the Leader of the House, what his Office's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27937","27937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454279","2016-02-25","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what her Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27938","27938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454280","2016-02-25","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in her Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27959","27959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454281","2016-02-25","Prime Minister","2016-02-23","To ask the Prime Minister, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in 10 Downing Street.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27960","27960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454282","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what 10 Downing Street's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27939","27939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454283","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many non-pensionable bonuses were awarded to his officials in each of the last five years; and what the total of such bonuses was to the public purse.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28045","28045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454284","2016-02-25","Prime Minister","2016-02-23","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent representations he has made to officials working on the Chilcot Inquiry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28041","28041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454285","2016-02-25","Prime Minister","2016-02-23","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will make representations to bodies campaigning on the EU referendum to ensure that members of the Royal Family are not referred to in the debate on that referendum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28051","28051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454286","2016-02-25","Prime Minister","2016-02-23","To ask the Prime Minister, which hon. Members have security clearance for access to 10 Downing Street.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27889","27889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454287","2016-02-25","Prime Minister","2016-02-23","To ask the Prime Minister, how many times his ministerial office has been decorated in the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27891","27891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454288","2016-02-26","Prime Minister","2016-02-23","To ask the Prime Minister, how many meetings he has had with UK Trade and Investment trade envoys since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27900","27900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454289","2016-02-25","Prime Minister","2016-02-23","To ask the Prime Minister, which Government Ministers have had use of Chevening House since May 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27890","27890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454290","2016-02-25","Scotland Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27940","27940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454291","2016-02-25","Scotland Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27961","27961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454292","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27962","27962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454293","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27941","27941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454294","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential of Westbury to become the north-south/east-west rail hub for the central south of England.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27996","27996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454295","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that UK rail operators who may lose their franchise as a result of the recently announced proposals to transfer the responsibility for inner suburban rail services in London from his Department to Transport for London maintain and improve their services while this change takes place.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27986","27986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454296","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effect on passenger safety of reduced staff numbers on London Underground.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28030","28030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454297","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effect on passenger safety of reducing staffing at control rooms on London Underground.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28031","28031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454298","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with London Underground (LU) on the effect on passenger safety of reducing staffing on LU.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28032","28032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454299","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the merits of staffing (a) railway stations and (b) trains.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28033","28033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454300","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that rail companies improve their passenger safety procedures.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28034","28034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454301","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to reduce the amount of litter on Network Rail's land; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27976","27976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454302","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to reduce the amount of litter on Highways England's road network; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27977","27977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454303","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the provision of free Wi-Fi connections on board all (a) Network Rail and (b) Transport for London carriages.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28091","28091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454304","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Transport of 10 December 2015, Official Report, column 1132, on smart ticketing, whether the 80 million funding referred to has been allocated to the South East Flexible Ticketing programme; and what proportion of that funding his Department has so far spent on which elements of that programme.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28078","28078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454305","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 27121, what the implied average annual season ticket fare referred to in that Answer is.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27898","27898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454306","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the premium and subsidy profile of the new TransPennine Express franchise will be in each year of that franchise's operation.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27906","27906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454307","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February 2016 to Question 26170, whether his departmental officials conducting EU negotiations on behalf of the Government on the European Commission's Fourth Railway Package have a consolidated version of Regulation (EC) No 1370/2007 as amended or a similar equivalent.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27854","27854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454308","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will support changing the Air Traffic Management in the Future Airspace Strategy to give residents a higher priority than commercial interests.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27846","27846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454309","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much in Schedule 4 and Schedule 8 compensation payments Network Rail paid to train operating companies in each year from 2009-10 to 2015-16; and what Schedule 4 payments Network Rail received from train operating companies in that period.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27860","27860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454310","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many heavy rail vehicles built before 1999 have not been refurbished to comply with (a) RVAR 10 and (b) PRM TSI regulations; and what proportion of the national heavy rail fleet meets those requirements.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27881","27881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454311","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to HS2 Ltd's Information Paper, G3: Construction Commissioner, published on 16 December 2015, what annual salary he expects to pay to the HS2 Construction Commissioner; to what body the Construction Commissioner will report; what steps he will take to safeguard the Commissioner's independence from his Department and HS2 Ltd; for what reasons the Commissioner will not be able to consider claims for losses of over 10,000; and what the exemption from the role of matters considered by Parliament in approving the project is planned cover.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28079","28079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454312","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the five times increase in the annual upfront fee charges for private hire operator licences by local authorities on small and self-employed operators.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28080","28080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454313","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the local licensing authorities on the introduction of five-year private hire operator licences by local authorities.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28081","28081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454314","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consultations have taken place on privatisation of railway stations currently owned by Network Rail; and which stakeholders have been so consulted.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28067","28067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454315","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans there are for (a) Transport for the North, (b) Transport for Greater Manchester and (c) Transport for London to take over from Network Rail the management or ownership of railway stations.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28068","28068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454316","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which railway stations currently owned by Network Rail are being considered for potential sale or new concessions.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28066","28066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454317","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what work Citigroup is conducting for Network Rail in relation to the ownership of railway stations; what fee has been paid to Citigroup for such work; and when the review into the ownership of railway stations is expected to report.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28064","28064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454318","2016-02-26","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the value of railway stations owned by Network Rail.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28065","28065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454319","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Mayor of London on the effect on black taxi drivers of the operation of Uber in London.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28148","28148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454320","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much of the Regional Air Connectivity Fund has not yet been allocated.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28118","28118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454321","2016-02-25","Wales Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for the completion of projects funded in Wales by EU structural funds in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28117","28117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454322","2016-02-25","Wales Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27943","27943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454323","2016-02-25","Wales Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27964","27964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454324","2016-02-25","Women and Equalities","2016-02-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will take steps to ensure that there is equality of educational achievement between girls and boys in schools.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27848","27848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454325","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that employees who initially opted out of the automatic enrolment into pension provision are informed of the importance of revising of their individual pension status.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27857","27857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454326","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 19 November 2015 to Question 16115, if he will make it his policy to collect centrally data on Flexible Support Funding spent on childcare support.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27973","27973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454327","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he intends to answer the letter to him dated 12 January 2016 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton, with regard to Ms S Lyons.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27845","27845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454328","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) policy and (b) other responsibilities are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27965","27965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454329","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's wellness strategy is.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27944","27944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454331","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have withdrawn more than the 25 per cent tax-free allowance from their pension fund as a lump sum since 2014.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27997","27997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454332","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Schedule 14 and Section 24 of the Pension Act 2014, how many employees have been affected by the introduction of the statutory over-ride which provides for employers who sponsor contracted-out occupational pensions schemes to pass on increases in national insurance contributions to employees.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28010","28010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454333","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications to the National Enterprise Allowance scheme were rejected in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27982","27982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454334","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will provide a breakdown of the main reasons why applications to the National Enterprise Allowance scheme were turned down in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27983","27983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454335","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the effect is on the public purse of not annually uprating the UK state pensions of British pensioners living overseas.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28149","28149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454336","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to provide British pensioners living overseas with the same annual uprating of their state pension as British pensioners who are resident in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28143","28143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454337","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average financial cost is to an individual woman who has seen her state pension age increased by the maximum 18 months.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28107","28107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454338","2016-02-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many calls have been made to the Universal Credit 03456000723 number to date; what the average duration is of such calls; what the average cost is of each call; and how much revenue in total has been generated by these calls.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 28133","28133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455283","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to reform compensation for armed forces veterans affected by mesothelioma.","Biography information for Baroness Blackwood of North Oxford","Nicola Blackwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903767","903767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455853","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of planned changes to pay and allowances on the morale of the armed forces.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903775","903775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455854","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations he has received from war widows who remarried between 1973 and 2005 on reinstatement of their war widow's pension.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903777","903777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455855","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015 on the Royal Navy's global reach.","Biography information for Suella Braverman","Suella Fernandes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903779","903779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455856","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to protect the armed forces from persistent legal claims.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903774","903774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455857","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on reducing the proportion of the defence budget which is spent on legal fees.","Biography information for David Mowat","David Mowat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903778","903778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/455858","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect on national security of the continuous at-sea nuclear deterrent.","Biography information for David Rutley","David Rutley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903776","903776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/456740","2016-03-02","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent assessment she has made of the level of the threat of terrorism in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903789","903789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/456809","2016-03-02","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps the Government is taking to tackle organised crime in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903792","903792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/456810","2016-03-02","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on cross-border trade in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903790","903790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453622","2016-02-24","Attorney General","2016-02-22","To ask the Attorney General, how many full-time equivalent staff his Department provided to assist with (a) Home Office immigration and asylum cases and (b) other Home Office legal cases in reach year since 2009-10; and how much was spent by his Department on such cases in each of those years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27611","27611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453623","2016-02-25","Attorney General","2016-02-22","To ask the Attorney General, how many people have been prosecuted for going abroad to assist Daesh.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27830","27830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453624","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the public sector exit cap proposed in the Enterprise Bill on employees of the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27757","27757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453625","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 16 February 2016 to Question 26010, when his Department plans to establish the reading room for classified documents relating to the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27767","27767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453626","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of a UK withdrawal from the EU on the (a) number of EU students in the UK university student body, (b) ability of UK universities to recruit EU staff into the academic workforce and (c) number of UK students participating in the European exchange programme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27698","27698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453627","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department plans to take to extend the levels of support being given to the aluminium industry to the same level as that given to the steel industry.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27622","27622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453628","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans his Department has to publish a national strategy for English for speakers of other languages for England.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27619","27619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453629","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much Government funding further education colleges in (a) East Lancashire and (b) Burnley received in (i) 2014, (ii) 2015 and (iii) 2016.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27624","27624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453630","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students currently attend further education colleges in (a) East Lancashire and (b) Burnley.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27625","27625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453631","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many disabled students allowance awards were made by the Student Loans Company to students (a) studying at higher education institutions, (b) with a term-time residence and (c) with a vacation time residence in Hampstead and Kilburn constituency in the most recent academic year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27628","27628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453632","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what mechanisms (a) are available and (b) will be available from 2016-17 for applicants for disabled students' allowance (DSA) who wish to appeal against an assessment by an independent needs assessor; how many students have appealed against such a DSA assessment in each year since 2009-10; and how many of those appeals have been found in favour of the appellant in each of those years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27629","27629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453633","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with (i) arms manufacturers, (ii) tobacco manufacturers and (iii) representatives of the Israeli embassy since the period covered in the Cabinet Office's most recent ministerial gifts, hospitality, travel and meetings data release.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27633","27633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453634","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many assessments for disabled students' allowance (DSA) were carried out by an independent needs assessor in each year since 2009-10; what the average such award was in each of those years; and who was contracted to carry out each of those assessments in each of those years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27630","27630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453635","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many officials of his Department are (a) responsible for external trade policy, (b) working on policy related to the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership and (c) worked on policy related to the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27658","27658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453636","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of applicants for disabled students' allowance (DSA) used supporting notes from (a) medical professionals connected to and (b) medical professionals not connected to their higher education institution to back up their application; and what estimate he has made of the proportion of people who claim DSA without the knowledge of their higher education institution.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27598","27598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453637","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in employment earn (a) the national minimum wage rate which will apply from 1 April 2016 and (b) between that rate and one per cent above that rate.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27643","27643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453638","2016-02-24","Cabinet Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with (i) arms manufacturers, (ii) tobacco manufacturers and (iii) representatives of the Israeli embassy since the period covered in his Department's most recent ministerial gifts, hospitality, travel and meetings data release.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27634","27634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453639","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Office for National Statistics on devolving statistics and data collecting powers and obligations when powers are devolved to combined authorities.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27733","27733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453640","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what requirements are in place for (a) the Office for National Statistics (ONS) and (b) other government agencies to collect data on a regional basis; and what discussions he has had with the ONS to collect the provision of regional data.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27736","27736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453641","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 28 November 2014 to Question 215333, what amount was paid to Transport for London in relation to the decision to raise Transport for London rail fares by the retail price index in January 2015.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27763","27763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453642","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which estate agents in London have been penalised for failing to comply with the Money Laundering Regulations 2007 in each year since the introduction of those regulations; and what the level of the fine was in each such case.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27770","27770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453643","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many estate agents in (a) England and Wales and (b) London have been penalised for failing to comply with the Money Laundering Regulations 2007.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27768","27768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453644","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on stakeholders of the proposed changes to the Transactions in Securities rules.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27686","27686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453645","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on stakeholders of the proposed changes to entrepreneurial tax relief.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27687","27687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453646","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what work his Department is undertaking to assist small and medium-sized enterprises in the construction industry to expand and create more jobs.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27688","27688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453647","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what formula was used to calculate the Government's proposed living wage.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27715","27715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453648","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether benefits for people with disabilities will be exempt from the freeze on working-age benefits.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27720","27720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453649","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what (a) meetings, (b) hospitality, (c) gifts and (d) overseas travel officials at Grade 7 or above in HM Revenue and Customs have received or undertaken in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16 to date.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27823","27823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453650","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what revenue was received by the Exchequer from the total amount of food imported by the UK from other member states of the EU in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27726","27726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453651","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce the productivity gap.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27727","27727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453652","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of people who want to work full-time who are in part-time rather than full-time work.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27835","27835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453653","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the revenue the Government received from VAT on domestic energy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27805","27805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453654","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the revenue the Government received from VAT on hotel stays and restaurant meals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27806","27806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453655","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with (i) arms manufacturers, (ii) tobacco manufacturers and (iii) representatives of the Israeli embassy since the period covered in the Cabinet Office's most recent ministerial gifts, hospitality, travel and meetings data release.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27640","27640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453656","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who did not meet the 31 January 2016 deadline for submitting tax returns.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27608","27608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453657","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of what the most appropriate fiscal framework mechanism would be to accompany the devolution of income tax powers of Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27626","27626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453658","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government on the fiscal framework to accompany the devolution of income tax powers to Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27627","27627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453659","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what (a) discussions he has had with and (b) representations he has received from (i) businesses, (ii) members of the public and (iii) other stakeholders on new double taxation treaties since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27657","27657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453660","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the economic impact of fixed odds betting terminals; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27667","27667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453661","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government on the specific deduction method to accompany the devolution of income tax powers to Wales.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27664","27664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453662","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether public sector net debt is forecast to fall in the next financial year.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27604","27604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453663","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax credit claims have been (a) identified as potentially fraudulent and (b) reviewed by Concentrix in each local authority area.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27602","27602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453664","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on levels of self-employment in the construction industry of his proposed changes to tax relief for travel and subsistence.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27586","27586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453665","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to consult on the transposition of the fourth anti-money-laundering directive.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27588","27588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453666","2016-02-24","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to reduce domestic rent prices in London.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27839","27839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453667","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what research his Department has (a) commissioned and (b) carried out on the structural factors in the economy that have contributed to the scale of the productivity gap.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27800","27800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453668","2016-02-25","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the scale of the productivity gap.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27801","27801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453669","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of mandatory electrical safety checks in care homes.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27590","27590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453670","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has undertaken of the electrical safety and adequacy of measures to prevent electrical fires in care homes in England.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27591","27591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453671","2016-03-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received in the last 12 months on low turnouts in certain previous elections for Mayors.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27607","27607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453672","2016-02-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what work his Department is doing in relation to its responsibility for the European Regional Development Fund.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27684","27684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453673","2016-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25978, whether the timetable for making a decision on applying to the EU Solidarity Fund has been extended.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27613","27613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453674","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the effect of the European Regional Development Fund on economic growth.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27659","27659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453675","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential effect of exit from the EU on his Department's work on the European Regional Development Fund.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27660","27660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453676","2016-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 26570, on planning permission, which local authority made each of those article 4 directions; and what modifications his Department made to eight of those directions.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27631","27631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453677","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 27055, what the Government considers to be the date of first damage by floods in Cumbria during December 2015.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27822","27822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453678","2016-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if the Government will bring forward proposals to review the needs-based formula for local government.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27716","27716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453679","2016-02-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish as soon as possible a full analysis of responses to his Department's recent consultation on the deregulation of Sunday trading.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27699","27699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453680","2016-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent representations he has made to Premier League football clubs on the level of ticket prices.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27783","27783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453681","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether he or Ofcom have made an assessment or hold information on the proportion of BT's ducts that were able to have fibre blown through them without further civil works in the superfast broadband rollout.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27735","27735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453682","2016-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential effect of a UK withdrawal from the EU on cultural, sporting and media initiatives within the UK currently supported by the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27701","27701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453683","2016-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in other EU member states on the potential effect of a UK withdrawal from the EU on cultural, sporting and media initiatives currently supported by the EU within the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27702","27702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453684","2016-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to all-weather football pitches at grassroots level.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27690","27690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453685","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26900, if he will request that Ofcom publish an assessment of the extent to which the indicative assessment of BT's ducts in the report, Telecoms infrastructure access - sample survey of duct access, published in March 2009, was borne out in the subsequent rollout by BT of superfast broadband.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27827","27827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453686","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Gaming Machine Regulations 2015 on the volume of bets being staked at just under 50; and what steps his Department is taking to assess the levels of staff interaction with fixed odds betting terminal players in bookmakers.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27807","27807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453687","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of homes receiving fibre-optic broadband services in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) the UK in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27652","27652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453688","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of fibre-optic broadband coverage across the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27653","27653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453689","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent representations his Department has received from internet service providers on the rollout of fibre-optic broadband; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27655","27655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453690","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of spending on infrastructure to support fibre-optic broadband installation in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27654","27654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453691","2016-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what duties apply to betting companies to ensure that vulnerable customers using their services gamble responsibly.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27665","27665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453692","2016-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of gambling on vulnerable people; and what provisions are in place to assist people who have gambling problems.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27666","27666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453693","2016-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he plans to take to help prevent disproportionate increases in the price of football tickets.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27674","27674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453694","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representative bodies (a) his Department and (b) the Gambling Commission has met to discuss the next review of gaming machines stakes and prizes.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27596","27596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453695","2016-02-25","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when his Department plans to launch the next triennial review of gaming machine stake and prize limits.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27597","27597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453696","2016-02-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make representations to the BBC on increasing the provision of voice-overs for BBC programmes.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27600","27600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453697","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions his Department has had on the F-35's digital logistics system and its potential vulnerability to cyber attacks.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27678","27678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453698","2016-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which government departments and agencies plan to participate in Exercise Joint Venture later this year.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27661","27661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453699","2016-02-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with (i) arms manufacturers, (ii) tobacco manufacturers and (iii) representatives of the Israeli embassy since the period covered in the Cabinet Office's most recent ministerial gifts, hospitality, travel and meetings data release.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27635","27635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453700","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department made of the legality of US airstrikes in Libya before authorising use of RAF Lakenheath for airstrikes in Libya on 19 February 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27840","27840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453701","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what procedure was followed before the authorisation of the use of RAF Lakenheath for airstrikes in Libya on 19 February 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27841","27841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453702","2016-02-25","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of his Department's invoices for goods and services supplied by (a) private companies and (b) small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) are completed on time; and what proportion of the (i) number and (ii) value of contracts between his Department and private companies are held by SMEs.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27777","27777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453703","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to prepare for RansomWare attacks on NHS facilities.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27838","27838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453704","2016-02-25","Department for Education","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to reply to the letter of 15 February 2016 from the Rt hon. Member for Birkenhead regarding free school meals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27749","27749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453705","2016-02-25","Department for Education","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has plans to adjust the eligibility criteria for claiming free childcare so that it can be claimed from the child's third birthday rather than from the next term date after the child turns three.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27656","27656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453706","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on teachers' workloads of the new system for assessment of pupils' achievement in reading, writing and mathematics at Key Stage 1 and Key Stage 2.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27663","27663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453707","2016-02-25","Department for Education","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to publish examination performance data for academy chains; and if she will make an assessment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27680","27680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453708","2016-02-25","Department for Education","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the threshold for the number of coasting academies in an academy chain above which her Department plans to take action.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27681","27681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453709","2016-02-25","Department for Education","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether Ofsted plans to inspect academy chains as well as individual academies; and if she will make an assessment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27682","27682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453710","2016-02-25","Department for Education","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support best practice from successful academy chains being passed on to other academy chains.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27683","27683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453711","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason her Department did not give one year's notice of the new system for assessment of pupils' achievement in reading, writing and mathematics at Key Stage 1 and Key Stage 2.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27668","27668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453712","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the findings in the Chief Schools Adjudicator for England's 2015 Annual Report, published in December 2015, what assessment she has made of the effect of the level of the religious oversubscription criteria used by some schools on parents applying to such schools.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27603","27603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453713","2016-02-24","Department for Education","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is her Department's policy to publish details of repayments to the public purse made by cancelled or withdrawn free schools.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27594","27594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453714","2016-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, who was involved in designing the Sellafield Workforce Reform initiative.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27662","27662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453715","2016-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what meetings (a) she and (b) Ministers of her Department have had with (i) arms manufacturers, (ii) tobacco manufacturers and (iii) representatives of the Israeli embassy since the period covered in the Cabinet Office's most recent ministerial gifts, hospitality, travel and meetings data release.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27636","27636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453716","2016-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what information she plans to publish on the outcome of her Department's efforts to pursue civil penalties issued to aircraft operators for failure to surrender sufficient allowances under the EU Emissions Trading Scheme; what the expected timescale is for those proceedings; and whether any of the operators subject to those proceedings opened accounts for trading periods covering the period 2013 to 2015.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27721","27721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453717","2016-02-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2016 to Question 24408, if she will discuss with the Sustainable Energy Association and other relevant bodies how to achieve the potential for buildings to contribute to the Government's goals on reducing carbon and tackling fuel poverty.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27692","27692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453718","2016-02-25","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to tackle fuel poverty in the UK.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27764","27764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453719","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the Government is doing to encourage supermarkets to act responsibly when sourcing and purchasing fish products.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27737","27737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453720","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to encourage young people to take up a career in the fishing industry.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27738","27738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453721","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to promote seafood as a healthy British food.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27739","27739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453722","2016-02-25","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to apply for assistance from the EU Solidarity Fund to help flood-affected areas.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27758","27758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453723","2016-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings (a) she and (b) Ministers of her Department have had with (i) arms manufacturers, (ii) tobacco manufacturers and (iii) representatives of the Israeli embassy since the period covered in the Cabinet Office's most recent ministerial gifts, hospitality, travel and meetings data release.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27637","27637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453724","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential financial effect of leaving the EU on agriculture in Britain and Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27595","27595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453725","2016-02-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she plans to bring forward proposals to ban the use of wild animals in circuses.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27601","27601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453726","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of (a) the geographical extent of ash dieback disease and (b) its effect upon woodland and the number of ash trees in the UK.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27802","27802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453727","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the ecological effect of ash dieback disease in rural areas.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27803","27803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453728","2016-02-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made in identifying ash trees with resistance to ash dieback disease; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27804","27804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453730","2016-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with (i) arms manufacturers, (ii) tobacco manufacturers and (iii) representatives of the Israeli embassy since the period covered in the Cabinet Office's most recent ministerial gifts, hospitality, travel and meetings data release.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27638","27638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453731","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of his Department's budget was spent on Christmas parties hosted by British embassies and consulates in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15; and what estimate he has made of such planned spending in 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27651","27651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453732","2016-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much (a) the Government and (b) each government department spent on (i) arrangements and (ii) hospitality for the Chinese state visit in October 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27617","27617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453733","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of a UK withdrawal from the EU on relations between the UK and Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27750","27750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453734","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether Russian airstrikes in Syria have breached international humanitarian law.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27747","27747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453735","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had discussions with the Israeli government on the displacement of Bedouin people from townships in the Negev.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27755","27755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453736","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Government's response to the Foreign Affairs Committee's First Special Report of Session 2015-16, published on 11 February 2016, HC816, when he expects the internal review of his Department to be completed; what the key priorities of his Department are on which that review will be focussed; and if he will publish the conclusions of that review.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27748","27748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453737","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 5 January 2015 to Question 219046, what response his Department has received from Democratic People's Republic of Korea authorities; and whether progress has been made on improving North Korean women's rights in China.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27824","27824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453738","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether UK-owned tour companies that operate in North Korea contribute financially to that country's nuclear and missile programmes or to elements of the Democratic People's Republic of Korea government responsible for human rights violations.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27825","27825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453739","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which elements of the Democratic People's Republic of Korea  government fund or participate in that country's nuclear and missile programmes.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27826","27826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453740","2016-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure there are sufficient safeguards to respect individual privacy in place in respect of intelligence gathered by GCHQ.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27837","27837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453741","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK staff worked at the Permanent Representation to NATO in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14, (c) 2014-15 and (d) the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27746","27746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453742","2016-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the installation by China of missile launchers on Woody Island in the South China Sea; what representations he has made to China on that matter; and if he will discuss with his Japanese counterpart what steps the UK and Japan can take to oppose the militarisation of the South China Sea.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27697","27697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453743","2016-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much UK embassies spent on official hospitality in 2014-15; and what estimate he has made of the level of such spending in 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27689","27689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453744","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment the Government has made of the extent to which NHS providers have met NICE quality standard on rheumatoid arthritis since 2013.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27718","27718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453745","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of his Department's invoices for goods and services supplied by (a) private companies and (b) small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) are completed on time; and what proportion of the (i) number and (ii) value of contracts between his Department and private companies are held by SMEs.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27778","27778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453746","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment the Government has made of trends and development in the quality of care given by NHS trusts to people with rheumatoid arthritis in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27717","27717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453747","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of reductions in the public health grant for local authorities on local smoking cessation services in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27774","27774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453748","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to address inequalities in cancer incidence across England resulting from smoking.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27773","27773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453749","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that the Government meets its commitment that all patients throughout England with musculoskeletal conditions have the support they need to live healthily and independently, with better control over the care they receive, notwithstanding reductions in public health budgets.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27719","27719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453750","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on whether the resource impact assessment that NICE plans to publish alongside its guidance following its review of TA 85[ID456] of immunosuppressant agents for kidney transplant will include the effect on (a) the number of successful kidney transplants, (b) kidney dialysis capacity, (c) the UK national transplant waiting list and (d) the NHS Organ Donor Register.","Biography information for Mark Durkan","Mark Durkan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27724","27724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453751","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the report of the independent cancer taskforce, Achieving world class cancer outcomes: A strategy for England 2015-2020, published in July 2015, what progress has been made in developing a new tobacco control strategy.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27740","27740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453752","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the report of the independent cancer taskforce, Achieving world class cancer outcomes: A strategy for England 2015-2020, published in July 2015, what progress NHS England has made in putting a mandate in place to ensure that GPs have direct access to key investigative tests for suspected cancers.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27741","27741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453753","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what record his Department maintains on morale amongst A&E staff.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27754","27754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453754","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Oral Statement of 11 February 2016, Official Report, column 1763, on junior doctors' contracts, which senior NHS leaders asked him to proceed with the introduction of a new contract for junior doctors.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27834","27834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453755","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the implications for her policies on harm caused by alcohol are of the finding in the Balance report, The second hand harm of alcohol in the North East, published on 17 February 2016, on the proportion of people in the North East who have suffered harm at least once due to the drinking of others in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27794","27794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453756","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of staff retention in the NHS of his decision to impose a new contract on junior doctors.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27816","27816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453757","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if NHS England will issue a consultation on a new Prioritisation Framework for making decisions on investment in specialised services and highly specialised services.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27820","27820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453758","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans NHS England has to involve NICE in the specialised commissioning policy development process.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27782","27782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453759","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if NHS England will publish a list of the commissioning policies scheduled to be developed in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27791","27791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453760","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library copies of the local blueprint submissions for the NHS Sustainability and Transformation Plan.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27676","27676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453761","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many members of staff aged under 18 have been employed by NHS 111 in each of the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27675","27675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453762","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if NHS England will publish the (a) agendas and (b) minutes of all future meetings of the (i) Clinical Advisory Group and (ii) Specialised Commissioning Committee within a reasonable period after each such meeting takes place.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27792","27792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453763","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time for an outpatient paediatric ophthalmology appointment was in 2014-15.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27793","27793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453764","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the average change in the level of pay for those junior doctors who will be offered pay protection as part of the transition to a new contract.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27828","27828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453765","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what risk assessment was carried out on his policy to impose a new contract on junior doctors.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27829","27829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453766","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with (i) arms manufacturers, (ii) tobacco manufacturers and (iii) representatives of the Israeli embassy since the period covered in the Cabinet Office's most recent ministerial gifts, hospitality, travel and meetings data release.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27639","27639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453767","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the 1.25 billion funding for children and young people's mental health services announced in the 2015 Budget, published in March 2015, how much of that funding (a) has been transferred to clinical commissioning groups (CCGs) to date, (b) have the CCGs spent to date and (c) he estimates CCGs will have spent by the end of the 2015-16 financial year; and if he will ensure that any shortfall is rolled over into the 2016-17 budget.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27614","27614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453768","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of GPs working in the NHS were over 50 in (a) 2012 and (b) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27609","27609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453769","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce GP appointment waiting times.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27618","27618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453770","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the costs to the NHS of the treatment of people with addiction to fixed odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27615","27615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453771","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many outpatient paediatric ophthalmology appointments were (a) cancelled and (b) missed because the patient did not attend in 2014-15.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27616","27616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453772","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of NHS 111 staff are clinically trained.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27669","27669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453773","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of clinical staff have suffered from work-related stress in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27670","27670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453774","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of whether the nine pilot schemes for a proposed national medical examiner system improved the accuracy of death certification.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27671","27671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453775","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the commissioning of a national molecular diagnosis service.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27673","27673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453776","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the cost-effectiveness of the proposed national medical examiner system on the basis of the nine pilot schemes.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27672","27672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453777","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's policy is on junior doctors who whistleblow about safety concerns in the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27606","27606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453778","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average unit cost of a first outpatient paediatric ophthalmology appointment was in 2014-15.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27593","27593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453779","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to begin assessing (a) drugs for rare cancer and (b) cancer drugs under the proposed new Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27605","27605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453780","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of gambling addiction in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27589","27589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453781","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths were recorded for which an eating disorder was mentioned on the death certificate in (a) the UK and (b) England in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27795","27795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453782","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to bring forward proposals to change the closest living relative definition in the Mental Health Act 1983 to include unmarried fathers once their children are aged 18.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27796","27796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453783","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the NHS England plans to publish its consultation on the future of mental health support for veterans of the armed forces, referred to in the NHS England Mental Health Taskforce.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27797","27797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453784","2016-02-25","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many first admission episodes there were with a primary diagnosis of an eating disorder in (a) England and (b) the UK in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) each month in 2015-16 for which figures are available.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27798","27798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453785","2016-02-25","Cabinet Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many deaths there were in (a) the UK and (b) England for which an eating disorder was the underlying cause of death for deaths registered in each year between 2010 and the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27799","27799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453786","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the current average waiting time is for an application for leave to remain.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27592","27592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453787","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidelines her Department produces on the inclusion of non-conviction information or soft information on DBS forms.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27587","27587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453788","2016-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been convicted of offences under sections 58 and 59 of the Offences Against the Person Act 1861 related to abortions in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27599","27599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453789","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police call-outs to betting shops there were due to violence related to fixed odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27649","27649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453790","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the effect of fixed odds betting terminals on levels of crime; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27650","27650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453791","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that applications for passports are processed without delays over the peak summer period.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27642","27642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453792","2016-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many consent orders have been signed by courts for the settlement of judicial review cases for asylum and immigration applications in each year since 2009-10; how many such cases were decided in favour of the appellant upon reconsideration; how many found in contempt of court for the breaching such consent orders; and on how many occasions the courts has refuse to sign a consent order.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27632","27632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453793","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people with dependants who have been granted leave to remain in the UK had a no recourse to public funds condition attached to their leave in (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13, (c) 2013-14 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27729","27729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453794","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people under the age of 18 were dependants of adults who had been granted leave to remain in the UK and had also had a no recourse to public funds condition attached to their leave in the financial years (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13, (c) 2013-14 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27730","27730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453795","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests were made to her Department for a change of conditions of leave lifting the condition of no recourse to public funds in financial years (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13, (c) 2013-14 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27731","27731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453796","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests were made to her Department for a change of conditions of leave were approved in lifting the no recourse to public funds condition to the applicants conditions of leave in financial years (a) 2011-12, (b) 2012-13, (c) 2013-14 and (d) 2014-15.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27732","27732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453797","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of asylum seekers who have been found to have fraudulently claimed to be under the age of 18 in each of the last years.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27788","27788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453798","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers claiming to be under the age of 18 have been charged with a criminal offence in the last year; and what proportion of such asylum seekers were subsequently found to have fraudulently claimed to be under the age of 18.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27789","27789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453799","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average length of time was for an application for British citizenship from submission of initial application to decision in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Anne McLaughlin","Anne McLaughlin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27815","27815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453800","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many custody nurses were employed by the Metropolitan Police (a) in total and (b) in each London borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27769","27769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453801","2016-02-25","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of her Department's invoices for goods and services supplied by (a) private companies and (b) small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) are completed on time; and what proportion of the (i) number and (ii) value of contracts between her Department and private companies are held by SMEs.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27779","27779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453802","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to reduce the number of fires caused by an electrical source of ignition in domestic dwellings.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27722","27722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453803","2016-02-24","Home Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has for the future of its Fire Kills campaign.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27723","27723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453804","2016-02-24","House of Commons Commission","2016-02-22","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what the Commission's policy is on the allocation of service charges paid by card to (a) permanent and (b) contracted canteen and hospitality staff working on the parliamentary estate.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27612","27612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453805","2016-02-24","Department for International Development","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the Government plans to do to support reforms to research and development of pharmaceuticals at the World Health Organisaiton meeting in March 2016.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27784","27784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453806","2016-02-24","Department for International Development","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, who the Government plans to send as its representative to the discussions on research and development of pharmaceuticals at the World Health Organisation meeting in March 2016.","Biography information for Paul Maynard","Paul Maynard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27785","27785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453807","2016-02-24","Department for International Development","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance  her Department plans to provide to help tackle hunger in Malawi.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27786","27786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453808","2016-02-25","Department for International Development","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's spending was allocated to (a) Nigerian state organisations, (b) non-governmental organisations and (c) the private sector in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27734","27734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453809","2016-02-24","Department for International Development","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the availability of food to people in Malawi.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27787","27787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453810","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many key lock incidents there have been in each month since May 2010; how many such incidents related to doors of gates left unlocked; and in which establishments those incidents took place.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27832","27832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453811","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents at height in respect of each method of access there have been in each prison in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27833","27833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453812","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2016 to Question 21315, whether the changes to the Incident Report System of September 2015 made any improvements to the recording of knife finds.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27813","27813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453813","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken in response to the findings set out in the 2014-15 Annual Report of the Independent Monitoring Board at HM Prison Belmarsh on the prison's online and telephone booking system.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27808","27808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453814","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 26908, what steps he is taking to improve the recording of knife finds in prisons to ensure that the data is easy to use and analyse.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27812","27812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453815","2016-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what research his Department has (a) commissioned and (b) conducted on the potential effect of a UK withdrawal from the EU on (a) relationships between his Department and its counterparts in other EU member states and (b) the effectiveness of pan-European justice mechanisms; and what assessment his Department has made of the results of that research.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27728","27728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453816","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason not all the monthly announcements of Freedom of Information releases for 2015 have been published on his Department's website.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27756","27756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453817","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many properties that have been bought and sold in (a) London and (b) each London borough in the last 10 years record no sale price on the Land Registry.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27771","27771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453818","2016-02-25","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many properties in (a) England and Wales, (b) London and (c) each London Borough are registered with the Land Registry (i) in total and (ii) to off-shore companies.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27772","27772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453819","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times (a) family and (b) legal visits to prisoners in HM Prison Belmarsh have been cancelled in each of the last 12 months; and for what reason each such visit was cancelled.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27766","27766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453820","2016-02-25","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to prevent family and legal visits being cancelled in prisons in England and Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27765","27765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453821","2016-02-24","Leader of the House","2016-02-22","To ask the Leader of the House, what discussions he has had with the House of Commons Commission on the potential effect on staffing and other costs and expenditure on repair and maintenance contracts of uncertainty about the dates of 2016 parliamentary recesses.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27623","27623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453822","2016-02-25","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the implications for border security arrangements of recent gangland-related murders in the Irish Republic.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27641","27641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453823","2016-02-25","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of a UK withdrawal from the EU on security in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27751","27751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453824","2016-02-25","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with Irish Ministers on the potential effect of a UK withdrawal from the EU on security in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27752","27752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453825","2016-02-25","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with Irish Ministers on the potential effect of a UK withdrawal from the EU on relations with Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27753","27753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453826","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government plans to introduce legislative proposals related to the agreement reached on the UK's relationship with the EU at the European Council on 19 February 2016.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27644","27644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453827","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the planned availability of toilet facilities is (a) on Crossrail trains and (b) at Crossrail train stations.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27646","27646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453828","2016-02-24","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the distinctions between Volkswagen's practices (a) on the use of defeat devices and (b) in mitigating customer inconvenience in the US and the UK; and whether his Department has made an assessment of the reasons for those distinctions.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27610","27610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453829","2016-02-24","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on measures to improve air quality; and what discussions he has had with Highways England on the level of priority it accords to issues of air quality.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27620","27620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453830","2016-02-24","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which Government policies on ensuring the (a) security of UK ports and (b) identification and checking of containers for contraband, trafficked persons or other illegal activity are the responsibility of his Department; and which such policies which are the responsibility of another department his Department has a secondary role in.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27817","27817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453831","2016-02-24","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of drivers potentially affected by the extension of the radius from 50km to 100km from base within which vehicles are exempt from regulations limiting drivers' hours.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27819","27819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453832","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the value of Network Rail's Regulated Asset Base in respect of the (a) Anglia, (b) LNE and East Midlands, (c) LNW, (d) Scotland, (e) Southeast, (f) Wales, (g) Wessex and (h) Western Network Rail routes in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27760","27760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453833","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to data table BUS0842, published in Department for Transport Statistics, what guidance his Department gives to travel concession authorities for reporting purposes on the definition of commercial youth concessions.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27761","27761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453834","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 26134, what the reason is for the difference between the data series given in that Answer in relation to suicides and suicide attempts on the Strategic Road Network and the data given in the Answer of 15 December 2015 to Question 19015 asked by the hon. Member for Huddersfield; and if he will update the figures given in the Answer of 15 December 2015 to include the number of suicides and suicide attempts on the Strategic Road Network in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27762","27762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453835","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what income, by category of payment, Network Rail received from each of its directly managed stations in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27759","27759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453836","2016-02-24","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of people applying for a Blue Badge affected by (a) Alzheimer's disease, (b) myalgic encephalomyelitis and (c) autism were successful in the latest period in which figures are available.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27700","27700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453837","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the Government will introduce incentives for the adoption of new technologies designed to manage noise from aircraft on the ground.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27725","27725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453838","2016-02-25","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of his Department's invoices for goods and services supplied by (a) private companies and (b) small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) are completed on time; and what proportion of the (i) number and (ii) value of contracts between his Department and private companies are held by SMEs.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27780","27780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453839","2016-02-24","Department for Transport","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will widen the Blue Badge criteria to allow for cognitive as well as physical disabilities.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27712","27712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453840","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to increase representation of BME students in leading universities.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27693","27693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453841","2016-02-24","Cabinet Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of Senior Civil Service roles are occupied by people from BME backgrounds.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27694","27694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453842","2016-02-24","Cabinet Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of the Civil Service workforce is from BME backgrounds.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27695","27695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453843","2016-02-24","Cabinet Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of applicants to the Civil Service Fast Stream are (a) from BME backgrounds and (b) successful and from BME backgrounds.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27696","27696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453844","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps the Government is taking to close the higher education attainment gap between BME students and other students.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27836","27836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453845","2016-02-25","Women and Equalities","2016-02-22","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will meet Girlguiding to discuss the findings of its 2015 Girls' Attitudes survey.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27831","27831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453846","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of providing a fiduciary duty for the governance committees of pension funds to their members.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27818","27818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453847","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on the introduction of a learning disabilities commissioner with a statutory duty to promote and protect the rights of all people with learning disabilities and their families as recommended by the report of the Transforming Care and Commissioning Steering Group, Winterbourne View - Time for Change, published in November 2014.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27814","27814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453848","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in how many current Child Support Agency arrears cases there is (a) a current or ongoing liability for a child and (b) no such ongoing liability.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27743","27743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453849","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in how many current Child Support Agency arrears cases with a current or ongoing liability for a child repayments are currently being made towards the arrears.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27744","27744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453850","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in how many arrears-only Child Support Agency cases repayments are currently being made towards the arrears.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27745","27745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453851","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 26069, whether trades unions which are not formally recognised by an employer will be entitled to request and receive the Chair's Statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27809","27809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453852","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the provisions of the Welfare Reform and Work Bill on social mobility.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27677","27677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453853","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 26069, when the Government and the Financial Conduct Authority plan to publish the evidence received on transaction costs for pension trusts; and what the timetable is for determining the next steps referred to.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27810","27810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453854","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 26069, for what reason the Chair's Statement must be requested by beneficiaries rather than provided automatically.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27811","27811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453855","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to review the governance arrangements of pension funds.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27790","27790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453856","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people living with the long-term effects of cancer can access appropriate financial support through the welfare system for as long as they need it.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27703","27703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453857","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of (a) disability living allowance and (b) personal independence payments are (i) undergoing treatment for and (ii) recovering from cancer.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27704","27704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453858","2016-02-24","Department of Health","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the financial implications of caring for people with cancer and their families.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27705","27705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453859","2016-02-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2016 to Question 21380, what recent information he has received from the Danish authorities in relation to the death of Stephen O'Malley; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27742","27742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453860","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of employment and support allowance are (a) undergoing treatment for and (b) recovering from cancer.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27710","27710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453861","2016-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people appealing their ineligibility for the enhanced rate of mobility under personal independent payment have been successful in their appeals.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27711","27711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453862","2016-02-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people recovering from cancer have appealed (a) an employment and support allowance award and (b) a disability living allowance or personal independence payment award decision in the last five years; and how many such appeals were successful.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27709","27709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453863","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people with cancer currently in the work-related activity group of employment and support allowance were previously in the support group.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27708","27708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453864","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) junior doctors, (b) consultants, (c) nurses and (d) healthcare assistants have been employed to undertake work capability assessments in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27691","27691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453865","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people currently in the work-related activity group of employment and support allowance for a condition other than neoplasms who have previously had a cancer diagnosis.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27706","27706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453866","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with cancer have been placed in the work-related activity group in (a) each of the last five years and (b) total since the introduction of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27707","27707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453867","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disabled people have had their Mobility Scheme vehicle taken away as a result of personal independence payment replacing disability living allowance.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27713","27713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453868","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will carry out an impact assessment of the effect that the replacement of disability living allowance by personal independence payment has had on the mobility of disabled people.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27714","27714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453869","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what amount of direct pay arrears has accrued on the 2012 Child Maintenance Scheme; and to how many case groups those arrears relate.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27775","27775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453870","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what amount of (a) 1993 and (b) 2003 Child Support Agency scheme arrears are currently being handled by the Child Maintenance Service; and to how many case groups those arrears relate.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27776","27776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453871","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of his Department's invoices for goods and services supplied by (a) private companies and (b) small and medium-sized enterprises (SMEs) are completed on time; and what proportion of the (i) number and (ii) value of contracts between his Department and private companies are held by SMEs.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27781","27781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453872","2016-02-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department provides to its staff on proactively making callers claiming universal credit or seeking advice by telephone related to that benefit aware that they can be rung back free of charge.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27621","27621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453873","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with epilepsy have been assessed as being fit to work by their work capability assessments in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27647","27647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453874","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims have been made for a Short Term Benefit Advance in the last six months for which data is available; and what the outcomes of those claims were.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27645","27645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453875","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with epilepsy are claiming employment and support allowance and personal independence payments.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27648","27648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453876","2016-02-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit sanctions were issued in error and subsequently cancelled in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27679","27679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453877","2016-03-01","HM Treasury","2016-02-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Government has to provide funding to the Welsh Government until the end of the Parliament for payments under the Independent Living Fund.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27685","27685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454624","2016-02-25","Attorney General","2016-02-22","To ask the Attorney General, what steps the Government is taking to increase public understanding of the law.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903724","903724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453036","2016-02-23","Attorney General","2016-02-19","To ask the Attorney General, what steps the CPS is taking to ensure a higher rate of prosecution for knife crimes.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27527","27527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453037","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what grants and schemes his Department offers to small and medium-sized businesses to encourage innovation.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27516","27516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453038","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department has conducted an impact assessment on the closure of the Business Growth Service.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27511","27511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453039","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the rate of pay is for cleaners in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27548","27548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453040","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress his Department has made on the establishment of 12 hydrogen refuelling stations announced on 27 March 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27568","27568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453041","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received on faulty tumble dryers causing fires; and when his Department was first made aware of safety concerns related to such tumble dryers.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27576","27576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453042","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which British Overseas Territories will be included within the proposed Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27493","27493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453043","2016-02-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which British Overseas Territories will be included within the Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27494","27494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453044","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 3 February 2016 to Question 25610, on minimum wage, what the average call time was to the Pay and Work Rights and ACAS helplines;  how many calls reached an ACAS operative; what definition of call was used in the data provided; and what translation facilities are available on the ACAS helpline.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27462","27462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453045","2016-02-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-19","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many businesses have signed agreements with the Business Growth Service in (a) the UK and (b) Kirklees.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27510","27510"
