"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056762","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many officials from his Department have been seconded from their primary role to make preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218164","218164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056763","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many officials from his Department have been seconded from their primary role to make preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218165","218165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056764","2019-02-11","Northern Ireland Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many officials from her Department have been seconded from their primary role to make preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218166","218166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056765","2019-02-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the press release entitled, Dentists welcome official investigation into fines hitting vulnerable NHS patients, published on 30 January 2019 by the British Dental Association; what steps his Department is taking to ensure that fear of receiving a fine for ticking the wrong box when claiming for free dental care does not discourage people from low income families from attending the dentist.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218312","218312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056766","2019-02-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if his Department will review the list of exemptions for hunting with dogs in the Hunting Act 2004 with specific reference to deer hunting.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218367","218367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056767","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment he has made of the potential merits of rolling out the technology used for the EU Settled Status Scheme to other Home Office applications.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218368","218368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056768","2019-02-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the announcement entitled Dentists welcome official investigation into fines hitting vulnerable NHS patients, published by the British Dental Association on 30 January 2019, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that patients ticking the wrong box for free dental care does not negatively affect vulnerable patients.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218313","218313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056770","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to publish its evaluation of the right to request flexible working.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218370","218370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056771","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to publish its evaluation of shared parental leave.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218371","218371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056772","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total sum recovered via the Compensation Recovery Unit was by way of NHS recoupment under (a) the Road Traffic (NHS Charges) Act 1999, (b) the Health and Personal Social Services Act (Northern Ireland) 2001, (c) the Health and Social Care (Community Health and Standards) Act 2003 and (d) the Recovery of Health Services NHS Charges (Northern Ireland) Order 2006 in the (i) 2016-17 and (ii) 2017-18.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218372","218372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056773","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of an increase to the small claims limit on the ability of police officers injured in a road traffic accident while travelling on a motorbike in the course of their employment to access free legal representation.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218373","218373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056774","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of an increase to the small claims limit on the ability of police officers injured in a road traffic accident while mounted on a horse in the course of their employment to access free legal representation.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218374","218374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056775","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of an increase to the small claims limit on the ability of police officers injured in a road traffic accident while travelling on a bicycle in the course of their employment to access free legal representation.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218375","218375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056776","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of an increase to the small claims limit on the ability of paramedics injured in a road traffic accident while travelling on a bicycle in the course of their employment to access free legal representation.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218376","218376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056777","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of an increase to the small claims limit on the ability of paramedics injured in a road traffic accident while travelling on a motorbike in the course of their employment to access free legal representation.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218377","218377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056778","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of an increase to the small claims limit on the ability of police officers injured in a road traffic accident while travelling on foot in the course of their employment to access free legal representation.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218378","218378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056780","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of an increase to the small claims limit on the ability of couriers injured in a road traffic accident while travelling on a bicycle in the course of their employment to access free legal representation.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218379","218379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056781","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of an increase to the small claims limit on the ability of police officers injured in a road traffic accident while travelling in a car in the course of their employment to access free legal representation.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218380","218380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056782","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of an increase to the small claims limit on the ability of paramedics injured in a road traffic accident while travelling in an ambulance in the course of their employment to access free legal representation.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218381","218381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056783","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of an increase to the small claims limit on the ability of postal worker injured in a road traffic accident while travelling in a postal van in the course of their employment to access free legal representation.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218382","218382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056784","2019-02-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce waiting times for children who have suffered brain injuries.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218315","218315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056785","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding his Department has provided to Fife Migrants Forum.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218332","218332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056786","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what future funding his Department plans to provide to Fife Migrants Forum.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218333","218333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056787","2019-02-11","Department for International Trade","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Government plans to rollover the EU Free Trade Agreement with Canada in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218288","218288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056788","2019-02-11","Department for International Trade","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to ensure that new free trade agreements after the UK leaves the EU do not (a) lower standards in and (b) privatise NHS services.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218289","218289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056789","2019-02-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussion he has had with his Saudi and Emirate counterparts on allowing journalists access to the north of Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218346","218346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056790","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of firefighters are (a) female, (b) from a black, minority or ethnic background and (c) female and from a black, minority or ethnic background in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218290","218290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056791","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what replacement funding will be available for the National Ophthalmology Database audit when its current funding from the Health Quality Improvement Partnership ceases in August 2019.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218291","218291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056792","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2019 to Question 211305 on Pubs Code, if he will conduct a public consultation on the review of the Pubs Code.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218383","218383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056793","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will announce a review of the business rates system for pubs.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218384","218384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056794","2019-02-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to his Oral Statement of 31 October 2016 Nissan: Sunderland, whether the award of £61 million to Nissan in June 2018 detailed in his letter to the BEIS Select Committee of 4 February 2019 was scrutinised by the Industrial Development Advisory Board and reported to Parliament.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218327","218327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056795","2019-02-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with representatives of the telecommunications industry on the introduction of roaming charges after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218292","218292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056796","2019-02-12","Treasury","2019-02-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, who authorised the Commissioners to approve the Asset Protection Agency’s agreement with RBS on behalf of Her Majesty’s Government.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218385","218385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056797","2019-02-12","Treasury","2019-02-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the legal agreement dated 26 November 2009 between the Royal Bank of Scotland and the Asset Protection Agency.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218386","218386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056798","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what representations his Department has received from the Greater Manchester combined authority on financial assistance under the Bellwin scheme from July 2018 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218222","218222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056800","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has provided funds through the Bellwin scheme to the Greater Manchester combined authority from July 2018 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218223","218223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056801","2019-02-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will commission a review of the Pubs Code.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218388","218388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056802","2019-02-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will review trends in the level of pub closures in (a) the UK, (b) Scotland and (c) Midlothian.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218389","218389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056803","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will list all discretionary payments made by his Department through the Bellwin scheme of emergency financial assistance to local authorities from May 2015 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218224","218224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056804","2019-02-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to implement a pubs strategy to tackle the closure of pubs.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218390","218390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056805","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what (a) financial assistance and (b) non-financial assistance his Department has provided to the Greater Manchester combined authority in response to the Moors Fire from July 2018 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218225","218225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056806","2019-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January 2019 to Question 204628 on Universal Credit, when he plans to respond to the hon Member for High Peak.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218391","218391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056807","2019-02-12","Home Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department's guidance entitled European Temporary Leave to Remain in the UK, published on 28 January 2019, whether his Department plans to publish guidance for employers and applicants on European Temporary Leave to Remain.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218303","218303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056808","2019-02-12","Home Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department's guidance entitled European Temporary Leave to Remain in the UK, published on 28 January 2019, whether dependant family members of EEA nationals obtaining three months leave to remain will each be required to make a separate application for leave to remain.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218304","218304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056809","2019-02-12","Home Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department's guidance entitled European Temporary Leave to Remain in the UK, published on 28 January 2019, what fee his Department plans to charge for an application for European Temporary Right to Remain.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218305","218305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056810","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of bringing forward (a) the planned expansion of legacy benefit run-ons and (b) the extension of the advance payment repayment period to 16 months for claimants moving onto universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218203","218203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056811","2019-02-12","Home Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department's guidance entitled European Temporary Leave to Remain in the UK, published on 28 January 2019, whether a (a) skills surcharge and (b) health surcharge will apply to people applying for European Temporary Leave to Remain.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218306","218306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056812","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of moving the start date of a universal credit claim to the point when a claimant sets up as universal credit account for assessment purposes.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218204","218204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056813","2019-02-12","Home Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department's guidance entitled European Temporary Leave to Remain in the UK, published on 28 January 2019, whether people with European Temporary Leave to Remain will be able to apply  from within the UK for different categories of visa when their 3-year leave expires; which visa categories people will be eligible to apply for after their European Temporary Leave to Remain expires; and whether time spent in the UK with European Temporary Leave to Remain will count towards the residency requirement for people who go on to apply for Indefinite Leave to Remain.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218307","218307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056814","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing an affordability test into the calculation of deductions taken from universal credit payments.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218205","218205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056815","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit claims had a deduction applied in the most recent month for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218206","218206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056816","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Manchester Evening News article, Greater Manchester is still owed £1 million by the government for battling last summer's moorland blazes, published on 6 February 2018, when his Department plans to issue its response to the Greater Manchester Combined Authority’s application for funding under the Bellwin Scheme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218226","218226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056817","2019-02-12","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Manchester Evening News article, Greater Manchester is still owed £1 million by the government for battling last summer's moorland blazes, published on 6 February 2018, whether his Department has repaid any of the £70,000 given to it by the Greater Manchester combined authority.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218227","218227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056819","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit claims that had a deduction applied had (a) up to 20 per cent, (b) between 21 and 30 per cent, (c) between 31 and 40 per cent and (d) more than 41 per cent deducted in the latest period for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218207","218207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056822","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of universal credit claimants have (a) been informed of, (b) applied successfully for, and (c) applied unsuccessfully for twice monthly payment options.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218208","218208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056824","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will consider enabling universal credit claimants to choose a payment schedule that aligns their assessment periods and payment dates with earnings patterns and the payment of housing costs.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218210","218210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056825","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of allowing greater flexibility on start dates for assessment periods to claim universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218211","218211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056826","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that universal credit is paid to the primary caregiver in a household by default.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218212","218212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056827","2019-02-11","Department for Transport","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research Department has commissioned or gathered on the effect of open loop scrubbers on sediment quality in UK waters; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218293","218293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056828","2019-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research his Department has commissioned or gathered on the effect of open loop scrubbers on sediment quality in UK waters; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218294","218294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056830","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department monitors the amount of greenhouse gases that are emitted by importing minerals such as (a) clay, (b) chalk, (c) limestone and (d) coal to the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218240","218240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056831","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2019 to Question 214134 on Debt Collection, how many certified enforcement officers have lost their licence to enforce debts since April 2014 as a consequence of a judicial order following a judgment that they were not a fit and proper person to hold a certificate.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218392","218392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056833","2019-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the situation in Sudan since demonstrations began on 19 December 2018; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218342","218342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056835","2019-02-12","Treasury","2019-02-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff in HMRC are allocated to investigating non-payment of the minimum wage.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218339","218339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056837","2019-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make it her Department's policy to refer claimants of universal credit to foodbanks.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218340","218340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056838","2019-02-11","Department for International Development","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to provide assistance to the proposed vaccination programme for Venezuelan refugees across Latin America.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218276","218276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056839","2019-02-12","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on tax concessions for small music venues.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218219","218219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056840","2019-02-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for the Typhoon and F-35 to deliver the full spectrum of weapons capabilities currently provided by Tornado; and what plans he has to fill the capability gap in the meantime.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218277","218277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056841","2019-02-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the findings of the IHS Markit report published on 6 February, that the UK will become a net defence importer by 2024 and the fifth largest global market for defence imports.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218278","218278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056842","2019-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of full service universal credit claimants have had their claims stopped each month due to a zero award.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218334","218334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056843","2019-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full service universal credit claimants have had their claims stopped each month due to a zero award.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218335","218335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056844","2019-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of full service universal credit claimants who have had their claims stopped re-apply the following month, in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218336","218336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056845","2019-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons her Department's policy changed from live service universal credit to full service universal credit to end a claim after one month of zero award.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218337","218337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056846","2019-02-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has conducted an impact assessment on the change in policy from live service universal credit to full service universal credit on the automatic ending of claims after a zero award.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218338","218338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056847","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children placed in children’s homes (a) inside the local authority responsible, (b) outside the local authority responsible and (c) nationally (i) were reported missing by (A) duration of missing incident and (B) age of child at the start of missing incident and (ii) went missing more than once during the year for each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218196","218196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056848","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children placed in children’s homes (a) inside the local authority responsible, (b) outside the local authority responsible and (c) in each local authority area (i) were reported missing by (A) duration of missing incident, (B) age of child at the start of missing incident and (ii) went missing more than once during the year, for each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218197","218197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056849","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the contribution to the UK economy of the shale gas industry to date.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218279","218279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056850","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the contribution to the economy of Fylde of the shale gas industry to date.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218280","218280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056851","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many looked-after children in (a) foster placements and (b) children’s homes were placed (i) inside and (ii) outside of the local authority responsible; and for those children placed outside of the local authority responsible what the average distance the placement was from the placing authority in each local authority area for each year since 2012.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218198","218198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056852","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of shale gas extraction on (a) domestic and (b) commercial energy tariffs.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218281","218281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056853","2019-02-12","House of Commons Commission","2019-02-07","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what assessment the Commission has made of the effect of the contract for offsite screening of incoming mail to the Houses of Parliament on the ability of Members to receive next-day mail.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218231","218231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056854","2019-02-12","House of Commons Commission","2019-02-07","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, if the Commission will investigate delays experienced by Members receiving incoming mail.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218232","218232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056855","2019-02-11","Department for Transport","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the total cost to the public purse of Network Rail compensation payments to service providers following disruption to the rail infrastructure network in 2018.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218282","218282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056856","2019-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve flood prevention in rural Fylde.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218283","218283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056857","2019-02-11","Department for Transport","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to increase the number of train carriages from the Medway towns to London in (a) morning rush hour and (b) overall.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218273","218273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056858","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on his policies of the EU returning to duty free arrangements in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and whether the UK will reciprocate to ensure a parity of arrangements for UK businesses.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218193","218193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056859","2019-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) legislative and (b) non-legislative steps his Department is taking to tackle toxic air pollution.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218213","218213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056860","2019-02-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS Long Term Plan, what plans the Government has to support cancer alliances to change their footprints to align with sustainability and transformation plans.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218234","218234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056861","2019-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of noise levels at the Preston New Road Shale Gas site since the commencement of (a) exploratory drilling and (b) exploratory fracturing.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218284","218284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056862","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking in response to the resolution of the House of 24 January 2019 on appropriate ME treatment.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218214","218214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056863","2019-02-12","Department for Transport","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans are in place to repair the potholes and poor road surface on the A1M northbound carriageway south of junction 7; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218220","218220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056864","2019-02-12","Cabinet Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question  216324 on Department for Exiting the European Union: Facebook, what the (a) age profile, (b) gender and (c) location was of custom audiences that were targeted by the 10 Downing Street Facebook page since 21 November 2017.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218302","218302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056865","2019-02-12","Department for Education","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 28 November 2018 to Question 195085, whether his Department made a subsequent assessment of the viability of The Hoo as a location for the proposed Abacus Free School in Belsize Park since the reduction of its listed price at auction.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218343","218343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056866","2019-02-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the memorandum of Dr David Rosser of University Hospitals Birmingham published on 30th January 2019, what steps his Department is taking to ensure adequate distribution of NHS medicines in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with a Withdrawal Agreement and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218295","218295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056867","2019-02-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS Blood and Transplant’s comments on blood transfusions published on 29th January 2019, what steps his Department is taking to reduce congestion at Channel ports to ensure the continuity of blood donor sessions in the event that the UK leaves the EU (a) with a Withdrawal Agreement and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218296","218296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056868","2019-02-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of the reduction to the public health budget on the number of patients admitted to hospital because of alcohol-related diseases and injuries.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218297","218297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056869","2019-02-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on patients' health of reducing the budget for (a) sexual health services and (b) drug and alcohol services by £85 million.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218298","218298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056870","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to conduct a review of the Pubs Code.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218194","218194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056871","2019-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will publish the responses to Annex A of the Seasonal Workers Pilot Request for Information submitted by (a) Pro-Force Limited and (b) Concordia UK.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218320","218320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056872","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Pubs Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218195","218195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056874","2019-02-12","Department for Transport","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of HS2 funding (a) has been spent, (b) will be spent in the 2019-20 financial year and (c) will be spent after the end of the 2019-20 financial year in each (ii) nation and (ii) region of the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218215","218215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056875","2019-02-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what data his Department holds on the routes through which young people with severe mental health issues are referred to local authorities and health trusts for assessment and treatment.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218169","218169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056876","2019-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, who his Department consulted in assessing responses to Annex A of the Seasonal Workers Pilot Request for Information.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218321","218321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056877","2019-02-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish a consultation on the Shared Prosperity Fund; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218393","218393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056878","2019-02-12","Department for Transport","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the proportion of (a) total route length, (b) train stations, and (c) level crossings that are the responsibility of Network Rail Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218216","218216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056879","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if the Government will make it its policy to ringfence funding in the UK Shared Prosperity Fund for programmes providing employment support to disadvantaged communities.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218394","218394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056880","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether bad weather payments will be available to workers under the pilot Seasonal Agricultural Scheme where weather conditions cause work to be unavailable or of limited availability during the period of migrants' stay.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218322","218322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056881","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if the Government will make it its policy to match the level of funding allocated for employment support in the Shared Prosperity Fund to that in the European Social Fund after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218395","218395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056882","2019-02-12","Home Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria his Department uses to define low risk countries for participation in the 12 month short-term work visa proposed in the immigration White Paper published on 19th December 2018, The UK's Future Skills-Based Immigration System; and when his Department plans to publish a list of those countries.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218323","218323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056883","2019-02-12","Department for International Development","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the poverty levels of countries traded with under the Everything But Arms Agreement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218396","218396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056884","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was levied in respect of service credits in each key performance indicator designated met in each Compass asylum accommodation region in 2018-19.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218324","218324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056885","2019-02-11","Department for International Development","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department funds aid programmes that support female garment factory workers in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218244","218244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056886","2019-02-12","Department for Education","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of schools in England that contain asbestos in their buildings and premises.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218328","218328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056887","2019-02-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of hospitals in England that contain asbestos in their building and premises.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218329","218329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056889","2019-02-12","Department for Education","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps his Department is taking to support universities in protecting the mental health of students.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218331","218331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056890","2019-02-12","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral contribution of the hon. Member for Sefton Central on 5 February 2019 Official Report column 159, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of adopting the system of fetal alcohol spectrum disorder courts used in the Canadian province of Manitoba.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218300","218300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056891","2019-02-12","Department for Transport","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish (a) the names of the companies that made successful bids to build (i) Old Oak Common station and (ii) Euston station, (b) the dates on which the contracts for that work are expected to be signed and (c) the scope of the works in those contracts.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218138","218138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056892","2019-02-12","Department for Transport","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date he expects the main contractors building High Speed Two Phase 1 to commence their work.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218139","218139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056893","2019-02-12","Department for Transport","2019-02-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the names of contractors and companies that have been paid more than £500,000 for work in connection with High Speed Two and the (a) amounts paid to and (b) works carried out by each of those contractors and companies since 1 January 2017.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218140","218140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054745","2019-02-06","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will consider implementing an obligatory tenancy deposit scheme for commercial premises with a rateable value of £51,000 or less to ensure that small and medium enterprises which put down deposits in order to secure business premises have their deposits protected.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216404","216404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055228","2019-02-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which Ministers will attend meetings of the Alternative Arrangements Working Group.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217087","217087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055726","2019-02-06","Cabinet Office","2019-02-06","What plans he has to change the time limit on the entitlement of UK citizens living overseas to register to vote in UK parliamentary elections.","Biography information for Nigel Huddleston","Nigel Huddleston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909034","909034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055727","2019-02-06","Cabinet Office","2019-02-06","What steps his Department has taken to prepare for the UK's voluntary national review of the Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909036","909036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055777","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of child protection procedures on families affected by myalgic encephalomyelitis.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217626","217626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055778","2019-02-11","Department for International Trade","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the three extant Open Individual Trade Control Licences for bombs and missiles to Saudi Arabia, who manufactured those bombs and missiles; how many have been transferred under the Licences in each year since those Licences were granted; and what the value is of each such transfer in each of those years.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217627","217627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055779","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the level of the Special Grant for 2019-20; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217628","217628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055780","2019-02-11","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will hold discussions with Heathrow Airport Management on providing Government support for the development of regional logistic hubs in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217490","217490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055781","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of (a) current and (b) future visa requirements and processes for Catholic clergy and members of religious orders.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217629","217629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055782","2019-02-08","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, in relation to the Loan Charge 2019, whether Employment Benefit Trust schemes have always been considered defective by HMRC; and what the evidential basis is for the requirement to bring forward legislative proposals to enable HMRC to collect tax on loans issued since 1999.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217479","217479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055783","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the findings of the Human Rights Watch December 2018 report Bangladesh Election Crackdown on Political Opponents and Critics and the Transparency International Bangladesh January 2019 Review of Election Process of 11th National Election, what steps the Government is taking to help tackle electoral fraud in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217478","217478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055784","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will meet representatives of the Equitable Members Action Group to discuss compensation for Equitable Life investors before the spring financial statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217630","217630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055785","2019-02-08","Prime Minister","2019-02-06","To ask the Prime Minister, when she plans to respond to the letter of 30 November 2018 from the hon. Member for Ellesmere Port and Neston.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217631","217631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055786","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has in place for increasing secondary school places in Ashford after 2022; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217426","217426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055787","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2019 to Question 210043, with what organisations and agencies other than HMRC, the Department for Work and Pensions and the NHS his Department has shared data; for what purposes; and how many instances of data sharing there have been for each purpose.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217431","217431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055788","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason personal independence renewal documents may not be processed when they are received by her Department, which resulted in my constituent Ms Selina Wilkinson's personal independence payment being stopped.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217507","217507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055789","2019-02-11","Northern Ireland Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress she has made in the last 12 months in implementing the Bengoa recommendations for the health service in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217491","217491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055790","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, which local authorities operate a selective licensing scheme for private landlords.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217467","217467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055792","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what meetings his Department has had with counterparts in the Department for Transport on the forthcoming aviation strategy.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217633","217633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055794","2019-02-08","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of imported chocolate is Fairtrade.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217635","217635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055795","2019-02-11","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to encourage businesses throughout the UK to purchase Fairtrade products.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217636","217636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055796","2019-02-08","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of chocolate products sold in (a) shops, (b) vending machines, and (c) kiosks located within her Department are certified as Fairtrade.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217637","217637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055797","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department has issued to NHS organisations on reducing waiting times for dermatology treatments.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217638","217638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055798","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of workforce shortages in the NHS on the delivery of dermatology services.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217639","217639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055799","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure dermatology services meet the 95 per cent target of an 18 week waiting time from referral to treatment.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217640","217640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055800","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding his Department has allocated to special needs provision in schools in Barnsley; and what the average allocation was for schools in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217584","217584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055801","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to tackle variations in the 18-week referral to treatment waiting time for dermatology services.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217641","217641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055802","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the efficacy of the energy regulator.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217537","217537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055803","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the effectiveness of the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217538","217538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055804","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the effectiveness of the Local Government Ombudsman.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217539","217539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055805","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people are not issued with a penalty charge for ticking the wrong box on the claim form when claiming for free dental care.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217585","217585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055806","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the press release entitled, Dentists welcome official investigation into fines hitting vulnerable NHS patients, published on 30 January 2019 by the British Dental Association; whether he has plans to simplify the process for claiming free dental care to reduce the number of fines issued for ticking the wrong box on dental forms.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217586","217586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055807","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December to Question 193360 on Access to Work Programme, how many of the access to work elements that were approved in 2016-17 included elements assessed as costing (a) over £1,000 and (b) under £1,000.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217427","217427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055808","2019-02-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to his Department's paper, Future Telecoms Infrastructure Review, published in July 2018, when his Department plans to publish proposals for transparency measures required of BT Openreach.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217428","217428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055809","2019-02-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his Department has had with BT Group and Openreach on increasing the transparency of its full-fibre deployment plans.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217429","217429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055810","2019-02-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the risk to (a) alternative full-fibre network providers and (b) the Government’s target of national full-fibre connectivity by 2033 from anti-competitive overbuild of existing networks.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217430","217430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055811","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with the EU Commission on the European Court of Justice ruling in November 2018 to suspend the UK's Capacity Market.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217420","217420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055812","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the effectiveness of the Financial Services Ombudsman.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217540","217540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055813","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether it is his policy to reinstate payments under the Capacity Market for Autumn 2019.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217421","217421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055814","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether retrospective payments will be paid to generators in the event that the Capacity Market is reinstated.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217422","217422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055815","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on the provision of social housing for people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217456","217456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055817","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Department has taken to ensure that solar power is able to compete on a level playing field with other energy generation technologies.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217466","217466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055818","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many electricity generation plants have (a) closed and (b) ceased operation since 15 November 2018.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217423","217423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055819","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2019 to Question 209287 on NHS: Members' Constituency Work, when the NHS started to require hon. Members to have signed authority before replying to such Members on issues raised by constituents.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217477","217477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055820","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of specialist teachers for deaf children.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217457","217457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055821","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much funding his Department has allocated to the development of a national stroke plan.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217450","217450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055822","2019-02-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of youth centres that have closed in each year since 2010 in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217458","217458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055823","2019-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Russia on the religious freedom of Jehovah's Witnesses in that country.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217459","217459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055824","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the workforce implementation plan will include the level of investment required to fund proposed increases in NHS staffing levels.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217642","217642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055825","2019-02-11","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in the Irish Government on a joint bid to host the 2030 World Cu; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217460","217460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055826","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the transition from the asylum accommodation COMPASS contracts to the Asylum Accommodation and Support Transformation contracts, whether transition, risk management and contingency plans have been shared with local authorities in participating asylum dispersal areas.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217596","217596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055827","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether direct financial support will be provided to local authorities participating in the asylum dispersal scheme.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217597","217597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055828","2019-02-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will publish the names of the non-civil servant attendees at each of the meetings of the Alternative Arrangements Working Group.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217468","217468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055829","2019-02-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether Shanker Singham has attended any of the meetings of the Alternative Arrangements Working Group.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217469","217469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055830","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, from which local authorities he has received written correspondence since August 2018 indicating that they may withdraw from the asylum dispersal scheme.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217598","217598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055831","2019-02-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the provision of civil service support to the Alternative Arrangements Working Group complies with the Civil Service Code.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217470","217470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055832","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he provided existing asylum dispersal local authorities with details of the proposed contracts for asylum accommodation beyond the Statement of Requirements in advance of those contracts being signed and announced in January 2019.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217599","217599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055834","2019-02-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether opposition MPs have been invited to join the Alternative Arrangements Working Group.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217472","217472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055835","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with which local authorities did his Department's contract compliance team conduct joint inspections of asylum accommodation in 2018.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217600","217600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055836","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria EU citizens will have to fulfil to be eligible for postgraduate funding in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217528","217528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055837","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there is annual requirement in the Asylum Accommodation and Support Transformation contracts for joint inspections between his Department's contract compliance team and local authorities in existing asylum dispersal areas.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217601","217601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055838","2019-02-08","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether copies of the Institute for Economic Affairs' report entitled, Plan A+: creating a prosperous post-Brexit UK, were distributed at meetings of the the Alternative Arrangements Working Group.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217473","217473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055839","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will establish a service for EU citizens in the UK to obtain advice on their (a) educational status and (b) eligibility for funding support.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217529","217529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055840","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of his Department operating the asylum dispersal scheme in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217602","217602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055841","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether EU citizens with confirmed places at university will continue to be funded for the duration of their courses in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217530","217530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055842","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the cost to local authorities of participating in the asylum dispersal scheme in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217603","217603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055843","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding his Department allocated to local authorities for their participation in the asylum dispersal scheme in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217604","217604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055844","2019-02-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to increase tourism in (a) Kent and (b) Medway.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217566","217566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055845","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of asylum accommodation in each COMPASS region is in the (a) social housing, (b) registered social landlord and (c) private sector.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217605","217605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055846","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many landlords or letting agents receiving public monies under the COMPASS asylum accommodation contracts have received a (a) civil penalty notice and (b) banning order under the Housing and Planning Act 2016 since April 2017; and how many landlords or letting agents have been prosecuted under the Housing Act 2004 since September 2012.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217606","217606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055847","2019-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Soft Power Strategy will be published.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217486","217486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055848","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to improve (a) pay and (b) employment opportunities for disabled people.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217643","217643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055849","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214560 on Buildings: Insulation, if he will publish the bespoke test methodology which the Building Research Establishment (BRE) has developed.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217589","217589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055850","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214560 on Buildings: Insulation, whether building material such as cladding or insulation that fails the bespoke test will be removed.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217590","217590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055851","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the forthcoming workforce implementation plan will include a plan to increase the number of general practitioners.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217514","217514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055852","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2019 to Question 208843 on Department for Work and Pensions: Overseas Aid, what that money was spent on.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217509","217509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055853","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 211608 on Climate Change Convention, if he will publish his formal application to host COP26 in 2020.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217424","217424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055854","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2019 to Question 208842 on Home Office: Overseas Aid, what that money was spent on.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217510","217510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055855","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214560 on Buildings: Insulation, if his Department will publish a consolidated schedule of all the materials that it intends to test before that testing is carried out.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217591","217591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055856","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, to what extent professional qualifications and registrations will continue to be mutually recognised between the UK and the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217487","217487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055857","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214560 on Buildings: Insulation, if his Department will publish guidance for building owners and local authorities with buildings with High-Pressure Laminate cladding before the BS 8414 test is carried out outlining what steps should be taken if that system fails the test.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217592","217592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055858","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans the Government has to maintain mutual recognition of EU health insurance policies after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr John Baron","Mr John Baron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217488","217488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055859","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214560 on Buildings: Insulation, whether his Department will undertake a BS 8414 test on a system with rendered Expanded Polystyrene insulation.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217593","217593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055860","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2019 to Question 208844 on Department for Education: Overseas Aid; if he will set out what specific programmes that funding was spent on.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217511","217511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055861","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many survivors of modern slavery making a claim for employment and support allowance have undergone a Work Capability Assessment; and of those claimants, how many were (a) placed in the Support Group, (b) placed in the Work Related Activity Group and (c) found Fit For Work.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217480","217480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055862","2019-02-08","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 23 January 2019, to Question 208845 on Revenue and Customs: Overseas Aid, what that money was spent on.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217512","217512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055863","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2019 to Question 208846 on Ministry of Defence: Overseas Aid,  what that money was spent on.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217513","217513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055864","2019-02-11","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the interim recommendations of the Crossrail 2 Independent Affordability Review; and what his timeframe is for publishing the final recommendations of that review.","Biography information for Sir Vince Cable","Sir Vince Cable","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217432","217432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055865","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many charter flights have been scheduled for (a) removals, (b) deportations and (c) mixed removals and deportations to Commonwealth countries for March 2019.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217516","217516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055866","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many charter flights have been scheduled for (a) removals, (b) deportations and (c) mixed removals and deportations to Commonwealth countries for April 2019.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217517","217517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055867","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to monitor the effect of non-invasive pregnancy testing on the number of babies born with Down’s syndrome.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217541","217541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055868","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason NICE in developing its guidelines on termination of pregnancy has not included an assessment of the physical, emotional and economic effect of premature births and their correlation with previous abortions.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217542","217542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055869","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason NICE has omitted from its new guidance on termination of pregnancy an assessment of the the long-term effect of abortion on the (a) mortality, (b) future premature births, (c) infertility, (d) mental illness and (e) other health issues of women (i) under 25 and (ii) of other ages.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217543","217543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055870","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether painkiller will be administered to unborn babies with spina bifida who undergo spinal surgery; and at what age those unborn babies will undergo that surgery.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217544","217544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055871","2019-02-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of civil servants working full-time for two days on meetings related to a compromise plan for exiting the European Union.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217644","217644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055872","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what research his Department has commissioned in the last five years into the long-term effect of abortion on (a) future miscarriages, (b) premature births, (c) suicide and (d) other health issues among women (i) under 25 and (ii) of other ages.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217545","217545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055873","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many flights have been chartered for (a) removals, (b) deportations and (c) mixed removals and deportations to Commonwealth countries scheduled for May 2019.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217518","217518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055874","2019-02-08","Women and Equalities","2019-02-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether the Government Equalities Office is taking steps to (a) tackle the 90 per cent termination rate following a prenatal diagnosis of Down's syndrome and (b) assess the effect of that rate on the community of people with Down’s syndrome; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217546","217546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055875","2019-02-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to support the food and beverage sector in Kent.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217567","217567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055876","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many flights have been chartered for (a) removals, (b) deportations and (c) mixed removals and deportations to Commonwealth countries scheduled for June 2019.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217519","217519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055877","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are currently held in detention centres in the United Kingdom awaiting (a) removal and (b) deportation to Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217520","217520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055878","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many out-of-country appeals have been made against (a) deportations and (b) removals from the UK to Commonwealth countries in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217521","217521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055879","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what changes have been made to immigration policy as a result of the Windrush Lessons Learned Review.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217522","217522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055880","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how people who are awaiting (a) deportation and (b) removal to a Commonwealth country arrived in the UK between the ages of (i) 0-5, (ii) 5-10, (iii) 10-15, (iv) 15-20, and (v) 20-25.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217523","217523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055881","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) mean, (b) median, (c) shortest and (d) longest total lengths of stay in the UK to date are of the people awaiting (i) deportation and (ii) removal to a Commonwealth country.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217524","217524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055882","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department provides guidance to the writers of educational textbooks on how to present the issue of migration in their books.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217645","217645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055883","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what offences each of the people awaiting deportation to a Commonwealth country have been convicted of.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217525","217525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055884","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of people awaiting (a) deportation and (b) removal to a Commonwealth country have children who are UK nationals.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217526","217526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055885","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people awaiting (a) deportation and (b) removal to a Commonwealth country served in the UK armed forces.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217527","217527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055886","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2019 to Question 213415, what the total amount requested by the Metropolitan Police was between 2017-18 and 2018-19 for which the Government chose to award £22 million in Special Grant funding.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217646","217646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055887","2019-02-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans he has to lay the statutory instrument required for the licensing of small-scale DAB radio.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217515","217515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055888","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fees for settled status applications his Department has processed since 21 January 2019.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217647","217647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055889","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much money his Department has collected in fees for applications for Settled status from (a) adults and (b) children.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217648","217648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055890","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, under what circumstances an EU Citizen applying for Settled Status will be required to pay for biometric enrolment.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217649","217649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055891","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has made an assessment of the potential merits of waiving fees for applications for (a) residence and (b) permanent residence cards.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217650","217650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055892","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of waiving biometric enrolment fees for EU citizens and their family members.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217651","217651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055893","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to commission an independent review of the experience of asylum seekers in asylum accommodation.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217607","217607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055894","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the existing 1:200 dispersal ratio in the COMPASS asylum accommodation arrangements will be applied at local authority ward level.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217608","217608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055895","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make it his policy to consult with local authorities before making use of the powers under section 100 and section 101 of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 that require a (a) local authority and (b) registered social landlord to assist or designate part of their housing for the purposes of asylum accommodation.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217609","217609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055896","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many local authorities that agreed to participate in asylum dispersal subsequently withdrew that agreement before any asylum seeker was accommodated since January 2017.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217610","217610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055897","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Bridgend of 8 January 2019 reference MM/JH/08/01/2019.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217502","217502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055898","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department undertook a Data protection impact assessment (a) or (b) after the introduction of the Aspen card in asylum support arrangements.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217611","217611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055899","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has held discussions with the Information Commissioner on the effect of the introduction of the Aspen on (a) data protection and (b) an individuals privacy.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217612","217612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055900","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers have had their asylum support (a) suspended and (b) discontinued as a result of information obtained by the monitoring of the usage of an Aspen card.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217613","217613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055901","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria his Department used to assess the availability of spaces in local authority care for unaccompanied child refugees.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217652","217652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055902","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement on the UK (a) automotive and (b) steel industries.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217653","217653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055903","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will issue a response to Early Day Motion 2033 on Pension Credit - Debate and Vote.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217594","217594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055904","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2019 to Question 215206 on Gold and Foreign Exchange Reserves, if he will list the (a) 70 countries who are gold customers of the Bank of England and (b) total value of the gold deposited in those countries' accounts.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217614","217614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055905","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish in full the business case and any documents relating to the financial evaluation of the decision to close St John's House HMRC office in Bootle.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217615","217615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055906","2019-02-08","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of harmonising reporting requirements across donors.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217624","217624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055907","2019-02-08","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps her Department has taken to reduce the bureaucratic cost of delivering humanitarian aid.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217625","217625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055908","2019-02-08","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to engage with international working groups that work to fulfil the 10 Grand Bargain principles.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217654","217654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055909","2019-02-08","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to independently verify the performance of the UN humanitarian agencies that it contributes to funding in South Sudan.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217655","217655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055910","2019-02-08","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the transaction costs incurred by her Department’s reporting requirements for UN humanitarian agencies.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217656","217656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055911","2019-02-08","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that economic development programmes help the most marginalised and vulnerable in target countries.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217657","217657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055912","2019-02-08","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to increase the proportion of Official Development Assistance spent in the least developed countries and fragile states.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217658","217658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055913","2019-02-08","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department’s Official Development Assistance is delivered through local and national partners.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217659","217659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055914","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) male and (b) female prisoners who have suffered a traumatic brain injury at some point in their life.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217484","217484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055915","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the number of higher rate tax payers in each constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217579","217579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055916","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have accessed cannabis-derived medicinal products under schedule 2 of the Misuse of Drugs Regulations 2001.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217660","217660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055917","2019-02-11","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he will be depositing all records relating to the 1994 Chinok helicopter crash in the National Archives at Kew.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217489","217489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055918","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the oral contribution of 6 February 2019 by the hon. Member for Ipswich, whether the Home Office guidance in respect of the EEA E10 residence card will be altered to allow spouses of British citizens who obtained their E10 card in other EEA countries to benefit from the tenancy of properties in the UK.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217661","217661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055919","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the amount that he (a) has allocated and (b) will allocate to each local authority area from the £10 billion of business rates support.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217583","217583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055920","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the financial benefits for drivers of LPG vehicles; and whether the Government has plans to reduce tax for drivers who have converted their vehicle to run on LPG.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217582","217582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055921","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to  Question 214495 on Private Rented Housing: Housing Benefit, if he will ask the UK Statistics Authority to collect data on the number of fines brought by local authorities against private landlords.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217481","217481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055922","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his Answer of 5 February 2019 to Question 213249 on Diabetes: Medical Equipment, what role integrated care systems will play in ensuring that people with diabetes are able to access their preferred glucose meter.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217483","217483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055923","2019-02-11","Cabinet Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the process by which people travelling overseas are able to register to vote by proxy.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217505","217505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055924","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing a voucher scheme to (a) cover in full or (b) subsidise the costs of school uniforms for children from households whose annual income is less than £16,000.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217482","217482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055925","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many noise abatement orders have been granted by courts in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217474","217474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055926","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many environmental health staff with responsibility for dealing with noise nuisance were employed in local authorities in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217475","217475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055927","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether (a) local authorities and (b) housing providers are required to notify the occupant of property A before noise recording equipment is installed in property B in connection with suspected noise nuisance from property A.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217476","217476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055928","2019-02-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the change was in the level of rent arrears among public sector housing tenants between 2016 and 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217492","217492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055929","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer on 5 February 2019 to Question 213317 on NHS: Drugs, what process NICE plans to follow when scoping its review of its technology appraisal methods in the 2019-20 business year.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217532","217532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055930","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer on 5 February 2019 to Question 213317 on NHS: Drugs, how NICE plans to engage with patient organisations as part of its scoping process for its review of its technology appraisal methods in the 2019-20 business year.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217533","217533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055931","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to Answer of 5 February 2019 to Question 215231 on Universal Credit: Private Rented Housing, what timings her Department records when measuring time elapsed relating to complaints received from Private Rental Sector Landlords about universal credit full service tenants.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217662","217662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055932","2019-02-11","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has had discussions with ports in Northern Ireland that have resolved any issues that may arise after 29 March 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217493","217493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055933","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the forthcoming NHS workforce implementation plan ensures that there are sufficient numbers of staff to diagnose and treat cancer.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217577","217577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055934","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the oral evidence of Dr Olwen Williams, the President of the British Association for Sexual Health and HIV, to the Health and Social Care Committee on Sexual Health on 5 February 2019, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the increase in the number of cases of syphilis diagnoses recorded in 2018.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217568","217568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055935","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the reasons for the increase in the rate of abortions among women aged 30 to 34 in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217569","217569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055936","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the oral evidence of Dr Olwen Williams, the President of the British Association for Sexual Health and HIV, to the Health and Social Care Committee on Sexual Health on 5 February 2019, what steps his Department plans to take to tackle the matter of neonatal deaths as a result of syphilis.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217570","217570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055937","2019-02-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the recommendations on page 16 of the Carers UK report, Juggling work and unpaid care: A growing issue, published on 5 February 2019, if he will make it his policy to introduce new rights to paid care leave and a longer period of unpaid leave.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217571","217571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055938","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2019 to Question 215173, what plans his Department has to work with EU nationals employed by the NHS to ensure that they stay in the UK and feel welcome and encouraged to do so.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217572","217572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055939","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress he has made in setting up a mirror system that is linked to the EU Emissions Trading System.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217425","217425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055940","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2019 to Question 211708, on Special Guardianship Orders, for what reason the Government does not record disruption rates of adoptions and special Guardianship orders, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217536","217536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055941","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that UK seafarers can continue to work on EU flagged vessels in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217663","217663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055942","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has received any assurances from the Chair of the Climate Change Committee on potential conflicts of interests arising from his involvement with Sancroft International.","Biography information for Conor Burns","Conor Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217531","217531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055943","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has made to the European Maritime Safety Agency on UK seafarers continuing to work on EU flagged vessels in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217664","217664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055944","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on UK seafarers continuing to work on EU flagged vessels in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217665","217665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055945","2019-02-11","Cabinet Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the press release entitled Next round of Voter ID pilots announced for 2019, published 3 November 2018, which local authorities are (a) continuing to take part in and (b) have withdrawn from the pilot process; and what the reasons were for each local authority that has withdrawn.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217666","217666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055946","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department has spent on funding teacher training to support teachers in facilitating lessons on the holocaust in classroom settings in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217667","217667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055947","2019-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-06","the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 31 January 2019 to Question 211705 on Pesticides, if he will publish the (a) conclusions of the Government’s review of the National Action Plan for the Sustainable Use of Pesticides and (b) stakeholder submissions that contributed to that review.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217534","217534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055948","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the squadron deployed to Minden will be activated; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217503","217503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055949","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that certificates of competency for UK seafarers will be recognised by EU member states in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217668","217668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055950","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of encouraging UK seafarers to renew EU members state endorsements attesting to their recognition before 29 March 2019 in order to mitigate the effect on UK seafarers working on EU flagged vessels in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217669","217669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055951","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to Answer of 24 April to Question 136144 on Antisemitism, what progress his Department has made on creating a database of (a) symbols, (b) slogans and (c) flags that may be illegal as a result of their use to incite hatred.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217670","217670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055952","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that hospital trusts adhere to (a) shared decision-making principles and (b) patient consent guidance within NHS England's Commissioning framework for biological medicines (including biosimilar medicines) when implementing bio-similar medicine switching programmes.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217619","217619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055953","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps are taken in cases where guidance within NHS England's Commissioning framework for biological medicines for biological medicines (including biosimilar medicines) is shown not to have been taken and patients are switched to a different medicine without their knowledge or consent.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217620","217620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055954","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many M3 Amphibious Rigs are available at Ayrshire Barracks in Monchengladbach; when those M3 Amphibious Rigs will be transferred to the German Army barracks at Minden; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217504","217504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055955","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps NHS England is taking to ensure that that hospital trusts across the NHS are following shared decision-making principles and patient consent guidance within NHS England's Commissioning framework for biological medicines (including biosimilar medicines) when implementing biosimilar switching programmes.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217621","217621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055956","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the number of pensioners that will be affected by the changes to the claiming of pension credit by mixed age couples.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217671","217671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055957","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps NHS Improvement is taking to ensure that hospital trusts across the NHS are following shared decision-making principles and patient consent guidance within NHS England's Commissioning framework for biological medicines (including biosimilar medicines) when implementing biosimilar switching programmes.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217622","217622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055958","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate her Department has made of the savings for the public purse that will be made as a result of the changes to the claiming of pension credit by mixed age couples.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217672","217672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055959","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the NHS document entitled Commissioning framework for biological medicines (including biosimilar medicines), what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that any decision to conduct a switch between biological medicines and biosimilar medicines is done with the approval of a physician and in consultation with patients.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217623","217623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055960","2019-02-11","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons his Department allocates the Jewish Community Protective Security Grant on an annual rather than multi-annual basis.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217673","217673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055961","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what (a) steps his Department has taken and (b) representations his Department has made to (i) local authorities and (ii) the police to protect (A) Islamic and (B) Jewish cemeteries from incidents of targeted vandalism and desecration.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217674","217674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055962","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will publish details of the financial turnaround plan agreed between his Department, the Education and Skills Funding Agency (ESFA) and the Academies Enterprise Trust (AET), including (a) how much public money provided by the ESFA has been earmarked to fund AET staff redundancy costs, (b) whether interest is being charged on any grants or loans to AET, (c) the loan repayment schedule for any such grants or loans, (d) financial savings AET is forecast to make while the plan is implemented and (e) whether the plan includes arrangements for outsourcing any AET staff.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217588","217588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055963","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 7 January to Question 203875, when NHS England plans to make a decision on which tumour profiling tests will be available to guide adjuvant chemotherapy decisions in early breast cancer.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217578","217578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055964","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will add a prominent hyperlink to the SEND Gateway on his Department's website.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217675","217675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055965","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2018 to Question 164517 and the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 213335 on Child Arrangement Orders, what timescale is in place for his assessment of steps to help grandchildren maintain contact with their grandparents after a parental separation.","Biography information for Anna McMorrin","Anna McMorrin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217676","217676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055966","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to Answer of 30 January 2019 to Question 214461, what comparative estimate his Department has made of cost of filing 80 per cent of nursing and 85 per cent of medical vacancies with (a) the bank and agency staff and (b) permanent staff members.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217436","217436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055967","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what contracts the Department of Education has with the companies that supply laptops under the Disabled Student Allowance.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217437","217437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055968","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the value for money students who have paid £200 to receive a laptop under the Disabled Student Allowance receive.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217438","217438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055969","2019-02-11","Attorney General","2019-02-06","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 213932, what the change has been in the case load of the Crown Prosecution Service for each crime type, in the West Midlands, in each year from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217439","217439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055970","2019-02-11","Attorney General","2019-02-06","To ask the Attorney General, what the change has been in the level of funding allocated by the Crown Prosecution Service at (a) a regional level and (b) CPS Direct level in each year from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217440","217440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055971","2019-02-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much money from the public purse has been spent on assessing the viability of alternative arrangements for the Irish border.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217573","217573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055972","2019-02-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much time the Civil Service plans to allocate towards supporting the Alternative Arrangements Working Group.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217574","217574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055974","2019-02-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the amount of time that the Civil Service has spent on assessing the viability of alternative arrangements for the Irish border for when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217575","217575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055975","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether G4S will resume management of HMP Birmingham once the safety standards of the prison have improved; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217442","217442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055976","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the rates of learning difficulties among the prison population.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217443","217443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055977","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government provided to the French Government in 2010 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other programmes linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity in the Departments of Nord and Pas-de-Calais.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217547","217547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055978","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of (a) deaths, (b) assaults and (c) cases of self-harm in prisons.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217444","217444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055979","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government provided to the French Government in 2011 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity in the Departments of Nord and Pas-de-Calais.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217548","217548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055980","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment his Department made of the level of violent crime directed at homeless people.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217445","217445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055981","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government provided to the French Government in 2012 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime, (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity in the Departments of Nord and Pas-de-Calais.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217549","217549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055982","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government provided to the French Government in 2013 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity in the Departments of Nord and Pas-de-Calais.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217550","217550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055983","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  how much funding the Government provided to the French Government in 2014 for the purposes of (a)  border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity in the Departments of Nord and Pas-de-Calais.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217551","217551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055984","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government provided to the French Government in 2015 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity in the Departments of Nord and Pas-de-Calais.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217552","217552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055985","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government provided to the French Government in 2016 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity in the Departments of Nord and Pas-de-Calais.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217553","217553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055986","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government provided to the French Government in 2017 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity in the Departments of Nord and Pas-de-Calais.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217554","217554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055987","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government provided to the French Government in 2018 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity in the Departments of Nord and Pas-de-Calais.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217555","217555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055988","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the NHS is able to recruit nurses from the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217446","217446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055989","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding the Government has provided to the French Government since 1 January 2019 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity in the Departments of Nord and Pas-de-Calais.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217556","217556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055990","2019-02-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps he has taken to tackle overcrowding in social housing.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217447","217447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055991","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of migrants entering the UK illegally in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217557","217557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055992","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to his policy paper Tackling antimicrobial resistance 2019 to 2024: the UK's 5-year national action plan, if he will amend the code of practice for the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation to require that Committee to assess the effect on the level of anti-microbial resistance of (a) a new, (b) major changes to and (c) the discontinuation of an immunisation programme.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217595","217595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055993","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many migrants entering the UK illegally were detected at port in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217558","217558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055994","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many migrants entering the UK illegally were detected at Port of Dover in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217559","217559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055995","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many migrants entering the UK illegally in small boats were detected in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217560","217560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055996","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of migrants entering the UK illegally in small  boats in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217561","217561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055997","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214460 on Nurses: training and with reference to NHS Digital data showing 33,500 nurses left the NHS in 2016-17, what steps his Department is taking to increase the recruitment and retention of nurses.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217448","217448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055998","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much the Government spent in 2010 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity at the Port of Dover.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217562","217562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055999","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much the Government spent in 2011 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity at the Port of Dover.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217563","217563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056000","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much the Government spent in 2012 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity at the Port of Dover.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217564","217564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056001","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much the Government spent in 2013 for the purposes of (a) border security, (b) border infrastructure, (c) countering organised crime (d) countering people trafficking and (e) any other payments linked to countering migrant and people trafficking activity at the Port of Dover.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217565","217565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056002","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to provide community pharmacies with a multi-year funding settlement.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217677","217677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056003","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to invest in transport infrastructure in Cornwall.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217678","217678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056004","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the supply of medications for bleeding disorders in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217506","217506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056005","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training his Department provides to members of the Parole Board on interviewing serving prisoners at hearings.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217679","217679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056006","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of defence lawyers (a) commissioning and (b) presenting psychology reports in relation to their clients at parole hearings.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217680","217680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056007","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many serving prisoners have taken the Parole Board to a Judicial Review in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217681","217681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056008","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timeframe is for the introduction of the right of a victim to make representations in relation to a Parole Board decision.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217682","217682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056009","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria his Department will use to determine whether a Parole Board decision is referred to a parole board Judge  after representations have been made by a victim.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217683","217683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056010","2019-02-08","Cabinet Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, in how many cases of domestic homicides the victim was female in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217684","217684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056011","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data his Department collects on the (a) breach and (b) multiple breaches of restraining orders.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217685","217685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056012","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support for funding is available to international students from (a) India and (b) China to study at UK universities.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217461","217461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056013","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of students studying at overseas campuses of UK universities in (a) India and (b) China in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217462","217462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056014","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will list the planned large-scale national infrastructure projects which have been cancelled by (a) private sector entities, (b) public sector entities and (c) public private partnerships in each of the last nine years; and what the (i) location and (ii) estimated value was of each such project.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217485","217485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056015","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who have downloaded the EU Exit: ID Document Check app.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217463","217463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056016","2019-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has provided diplomatic or operational support for the transfer of  Badme from Ethiopian to Eritrean jurisdiction.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217433","217433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056017","2019-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department is providing support to residents of Badme who are transferring from Ethiopian to Eritrean nationality.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217434","217434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056018","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the level of human rights violations that have recently taken place in Zimbabwe.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217580","217580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056019","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to Answer of 15 November 2018 to Quesrion 188258, whether any steps have been taken on behalf of Bahraini female political prisoners Hajer Mansoor, Najah Yusuf and Medina Ali to ensure that the Bahraini authorities allow them to see their families without the physical barrier which was imposed in September 2018.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217686","217686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056020","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of progress on Sri Lankan adherence to measures outlined in (a) Resolution 30/1 of the 30th Session of the UNHRC in 2015 and (b) Resolution 34/1 of the 34th Session of the UNHRC in 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217451","217451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056021","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Sri Lankan counterpart on the human rights of the Tamil community in that country.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217452","217452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056022","2019-02-08","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions his Department has had with the National Association of Cider Makers on duty thresholds for craft cider makers.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217494","217494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056023","2019-02-08","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what fiscal support his Department is providing to promote the growth of craft cider makers.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217495","217495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056024","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the forthcoming workforce implementation plan will be funded to ensure any recommendations for increased NHS staffing levels are delivered.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217535","217535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056025","2019-02-11","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what proposals for alternative arrangements for the Irish backstop are being considered.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217576","217576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056026","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve the provision of education services for visually impaired children.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217496","217496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056027","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the challenges facing human rights defenders and rights-focused organisations operating in (a) Israel and (b) the occupied Palestinian territories.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217453","217453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056028","2019-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how the Government measures rural poverty; what steps the Government is taking to tackle rural poverty; and what plans the Government has to include rural poverty in its policies on rural proofing.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217435","217435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056029","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in North Korea; and what representations he has made and to whom on that subject.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217454","217454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056030","2019-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of people with epilepsy entering employment.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217687","217687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056031","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to achieve the 95 per cent four-hour A&E waiting time in (a) Herefordshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217497","217497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056032","2019-02-08","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent estimate she has made of the number of internally-displaced persons in Myanmar in the most recent period for which figures are available; and what assessment she has made of trends in the number of internally-displaced people in Myanmar in the last three years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217455","217455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056033","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the effect of social media on the mental health of young people.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217581","217581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056034","2019-02-11","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of train tickets purchased for travel by (a) people working for HS2 Ltd and (b) reimbursed to any third party by HS2 Ltd; which departure and station and arrival station the tickets were used for; and the class of travel between 1 January 2018 and 31 December 2018.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217418","217418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056035","2019-02-11","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of (a) the hotel expenses paid for by HS2 Ltd in relation to HS2 Ltd personnel and (b) reimbursed to third parties by HS2 Ltd; if he will publish the (i) dates of stay and (ii) name of hotels used in relation to those costs; and the purpose of those visits between 1 January 2018 and 31 December 2018.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217419","217419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056036","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has plans to increase the level of funding allocated to science research after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217498","217498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056037","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies received corporation tax relief through the ring-fenced Oil and gas trades: Investment Allowance used against supplementary charge in (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2018-19.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217616","217616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056038","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies received corporation tax relief through ring-fenced oil and gas trades: tax relief for decommissioning expenditure in (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2018-19.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217617","217617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056039","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies received tax relief for decommissioning expenditure in 2017-18.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217618","217618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056040","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken to increase funding for the repair of local roads in North Herefordshire.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217499","217499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056041","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of potential improvements to the environmental performance of railways.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217500","217500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056042","2019-02-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to improve security in prisons.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217501","217501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056043","2019-02-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to replace (a) EU LIFE funding and (b) EU BEST funding for programmes after 2020.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217508","217508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056044","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many free abortions were performed on the NHS for citizens from (a) other EU countries and (b) non-EU countries under reciprocal healthcare arrangements in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217464","217464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056045","2019-02-11","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to page 77 of the NHS Long Term Plan, what criteria will determine which medical technology innovations are ready for adoption; and what plans are being put in place for the individualised support described in that document.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217587","217587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056046","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of providing free abortions on the NHS for citizens from (a) other EU countries and (b) non-EU countries under reciprocal healthcare arrangements in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217465","217465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056047","2019-02-11","Department for Education","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 6 February 2019 to Question 213927, if he will make further financial assistance available to students already in receipt of the maximum amount of maintenance loan who are required to pay £200 in order to receive specialist computer hardware allocated to them under the Disabled Student Allowance.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217449","217449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056641","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce delays in personal independent payment tribunal hearings being held.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218353","218353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056645","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress the Government has made on implementing the Children's Funeral Fund.","Biography information for Laura Smith","Laura Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218356","218356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056650","2019-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps he is taking to reduce tribunal waiting times for people attempting to claim personal independence payment.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218359","218359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056670","2019-02-11","Women and Equalities","2019-02-06","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of intimidation carried out by some LGBT activists towards those who refuse to identify transgender individuals by their preferred pronouns.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218186","218186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056674","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the United Kingdom has contributed to the EU budget in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Sir John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218190","218190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056769","2019-02-11","Cabinet Office","2019-02-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of working parents and carers in (a) the UK, (b) England, (c) Scotland, (d) Wales and (e) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218369","218369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056779","2019-02-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he has any plans to review the effectiveness of the way the Government shares information with devolved regional governments including metro mayors.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218314","218314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056799","2019-02-12","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of altering business rates to support local pubs.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218387","218387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056818","2019-02-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Manchester Evening News article, Greater Manchester is still owed £1 million by the government for battling last summer's moorland blazes, published on 6 February 2018, what discussions she has with the Prime Minister on the payment of funds through the Bellwin Scheme to Greater Manchester combined authority.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218228","218228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056820","2019-02-12","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what advice the Cabinet Office provides his Department on payment to local authorities of funds through the Bellwin Scheme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218229","218229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056821","2019-02-11","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Manchester Evening News article, Greater Manchester is still owed £1 million by the Government for battling last summer's moorland blazes, published on 6 February 2018, what the timeframe is for the Government to respond to an application for funds under the Bellwin Scheme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218230","218230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056823","2019-02-11","Treasury","2019-02-06","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of including debts which can be deducted directly from universal credit in the statutory Breathing Space scheme.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218209","218209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056829","2019-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to commission a comparative assessment of the PM 2.5 emissions generated per kwh for each fuel type burned on an open domestic fire only as part of his consultation on the cleaner domestic burning of solid fuels and wood; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218239","218239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056832","2019-02-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to require manufacturers to reduce the level of nitrates in processed foods; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218218","218218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056834","2019-02-11","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to provide humanitarian aid to Colombia to assist with the Venezuelan refugees that reside there.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218274","218274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056836","2019-02-11","Department for International Development","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to provide humanitarian aid to Peru to assist with the Venezuelan refugees that currently reside there.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218275","218275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056873","2019-02-12","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidelines his Department has put in place for local authorities and health trusts on target waiting times for young people with severe mental health issues before they are (a) assessed and (b) offerered appropriate treatment.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218168","218168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1056888","2019-02-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to promote the use of solar energy.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 218330","218330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054900","2019-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","If he will make it his policy to return the probation service to the public sector.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909006","909006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054903","2019-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","What recent assessment he has made of the performance of prison contractors.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909007","909007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054904","2019-02-05","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","What assessment he has made of the potential effect of independent regulation on the conduct of rogue bailiffs.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 909008","909008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054995","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2018 to Question 168121 on Armed Forces: Training, what account his Department takes of the human rights records of those countries prior to engaging in training those countries' armed forces.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217009","217009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054996","2019-02-07","Treasury","2019-02-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of implementing transition arrangements in the event that the Financial Conduct Authority becomes responsible for the pre-paid funeral plan market.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217010","217010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054998","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to publicise his Department's consultation on mandatory training on learning disabilities for healthcare professionals.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217137","217137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1054999","2019-02-08","House of Commons Commission","2019-02-05","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, for what reasons the terms, conditions and rates of overtime pay of House of Commons security staff have been altered.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216913","216913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055000","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2019 to Question 210488, which representative organisations for people with (a) dementia, (b) brain injuries and (c) learning difficulties he has met to discuss the effect of the Mental Capacity (Amendment) Bill on those people.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217011","217011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055001","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce levels of anti-social behaviour on buses.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216914","216914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055002","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of police officers that are trained to use a taser in each police force.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216915","216915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055003","2019-02-08","Department for International Trade","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate his Department has made of the level of overseas direct investment (a) put in to the West Midlands economy and (b) invested abroad by West Midlands-based businesses in each year that information is available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216916","216916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055005","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has held with representatives of the Governments of other UN Security Council member states on the possibility of a UN investigation into China’s detention of Uighurs and other Muslims in Xinjiang province.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216945","216945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055006","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with representatives of Mercosur on the implications of the current political instability in Venezuela on their continued suspension from that organisation.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216946","216946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055007","2019-02-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions his officials have had with officials in the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the potential effect on (a) the economic sustainability of and (b) employment rights of people working in the entertainment industry of that Department’s plans to align employment status frameworks for the purposes of employment rights and tax.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216947","216947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055009","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will (a) stay the imminent deportation charter flight to Jamaica and (b) cancel all such flights pending the completion of an independent review of (i) the effect on black and minority ethnic communities of his Department’s immigration policy and practice and (ii) how that policy and practice might be reformed to improve fairness and efficiency.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217012","217012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055010","2019-02-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has received representations raising concerns on the matter of hon. Members receiving agricultural payments whilst participating in parliamentary proceedings under the Agriculture Bill.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217013","217013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055011","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214627 on State Retirement Pensions: Females, whether she plans to instruct her Department to re-open complaints relating to the equalisation of the state pension age in the event that (a) the matter is no longer the subject of legal proceedings and (b) there has been no legal determination on the issues which form the basis of the complaint to the Independent Case Examiner as set out in that Answer.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217138","217138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055012","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people have been recruited to the Army in each year from 2010 to 2018.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217014","217014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055013","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to his Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 213914 and with reference to page 11 of the 2018 report of the Air Quality Expert Group (AQEG) entitled Ultrafine Particles (UFP) in the UK, if he will list the studies that the AQEG report states show highly effective removal of UFP by their pollution control systems.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216917","216917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055014","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the change has been in the number of people making blood donations between 2008 and 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216948","216948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055016","2019-02-08","Department for International Trade","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the agreement in principle with the Government of Israel to roll over the EU-Israel Free Trade Agreement, what specific territory that agreement applies to.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216949","216949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055017","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 214009 on HMS Mersey: English Channel, if he will publish the correspondence sent by the Home Office on 3 January 2019.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217015","217015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055018","2019-02-08","Department for International Trade","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the Government has offered any financial support to companies involved in the exporting of cannabis for medicinal purposes since 2010.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217016","217016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055020","2019-02-08","Treasury","2019-02-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the contribution of the medicinal cannabis industry to the UK economy since 2010.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217017","217017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055021","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) RP02a and (b) RP07 forms Companies House has received in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216950","216950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055022","2019-02-07","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many prosecutions have been made in each of the last five years for fraudulent use of an address through Companies House.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216951","216951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055023","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many applications his Department has received for European Conference of Ministers of Transport permits since November 2018; and how many such permits have been provided.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217018","217018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055024","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what form a proof of being a family carer is acceptable for an EEA National for the purpose of claiming treaty rights for a non-EEA partner in Northern Ireland where there is no provision for local registration.","Biography information for Paul Girvan","Paul Girvan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217019","217019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055025","2019-02-08","Department for International Development","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with her Venezuelan counterpart on addressing the food shortages in that country.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217020","217020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055026","2019-02-07","Department for International Development","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the scale of food shortages affecting Venezuela.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217021","217021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055028","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the review of exclusions practice led by Edward Timpson CBE will publish its final report.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217022","217022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055029","2019-02-07","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to mitigate the effects of tech farming initiatives on the livelihood of people employed in the farming industry.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217139","217139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055030","2019-02-07","Department for International Trade","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans he has to promote high food and environmental standards with the UK’s future trading partners.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217140","217140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055031","2019-02-07","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of recent strategies put forth by technology companies in relation to online safety.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217141","217141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055032","2019-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will ensure that a range of appointment times are offered to claimants awaiting universal credit assessment appointments.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217142","217142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055033","2019-02-07","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support the Government plans to provide to NHS workers applying for EU settled status.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217143","217143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055034","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2019 to Question 208914 on Personal Independence Payment: Medical Examinations, what her Department’s definition is of prescriptive.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217023","217023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055036","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many rural GP practices were closed by the NHS in 2017.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216952","216952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055037","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has plans to limit the number of rural GP practices that close each year.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216953","216953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055038","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the average cost per year of running a rural GP practice is.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216954","216954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055039","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) guidance and (b) regulations have been produced on how social workers are able to spend devolved budgets in relation to What Works Centre change projects in (a) Darlington Borough Council, (b) Hillingdon Borough Council and (c) Wigan Council.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217024","217024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055040","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's guidance is on the (a) use of, (b) reporting requirements on the use of and (c) complaint mechanisms for parents of children who have been subjected to restrictive practices in specialist schools.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217025","217025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055041","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what gender-specific support on (a) employment and (b) mental health women service personnel receive when leaving the armed forces.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217026","217026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055043","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 213885, Deportation: English Language, how many (a) refusal, (b) curtailment and (c) removal decisions have been made in respect of ETS-linked cases to date.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216918","216918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055044","2019-02-08","Home Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 213885, Deportation: English Language, how many (a) removals and (b) departures there have been in respect of ETS-linked cases to date.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216919","216919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055045","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to track outcomes for the Youth Obligation; and whether that tracking will be backdated to the launch of that programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216920","216920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055046","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many times and for what reasons NHS England chief digital officer Juliet Bauer met Livi in her official capacity.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217027","217027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055048","2019-02-08","Women and Equalities","2019-02-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps her Department plans to take with the Department for Health and Social Care to ensure that trans patients do not have to seek unaffordable private healthcare as a result of long waiting times in order to receive treatment and medication.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217144","217144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055049","2019-02-08","Women and Equalities","2019-02-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she plans to take to improve transition healthcare for people with gender dysphoria.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217145","217145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055050","2019-02-08","Women and Equalities","2019-02-05","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will take steps with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care to tackle (a) GPs not being allowed to run oestrogen tests if a patient is still registered as male on the NHS and (b) other barriers in relation to those test barriers.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217146","217146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055051","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) adults and (b) children attended (i) Lewisham Hospital A&E and (ii) Kings College Hospital A&E as a result of asthma in each year since 2010; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of A&E admissions for asthma.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217028","217028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055052","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) adults and (b) children were admitted to hospital as a result of asthma in (i) Lewisham borough, (ii) London and (iii) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217029","217029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055054","2019-02-07","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many asthma inhalers have been issued in (a) Lewisham borough, (b) London and (c) England to (i) children and (ii) adults in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217030","217030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055055","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her Department's target timetable is for deciding whether complaints to the Independent Case Examiner will be accepted for investigation; what (a) proportion and (b) number of complaints met that target in each year for which information is available; and how many complaints are currently awaiting a decision on whether or not they will be investigated.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217031","217031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055056","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people in Northern Ireland have applied for a green card as proof of insurance in order to be able to drive in the EU in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216897","216897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055057","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many applications the Government has received for the green card proof of insurance that is required in order to be able drive in the EU in the event of the leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216898","216898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055059","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the (a) mean, (b) median, (c) 10th percentile and (d) 25th percentile period between the date of a purchase of a social housing unit under Right to Buy and the date that that property has been let within the private rental sector, using a representative sample of housing units meeting these conditions, for each of the last 10 years for each region in England.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217032","217032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055060","2019-02-07","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of a statutory waiting time between the date when a social housing unit is purchased under Right to Buy and when that unit may be lawfully offered for private let.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217033","217033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055061","2019-02-08","Department for Education","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what resources his Department provides to Durham County Council for (a) the extension and modernisation of dilapidated school buildings and (b) the construction of new schools.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217034","217034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055062","2019-02-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2019 to Question 212675 on Personal Independence Payment, for what reason the treatment of dialysis whilst in a hospital is not classified as therapy in relation to personal independence payment.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217147","217147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055063","2019-02-08","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timeframe is for the Crossrail station in Burnham to become operational.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217035","217035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055065","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the (a) aims and (b) objectives are of UK policy towards China.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216889","216889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055066","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to publish a response to its consultation entitled Creating a responsible payment culture: a call for evidence on tackling late payment.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217036","217036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055067","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether people based in the camps around Omdurman, Sudan are refugees or internally displaced persons.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216921","216921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055068","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which parties were signatories to the current peace deal in South Sudan; and which parties refused to sign it.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216922","216922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055070","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress is being made towards a lasting peace deal in Darfur; which parties have (a) signed and (b) not signed the 2006 peace deal for that region.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216923","216923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055071","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the role participation in sports at school can play in tackling obesity.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216955","216955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055072","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with countries listed in the Open Doors 2019 World Watch List of the 50 countries where Christians face the most extreme persecution.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216956","216956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055073","2019-02-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to support the resolution of the conflict in the Jebel Marra mountains in Darfur in Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216924","216924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055075","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the levels of participation in sport in secondary schools.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216957","216957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055076","2019-02-07","Department for Education","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the levels of participation in sport in primary schools.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216958","216958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055077","2019-02-08","Prime Minister","2019-02-05","To ask the Prime Minister, with reference to her oral contribution of 21 January 2019, Official Report, column 27, on Leaving the EU, with which representatives of the English regions she has since engaged; and what form those discussions took.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217037","217037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055078","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK Government recognises the outcome of the Bangladesh General Election held on 30 December 2018; and what his policy is on that country's regime.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217038","217038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055079","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking in response to reports of electoral fraud during the recent General Election in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217039","217039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055080","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been on the implementation of the recommendations from Sir Michael Holden's review into the performance of South Western Railway and Network Rail.","Biography information for Paul Scully","Paul Scully","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217040","217040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055082","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to reports of electoral fraud during the recent General Election in Bangladesh, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of applying sanctions against Bangladesh until a full and independent investigation is carried out.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217041","217041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055083","2019-02-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 January 2019 to Question 204471 on Personal Independence Payment: Blaenau Gwent, what information her Department holds on the (a) number and (b) value of hardship payments made to claimants from Blaenau Gwent while awaiting payment for arrears as a result of a successful Tribunal decision.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217042","217042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055084","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for the Tornado aircraft after they are retired.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217043","217043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055085","2019-02-08","Cabinet Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has had discussions with the Greater London Authority on the raising of the European Union flag on the flag poles of Parliament Square in order for them to be ceremonially lowered on the day the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217044","217044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055086","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his Answer of  16 January 2019 to Question 207177 on Volkswagen: Exhaust Emissions, what investigations his Department conducted to determine that no wrongdoing has taken place within the UK.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217045","217045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055087","2019-02-07","Department for Transport","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2019 to Question 207177 on Volkswagen: Exhaust Emissions, what recent discussions he has had with his German counterpart on criminal proceedings against executives of Volkswagen.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217046","217046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055088","2019-02-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of teenagers with myopia compared with previous generations; and what assessment he has made of the causes of myopia in teenagers.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216899","216899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055090","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the eviction order issued to the Sabbagh family in East Jerusalem.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216925","216925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055091","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the number and frequency of eviction orders issued to and the forced displacement of Palestinians in (a) East Jerusalem and (b) the West Bank.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216926","216926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055092","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of Israeli settlers in (a) East Jerusalem and (b) the West Bank.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216927","216927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055093","2019-02-08","Treasury","2019-02-05","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many prosecutions have been initiated under sections 45 and 46 of the Financial Services Act 2017 for offences of failing to prevent tax evasion (a) in the UK and (b) abroad.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216928","216928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055095","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to maintain a permanent naval presence in (a) the Indo-Pacific region and (b) South East Asia.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216890","216890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055099","2019-02-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to create a permanent forward presence for naval facilities in South East Asia.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216900","216900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055102","2019-02-08","Department for International Trade","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will place in the Library a copy of the draft UK-Israel agreement that has been agreed in principle for trading arrangements after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216929","216929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055105","2019-02-07","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps are being taken to ensure that Bangladesh general election irregularities are fully and independently investigated.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217047","217047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055108","2019-02-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure the growth of wind power is responsibly managed and taxpayer funded constraint payments to that sector are reduced.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217048","217048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055111","2019-02-07","Ministry of Justice","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to his oral contribution of 5 February 2019, when the President of the Family Division plans to report back on his review of the guidance provided under Practice Direction 12J.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 217049","217049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1055115","2019-02-08","Department for International Trade","2019-02-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the trade deal agreed in principle between the UK and Israel for trade after the UK leaves the EU announced on 23 January 2019 will continue to distinguish in relevant dealings between the territory of the State of Israel and the territories occupied since 1967.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 216930","216930"
