"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146659","2019-10-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions Army bomb disposal units were called out in Northern Ireland between 1 January 2019 and 1 July 2019.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291280","291280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146660","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the response to his Department’s consultation entitled, Banning tyres aged 10 years and older, published in June 2019.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291256","291256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146661","2019-10-01","Treasury","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer HMG Reasonable Worst Case Planning Assumptions, what assessment he has made of potential delays for UK citizens travelling to and from the EU from (a) Holyhead port, (b) Liverpool John Lennon airport and (c) Manchester airport in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291260","291260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146662","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Emirati counterpart on supporting (a) religious freedoms and (b) right to enjoy a place of worship in that country.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291273","291273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146663","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress he is making to increase the recruitment and retention of childcare professionals.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291283","291283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146664","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to tackle the threat of online personal scams to vulnerable people.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291274","291274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146665","2019-10-01","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent progress has been made on implementing the commitment in the Queen's Speech 2017 to introduce an independent public advocate who will (a) act for bereaved families after a public disaster and (b) support those families at public inquests; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291257","291257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146666","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer HMG Reasonable Worst Case Planning Assumptions paragraph 11iii, what additional funding his Department has allocated to help (a) pensioners, (b) students, (c) workers and (d) travellers in EU countries access healthcare in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291261","291261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146667","2019-10-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer HMG Reasonable Worst Case Planning Assumptions, what assessment she has made of the probability of disruption to fuel supplies in each (a) nation and (b) region in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291262","291262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146668","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her international counterparts on ensuring that UK citizens who were ISIS fighters and are imprisoned in Iraq and Syria cannot evade justice.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291275","291275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146669","2019-10-01","Treasury","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer HMG Reasonable worst case planning assumptions paragraph 16, what estimate he has made of the proportion of insurance payments from UK insurers into the EU which would be delayed in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and what estimate his Department has made of the potential length of any such delays.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291263","291263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146670","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many human rights advisors are employed by police forces in England and Wales.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291276","291276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146671","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer HMG Reasonable worst case planning assumptions paragraph 19, what additional funding his Department has allocated for the purpose of enforcement of territorial fishing waters and increasing response capability in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291264","291264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146672","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many inspections into the age of public service vehicle tyres have been carried out by the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291258","291258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146673","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many public service vehicles inspected by the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency were identified as having tyres that exceed the 10-year age limit in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291259","291259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146674","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer HMG Reasonable worst case planning assumptions paragraph 20, what four local authorities have been identified as priority concerns, which Ministers or Departments identified those local authorities; and what the decision making process was by which those four local authorities were selected.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291265","291265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146675","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer HMG Reasonable Worst Case Planning Assumptions, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of intervention in the social care market in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291266","291266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146676","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to reduce the number of exclusions of young people from mainstream education.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291284","291284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146677","2019-10-01","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the merits of reintroducing citizenship by birthright.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291285","291285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146678","2019-10-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will publish the accounts of the data ethics and compliance issues that her Department produced for the cross data tracking of Gov.uk users.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291344","291344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146679","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the BBC Executive Complaints Unit’s interpretation of its impartiality guidelines in supporting a complaint against Ms Naga Munchetty for her comments about remarks made by the President of the United States.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291348","291348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146680","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the absence of additional funding for local authorities in connection with each additional local place in the PrEP Impact Trial on the (a) rate of increase of places available within the trial, (b) likelihood of meeting the target to double trial places and (c) likelihood of individuals seeking PrEP treatment not being able to access it over the next year.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291349","291349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146681","2019-10-01","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the effect on international student numbers by country of the decision to extend UK work visas for foreign graduates to two years after completion of their studies.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291290","291290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146682","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Electoral Commission's report entitled Accuracy and completeness of the electoral registers in Great Britain, what assessment his Department has made of the merits of additional ring-fenced funding for the purpose of increasing electoral register completeness for 18-34 year olds.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291267","291267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146683","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Electoral Commission's report Accuracy and completeness of the electoral registers in Great Britain, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the disparity between electoral register completeness of voters from white ethnic backgrounds and those from other ethnic backgrounds.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291268","291268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146684","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Electoral Commission's report Accuracy and completeness of the electoral registers in Great Britain, what assessment his Department has made of the factors influencing the increase in electoral register entries with major errors from 2015 to 2019.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291269","291269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146685","2019-10-01","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the ability of local authorities to prepare for the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and whether funds will be allocated to local authorities to help them prepare for that eventuality.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291484","291484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146686","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken, in light of the European Medicines Agency formally declaring that it recognises Post SSRI Sexual Dysfunction (PSSD) as a medical condition that can outlast discontinuation of SSRI and SNRI antidepressants, to provide symptomatic relief to those suffering from that condition on a long-term basis.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291225","291225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146687","2019-10-01","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many civil servants in his Department were actively working on preparations for (a) no deal and (b) a deal with the EU as of 26 September 2019.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291485","291485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146688","2019-10-01","Treasury","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many of the 95,000 non VAT registered companies estimated to need EORI numbers have registered for them.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291486","291486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146689","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to address the disparity in the provision of SEND support for children between different areas and local authorities in England in the upcoming Review into Support for Children with Special Educational Needs.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291226","291226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146690","2019-10-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment has been made of the ability of UK suppliers to meet demand for domestic food consumption in the event of trade disruptions arising from the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291487","291487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146691","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what funding for capital investment is being made available for GP surgery expansion and refurbishment by (a) constituency, (b) local authority and (c) region.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291232","291232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146692","2019-10-01","Department for Transport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any distributional analysis has been undertaken by (a) the Government and (b) HS2 Ltd of the passenger benefits that will accrue to towns in each region of the UK from High Speed Two.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291233","291233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146693","2019-10-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the Government plans to publish its report into the factors driving the use of food banks.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291234","291234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146694","2019-10-01","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information the Department holds on the real-terms changes to Special Educational Needs budgets by (a) constituency and (b) local authority since 2010.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291235","291235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146695","2019-10-01","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress the Government has made on its assessment of the merits of establishing a Town of Culture award.","Biography information for Yvette Cooper","Yvette Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291236","291236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146696","2019-10-01","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the (a) dates, (b) attendees and (c) topics of meetings his Department has had with representatives of food and drink charities and campaign groups in (i) 2018 and (ii) 2019; and if he will publish the (A) content discussed and (B) decisions made in those meetings.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291315","291315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146697","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether any funds from the public purse (a) have been and (b) will be spent on transport to or from the 2019 Conservative Party Conference in Manchester for Government Ministers.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291488","291488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146698","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress he has made on negotiations with Vertex Pharmaceuticals on access to Orkambi and Symkevi in England.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291489","291489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146699","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will (a) publish the memorandum of understanding between the Government Digital Service and Government departments on data ethics and compliance that enables cross tracking of Gov.UK, (b) state which Departments and non-departmental bodies the MOU was sent to and (c) set out the departments and non-departmental public bodies that have agreed the MOU.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291345","291345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146700","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Government form Security check / counter terrorist check questionnaire: NSV001, what definitions the Government uses for (a) overthrowing and (b) undermining parliamentary democracy; and what criteria the Government uses to determine those actions.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291490","291490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146701","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) contracted and (b) employed photographers and videographers were employed by each government department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291491","291491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146702","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many times (a) photographs and (b) videos produced for HMG official purposes were provided to the Conservative Party in the last 12 months; and what the cost of compensating HMG was for those rights.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291492","291492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146703","2019-10-01","Cabinet Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much is being spent by each Department in the Get ready for Brexit campaign; and whether the media buying for this campaign is taking place by OMD Group Ltd under the Crown Commercial Services for media buying services.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291346","291346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146704","2019-10-01","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many times (a) photographers  and (b) videos produced by the (i) Ministry of Defence, (ii) No.10, (iii) Government Communications Service, (iv) Armed Forces personnel and (v) an external agency contracted to one of those were provided to the Conservative Party for their use in the last six months; and what payments were made for that service.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291493","291493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146705","2019-10-01","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what mitigating methods he has planned to provide continuous access to the (a) SIS II database and (b) ECRIS for UK law enforcement and border force agencies in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291494","291494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146706","2019-10-01","Home Office","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which police forces have been requested to provide contingency resourcing for Operation Yellowhammer.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291495","291495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146707","2019-10-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that small businesses in East Yorkshire are prepared for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291270","291270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146708","2019-10-03","Department for Education","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeship starts there were in (a) East Yorkshire constituency and (b) Yorkshire in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291271","291271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146768","2019-10-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-26","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on food supplies of the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and what plans her Department has to maintain food supplies in that event.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291523","291523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145677","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students with SEN who have completed two years of post-16 education as part of their Education, Health and Care Plan before accessing A-level provision were still attending 6th form study over the age of 20 in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290674","290674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145678","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what alternative financial provision his Department has made available for young people with SEND who are (a) in full-time further education and (b) aged 20 or above and no longer have access to non-contributory employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290675","290675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145679","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps he has taken to reduce the waiting times for personal independence payments appeals to be heard in the Garston and Halewood constituency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290676","290676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145680","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time was for personal independence payments claimants awaiting an appeal on their claim to be heard in the Garston and Halewood constituency in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290677","290677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145681","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that previous claimants of the motability component under disability living allowance who have had their entitlement to the motability component removed under personal independence payments do not have their motability car removed while awaiting an appeal.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290678","290678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145682","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps to extend the six months grace period that claimants of personal independence payments have while awaiting an appeal on a decision to remove their entitlement to the motability component.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290679","290679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145683","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support her Department provides to claimants of personal independence payments who have had their motability car removed pending appeal and who need to travel to hospital appointments.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290680","290680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145684","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have (a) had their motability cars removed before a personal independence payments appeal hearing and (b) subsequently had their entitlement reinstated post-appeal in the Garston and Halewood constituency in each year since April 2013.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290681","290681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145685","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people received the enhanced mobility rate of personal independence payments after a successful appeal in the Garston and Halewood constituency in each year since April 2013.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290682","290682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145686","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what mitigation funding is available to schools wanting to reduce the effect of pollution in the surrounding area.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290710","290710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145687","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were placed (a) with foster carers and (b) in residential homes out of county in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290711","290711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145688","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish guidance for bus operators relating to disability equality training.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290712","290712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145689","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to extend the (a) teaching and (b) use of British Sign Language (BSL) in the (i) classroom, (ii) workplace and (iii) wider society.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290713","290713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145690","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many households in (a) York Central constituency, (b) City of York local authority area and (c) North Yorkshire are living in fuel poverty.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290714","290714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145691","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people in (a) City of York, (b) North Yorkshire, (c) Yorkshire and the Humber and (d) England received free school meals in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290715","290715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145692","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average pupil to teacher ratio was in (a) primary and (b) secondary schools in York in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290716","290716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145693","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the mean funding is per pupil for SEND provision in (a) York, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) England in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290717","290717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145694","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he will direct the Chief Executive of HMRC to hold meetings with honourable Members with constituencies that (a) include and (b) are close to Roadchef Motorway Services on the (i) M5 and (ii) M6 on outstanding issues in the dispute between HMRC and the Roadchef Employee Benefits Trust.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290601","290601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145695","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make a comparative assessment of her Department's guidance on the installation of heat pumps through the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme and the criteria by which Energy Performance Certificates are issued.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290602","290602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145696","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the number of data flow contractual clauses which will need to be arranged by businesses in the UK with business in the EU in the event of the UK leaving the EU (a) with and (b) without a deal.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290718","290718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145697","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Cabinet Colleagues on a potential intersection between East West Rail and High Speed 2; and what plans he has to implement a connection between those lines.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290719","290719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145698","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to increase Official Development Assistance spending on education.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290720","290720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145699","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the suitability of NICE's process of medicines appraisal for new cell and gene therapies.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290721","290721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145700","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on (a) wheat and (b) dairy farmers of the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and what assessment she has made of the level of the UK's reliance on imported bioethanol.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290722","290722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145701","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the Eatwell Guide of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290723","290723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145702","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of scheduled tests for salmonella in eggs that were (a) carried out behind schedule and (b) not carried out.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290637","290637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145703","2019-09-30","Scotland Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Edinburgh East of 25 July 2019 requesting a meeting with the Secretary of State.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290724","290724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145704","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date is of Kilroot GT Power Station.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290725","290725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145705","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Baglan Bay GT Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290726","290726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145706","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Drax GT Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290727","290727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145707","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Indian Queens Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290728","290728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145708","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Coolkeeragh GT Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290729","290729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145709","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Aberthaw GT Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290730","290730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145710","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Cowes Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290731","290731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145711","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Arnish Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290732","290732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145712","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Barra Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290733","290733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145713","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Bowmore Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290734","290734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145714","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Fiddler’s Ferry GT Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290735","290735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145715","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Five Oaks Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290736","290736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145716","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Keadby GT Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290737","290737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145717","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date Kirkwall Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290738","290738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145718","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Lerwick Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290739","290739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145719","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Stornoway Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290740","290740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145720","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Thatcham Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290741","290741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145721","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Ratcliffe GT Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290742","290742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145722","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation capacity and (b) estimated decommissioning date for Taylor's Lane GT Power Station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290743","290743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145723","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the (a) generation and (b) allowable capacity for Peterhead Natural Gas Power Station is; what the reasons for that capacity are; and what the estimated decommissioning date of that power station is.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290744","290744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145724","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the supply of medicines to hospitals in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291030","291030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145725","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she will take to mitigate the effect of the loss of access to the European criminal databases in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291031","291031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145726","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans her Department has to prepare for potential jobs losses in the event the UK leaves the EU without a negotiated withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291032","291032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145727","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to make sure people returning from holidays will not be affected by increased checks at border posts in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Janet Daby","Janet Daby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291033","291033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145728","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the disability employment gap is in her Department.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290745","290745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145729","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Trades Union Congress's report entitled TUC calls on Government to make employers report their disability pay gap, what steps her Department has taken to address the disability pay gap.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290746","290746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145730","2019-09-30","Attorney General","2019-09-25","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the additional funding for the Crown Prosecution Service announced in August 2019, what criteria he will use to decide how to distribute that funding across that Service.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290624","290624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145731","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment the Government makes of the effectiveness of sentences for criminal offences prosecuted by the Crown Prosecution Service.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290625","290625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145732","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what due diligence her Department has taken to ensure that the funding provided for the Action Fraud contact meets the demand of the service.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290747","290747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145733","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of reducing duty on beer.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290626","290626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145734","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2019 to Question 263684, what assessment his Department has made of the compliance of schools with (a) equalities legislation and (b) the schools admission code in their admittance and treatment of children with SEND.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290627","290627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145735","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse was of providing free television licences to people over the age of 75 for qualifying residents in (a) Glasgow South West constituency, (b) Glasgow City local authority area and (c) Scotland in  2018-19; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290748","290748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145736","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many advance benefit payments have been made to people in Glasgow in each month between April 2019 to August 2019; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290749","290749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145737","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to visit a food bank in Glasgow South West constituency in October 2019; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290750","290750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145738","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on the procurement of new land platforms (a) MRVP and (b) MIV; and if he will make a statement","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290751","290751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145739","2019-09-30","Scotland Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what plans he has to visit a food bank in the Glasgow South West constituency in October 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290752","290752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145740","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has for a UK-wide high profile publicity campaign to raise awareness of the climate emergency.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290753","290753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145741","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the level of take-up of the EU Settlement Scheme among naturalised EU citizens of non-EU origin.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291034","291034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145742","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to raise awareness of the EU Settlement Scheme among (a) EU citizens of Somali origin and (b) other large communities of EU citizens of non-EU origin.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291035","291035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145743","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his UAE counterpart on the treatment and release of the group of Emirati prisoners of conscience known as the UAE 94.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290571","290571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145744","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timescale is for the introduction of the new victim care contract to support victims of modern slavery under the National Referral Mechanism; and if she will place a copy of that contract in the Library.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290666","290666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145745","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's plans are for the new programme of victim support, subsequent to the High Court ruling that limiting victim support to 45 days was unlawful under Article 12 of the Council of Europe Convention on Action against Trafficking in Human Beings; and whether the new programme will continue after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290667","290667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145746","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the child trafficking guardian service will be rolled out to the remaining local authorities; and what provision was made for that service in the recent spending review.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290668","290668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145747","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many inquests relating to benefits claimants who have ended their life by suicide her Department has submitted evidence to since 2013; and in how many inquests it was ruled that the policies of her Department were partly responsible for the deceased person’s state of mind.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290669","290669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145748","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason the return envelopes provided for UC50 and ESA50 forms are first class envelopes and the envelopes provided for personal independence payments are second class.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290670","290670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145749","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will place in the Library (a) information for each of the benefits in respect to which Kofax Capture software is used and (b) the indexing business rules for each of those benefits.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290671","290671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145750","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the salary is for the vacant post of HS2 Ltd Chief Operating Officer.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290550","290550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145751","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many HS2 Ltd staff have received redundancy payments in each of the last six months; and what the amount of each of those payments was.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290551","290551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145752","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many HS2 Ltd personnel have received bonus payments in the last two years; and what the amount of each bonus payment was.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290552","290552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145753","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions (a) he, (b) his Ministers and (c) his officials have had with the management of the Royal Bank of Scotland on Thomas Cook UK between 14 September 2019 and the collapse of that company.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290754","290754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145754","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the final package of support was that Thomas Cook UK requested from the Government prior to its collapse.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290755","290755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145755","2019-09-30","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the merits of visa-free travel between the UK and the EU for short work visits after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290756","290756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145756","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the management of Action Fraud by the City of London Police.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290643","290643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145757","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance the Government is offering to the Government of Pakistan following the aftermath of the recent earthquake in Azad Kashmir.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290644","290644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145758","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the Indian Government on the situation in Jammu and Kashmir.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290645","290645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145759","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the availability of documents on the gov.uk website in alternative digital formats for people with disabilities.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291036","291036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145760","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make all documents on the gov.uk website available in alternative digital formats.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291037","291037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145761","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department is rationing the supply of medical isotopes in advance of the UK potentially leaving the EU without a deal; and what steps he is taking to ensure an adequate supply of medical isotopes in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291038","291038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145762","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to increase the supply of HRT patches; and whether stock levels of HRT patches have been affected by uncertainty over the UK's departure from the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291039","291039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145763","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on HM Treasury’s September 2019 publicity campaign on duty free cigarettes and alcohol for travellers to EU countries in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290757","290757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145764","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of including plant milks in the Healthy Start voucher scheme.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291040","291040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145765","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a proportion of the additional £2.2 billion announced in the Spending Round 2019 for the armed forces can be allocated towards increasing the headcount of procurement-related civil servants and support services.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290758","290758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145766","2019-09-30","Women and Equalities","2019-09-25","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the potential benefits of providing free sanitary products to women on low incomes beyond compulsory school age.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290759","290759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145767","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of capping (a) all charges, (b) custody charges and (c) transfer charges on (i) SIPPs and (ii) ISAs.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291041","291041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145768","2019-09-30","Department for International Trade","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to her letter dated 16 September 2019 to the Chair of the Committees on Arms Export Controls, how the breaches of the undertaking given to the Court by the Secretary of State in the Order of the Court dated 20 June 2019 took place; and what steps she is taking to ensure no further breaches take place.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290760","290760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145769","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Treasury’s September 2019 publicity campaign on duty free cigarettes and alcohol for travellers to EU countries was subject to approval by Ministers in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290761","290761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145770","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of peer-reviewed research on the net effect of free ports and enterprise zone schemes on employment levels.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290762","290762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145771","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to section 2.26 of the print version of the Spending Round 2019 document, whether additional funding will be made available to the (a) Northern Powerhouse and (b) Midlands Engine.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290763","290763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145772","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's press release dated 2 September 2019 entitled £30,000 starting salaries proposed for teachers, whether the increase in starting salaries will be funded through (a) the National Funding Formula and (b) a separate grant.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290764","290764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145773","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the total cost to the public purse is of the Get Ready For Brexit campaign.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290765","290765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145774","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to bring forward the technical proposal for the digital imprint regime.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290766","290766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145775","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made toward securing the future of family reunion routes in negotiations with the EU; and whether the UK will continue to apply the Dublin III Regulation if the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290767","290767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145776","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children accessing the (a) 15-hours free childcare scheme for three and four-year-olds and (b) 12.5-hours free childcare offer which preceded it in (i) East Hampshire constituency, (ii) Hampshire local authority area and (iii) England in each year since the inception of each offer.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Mr Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290768","290768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145777","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children accessing the 15-hours free childcare scheme for disadvantaged two-year-olds in (a) East Hampshire constituency, (b) Hampshire local authority area and (c) England in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Mr Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290769","290769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145778","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) children and (b) families accessing the 30-hours free childcare scheme in (i) East Hampshire constituency, (ii) Hampshire local authority area and (iii) England in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Mr Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290770","290770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145779","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) children and (b) families benefiting from tax-free childcare in each year since its inception in (a) East Hampshire constituency, (b) Hampshire local authority area and (c) England.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Mr Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290771","290771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145780","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2019 to Question 286692, what equivalent data exists for the county of Hampshire and not limited to Hampshire Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Mr Damian Hinds","Mr Damian Hinds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290772","290772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145781","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on the cost of living for low-income families in Garston and Halewood constituency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290683","290683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145782","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the fiscal effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on the (a) automotive industry, (b) pharmaceutical industry and (c) food industry in the North West in the subsequent (i) three months and (ii) six months.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290684","290684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145783","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent fiscal steps his Department has taken to mitigate the effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on the (a) automotive industry, (b) pharmaceutical industry and (c) the food industry in the North West; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290685","290685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145784","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the New York Times report, entitled How YouTube Radicalised Brazil, published 11 August 2019, if she will make an assessment of whether YouTube’s recommendation algorithm has played a role in increasing (a) radicalisation and (b) misinformation.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290773","290773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145785","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the effect of YouTube’s recommendation algorithm on trends in the level of (a) radicalisation and (b) misinformation in the UK in the last three years.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290774","290774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145786","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect of YouTube’s recommendation algorithm on the dissemination of misinformation on public health.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290775","290775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145787","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her Department's policies of recent trends in the level of deforestation in the Amazon rainforest.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290776","290776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145788","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent meetings Ministers and Official in his Department have had with (a) businesses and (b) public authorities in the North West on the effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal on 31 October 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290686","290686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145789","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department is providing to (a) promote truth and reconciliation and (b) prevent the re-emergence of conflict between Yazidi people who have returned to their home areas in Iraq and non-Yazidi people living in those areas.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290777","290777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145790","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase funding for sixth form colleges in England in 2019-20.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290778","290778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145791","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of applicants to the EU Settlement Scheme who are resident in Luton who have (a) been granted settled status, (b) been granted pre-settled status and (c) had their application turned down in each year since the introduction of that scheme.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290779","290779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145792","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has issued to schools on the eligibility of EU citizens without settled status to receive state-funded education up to the age of 18.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290780","290780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145793","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to tackle number plate cloning.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290781","290781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145794","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effect on the UK's international reputation in relation to (a) the rule of law and (b) the integrity of the UK's arms control regime of the recent failure to abide by UK court rulings in relation to arms sales licences for Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290782","290782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145795","2019-09-30","Department for International Trade","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of Government adherence to the rule of law regarding the issuance of arms export licences to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290783","290783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145796","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the environmental impact of planned works in preparation for High Speed Rail 2 around Steeple Claydon in Buckinghamshire.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290784","290784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145797","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the necessity of commencing planned works in preparation for High Speed 2 around Steeple Claydon in Buckinghamshire, including the clearance of 500 acres of land, in advance of Notice to Proceed.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290785","290785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145798","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2019 to Question 268421, if she will publish details of the Service Levels relating to the Next Generation Visa (NGOV) Services contract delivered by VFS Global.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290786","290786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145799","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had on whether to extend the contract for Next Generation Visa (NGOV) Services delivered by VFS Global beyond the current expiration date of 31 March 2021.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290787","290787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145800","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect on patients of the three month waiting time to see an NHS physiotherapist in Dudley.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290788","290788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145801","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce waiting times for patients waiting to see an NHS (a) physiotherapist and (b) orthotist.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290789","290789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145802","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans he has to require countries in receipt of Official Development Assistance for the health sector to commit five per cent of their GDP to spending on that sector.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290790","290790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145803","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to help strengthen the tax systems of developing countries.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290791","290791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145804","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints her Department has received about VSF Global each year since the start of its contract with her Department in 2013.","Biography information for Alistair Burt","Alistair Burt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290792","290792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145805","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how frequently the regulatory framework for drone safety is (a) reviewed and (b) updated in the UK.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291042","291042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145806","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has for speeding up the planning process for large developments whilst ensuring adequate consultation with affected local residents.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290793","290793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145807","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that drone safety regulations are maintained when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291043","291043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145808","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answers of 25 July 2019 to Question 280367 and 17 July 2019 to Question 276193 and with reference to the findings of the independent assessment commissioned by the Joint Funds Unit which identified areas where the process could be improved, what specific recommendations were made for improving the Overseas Security and Justice Assistance process.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291044","291044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145809","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure all patients receive sight saving treatment when they need it.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290794","290794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145810","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of empty homes in (a) the West Midlands region, (b) City of Wolverhampton local authority area and (c) Wolverhampton North East constituency in each year since 2010; and what steps he is taking the reduce the number of empty homes.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290795","290795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145811","2019-09-30","Scotland Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he plans to visit a food bank in October 2019.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291045","291045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145812","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when she plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Glasgow East of 24 July 2019, reference DL3066.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291046","291046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145813","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if she will make it her Department's policy to centrally record the number of workers underpaid through work trials.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290796","290796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145814","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government provides ring-fenced funding to local authorities to spend on supporting women's refuges.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290797","290797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145815","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of women's refuges operating in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290798","290798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145816","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate she has made of the number of people who have undertaken unpaid work trials in 2018-19.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290799","290799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145817","2019-09-30","Women and Equalities","2019-09-25","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the Equality Act 2010, what steps the Government is taking to inform businesses and the service sector of the rights of assistance dogs.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290800","290800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145818","2019-09-30","Women and Equalities","2019-09-25","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the Equality Act 2010 in relation to assistance dogs.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290801","290801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145819","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will estimate the number of people posing a sexual threat to children (a) online and (b) offline in the UK.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290802","290802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145820","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to publish an update to the tackling child sexual exploitation progress report published on 16 February 2017.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290803","290803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145821","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of money allocated from the public purse for the prevention of child sexual abuse and exploitation was spent on disrupting perpetrators in the most recent period for which such information is available.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290804","290804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145822","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of rises in income tax thresholds on income distribution in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290638","290638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145823","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to help further understand the specific characteristics and motivations of child sexual abuse offenders whose methodology is defined as group-based grooming as set out in the National Crime Agency’s National Strategic Assessment of Serious and Organised Crime 2018.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290805","290805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145824","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people in Airdrie and Shotts constituency have (a) opted out after being auto-enrolled into a workplace pension and (b) saved more than the auto-enrolment minimum contribution.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290806","290806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145825","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has (a) geographically mapped the prevalence of different methodologies for perpetrating child sexual abuse in the UK as set out in the National Crime Agency’s National Strategic Assessment of Serious and Organised Crime 2018 and (b) discrete plans for tackling each such methodology of perpetration.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290807","290807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145826","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the fires at Samuel Garside House in Barking Riverside, Beechmere retirement complex in Crewe and Sherbrooke Way in Worcester Park, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of banning the use of timber cladding in residential buildings.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290808","290808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145827","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the longest time is that an applicant has had to wait for the renewal of an S1 form in 2019.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290809","290809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145828","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many outstanding claims for healthcare cover under the S1 scheme there were on 25 September 2019.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290810","290810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145829","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Operaton Yellowhammer HMG reasonable worst case planning assumptions chapter 17, what steps his Department is taking to protect low income groups from price rises in food and fuel.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290700","290700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145830","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government guidance, Calculating the Minimum Wage, if she will make it her Department's policy to review and update the guidance on unpaid work trials.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290811","290811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145831","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer HMG Reasonable Worst Case Planning Assumptions, what estimate he has made of (a) the reduced flow rate in the Port of Holyhead  and (b) the potential effect of reduced flow rates on traffic congestion on the A55 and surrounding roads in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal; and if he will place in the Library copies of all research undertaken by the Government on the effects of leaving the EU without a deal on the (i) Port of Holyhead and (ii) local transport infrastructure.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290701","290701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145832","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer HMG Reasonable Worst Case Planning Assumptions paragraph 6, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the (a) geographically equitable and (b) economically equitable distributions of medicines in limited supply in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290702","290702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145833","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he will hold discussions with the Office of National Statistics on the potential merits of introducing alternatives to the write-in option and search box to be used in the 2021 Census to ensure more accurate data on the Jain community in that census; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290594","290594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145834","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans he has to promote to the Jain population in the UK the ability to identify as a Jain in the 2021 census, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290595","290595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145835","2019-09-30","Northern Ireland Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer HMG Reasonable Worst Case Planning Assumptions paragraph 18, what assessment he has made of the sectors most likely to cease trading to avoid tariffs in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290703","290703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145836","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Governor of the Bank of England on when the Governor's term of office ends.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290812","290812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145837","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Office of National Statistics to ensure that the religious classification of Jainism is not confused with the term Hindu; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290596","290596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145838","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to ensure that public sector services operate to the same (a) deadlines and (b) penalties as private sector contractors on (i) fully and (ii) partially publicly funded projects.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290813","290813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145839","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his timescale is for assessing the appointability of the  shortlisted candidates for the position of Bank of England Governor that were submitted to his predecessor.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290814","290814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145840","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the results of the regulation of pre-paid funeral plans consultation.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290815","290815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145841","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make an assessment of the financial effect on disabled people of the replacement of six income-related benefits with universal credit; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290597","290597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145842","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has received legal advice on the compliance of the Get ready for Brexit campaign with the European Union (Withdrawal) (No. 2) Act 2019.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290816","290816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145843","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what additional staffing resources his Department has received in the last 12 months to support learning on managing Official Development Assistance across Government.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291047","291047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145844","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he has taken to amend the Get Ready for Brexit advertising campaign as a result of the European Union (Withdrawal) (No. 2) Act 2019.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290817","290817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145845","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Reported road casualties Great Britain, main results: 2018, published on 25 July 2019, what recent steps he has taken to decrease the number of people killed on the roads.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291048","291048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145846","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Reported road casualties Great Britain, main results: 2018, published on 25 July 2019, what recent steps he has taken to decrease the number of people seriously injured on the roads.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291049","291049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145847","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps she has taken to encourage companies operating in the UK to ensure that workers throughout its supply chain are paid a living wage.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291050","291050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145848","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will suspend the 2019 Loan Charge while the review of that charge is ongoing.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290818","290818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145849","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the (a) research and (b) reports that her Department has commissioned and requested on (i) the Sikh community and (ii) Sikh groups and organisations in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291051","291051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145850","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on developing countries of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291052","291052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145851","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff in his Department are deployed to other Departments and working on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291053","291053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145852","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, to which Departments staff in his Department are seconded and transferred as a result of preparations for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291054","291054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145853","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department’s response to the 10th report of the Home Affairs Select Committee 2017-19 HC 515: Policing for the future, CP62, published 15 March 2019, page 22, what the expected publication date is of the updated Missing Children and Adults Strategy.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290819","290819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145854","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment the Department has made of the cost to police forces of dealing with missing persons cases in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290820","290820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145855","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department has taken to prevent third-party universal credit fraud.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291055","291055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145856","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many third parties who have allegedly scammed people into making a universal credit claim have been identified and investigated; and how many of those third parties have been referred for prosecution.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291056","291056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145857","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of local authorities using the Town and Country Planning (General Permitted Development) Order 1995 Article 4 powers to restrict the number of Houses in Multiple Occupation in defined areas.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290821","290821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145858","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish (a) the most up-to-date version of the 1 August 2019 Operation Yellowhammer document and (b) the dates on which each version of that document was circulated; what the distribution list is for that document; and for what reasons the assumptions in each version changed.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291057","291057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145859","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of the UK leaving the EU without a deal that cannot be mitigated; and what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the UK of those unmitigated effects.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291058","291058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145860","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment has been made of the potential effect on the domestic fuel industry of the UK leaving the EU without a deal; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291059","291059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145861","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the availability of child and adolescent psychoanalytic psychotherapists in (a) England, (b) the West Midlands and (c) Birmingham.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291060","291060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145862","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of violence in prisons.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290639","290639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145863","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the merits of reducing the retirement age for prisons officers.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290640","290640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145864","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many additional police officers she plans to fund through the Uplift operation for each policy force by 31 March 2021.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290654","290654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145865","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether it is her Department's policy to develop new nuclear power stations.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290822","290822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145866","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to encourage (a) ports and (b) transport companies involved in the movement of plastic (i) pellets and (ii) nurdles to sign up to the British Plastics Federation’s industry-led scheme Operation Clean Sweep to reduce the loss of plastic pellets in transit.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290823","290823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145867","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what research her Department has commissioned into the effect on human health of ingesting (a) micro- and (b) nano-plastics that have found their way into the food chain.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290824","290824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145868","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what formula her Department plans to use to allocate (a) the initial 6,000 officers and (b) subsequent officers to territorial policing as set out in the 2019 Spending Review.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290825","290825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145869","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many energy smart meters in the UK are currently operating in dumb mode.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290826","290826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145870","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate she has made of the number of violent incidents against prison officers in prisons in each of last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290641","290641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145871","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Child Maintenance Service complaints were made by paying parents in relation to income data not being used to calculate payments; and what proportion of those complaints were upheld in the last three years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290827","290827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145872","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to improve the UK’s Ocean Health Index score.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290828","290828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145873","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Spending Review 2019, how the 20,000 officers pledged will be allocated between the territorial police forces, counter-terrorism policing and serious and organised crime.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290829","290829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145874","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that all mental health units provide their vulnerable patients with a good level of care.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290642","290642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145875","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress has been made on analysing the results of the consultation on introducing a Deposit Return Scheme for plastic drinks containers in England, Wales and Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290830","290830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145876","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much of the Plastics and Waste Investment Fund has been allocated to date; and which programmes have received money from that fund.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290831","290831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145877","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Spending Review 2019, 1.4 Tackling Crime, how many and what proportion of the 2,000 officers planned to be recruited in the current (a) calendar year and (b) financial year will be (i) additional posts and (b) replacements for existing vacancies.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290832","290832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145878","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken was to process a mandatory reconsideration for personal independence payment in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290833","290833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145879","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the maximum time taken was to process a mandatory reconsideration for personal independence payment in the last 12 months for which information is available.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290834","290834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145880","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that personal independence payment rejection letters are empathetic.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290835","290835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145881","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many paying parents are in maintenance arrears through the Child Maintenance Service; and how much unpaid maintenance remains outstanding in Dunfermline and West Fife constituency.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290836","290836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145882","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason Regulation 4(1) of the Child Support (Child Support Maintenance) Calculations Regulations 2012 provides that a relevant tax year for the calculation of child maintenance by a paying parent is any one of the six years immediately preceding the date of request and not the most recent year for which tax data is available.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290837","290837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145883","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of UK citizens that have a right to healthcare cover in the EU (a) have applied for that cover and (b) are receiving that cover.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290838","290838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145884","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the time taken for benefit claimants to receive decision letters containing a four week deadline for appeal by post; and what assessment she has made of the effect of postal delays on the time available for claimants to make an appeal.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290839","290839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145885","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of Child Maintenance Service income challenges by paying parents were as a result of private pension payments not being deducted from income calculations.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290840","290840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145886","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of Army recruits who take sick leave return to work to complete their training; and what the average length of absence is.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290841","290841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145887","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress her Department has made on implementing small-scale DAB radio.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290842","290842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145888","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the Save the Children report entitled Transformative Aid.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291061","291061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145889","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to help strengthen the tax systems of developing countries.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291062","291062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145890","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reason his Department ended funding for the National Ophthalmology Database audit.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290843","290843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145891","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timeframe is for the conclusion of the discussions with the General Dental Council on increasing capacity for the Overseas Registration Exam.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291063","291063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145892","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has plans to undertake a review of the Parole Board guidance on remorse shown by an offender following the release of Vanessa George.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291064","291064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145893","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans she has to encourage companies operating in the UK to provide public and transparent lists of sites in other countries that manufacture their products.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291065","291065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145894","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans she has to encourage companies operating in the UK to ensure workers throughout its supply chain are able to engage in collective bargaining.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291066","291066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145895","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish details of Access to Work spending by region.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291067","291067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145896","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking to help ensure that UK nationals living in EU states who have applied for but not yet been issued with an S1 certificate by HMRC can access (a) routine and (b) emergency healthcare.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290844","290844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145897","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to encourage financial institutions to adopt investment policies which consider (a) human and (b) labour rights.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291068","291068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145898","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he will take to monitor the performance of ophthalmology services in the event of the cessation of the National Ophthalmology Database audit.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290845","290845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145899","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to monitor availability of provision in catract surgery after funding of the National Ophthalmology Database ceases.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290846","290846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145900","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, for what reason all leaseholders of buildings with Aluminium Composite Cladding must sign a State Aid Declaration for the building to be eligible to apply to his Department's private sector ACM cladding remediation fund.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290847","290847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145901","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the of Answer 23 July 2019 to Question 279062 on Buildings: Insulation, whether any burning had begun in large scale test in June 2019 that was aborted due to procedural issues.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290848","290848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145902","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what legislation or guidelines determine who should pay the cost of counsel when a court case is adjourned the night before that trial is scheduled to take place.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290849","290849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145903","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if his Department will publish a full report on the tests undertaken by the Building Research Establishment on behalf of his Department.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290850","290850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145904","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS England’s Commissioning Excellent Nutrition and Hydration 2015-2018 guidance, published on 8 October 2015, what progress he has made on the commissioning of a workforce to reduce the burden of malnutrition and dehydration through (a) identification, (b) prevention and (c) intervention.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291069","291069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145905","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to conduct further large-scale fire safety tests on High Pressure Laminate Cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290851","290851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145906","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many patients readmitted to hospital within (a) zero to seven and (b) eight to 180 days were recorded as suffering malnutrition as a (i) primary or (ii) secondary condition (a) in each of the last 10 years and (b) in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291070","291070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145907","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the findings of the video recording pilot for personal independence payments assessments will be made available.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290852","290852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145908","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the answer of 6 August 2019 to Question 280423, what is the remit of the review of national standards for healthcare food for patients staff and visitors started by the Healthcare Food Standards and Strategy Group in July 2018; when the review is intended to be completed; and whether the findings of the review will be publicly available.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291071","291071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145909","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the answer of 6 August 2019 to Question 280423, how the Hospital Food Review, announced on 23 August 2019, if he will take into account findings from the review by the Healthcare Food Standards and Strategy Group into the national standards for healthcare food for patients staff and visitors.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291072","291072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145910","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of delays in universal credit tribunal hearings on claimants seeking an appeal; and what the average waiting is for an appeal to be heard.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290853","290853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145911","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will list the members of the task group undertaking the Hospital Food Review launched in August 2019.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291073","291073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145912","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the intended timescale for the Hospital Food Review announced on 23 August 2019; and what organisations outside the NHS involved in the provision of food including medical foods will be consulted in the review.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291074","291074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145913","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, in light of recent fires involving timber construction materials, whether his Department plans to issue an advice note on the use of timber on the external walls of high-rise buildings.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290854","290854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145914","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of deaths in England with a (a) primary and (b) secondary cause of malnutrition in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291075","291075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145915","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent progress has been made on the review of the 2019 Loan Charge.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290855","290855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145916","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to commission a large scale fire safety test on systems incorporating timber cladding.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290856","290856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145917","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to suspend the 2019 Loan Charge for the duration of the review of that charge.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290857","290857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145918","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department plans to respond to the call for evidence on Building Bulletin 100: Design for Fire Safety in Schools, (BB100).","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290858","290858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145919","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department have made of the average life expectancy of rough sleepers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291076","291076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145920","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans he has to establish a requirement for countries in receipt of Overseas Development Assistance for health to make measurable progress towards committing five per cent of GDP to health spending.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290572","290572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145921","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of times police forces in England have been called to children's homes.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290859","290859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145922","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of UK companies are not required by HMRC to submit tax returns.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291077","291077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145923","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to help strengthen the tax systems of developing countries.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290573","290573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145924","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has spent from the public purse on tackling poor air quality in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290860","290860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145925","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent from the public purse on the badger cull in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290861","290861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145926","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has spent from the public purse on tree planting in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290862","290862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145927","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate HMRC has made of the number of dormant companies in the UK.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291078","291078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145928","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made on resolving the pay dispute at the Environment Agency.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290863","290863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145929","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect of fracking on trends in the level of methane emissions.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290864","290864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145930","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to protect farmers from imported food that is produced to lower environmental and animal welfare standards in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290865","290865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145931","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance her Department has issued to livestock transport companies on the welfare of animals in the event of delays to freight crossing to and from the EU if the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290866","290866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145932","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance her Department has issued to food transport companies on the effect on food quality and safety of delays to freight crossing to and from the EU in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290867","290867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145933","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the conclusions of the Save the Children report, Transformative Aid: How UK aid can transform global development and children’s futures.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290574","290574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145934","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many successful prosecutions there have been for hare coursing in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290868","290868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145935","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to review wildlife crime penalties.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290869","290869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145936","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to increase the funding to Natural England.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290870","290870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145937","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure rivers in England will be compliant with water quality standards by 2027.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290871","290871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145938","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to detect errors in data submitted to the UK Pollutant Release and Transfer Register.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290872","290872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145939","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2019 to Question 282339, in what circumstances would a prisoner serving a sentence be eligible to apply to the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290873","290873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145940","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2019 to Question 282339, how many prisoners have applied to the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290874","290874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145941","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 September 2019 to Question 282339 on Young Offenders: EU Nationals, whether EEA national prisoners' relatives who are third country nationals are eligible to apply to the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290875","290875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145942","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2019 to Question 252533, when her Department will publish the Data Protection Impact Assessment and Policy Equality Statement for the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290876","290876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145943","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government guidance entitled How the automated check calculates the period of residence, for what reason caseworkers are not shown information about an applicant's employment, pension or benefits.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290877","290877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145944","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government guidance entitled How your personal information is used within the Borders, Immigration and Citizenship System, if she will publish the memoranda of understanding between her Department and authorities and organisations outside the EEA on data sharing for settled status applications.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290878","290878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145945","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Government guidance entitled EU Settlement Scheme: how we use your personal information, if she will publish a list of organisations with whom the Government has shared the personal information of EU Settlement Scheme applicants.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290879","290879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145946","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the sharing of personal information of an EU Settlement Scheme applicant with an external organisation, if she will publish the criteria by which her Department judges whether an external organisation has taken sufficient steps to protect personal information shared with them.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290880","290880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145947","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will publish data sharing agreements with external organisations relating to the EU Settlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290881","290881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145948","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 May 2019 to Question 254812 on Immigration: EU Nationals, what the criteria and process is that her Department uses to determine whether staff require access to data in order to carry out their duties; and who in her Department is responsible for making that decision in each case.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290882","290882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145949","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has held with his counterparts in (a) the Government of Saudi Arabia and (b) the Government of Yemen on (i) opening Sana’a International airport, (ii) implementing a UN Verification and Inspection Mechanism to facilitate traffic through the airport and (iii) facilitating direct international flights for aid workers, journalists, humanitarian aid and seriously ill people.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290646","290646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145950","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to open direct talks with the Houthi leadership in Sana’a to find a solution to the conflict in Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290647","290647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145951","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support local authorities to deliver Pre-exposure prophylaxis (PrEP) for HIV.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291079","291079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145952","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has held with his Saudi Arabian and Government of Yemen counterparts on holding direct talks with the Houthi leadership to broker a nationwide ceasefire; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290648","290648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145953","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has held with his (a) Saudi Arabian, (b) Emirati and (c) Government of Yemen counterparts to facilitate access for the UN Humans Rights Council Panel of Eminent Experts to all regions of Yemen including Sana’a.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290649","290649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145954","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2019 to Question 285061, how many offices the NHS Business Service Authority has in the (a) North East and (b) North West.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290694","290694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145955","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children in primary schools in Wallasey constituency were eligible for free school meals in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290695","290695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145956","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate he has made of the operability of urban water and sanitation plants by each governorate in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290650","290650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145957","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the letter of 16 September 2019 from the Secretary of State for International Trade letter to the chair of the Committees on Arms Export Controls, when his Department knew that RSLF troops were deployed in Yemen.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291080","291080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145958","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships starts there were in Wallasey constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290696","290696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145959","2019-09-30","Attorney General","2019-09-25","To ask the Attorney General, how much was spent by the UK Government in undertaking legal action in the (a) Cherry and others (Respondents) v Advocate General for Scotland (Appellant) (Scotland), (b) R (on the application of Miller) (Appellant) v The Prime Minister (Respondent) in the Supreme Court, (c) case number CO/3385/2019 in the High Court, (d) reclaiming motion by Joanna Cherry QC MP and others against the Advocate General in the Outer Court of Scotland and (e) (First) Joanna Cherry QC MP and others for judicial review in the Outer Court of Scotland cases.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290699","290699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145960","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate he has made of the proportion of Yemeni Government workers by each Governorate in receipt of salary payments; and what the regularity of those payments is.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290651","290651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145961","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children in secondary schools in Wallasey eligible for free school meals went on to higher education in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290697","290697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145962","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate he has made of the (a) monetary value and (b) tonnage of commercial imports of (i) food, (ii) fuel, (iii) medical supplies and (iv) essential materials awaiting transshipment using letters of credit issued by the Government of Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290652","290652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145963","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Minister of State for Crime, Policing and the Fire Service has met representatives of the Merseyside Fire and Rescue Service.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290698","290698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145964","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to her Department's announcement entitled New boost to increase diversity in nation’s cyber security industry published on 14 August 2019, what target her Department has set on the number of people who will be assisted by the third round of funding from the Cyber Skills Immediate Impact Fund.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291081","291081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145965","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 22 July 2019 to Question 277853, whether her Department has set a timescale for the publication of guidance on the use of DNS over HTTPS.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291082","291082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145966","2019-09-30","Department for International Trade","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps she plans to take to ensure that her Department does not violate the court order on banning the issuing of new export licences to Saudi Arabia and its coalition partners for arms that could be used in Yemen.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291083","291083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145967","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent communications he has received from each Gov.UK Verify provider on their continued participation in the scheme.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291084","291084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145968","2019-09-30","Department for International Trade","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to the Secretary of State’s letter of 16 September 2019 to the Chair of the Committees on Arms Export Controls, what steps the Government is taking to review the way in which information is exchanged with the Joint Export Control Unit.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290582","290582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145969","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Secretary of State for International Trade’s letter of 16 September 2019 to the Chair of the Committees on Arms Export Control, when the British Embassy in Riyadh became aware that Royal Saudi Land Forces were operational in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290583","290583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145970","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2019 to Question 285406 on Offensive Weapons Act 2019, what additional resources he plans to provide to the police to ensure that they are able to enforce that legislation.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291085","291085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145971","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many administrative penalties her Department has levied on individuals who have reported they have been a victim of universal credit fraud.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291086","291086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145972","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in how many interviews under caution have individuals who have reported they have been a victim of universal credit fraud had a legal representative to accompany them.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291087","291087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145973","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many administrative penalties her Department has levied on victims of universal credit fraud who attended interviews under caution and who were accompanied by legal representatives.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291088","291088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145974","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what cooperation and sharing of information takes place between HMRC and Companies House on dormant companies.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291089","291089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145975","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many interviews under caution have been held with victims of universal credit fraud.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291090","291090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145976","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if his Department will take steps to change reporting on criminalisation data on children in care to all children in care and not just children who were in care for at least 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290883","290883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145977","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of applying Ofsted regulation to semi-independent accommodation for 16 and 17 year olds in care.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290884","290884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145978","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the NHS on NHS spending following media reports on 8 September 2019 that the NHS is to review the ban on single women receiving fertility treatment.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291091","291091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145979","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has make of the accuracy of the Saudi Press Agency release of 14 September 2018 that stated that an RSLF helicopter crashed on operations in in Al-Mahra province in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290584","290584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145980","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of social media on vulnerable children and young people.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290885","290885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145981","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to meet the Prime Minister's pledge for full-fibre broadband for all by 2025, including in Hampshire.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291092","291092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145982","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of allowing NHS-funded care home residents with long-term health conditions to claim benefits.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290603","290603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145983","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for its policies of the recent report by the Royal United Services Institute and Save the Children, The UK Strategy on Protection of Civilians.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290886","290886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145984","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that routine decision making for a foster child is delegated to their carers as set out in the Children Act 1989, Guidance and Regulations: Section 3.188 revised in 2013.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290887","290887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145985","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the review of the Protection of Civilians Strategy, if he will include civilian (a) casualty recording and (b) harm-tracking mechanisms in the Protection of Civilians Strategy.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290888","290888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145986","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to strengthen support for mechanisms enabling perpetrators to be held accountable for violations of international humanitarian and human rights law.","Biography information for Stephen Crabb","Stephen Crabb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290889","290889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145987","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Secretary of State for Trade’s letter of 16 September 2019 to the Chair of the Committees on Arms Export Control, for what reasons the Department for International Trade and Ministry of Defence were not immediately informed that the Royal Saudi Land Forces were operational in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290585","290585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145988","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the availability of adrenaline auto-injectors.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291093","291093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145989","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that environmentalism is in the National Curriculum; and what guidance his Department provides on teaching about climate change.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291094","291094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145990","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what (a) assessment he has made of the effect of reports of arbitrary indefinite detention in Kashmir and (b) representations the Government has made to the Government of (a) India and (b) Pakistan on the human rights of Kashmir residents.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291095","291095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145991","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support he is offering to provide for relief and reconstruction for people affected by the 5.8 magnitude earthquake near the town of Jhelum in Kashmir.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290890","290890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145992","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2019 to Question 285402 and the 2019 Spending Review, what additional funding will be allocated for (a) walking and (b) cycling to meet Government targets for levels of activity in those areas.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291096","291096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145993","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of invoices received by the NHS are paid within 30 days; and how many incur 29 per cent interest for late payment of more than 30 days.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290600","290600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145994","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row Q of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 46 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published in May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading Operations Service Personnel Staff Cost.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290891","290891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145995","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row R of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 46 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published in May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading Operations and Peacekeeping Civilian Personnel Staff Costs.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290892","290892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145996","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row S of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 47 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published in May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading Operations Infrastructure Costs.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290893","290893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145997","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row T of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 47 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published in May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading Operations Inventory Consumption.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290894","290894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145998","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate her Department has made of the processing times for applications made for statutory maternity pay.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290672","290672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1145999","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row U of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 47 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published in May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading Operations Equipment Support Costs.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290895","290895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146000","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department has taken to tackle the disability pay gap in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290896","290896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146001","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of disabled adults of working age in (i) England, (ii) Wales and (iii) Scotland received support from the Access to Work grant scheme in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290897","290897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146002","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate she has made of the disability employment gap in her Department.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290898","290898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146003","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employees left employment in her Department due to (a) disability and (b) long-term health conditions in (i) 2016, (ii) 2017 and (iii) 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290899","290899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146004","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has implemented the voluntary reporting framework on disability, mental health and well-being in the workplace introduced in November 2018.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290900","290900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146005","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row AA of the table entitled Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 47 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published on 9 May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading Defence Capability DE&S DEL Costs.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291097","291097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146006","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row AB of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 47 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published on 9 May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading War Pension Benefits Programme Costs.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291098","291098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146007","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row AC of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 47 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published in May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading Conflict, Stability and Security Fund.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291099","291099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146008","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row AD of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 47 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the Cash Release of Provisions Administration Costs.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291100","291100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146009","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to mitigate for the effect of potential price rises in fuel and food for low-income families in the North West in the event the UK leaving the EU with no deal.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290687","290687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146010","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment she has made of the effect of leaving the EU without a deal on the availability of jobs in a) the automotive industry, b) the pharmaceutical industry and c) the retail industry in Garston and Halewood constituency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290688","290688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146011","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will undertake an independent evaluation on what the evidential basis is for his Department's proposed test standard of BS 7176 for school noticeboards and if he will publish the results of that evaluation.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290604","290604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146012","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the annual revenue raised by Clause 16 and Schedule 4 of the Finance Act 2018.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291101","291101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146013","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to notify local education authorities and other approved education providers of their duties under the ESFA Output Specification Annex 3 Section 7.1.1.5  relating to fire standards and school notice boards.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290605","290605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146014","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent meetings (a) Ministers and (b) Officials in her Department have had with businesses in the (i) automotive (ii) pharmaceutical (iii) retail and food sector businesses about the impact of leaving the EU without a deal on their businesses; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290689","290689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146015","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to make the Fire and Rescue Services and other approved fire inspectors aware of their duties to ensure that school notice boards are fire compliant; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290606","290606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146016","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the additional revenue that would be generated by including corporation tax in the extension of offshore time limits.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291102","291102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146017","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have applied for settled status under the EU Settlement Scheme in (a) UK and (b) Garston and Halewood constituency.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290690","290690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146018","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been deemed eligible for settled status under the EU Settlement Scheme in (a) the UK and (b) Garston and Halewood constituency to date.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290691","290691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146019","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to extend the eligibility for settled status under the EU Settlement Scheme for EU citizens who have been in the UK for many years and can financially sustain themselves but do not work.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290692","290692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146020","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have (a) successfully obtained and (b) been denied settled status under the EU Settlement Scheme in (i) Garston and Halewood Constituency, (ii) Liverpool and (iii) the UK.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290693","290693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146021","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to review universal credit assessment periods when claimants receive two paychecks within the same assessment period due to a change of employer.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291103","291103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146022","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has recently conducted a risk assessment of its own capabilities to support a snap election.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290655","290655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146023","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to encourage the modernisation of train carriages.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291104","291104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146024","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of using the Charity Commission Section 72 mechanism to consolidate the five Acts of Parliament governing the Malvern Hills Trust into one new piece of legislation.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290901","290901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146025","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress has been made on developing large-scale electricity storage solutions.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291105","291105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146026","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many members of staff will be allocated to work for the Office for Veterans' Affairs.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290656","290656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146027","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what incentives have been put in place to support businesses in developing and implementing sustainable business practices.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291106","291106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146028","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason parts of Operation Yellowhammer: HMG Reasonable Worst Case Planning Assumptions, published on 11 September 2019 are redacted; and whether he plans to publish those redacted parts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290657","290657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146029","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to announce to Parliament the identity of the individual selected to be the next Governor of the Bank of England.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290902","290902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146030","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the newly created role of Chief Digital Information Officer will replace the unfilled role of Chief Data Officer.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290658","290658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146031","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the armed forces will be used to police civil unrest in the event that the scenarios outlined in Operation Yellowhammer: HMG Reasonable Worst Case Planning Assumptions occur.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290659","290659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146032","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2019 to Question 284212, how her Department plans to treat late applications to the EU Settlement Scheme from people who do not have reasonable grounds for missing the deadline.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291107","291107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146033","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to ensure all UK aid projects are environmentally sustainable.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291108","291108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146034","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Rapid Response Unit is involved in the Get ready for Brexit campaign.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290660","290660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146035","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row V of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 47 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published in May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading Operations Other Costs and Services.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290903","290903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146036","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row W of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 47 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published in May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading Operations Receipts and other Income.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290904","290904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146037","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row X of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 47 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published in May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading Operations Capital Single Use Military Equipment.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290905","290905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146038","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Department is taking to promote the building of (a) passive houses and (b) eco-homes.","Biography information for Gillian Keegan","Gillian Keegan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291109","291109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146039","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row Y of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 47 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published in May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading Non-Departmental Public Bodies Costs (net).","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290906","290906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146040","2019-09-30","Ministry of Defence","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to row Z of the table headed Spending in Departmental Expenditure Limits on page 47 of the Central Government Supply Estimates 2019-20: Main Supply Estimates, published in May 2019, if he will publish a breakdown of the spending allocation under the heading Defence Capability Admin Service Personnel Costs.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290907","290907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146041","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to update the Highway Code; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290908","290908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146042","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, how long supplies of toilet paper will last in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290909","290909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146043","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to establish a dedicated enquiry line for members' offices to discuss applications made by constituents to the EU Settlement Scheme; and whether the staff of the UKVI enquiry line will be given access to EU Settlement Scheme applications to discuss such applications with members' offices.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291110","291110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146044","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what advice he has provided to local authorities on the effect of speed bumps on air pollution; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290910","290910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146045","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the average time for calls to the EU Settlement Resolution Centre to be answered.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291111","291111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146046","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the number of contracting roles that will be lost to the UK economy as a result of the roll-out of the off-payroll rules.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290598","290598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146047","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on pay rates of the roll-out of the off-payroll rules.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290599","290599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146048","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much (a) residential, (b) commercial and (c) industrial waste originating in England has been sent for processing in Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290911","290911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146049","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the effect on consumer energy bills will be in each year of operation of a regulated asset base agreement for the proposed Sizewell C nuclear power station (a) prior to electricity production and (b) after electricity production has started.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290553","290553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146050","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support her Department is providing to (a) pilots and (b) cabin crew affected by the liquidation of Thomas Cook.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290912","290912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146051","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many British National (Overseas) passports issued to people from Hong Kong remain valid.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290665","290665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146052","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his (a) Saudi Arabian and (b) Emirati counterparts on the airstrike on a mosque in Al Sawad, Amran Governorate in Yemen on 23 September; and if he will make it his policy to support an independent investigation into that airstrike.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290586","290586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146053","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the  effect of Operation Transmission on the operation of the Port of Portsmouth in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290575","290575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146054","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his (a) Saudi Arabian and (b) Emirati counterparts on the two airstrikes on civilian residences in Al Fakher, Al Dhale’e Governorate in Yemen on 24 September; and if he will make it his policy to support an independent investigation into those airstrikes.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290587","290587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146055","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment his Department has made of the humanitarian effect of the recent escalation of military activity in Al-Daleh province, Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290588","290588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146056","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the implications for her policies of the Sustain Alliance’s report entitled, Brexit food resilience for the people who need it most; and what steps her Department has taken to establish a hardship fund to ensure that vulnerable people are not affected by the disruption highlighted in (a) that report and (b) Operation Yellowhammer.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290576","290576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146057","2019-09-30","Attorney General","2019-09-25","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the legal cases in relation to the prorogation of Parliament.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290577","290577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146058","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether it is the Government's policy to support the renewal and strengthening of the mandate of the UN Human Rights Council Group of Eminent Experts to investigate violations of human rights and humanitarian law in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290589","290589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146059","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Iranian counterpart on Iran's involvement in the conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290590","290590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146060","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessments he has made of the barriers to 3 network customers connecting to the 101 service due to tariff issues.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291112","291112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146061","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of trends in health visitor recruitment in (a) the UK, (b) Teesside, and (c) Stockton South constituency.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291113","291113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146062","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans his Department has to work with the NHS and other partners in primary and community care to increase health visitor numbers in (a) the UK, (b) Teesside, and (c) Stockton South constituency.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291114","291114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146063","2019-09-30","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, for what reasons the UK Government rejected the Scottish Government's proposals for the UK to remain in the Single Market and Customs Union, as set out in its 2016 paper, Scotland's place in Europe.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290913","290913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146064","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons there has been a change to permitted levels of gaseous tritium discharges at former Magnox Nuclear Stations as a result of the operation of the waste encapsulation plants.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290607","290607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146065","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what meetings her Department has had with Northumbrian Water to discuss preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291115","291115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146066","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what meetings her Department has had with the bioethanol industry to discuss preparations for the UK leaving the EU without a withdrawal agreement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291116","291116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146067","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether reference copies of statutory instruments are available in hard copy via the public library service; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290608","290608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146068","2019-09-30","Department for International Trade","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if she will ensure that the NHS is not included in a trade deal with the US Administration; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290914","290914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146069","2019-09-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to continue to provide funding for the Football Association Parklife project.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290609","290609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146070","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer HMG Reasonable Worst Case Planning Assumptions paragraph 13, what assessment she has made of which nations and regions of the UK are at the highest risk of increased public disorder and community tensions.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290704","290704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146071","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to make an announcement on the updating of the NICE guidelines for the diagnosis and treatment of (a) pernicious anaemia and (b) autoimmune metaplastic atrophic gastritis.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290610","290610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146072","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the Government plans to publish its response to the Farm Inspection and Regulation Review, published on 13 December 2018.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290611","290611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146073","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Operation Yellowhammer HMG Reasonable Worst Case Planning Assumptions paragraph 13, what assessment she has made of the operational capacity of (a) North Wales Police and (b) every other territorial police force to appropriately respond to increased public disorder and community tensions in the event that the UK leaves with EU without a deal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290705","290705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146074","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 August 2019 to Question 280135 on Agriculture: Subsidies, if she will publish a list of the 46 pilots which have been signed up to the Environmental Land Management Scheme; and whether those pilots are receiving financial compensation for taking part in that scheme.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290612","290612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146075","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role the troika of UK, US and Norway has had in Sudan’s constitutional settlement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290613","290613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146076","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2019 to Question 285042 on Large Goods Vehicles: EU Countries, which historic bilateral agreements are (a) most and (b) least likely to be carried over after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290578","290578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146077","2019-09-30","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when Ministers and officials of his Department last met with representatives of the UK automotive sector; and what assessment he has made of what Government assistance that sector will require in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290579","290579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146078","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of (a) his Department's and (b) others liability should medicine shortages, outlined in the Yellowhammer document, lead to preventable deaths.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290580","290580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146079","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has discussed term limits for governing and elected officials in Sudan with (a) military leaders and (b) civilian members of the (i) sovereign council and (ii) legislative council and (c) Ministers of that country.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290614","290614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146080","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Sudanese counterpart on the process of appointing a new President in that country.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290615","290615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146081","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he has taken since 14 August 2019 to ensure that human rights violators from Sudan do not enter the UK.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290616","290616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146082","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will increase her Department's grant to Gloucestershire constabulary to pay for the cost of additional police officers recruited as a result of her policies; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290621","290621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146083","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the troika of the US, UK and Norway has made to the new governing coalition in Sudan on tackling breaches of law and order in Darfur.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290617","290617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146084","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will increase the grant to Gloucestershire constabulary so that its reliance on local precepts is no greater than that of metropolitan areas; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290622","290622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146085","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of religious freedom and tolerance in Eritrea.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290618","290618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146086","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to avoid a recession in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290915","290915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146087","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the number of Eritrean troops fighting in Yemen.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290619","290619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146088","2019-09-30","Department for International Development","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Government's report on Investing in a better world: results of UK survey on financing the SDGs, what steps he is taking to increase public awareness of the UN Sustainable Development Goals.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291117","291117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146089","2019-09-30","Attorney General","2019-09-25","To ask the Attorney General, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the Crown Prosecution Service's complaince with legislation and guidance relating to the avoidance of unnecessary prosecution of children and young people who have been groomed, exploited or trafficked as part of county lines criminal activity.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290916","290916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146090","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to monitor projected changes in the environmental costs of a third runway at Heathrow airport.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290917","290917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146091","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will reconsider the £30,000 salary threshold for immigrant workers.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290918","290918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146092","2019-09-30","Attorney General","2019-09-25","To ask the Attorney General, what support he is providing to the Crown Prosecution Service to ensure that Modern Slavery Act 2015 provisions and associated guidance relating to the avoidance of unnecessary prosecution of children and young people who have been groomed, exploited or trafficked as part of county lines criminal activity is followed in full.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290919","290919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146093","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the level of adherence by police forces to legislation and guidance relating to the avoidance of unnecessary prosecution of children and young people who have been groomed, exploited or trafficked as part of county lines criminal activity.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290920","290920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146094","2019-09-30","Prime Minister","2019-09-25","To ask the Prime Minister, which (a) people and (b) businesses applying for Government funding he has provided advice to in each of the last five years; and what advice he has provided.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290921","290921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146095","2019-09-30","Home Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will not impose any restrictions on the number of seasonal agricultural workers coming to Scotland.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290922","290922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146096","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, what advice is provided to senior civil servants on the proper disciplinary approach to take towards civil servants who have been found not to have declared personal interests with an applicant for discretionary public funds where they are involved in the decision-making process.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290923","290923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146097","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of provision of teaching of financial literacy in secondary schools.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290924","290924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146098","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the availability of primary school places in (a) Woking constituency and (b) Surrey.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290925","290925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146099","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the report of the All Party Parliamentary Group for Runaway and Missing Children and Adults entitled, No place at home, published in September 2019, if his Department will allocated resources to local authorities in areas with high rates of county lines grooming and exploitation to ensure the provision of (a) in-area placements and (b) accommodation to children and young people (i) involved in and (ii) vulnerable to county lines criminal exploitation through (A) children’s services, (B) social housing services and (C) temporary and emergency housing.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290926","290926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146100","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans his Department has to ensure an adequate number of places at secondary schools in Surrey.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290927","290927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146101","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the benefits of the construction of a second runway at Gatwick airport; and what comparative assessment he has made of those benefits with proposals to build a third runway at Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290928","290928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146102","2019-09-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps she has taken to support businesses in Woking constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290929","290929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146103","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of grade inflation in (a) GCSEs and (b) A Levels since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290930","290930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146104","2019-09-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to create new community land trusts.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290931","290931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146105","2019-09-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role his Department plays in the prevention of human trafficking.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290932","290932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146106","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 September 2019 to Question 281567 on Children: Day Care, to which constituencies the £9.1 million was allocated.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290628","290628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146107","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 September 2019 to Question 281570 on Children: Day Care, how many local authority areas did not meet the duty to provide sufficient childcare in the latest period for which data is available.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290629","290629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146108","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2019 to Question 278348 on Pupils: Disadvantaged, whether he has made an assessment of trends in the level of attainment of children whose families are in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290630","290630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146109","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2019 to Question 278350 on Children: Day Care, how many short breaks local authorities provided for disabled children and their families in each (a) region and (b) local authority area in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290631","290631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146110","2019-09-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when the Government plans to publish its Green Paper on improving social care.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290933","290933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146111","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2019 to Question 278353 on Schools: Charitable Donations, how the income generated by schools is distributed across schools.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290632","290632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146112","2019-09-30","Northern Ireland Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps he is taking to restore the Northern Ireland Assembly.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290934","290934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146113","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2019 to Question 278353 on Schools: Charitable Donations, what the income was in cash terms from (a) donations and (b) voluntary funds in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290633","290633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146114","2019-09-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will investigate reports of badger culling within the FERA Woodchester Park research centre.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290620","290620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146115","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2019 to Question 278353 on Schools: Charitable Donations, what the income was in cash terms that was generated by schools in each Parliamentary constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290634","290634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146116","2019-09-30","Department for Education","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much apprenticeship levy was paid by levy employers in (a) May 2017 and expired in May 2019, (b) June 2017 and expired in June 2019, (c) July 2017 and expired in July 2019 and (d) August 2017 and expired in August 2019 because the funds had not been used.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290935","290935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146117","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the cost to UK business of the roll-out of the off-payroll rules to the private sector.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290936","290936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146118","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the number of contracting roles that will potentially be lost to the UK economy from the roll-out of the off-payroll rules.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290937","290937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146119","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the public sector of the off-payroll rules.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290938","290938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146120","2019-09-30","Treasury","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on rates of pay of the off-payroll roll-out.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290939","290939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146121","2019-09-30","Ministry of Justice","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the longest waiting time was in weeks for a trial where the defendant entered a not guilty plea for rape in each Crown Court in England and Wales in (a) 2010 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290940","290940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146122","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information her Department holds on reductions to deductions for claimants of universal credit in latest period for which data is available.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290635","290635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146123","2019-09-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of universal credit received a (a) budgeting loan and (b) deferral period in the latest period for which data is available.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290636","290636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146124","2019-09-30","Cabinet Office","2019-09-25","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster and Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish all the steps taken by the Government to mitigate the effects of the UK leaving the EU without a deal since 24 July 2019.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291118","291118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1146125","2019-09-30","Department for Transport","2019-09-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the air passenger contribution charge for ATOL protection will increase as a result of the collapse of Thomas Cook.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291119","291119"
