"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452450","2016-02-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25988, on Palestinian radicalism, what recent reports he has received on incitement to commit violence by the Palestinian Authority.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27191","27191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452451","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to encourage the government of Bangladesh to improve (a) working conditions, (b) safety standards and (c) pay in clothes factories used by international companies in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27155","27155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452452","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25979, which 10 Israeli NGOs receive funding from the Conflict Stability and Security Fund; and which two NGOs receive funds through the Bilateral Programme Budgets.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27124","27124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452453","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with his EU counterparts the EU undertaking a rule of law procedure against Hungary; and what representations he is making to his counterparts on recent reforms by the Hungarian government.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27146","27146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452454","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on preparations for the EU referendum.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27161","27161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452455","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the comment made on 22 January 2016 by the UN Special Rapporteur on the situation of human rights in the Democratic People's Republic of Korea.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27072","27072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452456","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for its policies of the recommendations of the UN Commission of Inquiry on human rights in North Korea, published in February 2014.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27073","27073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452457","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will provide assistance to farmers in Zimbabwe who are forced from their land by the policies of the government of that country.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27043","27043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452458","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether a Minister from his Department plans to attend the high-level meeting on global responsibility sharing through pathways for admission of Syrian refugees hosted by UNHRC in Geneva on 30 March 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27045","27045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452459","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the recital in paragraph one of section C of the revised version of the draft EU decision on a new settlement for the UK, what assessment he has made of whether the objectives of political integration enjoys wide support in the union.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27033","27033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452460","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she intends to answer the letter to her dated 4 January 2016 with regard to Ms J. Ellis.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26983","26983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452461","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons the Advisory Group on Freedom of Religion and Belief was not re-established after the 2015 General Election; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26993","26993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452462","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27000","27000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452463","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to develop the collection of information on the prevalence of epilepsy in England.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26985","26985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452464","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve access to speciality care for people with epilepsy.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26986","26986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452465","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the proportion of people with epilepsy in England and Wales who are living seizure-free.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26987","26987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452466","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the financial implications of removing the quality and outcomes framework indicator for seizure freedom (EP002) in 2014.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26988","26988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452467","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people under the age of 18 have epilepsy.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26989","26989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452468","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25396, if she will place in the Library the recovery plan in place at the Metropolitan Police Service for improving performance in completing Disclosure and Barring Service checks.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27013","27013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452469","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25396, what communication Ministers of his Department have had with the Metropolitan Police Force and other forces which are not meeting service level agreement standards for the time taken to complete local disclosure checks.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27014","27014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452470","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25396, if she will place in the Library a copy of the formal monthly performance reports provided by the Disclosure and Barring Service in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27015","27015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452471","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25396, if she will publish data from the Disclosure and Barring Service (DBS) on the performance of police forces against the service level agreement standards for the time taken to complete local DBS checks over the last six months.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27016","27016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452472","2016-03-01","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 February 2016 to Question 25882, if he will list the (a) 27 categories of information held in the Asset Management data set, (b) 13 categories of information held in the Facilities Management data set and (c) four categories of information held under the Finance data set.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27193","27193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452473","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to review plans to introduce a click and collect service as a result of P2U service failings over the 2015 Christmas period.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27167","27167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452474","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the smoking rate in (a) local authorities in which it is above the English average and (b) other local authorities.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27173","27173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452475","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the proportion of cancer patients who are offered the opportunity to take part in research in (a) trust areas in which participation rates are below the English average and (b) other areas.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27172","27172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452476","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential benefits of talking therapy for the treatment of mental health.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27108","27108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452477","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what changes his Department plans to pharmacy funding; and what assessment his Department has made of the effect of those changes on small independent businesses.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27141","27141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452478","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recourse is available to patients who believe they have undergone poor or harmful NHS psychotherapy treatment.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27095","27095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452479","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications of the reference to a number of protected characteristics in paragraph seven of the Government's Counter-Extremism Strategy, Cm 9148, for the effect of the Equality Act 2010 on all the protected characteristics it includes.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27102","27102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452480","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to notify groups and organisations who may be affected by the potential closure of the Collective Passport Service.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27190","27190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452481","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has spent on reducing reoffending in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27107","27107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452482","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the charity Broken Rainbow on renewing funding from her Department; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27123","27123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452483","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to close the Collective Passport Service by the end of February 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27129","27129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452484","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the proposed closure of the Collective Passport Office on the costs of obtaining passports for (a) school groups and (b) families.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27130","27130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452485","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the final decision was made to close the Collective Passport Service; and what discussions her Department has had with staff representatives on that closure.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27131","27131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452486","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of her Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27001","27001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452487","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers wear body-worn cameras in (a) Northamptonshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27034","27034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452488","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of making Disclosure and Barring Service certificates portable and valid from organisation to organisation by the person concerned.","Biography information for Michael Tomlinson","Michael Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26982","26982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452489","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has made an assessment of the effects on the tax revenue of developing countries of tax treaties with the UK.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26991","26991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452490","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department provides to developing countries to improve their tax revenue gathering capabilities.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26992","26992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452491","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of her Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27002","27002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452492","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 26100, what proportion of her Department's financial assistance for Palestinian development funds other projects which foster coexistence between Israelis and Palestinians.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27125","27125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452493","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 26100, what estimate her Department has made of the proportion of the £349 million spent in support of Palestinian development from 2011 to 2015 which has gone to support projects which promote coexistence.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27126","27126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452494","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 25684, what discussions she has had with her EU counterparts on the (a) destruction of structures confirmed to have been funded by the EU and (b) possibility of seeking costs related to that damage from Israeli authorities.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27150","27150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452495","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of the Accord on Fire and Building Safety on working conditions and safety standards in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27156","27156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452496","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 23 July 2015 to Question 6280, what work has been carried out to mitigate the risks identified from the EU's accession to the European Court of Human Rights.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27179","27179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452497","2016-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 1.26 of the National Audit Office report, Implementing reforms to civil legal aid reports, published in November 2014, what assessment he has made of the effect of the increase in the number of litigants in person in family courts for cases involving contact with children on the quality of child arrangements orders made in families known to have a history of domestic abuse.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27192","27192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452498","2016-02-22","Attorney General","2016-02-11","To ask the Attorney General, how many cases relating to each type of crime were prosecuted by the CPS in (a) magistrates' courts and (b) the Crown Court in each of the last 10 years; how many hours the CPS spent on prosecutions of each type in each type of court in those years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27182","27182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452499","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27003","27003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452500","2016-03-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many family courts have special access measures in place for victims of domestic violence attending the court for child contact cases.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27056","27056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452501","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which organisations have provided diversity and equality training to judges since 1 January 2012.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27062","27062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452502","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which organisations have provided diversity and equality training to prison governors since 1 January 2012.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27060","27060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452503","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for Exceptional Case Funding there were in 2015; and how many of those applications were successful.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27061","27061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452504","2016-02-22","Leader of the House","2016-02-11","To ask the Leader of the House, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Office were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27004","27004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452505","2016-02-22","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of her Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27005","27005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452506","2016-02-22","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent representations she has had on a public inquiry into events in Ballymurphy in August 1971; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27166","27166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452507","2016-02-22","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what representations she has received on the effect on Northern Ireland of proposals for new runway capacity in the London area.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27171","27171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452508","2016-02-22","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with (a) the Northern Ireland Executive and (b) airport operators in Northern Ireland and Great Britain on the Airports Commission: Final Report, published in July 2015.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27170","27170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452509","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Prime Minister has made of the potential effect of the investor state dispute settlement clause of the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership on public services managed by the Scottish government.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27195","27195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452510","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership is a mixed-competence agreement that will require ratification by the national parliaments of all EU member states.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27143","27143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452511","2016-02-22","Scotland Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if the Prime Minister will make it his policy to devolve responsibilities for the North Sea oil industry to the Scottish Government.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27144","27144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452512","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the reference in the Prime Minister's speech on life chances of 11 January 2016 to health liaison psychiatry services in A&E departments includes provision for paediatric mental health liaison psychiatry services in A&E departments.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27187","27187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452513","2016-02-22","Scotland Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27006","27006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452514","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27007","27007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452515","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with C2C on the effect of changes to its timetable on consumer satisfaction.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27031","27031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452516","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on the effect of changes in the timetable of C2C services.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27032","27032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452517","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Autumn Statement and Spending Review 2015, which cycling programmes his Department plans to fund from the £300 million fund for cycling for 2015-16 to 2020-21; and what other funding for cycling to which cycling programmes his Department plans to fund over that period.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27068","27068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452518","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2016 to Question 23856, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the increase in the number of pedal cyclist-killed or seriously injured casualties attributable to poorly-maintained local roads since 2010.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27044","27044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452519","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of increased waiting times for driving tests for young drivers on (a) failure rates and (b) increased travel time and cost to examination centres.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27057","27057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452520","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the estimated difference in cost between locating the Sheffield High Speed 2 station in the city centre and locating it in Meadowhall.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27132","27132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452521","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of agricultural land lost to UK farm production as a result of the construction of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27142","27142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452522","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the estimated difference between the current and original cost estimates of (a) locating the Sheffield High Speed 2 station in the city centre and (b) locating it in Meadowhall.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27133","27133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452523","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has received a copy of Sheffield City Region's study into connectivity for a city centre High Speed 2 station at Victoria in which Network Rail was involved.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27134","27134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452524","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether proposals for Northern Powerhouse Rail are based on city centre to city centre connectivity and on ensuring half-hour journeys between Leeds, Sheffield and Manchester.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27135","27135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452525","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the independent costings of linking High Speed 2 to the Northern Powerhouse Rail work for both Manchester and Sheffield city centre station locations.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27136","27136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452526","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on ensuring that High Speed 2 stations should be located where they can deliver maximum impact on public investment.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27137","27137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452527","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of additional jobs and (b) amount of additional housing resulting from a Meadowhall High Speed 2 station location.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27138","27138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452528","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of additional jobs and (b) amount of additional housing resulting from a Victoria High Speed 2 station location.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27139","27139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452529","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what methodology his Department used to determine that the proposed Sheffield station should be at Meadowhall and not Victoria; and whether that methodology has been independently verified.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27140","27140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452530","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2016 to Question 25018, what his Department's estimate is of the cost of the Emissions Testing Programme; and what Skoda's financial contribution is to the ongoing testing of VW vehicles outside that programme.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27119","27119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452531","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of Highways England's compliance with the conditions on environmental duties set out in paragraphs 5.23 and 5.24 of the Highways England: Licence, published in April 2015.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27117","27117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452532","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's press release of 18 August 2015, entitled Earnings outstrip rail fare increases for the first time in a decade, what the statistical evidential basis is for the statement that increasing regulated rail fares by the retail price index between 2016 and 2020 will save season-ticket holders around £425 each.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27121","27121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452533","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25993, whether his Department had a Cycling Health sub-group.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27118","27118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452534","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to performance indicators for helping cyclists, walkers and other vulnerable users of the network in the Highways England operational metrics manual, whether any additional resource funding has been allocated under the Road Investment Strategy to reduce vulnerable user casualties.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27180","27180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452535","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it is his policy to expand London's transport zones to include (a) Spelthorne constituency and (b) other new areas inside the M25 orbital that do not use the oyster system.","Biography information for Kwasi  Kwarteng","Kwasi Kwarteng","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27194","27194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452536","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he estimates the Severn River crossing concession will end.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27127","27127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452537","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2016 to Question 23952, how many meetings Ministers and officials of his Department have had with the Senior Traffic Commissioner and the Driver and Vehicle Standards Agency since 2010.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27149","27149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452538","2016-02-22","Wales Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27008","27008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452539","2016-02-22","Women and Equalities","2016-02-11","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of the Government Equalities Office were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26999","26999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452540","2016-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on developing proposals for implementing the Youth Obligation; and what organisations his Department are consulting to inform that process.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26997","26997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452541","2016-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27009","27009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452542","2016-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment for his policies of the findings of the National Federation of ALMOs Welfare reform survey relating to universal credit.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27076","27076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452543","2016-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken was between a fatal accident in construction and a conviction on the latest date for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 27162","27162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453442","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to reform the police complaints process.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903680","903680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453443","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the timeliness of the processing of Disclosure and Barring Service checks.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903676","903676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453444","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the Government's policy is on steps to increase cooperation between police forces and fire services.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903677","903677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453445","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to support the Metropolitan Police in tackling terrorism in London.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903681","903681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453446","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the police on the police grant settlement.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903683","903683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453729","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps have been taken during the Government's negotiations on the UK's membership of the EU to restore the UK's rebate to its full previous value.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903716","903716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453916","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on the options circulated by the President of the European Council on the UK's relationship with the EU.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903715","903715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453917","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made on the High Level Prosperity Partnership in Africa.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903717","903717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453918","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his French counterpart on the Treaty of Le Touquet; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903706","903706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453919","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his US counterpart on the lease extension of the military base on Diego Garcia.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903709","903709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453920","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of attacks on Christian places of worship in Israel in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903711","903711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453921","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to promote trade and diplomatic connections between the UK and other Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Chris Davies","Chris Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903718","903718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453922","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the outcome of discussions at the February 2016 European Council on the UK's relationship with the EU.","Biography information for Kelly Tolhurst","Kelly Tolhurst","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903714","903714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453923","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the strength of diplomatic and economic relations between India and the UK.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903712","903712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453924","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on the implementation of the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action with Iran.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903710","903710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/453925","2016-02-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Bahrain.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903713","903713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454549","2016-02-24","Wales Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with Ministers of the Welsh Government on strengthening financial accountability in government.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903630","903630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/454550","2016-02-24","Wales Office","2016-02-11","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the future of the steel industry in Wales.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 903629","903629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451842","2016-02-22","Attorney General","2016-02-10","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the implications of the judgment of the European Court of Justice in the case of Costa v ENEL in July 1964 for the Government's policy on the relative relationship between EU and UK law.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26879","26879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451843","2016-02-29","Attorney General","2016-02-10","To ask the Attorney General, what the CPS's policy is on seeking prosecutions of former members of paramilitary and terrorist organisations in Northern Ireland for attacks made against members of the armed forces during the Troubles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26902","26902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451844","2016-02-22","Attorney General","2016-02-10","To ask the Attorney General, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of the Law Officers' Departments were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26972","26972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451845","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26971","26971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451846","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the cost was to the public purse of settlement agreements for staff from  Crown Post Offices which were franchised in 2014 and 2015.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26945","26945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451847","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the total public expenditure on the UK space industry over the course of this Parliament.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26968","26968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451848","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the cost to the public purse has been of the refurbishment of Crown Post Offices in Lancaster since January 2010.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26946","26946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451849","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on benefit and tax credit demand from workers at franchises of former post offices; and what estimate his Department has made of the potential cost of that demand to the public purse.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26970","26970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451850","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of Sunday trading devolution on the premium pay of shop workers in Scotland.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26897","26897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451851","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Regulatory Policy Committee has made of the devolution of Sunday trading rules.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26898","26898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451852","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) business representative bodies, (b) central government bodies, (c) local authorities, (d) trade union or staff associations, (e) charity and social enterprises, (f) large businesses, (g) medium-sized businesses, (h) small businesses, (i) micro businesses, (j) convenience stores, (k) shop workers, (l) legal representatives, (m) religious organisations, (n) individuals and (o) other bodies responded to the consultation on Sunday trading devolution; how many responses of each category (i) supported and (ii) opposed devolution.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26899","26899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451853","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of a British exit from the EU on the international legal enforceability of protected UK food names.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26883","26883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451854","2016-02-22","Cabinet Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to start the consultation on introducing legislative change to require transparency of the beneficial ownership of all UK properties.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26884","26884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451855","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Post Office has spent refurbishing the premises of the Crown Post Office in Walworth Road since January 2010.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26885","26885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451856","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether (a) his Department and (b) another department has commissioned independent research on the economic effects of extending Sunday trading hours.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26886","26886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451857","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) local and (b) main post offices were open at the end of (i) April 2015 and (ii) January 2016.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26942","26942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451858","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the ability of the Government to reach the target set in 2012 of doubling exports to £1 trillion per annum by 2020.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26930","26930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451859","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff from Crown Post Offices that were franchised in 2014 and 2015 (a) transferred to employment with a franchise partner and (b) reached settlement agreements with the Post Office to leave its employment.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26943","26943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451860","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will take steps to ensure that jobs created by the (a) new nuclear project at Moorside and (b) the Solway Firth Tidal Lagoon project are available to local people.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26931","26931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451861","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the cost was to the public purse of indemnification of franchise partners to meet the costs for staff from Crown Post Offices who transferred into their employment in 2014 and 2015.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26944","26944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451862","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to ensure that young people in West Cumbria are equipped with the skills they need to access newly-created jobs in the nuclear and renewable energy sectors.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26932","26932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451863","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2016 to Question 24530, what methodology is used to calculate prices in connection with anti-dumping cases relating to the US and Russia.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26753","26753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451864","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will make an assessment of whether prices of imported ceramic goods from China reflect the domestic costs of production.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26754","26754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451865","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people who accumulate credit card debt after the Christmas period.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26765","26765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451866","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many responses his Department received from (a) convenience stores, (b) shop workers and (c) faith groups to the consultation on Sunday trading devolution.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26782","26782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451867","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff in his Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26810","26810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451868","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the investor-state dispute settlement mechanisms in the (a) Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership (TTIP) agreement and (b) EU-Canada Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement (CETA) apply to local authorities in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26772","26772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451869","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) business representative bodies, (b) local councils and (c) large and medium-sized businesses that responded to the consultation on Sunday trading devolution.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26804","26804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451870","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) business representative bodies, (b) central government bodies, (c) charity and social enterprises, (d) individuals, (e) large businesses, (f) legal representatives, (g) local authorities, (h) medium-sized businesses, (i) micro businesses, (j) religious organisations, (k) small businesses, (l) trade union or staff associations and (m) other bodies responded to the consultation on Sunday trading devolution; how many of each category (i) supported and (ii) opposed devolution; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26805","26805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451871","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will maintain the level of funding of the Charity Research Support Fund in real terms over the next five years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26777","26777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451872","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of responses to the Sunday trading consultation supported the devolution of Sunday trading hours.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26803","26803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451873","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of Sunday trading devolution on the premium pay of shopworkers.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26780","26780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451874","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Regulatory Policy Committee has made of the devolution of Sunday trading rules.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26781","26781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451875","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans that his Department's further education area reviews will incorporate equality impact assessments.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26840","26840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451876","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to his Department's press release of 5 February 2016, New National Minimum Wage offenders named and shamed, whether HM Revenue and Customs follows up successful investigations into companies found not to have complied with national minimum wage legislation with additional investigations into whether other employees of the same company were also not in receipt of the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26841","26841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451877","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what consideration his Department plans to give to local availability of courses in area reviews of further education.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26834","26834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451878","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what support the Government plans to provide to local authorities for implementation of the extension of primary authority under the Enterprise Bill.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26856","26856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451879","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received on the timescale for the completion of the area review process in further education.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26838","26838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451880","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the cost of (a) completing and (b) implementing further education area reviews.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26839","26839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451881","2016-02-22","Cabinet Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 January 2016 to Question 23331, what the average cost for each participant of the National Citizen Service has been in each year of its operation.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26796","26796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451882","2016-02-22","Cabinet Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in his Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26811","26811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451883","2016-02-22","Cabinet Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether a standard disclosure clause is included in Government procurement contracts.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26786","26786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451884","2016-02-22","Cabinet Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the procedures set out in the procurement policy note, Measures to promote tax compliance published in February 2014.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26787","26787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451885","2016-02-22","Cabinet Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many firms have been excluded from bidding for Government contracts since the introduction of the procurement policy note, Measures to promote tax compliance published in February 2014.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26788","26788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451886","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government has had discussions with Muslim charities on a possible restriction of banking facilities for such charities.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26701","26701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451887","2016-02-22","Cabinet Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26973","26973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451888","2016-02-22","Cabinet Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many freedom of information requests were (a) granted and (b) refused by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26963","26963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451889","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26981","26981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451890","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effects of the tax treatment of interest payments on tax revenues.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26752","26752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451891","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2016 to Question 20496, how many people were (a) prosecuted and (b) convicted of offences relating to (i) corporation tax, (ii) income tax, national insurance contributions, capital gains tax and inheritance tax and (iii) other tax-related offences in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26742","26742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451892","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with the financial sector and employer groups on workplace money management and workplace payroll savings schemes.","Biography information for Seema Kennedy","Seema Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26743","26743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451893","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff in his Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26827","26827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451894","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was raised from VAT on (a) air source heat pumps, (b) solar panels, (c) draught shipping, (d) insulation, (e) wood fuel boilers and (f) ground source heat pumps in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26809","26809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451895","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was raised from VAT on (a) renovating empty buildings, (b) building conversions, (c) children's car seats, (d) carry cots and (e) mobility aids for the elderly in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Redwood","John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26808","26808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451896","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many vessels (a) completed and (b) failed to complete the C1331 customs declaration form in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26831","26831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451897","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the long-term financial sustainability of councils with low council tax bases.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26870","26870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451898","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to merge local authorities with a low council tax base with neighbouring higher base councils to ensure financial sustainability and service provision.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26871","26871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451899","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received on reducing the number of (a) metropolitan district councils and (b) councillors in metropolitan counties with a combined authority and metro mayor.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26872","26872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451900","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if his Department will provide support for producers of anaerobic digestive installations in completing planning applications for those installations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26766","26766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451901","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26974","26974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451902","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he expects the Local Government Boundary Review will next consider the (a) ward and (b) councillor arrangements in the metropolitan districts within Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26874","26874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451903","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2016 to Question 26044, which three of the five funds Northstar Ventures manages are closed to new investments; and when the decision was taken that Northstar Ventures should exit from remaining deals.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26909","26909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451904","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2016 to Question 22981, if he will ask Ofcom to publish an assessment of whether the 26 per cent of BT's ducts identified as being empty in the report, Telecoms infrastructure access - sample survey of duct access, published in March 2009, reflected the proportion of BT's ducts that were able to have fibre blown through them without further civil works in the superfast broadband rollout.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26900","26900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451905","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26975","26975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451907","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress his Department has made on working with the EU Commission on extending the Public Lending Right to e-lending in local libraries.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26966","26966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451908","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many staff in his Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26812","26812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451909","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to identify the best ways to tackle cultural heritage destruction overseas.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26714","26714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451910","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will take steps to support the inclusion of the Fountain Cavern in Anguilla in the UNESCO World Heritage list.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26712","26712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451912","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to Sporting Future: A New Strategy for an Active Nation, published by his Department in December 2015, how his Department defines physical literacy.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26854","26854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451913","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of whether current arrangements for listed building status take account of potential measures that can be taken to improve the energy efficiency of data centres.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26798","26798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451914","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what countries take part in Flag Officer Sea Training courses for surface ships and submarines.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26807","26807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451915","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what project type his Department categorised the Successor Trident programme as for optimism bias purposes.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26802","26802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451916","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the evidence given by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State to the Foreign Affairs Committee on 10 February 2016, how many operations UK Reaper drones have undertaken in Libyan airspace this year.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26773","26773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451917","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2016 to Question 24110, whether he plans to publish the terms of reference for the Reaper User Group before the Group meeting on 14 to 18 March 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26843","26843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451918","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) details of contractor, (b) scope, (c) value and (d) cost overrun from the original estimate are of contracts awarded for the Successor Trident programme.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26801","26801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451919","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2016 to Question 25293, whether his Department distinguishes between the proposed use of deployed platforms with capabilities for (a) high value targeting and (b) intelligence surveillance and reconnaissance.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26842","26842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451920","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the Strategic Defence and Security Review on the global reach of the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26711","26711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451921","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 2.2.72 of his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2014-15, for which roles responsibility has been transferred from military to civilian personnel since 2010.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26739","26739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451922","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the report produced by Ernst and Young for his Department in February 2012 on development options and safety standards at RAF Northolt recommended that an Engineered Material Arresting System be installed at RAF Northolt; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26744","26744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451923","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 December 2015 to Question 20110, what specific benefits the UK derives from membership of (a) the European Defence Agency's Military Airworthiness Authorisation Forum, (b) European Defence Agency helicopter training programmes and (c) the Single European Sky initiative.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26747","26747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451924","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.61 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015, whether civilians employed by (a) the Royal Fleet Auxiliary, (b) Defence Equipment and Support and (c) trading funds are included in his Department's calculation of the size of the workforce he expects to cut by 30 per cent by the end of this Parliament.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26717","26717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451925","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2015 to Question 17914, which change programmes are expected to contribute to the planned reduction in the size of his Department's civilian workforce over the current Parliament; and what size of reductions he expects to result from each such change programme.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26718","26718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451926","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2015 to Question 17735, what change programmes are underway which are expected to reduce the size of his Department's civilian workforce.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26719","26719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451927","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2016 to Question 24285, how many times (a) Brimstone missiles, (b) Hellfire missiles and (c) Paveway IV guided bombs were deployed against targets in Iraq between 2 December 2015 and 29 January 2016.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26720","26720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451928","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff in his Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26813","26813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451929","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimates his Department has made of the amount of unexploded ordinance in the River Clyde.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26783","26783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451930","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people under the age of 18 in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK were recruited to the armed forces in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26784","26784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451931","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many visits the armed forces made to state secondary schools in (a) Inverclyde and (b) Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26785","26785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451932","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what programmes his Department is developing relating to cyber defence.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26767","26767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451933","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 26 January 2016 to Question 23620, what steps his Department has taken to implement new Government guidelines to help UK steel suppliers compete effectively for future defence projects; and what processes or policies have been changed as a result of those guidelines.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26755","26755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451934","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on recruitment agency fees in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26687","26687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451935","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) military and (b) civilian personnel have been employed as security guards (i) directly and (ii) by external third parties contracted by his Department in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26688","26688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451936","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK civilian personnel are currently deployed on military operations; and in what capacity such personnel are deployed.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26690","26690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451937","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) intelligence officers and (b) intelligence analysts served in each branch of the armed forces in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26693","26693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451938","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) military and (b) civilian personnel were employed within Defence Intelligence in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26694","26694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451939","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many full-time equivalent personnel employed by the (a) Royal Military Police, (b) Royal Naval Police and (c) Royal Air Force Police were deployed on overseas operations in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26695","26695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451940","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many full-time equivalent personnel were employed by the (a) Royal Military Police, (b) Royal Naval Police and (c) Royal Air Force Police in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26696","26696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451941","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian personnel were deployed in each operational theatre overseas in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26697","26697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451942","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many UK civilian personnel not formally deployed to an operational theatre visited such a theatre in the most recent year for which figures are available; and in what capacity those personnel carried out those visits.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26698","26698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451943","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) military and (b) civilian personnel were employed as (i) flight instructors, (ii) aircraft engineers and (iii) air traffic controllers in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26702","26702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451944","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many simulators were used for military flight training in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26703","26703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451945","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the RAF has spent on the marketing of RAF Northolt for civilian flights in the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26704","26704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451946","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the RAF has spent on the design and management of www.londonvipairport.com; how many hits the site generates each month; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26705","26705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451947","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether RAF personnel have attended any civilian aviation trade conferences or exhibitions to promote civilian flights at RAF Northolt over the last five years; which events were so attended; how many RAF personnel attended each such event; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26706","26706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451948","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether RAF personnel have been involved in the running and marketing of the civilian operation at RAF Northolt; how much in staff (a) time and (b) costs is spent on managing and marketing civilian flights; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26707","26707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451949","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Sea King HC4, (b) Wildcat, (c) Gazelle, (d) Apache, (e) Chinook HC2/3, (f) Puma HC2 and (g) Merlin Mk 3/3A helicopters are (i) in the Forward Available Fleet, (ii) in the Sustainment Fleet and (iii) classed as Short-Term Unserviceable.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26708","26708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451950","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) Sea King HC4, (b) Wildcat, (c) Gazelle, (d) Apache, (e) Chinook HC2/3, (f) Puma HC2 and (g) Merlin Mk 3/3A helicopters were used for military flight training in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26709","26709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451951","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26976","26976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451952","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what percentage optimism bias his Department applied to the Successor Trident programme.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26887","26887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451953","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department's estimates of the cost of the Successor Trident programme elemental contingency were included in addition to the programme contingency as was the case with the 2012 Olympics programme.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26888","26888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451954","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the potential sale value of the site of Kneller Hall, Whitton.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26893","26893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451955","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much the Government has spent on the upkeep of the site of Kneller Hall, Whitton, in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26894","26894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451956","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to provide immediate legal advice, without cost, to former service personnel required to submit to an interview about allegations related to past service during the Troubles.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26904","26904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451957","2016-02-29","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance his Department gives to former service personnel who are approached by officers of the Police Service of Northern Ireland investigating allegations of criminal behaviour during the Troubles; whether such assistance is given before or after that person has been charged; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26924","26924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451958","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many freedom of information requests were (a) granted and (b) refused by her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26940","26940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451959","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many students were entered for (a) GCSE and (b) A levels in (i) Arabic, (ii) modern Greek, (iii) Japanese, (iv) Urdu, (v) Bengali, (vi) modern Hebrew, (vii) Punjabi, (viii) Polish, (ix) Dutch, (x) Persian, (xi) Turkish, (xii) Albanian, (xiii) Cantonese and (xiv) Mandarin in (A) total and (B) each region in (1) 2011, (2) 2012, (3) 2013, (4) 2014 and (5) 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26917","26917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451960","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to improve teaching in schools on the risks of drug and alcohol abuse.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26935","26935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451961","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of pupils (a) in Warrington and (b) at schools in Warrington North constituency achieved GCSE grades A to C in (i) mathematics, (ii) a modern foreign language and (iii) physics in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26890","26890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451962","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of her Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26977","26977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451963","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what she expects the pass mark to be for each one to nine grade in the new GCSE grading system in (a) English, (b) science, (c) mathematics and (d) a modern foreign language in 2017.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26929","26929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451964","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make applications for EU structural funds for the purposes of alleviating pressure on school places caused by migration from other EU countries.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26958","26958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451965","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from faith schools on admissions and staffing policies in such schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26961","26961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451966","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from civil society organisations on the admissions criteria of faith schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26962","26962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451967","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's rationale was for allocating £30,000 to provide training or recruitment of teachers with protected characteristics.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26758","26758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451968","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff in her Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26814","26814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451969","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) trustees and (b) directors of academies and academy chains are paid salaries in excess of £142,500.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26848","26848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451970","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which academies and academy chains employ trustees and directors who are paid salaries in excess of £142,500.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26849","26849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451971","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many qualified PE teachers entered the teaching profession in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26850","26850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451972","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many state playing fields were sold in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26851","26851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451973","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what extra support is provided to foster carers receiving children who have experienced multiple placement breakdowns.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26852","26852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451974","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training on mental health awareness is provided to foster carers.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26853","26853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451975","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the financial effect of the provision of the Childcare Bill on primary schools with nursery provision.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26795","26795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451976","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many staff in her Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26815","26815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451977","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to assist people living in low-income households to improve energy-inefficient properties.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26757","26757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451978","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to ensure that all new electricity generation facilities that emit greenhouse gases are prepared for carbon capture and storage.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26722","26722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451979","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress the Government has made on reforming the EU Emissions Trading Scheme as a result of discussions with her EU counterparts and the recent COP21 climate conference.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26723","26723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451980","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the number of jobs that will be created by the construction phase of (a) the new nuclear build at Moorside and (b) Solway Firth Tidal Lagoon project in West Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26965","26965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451981","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the number of jobs that will be created by the running and maintaining of (a) new nuclear build at Moorside and (b) Solway Firth Tidal Lagoon project in West Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26964","26964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451982","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of her Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26978","26978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451983","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans the Government has to support research and development in the use of thorium reactor technology in (a) the UK, (b) the EU and (c) worldwide.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26937","26937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451984","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of recent flooding and severe weather in Cumbria on livestock prices.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26928","26928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451985","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of (a) homes and (b) businesses flooded in 2015 which did not have flood insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26837","26837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451986","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to ensure adequate funding of flood alleviation schemes planned for the River Spen in Cleckheaton and Liversedge.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26911","26911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451987","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding her Department plans to make available for flood defences along the River Calder and its tributaries in West Yorkshire in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26912","26912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451988","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of her Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26979","26979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451989","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect on the agriculture sector in Cumbria of recent flooding and severe weather.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26933","26933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451990","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if her Department will take steps to ensure that farming business is market-led rather than production-led.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26771","26771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451991","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff in her Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26816","26816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451992","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2016 to Question 25811, if she will list the (a) total funding, (b) total population and (c) funding per person for the (i) North and (ii) East region.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26799","26799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451993","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff in his Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26817","26817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451994","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support the Marrakesh Declaration, signed on 27 January 2016.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26756","26756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451995","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to encourage the Russian government to return the 2010 Polish presidential air plane wreck to Poland.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26738","26738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451996","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Bahraini counterparts on the amount of political prisoners held in Bahrain; and what representations he has made for such prisoners.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26691","26691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451997","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Bahraini counterpart on Mr. Hassan Mushaima and the provision of medical assistance for his condition.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26692","26692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451998","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the self-determination movement in Bahrain that seeks to establish a freely elected government.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26699","26699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451999","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the average hourly earnings of (a) female, (b) male, (c) full-time and (d) part-time employees of his Department were in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26980","26980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452000","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss with his Nigerian counterpart international assistance that can be provided to that country to tackle Boko Haram during 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26969","26969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452001","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of freedom of information requirements in the British Virgin Islands; and what plans he has to promote transparency in that territory.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26950","26950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452002","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of freedom of information requirements in Bermuda; and what plans he has to promote transparency in that territory.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26951","26951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452003","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking with troika partners Norway and the US to try to bring an end to atrocities against civilians in the Darfur region of Sudan.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26952","26952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452004","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he had made to his counterparts in (a) the US, (b) China, (c) France and (d) Russia on the recent ballistic missile launched by North Korea.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26949","26949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452005","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with officials of (a) NATO and (b) the EU on the recent ballistic missile launched by North Korea.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26948","26948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452006","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to support action at the International Criminal Court in respect of UK nationals suspected of having committed war crimes, crimes against humanity or genocide against members of the Yazidi community in Iraq.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26918","26918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452007","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information he holds on steps being taken to rescue Yazidis being held hostage by Daesh in Syria and Iraq.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26915","26915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452008","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times the UK has voted against an EU proposal at final adoption since 8 May 2015.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26875","26875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452009","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK plans to send forensic teams to Sinjar in Iraq to examine mass graves that have been discovered there.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26920","26920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452010","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many freedom of information requests were (a) granted and (b) refused by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26939","26939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452011","2016-02-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government recognises the killing of the Yazidis by Daesh as genocide.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26922","26922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452012","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many freedom of information requests were (a) granted and (b) refused by his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26938","26938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452013","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 5 January 2016 to Question 20189, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the thematic review and future monitoring of the Future in Mind policy address the needs of young carers to have more support for their mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26953","26953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452014","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) pharmacy closures and (b) job losses caused by planned reductions to the community pharmacy budget.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26862","26862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452015","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether (a) his Department and (b) the NHS has been asked by security and intelligence agencies for care.data data sets.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26865","26865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452016","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Nursing and Midwifery Council on extension of their remit to include root cause analysis of complaints and investigations.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26876","26876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452017","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulances waited more than 30 minutes to transfer patients to Warrington Hospital in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26881","26881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452018","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on patient access to medicines of planned reductions to the community pharmacy budget.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26861","26861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452019","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for activation of the full capacity protocol at Warrington Hospital's A&E department in 2015-16; and what effect (a) inability to access GP appointments and (b) reductions in the availability of social care had on the decision to activate that protocol in each such case.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26891","26891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452020","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of the doctors applying to Round 1 for Speciality Training posts commencing in the period August to December 2016 applied directly from Foundation Year Two.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26947","26947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452021","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his assessment is of the availability and adequacy of mental health services available to children in England with OCD.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26957","26957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452022","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his speech to the Local Government Association annual conference in July 2015, what progress has been made on the development and publication of unified health and social care metrics.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26956","26956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452023","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 26077, on suicide: females, if he will make it his policy to collect that information centrally.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26954","26954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452024","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to monitor implementation of the duties in the Children and Families Act 2014 on local authorities to (a) identify, (b) assess the needs of and (c) provide whole family support for young carers from April 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26955","26955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452025","2016-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with (a) fibromyalgia, (b) myalgic encephalomyelitis, (c) relapsing/remitting multiple sclerosis, (d) autism and (e) other mental health conditions have applied to move from disability living allowance to personal independence payment; and how many of those applications were successful.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26689","26689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452026","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support and guidance his Department has provided to clinical commissioning groups and NHS mental health trusts to support innovative home treatment and specialist nursing in the community for patients requiring mental health treatment.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26721","26721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452027","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal College of Nursing on the effect of sugary drinks on obesity.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26740","26740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452028","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that all clinical commissioning groups take account of the findings of the Commission on Acute Psychiatric Care's review led by Lord Crisp before they take steps to alter in-patient provision.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26728","26728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452029","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nationals of (a) the EEA excluding the UK and (b) non-EEA countries who are doctors or dentists have been brought before a fitness to practice panel and not suspended by their professional regulator as a result of poor English language skills in the last three years.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26745","26745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452030","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses were brought before a fitness to practise panel for lack of competence, communication issues between 2013 and 2015; and how many such nurses (a) were and (b) were not suspended.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26746","26746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452031","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had on presumed consent for organ donations in England.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26737","26737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452032","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal College of Nursing on the health effects of over-use of paracetamol to treat colds and flu.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26759","26759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452033","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with clinical bodies on potential links between prostate cancer and Alzheimer's disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26760","26760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452034","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with clinical bodies on potential links between taking antidepressants in pregnancy and autism in children.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26761","26761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452035","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS trusts in England on costs of the practice of sourcing nurses from Northern Ireland to cover weekend shifts.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26762","26762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452036","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of measures intended to curtail consumption of high sugar drinks on levels of consumption of drinks that require significant levels of added sugar to counteract their high acidity.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26775","26775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452037","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the waiting time for a non-urgent appointment with a GP in Mid Sussex constituency.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26806","26806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452038","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to raise awareness among parents of the six-week postnatal check.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26776","26776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452039","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff in his Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26819","26819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452040","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department allocated to the Stroke/Act FAST campaign in (a) 2014-15 and (b) 2015-16.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26858","26858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452041","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Government's response of 5 November 2015 to the e-petition, We demand the British Government reschedule cannabis, and to section 1.5.23 of Management of Multiple Sclerosis in Adults, whether the NHS plans to prescribe Sativex for multiple sclerosis-induced spasticity.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26859","26859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452042","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 25491, how many prisoners returned to jail having broken their licence conditions were subsequently found to be carrying concealed drugs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26857","26857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452043","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what public consultation there has been on the proposed closure of 15 HM Passport Office interview offices.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26844","26844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452044","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that companies with which the Government contracts to provide housing or other services for asylum seekers (a) treat such people with care and respect and (b) avoid measures which may make asylum seekers a target for hate crime.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26855","26855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452045","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many alerts were issued by the National Border Targeting Centre to the regional offices of Border Force relating to flights of potential interest in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26832","26832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452046","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff in her Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26820","26820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452047","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information she holds on the progress made by South Yorkshire Police in its review of its handling of allegations made against Sir Cliff Richard in August 2014; and what discussions her Department has had with South Yorkshire Police on that review.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26797","26797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452048","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of general aviation flights that arrived in the UK (a) had correctly completed general aviation reports, (b) had incorrectly completed general aviation reports and (c) failed to complete a general aviation report in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26774","26774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452049","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the correction of 9 February 2016 to Question 13206, (a) for what reasons the data initially published was incorrect, and (b) what steps her Department has taken to ensure accurate collection and publication of such information in future.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26800","26800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452050","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of occasions on which universities have withdrawn offers from international students who have stayed in the country for up to 28 days under the visa grace period.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26778","26778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452051","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect on universities of their financial liability for international students overstaying their visas.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26779","26779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452052","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many vessels which displayed the yellow Q flag (a) docked at UK ports and (b) were checked by Border Force officials in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26830","26830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452053","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to increase the number of missing people who are found.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26763","26763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452054","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to implement the EU Convention on preventing and combating violence against women and domestic violence.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26764","26764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452055","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions she has visited Cedars pre-departure accommodation.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26751","26751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452056","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many undeclared passengers were identified by the Border Force in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26729","26729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452057","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many flights were attended by the Border Force beyond the primary control points in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26730","26730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452058","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many general aviation flights were (a) attended and (b) cleared remotely by the Border Force in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26731","26731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452059","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects the Maritime Priority Assessment Tool to be fully implemented.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26732","26732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452060","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to release the full business case for the recently-announced closure of 15 HM Passport Office interview offices.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26726","26726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452061","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when a final decision was made to close 15 HM Passport Office interview offices; and what discussions her Department has had with staff representatives on those closures.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26727","26727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452062","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she expects to publish the results of her Department's assessment of exit checks data; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26700","26700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452063","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied child refugees in Europe the Government expects to relocate in 2016.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26901","26901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452064","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the correction of 9 February 2016 to Question 13206, what the cause was of the error in information on former unaccompanied minors removed between 2007 and 31 December 2015; and what steps she is taking to ensure that correct information is collected and published in future.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26910","26910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452065","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what reports she has received from the Metropolitan Police in the Royal Borough of Greenwich of delays in processing Disclosure and Barring Service applications.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26877","26877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452066","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications to the Disclosure and Barring Service from people living in Greenwich and Woolwich constituency have taken more than 60 days to process in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26878","26878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452067","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the contribution of the Minister for Immigration in the public bill committee stage of the Immigration Bill on 1 December 2015, Official Report, column 206, what the terms of reference are of the detailed analysis of the purposes of immigration detention being conducted by her Department.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26860","26860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452068","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason the Migration Advisory Committee did not provide its report by the end of January 2016.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26889","26889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452069","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to paragraph 24 of the Joint Ministerial Declaration on UK/French co-operation on managing migratory flows in Calais, published in August 2015, what progress has been made on the commitment to take stock of the operational effectiveness of the Dublin III Regulations.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26914","26914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452070","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will take steps to update guidance on the implementation of the Dublin III Regulations to ensure that unaccompanied children in Calais and Dunkirk can be united swiftly with their family in the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26913","26913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452071","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many freedom of information requests were (a) granted and (b) refused by her Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26941","26941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452072","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been transferred from the UK to other EU countries under the Dublin III Regulation (a) in total and (b) for the purposes of family reunification in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26926","26926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452073","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests for the transfer of an asylum application from other EU countries the UK has (a) received and (b) accepted in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26927","26927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452074","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been transferred from the UK to (a) Italy, (b) Hungary, (c) Croatia, (d) France, (e) Belgium, (f) Austria and (g) Germany under the Dublin III Regulation in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26925","26925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452075","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how her Department is working with the Department for Energy and Climate Change to ensure that official development assistance funding provided for international climate projects is prioritised in policies aimed at reducing poverty.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26724","26724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452076","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff in her Department and its non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26821","26821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452077","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the living conditions of the Yazidi community in refugee camps in Iraq.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26921","26921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452078","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance the UK is providing for reconstruction of Sinjar in Iraq.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26919","26919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452079","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress his Department has made on Action 36 of the UK Anti-Corruption plan, published in December 2014, relating to corporate criminal liability.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26916","26916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452080","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times (a) knife, (b) shiv, (c) shank, (d) chib and (e) another slang word for a blade were recorded on the Incident Report System in HM Prison Wandsworth in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26905","26905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452081","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times (a) knife, (b) shiv, (c) shank, (d) chib and (e) another slang word for a blade were recorded on the Incident Report System in HM Prison Wormwood Scrubs in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26906","26906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452082","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times (a) knife, (b) shiv, (c) shank, (d) chib and (e) another slang word for a blade were recorded on the Incident Report System in HM Prison Oakwood in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26907","26907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452083","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many times (a) knife, (b) shiv, (c) shank, (d) chib and (e) another slang word for a blade were recorded on the Incident Report System in HM Prison Parc in the last 12 months for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26908","26908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452084","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to Tables 5.1 and 5.2 of the official statistics bulletin, An Overview of Sexual Offending in England and Wales, published on 10 January 2013, what the average number of days from offence to completion for sexual offence criminal proceedings for each offence type was in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26866","26866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452085","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time between (a) offence commission and charge, (b) charge and first court appearance and (c) first court appearance to sentencing or acquittal was for all completed sexual offence cases in (i) 2013, (ii) 2014 and (iii) 2015.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26867","26867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452086","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to eradicate new psychoactive substances across the prison estate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26863","26863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452087","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidences of self harm were reported at HM Prison Rochester in each of the last 12 months; and what steps his Department is taking to reduce such incidences in the prison estate.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26864","26864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452088","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people who were victims of domestic abuse were incarcerated for violent crimes committed in response to the abuse they had received in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26936","26936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452089","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to increase opportunities for prisoners to acquire skills that could lead to earned release.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26934","26934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452090","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many trainees from Medway Secure Training Centre required hospital treatment as a result of injury from (a) assault and (b) restraint in (i) 2013, (ii) 2014 and (iii) 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26959","26959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452091","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff in his Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26822","26822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452092","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2016 to Question 23824, whether any staff in young offender institutions are (a) qualified speech and language therapists, (b) registered with the Mental Health and Care Professions Council and (c) qualified social workers.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26792","26792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452093","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time between (a) offence commission and charge, (b) charge and first court appearance and (c) first court appearance to sentencing or acquittal was for all sexual offences cases completed in Greater Manchester in (i) 2013, (ii) 2014 and (iii) 2015.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26833","26833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452094","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time between (a) offence commission and charge, (b) charge and first court appearance and (c) first court appearance to sentencing or acquittal was for all completed sexual offences cases where the victim was (i) a minor and (ii) an adult in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26836","26836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452095","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken as a result of the HM Chief Inspector of Prisons' report on HM Prison Rochester, published in September 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26845","26845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452096","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will review the National Offender Management Service's Benchmarking Policy and efficiency programme in HM Prison Rochester.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26846","26846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452097","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his Department's policy is on increasing the autonomy of prison governors to make decisions about the day-to-day running of their prisons.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26713","26713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452098","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to improve prisons' engagement with employers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26715","26715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452099","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans his Department has to sell unused property from the prison estate; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26716","26716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452100","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 22664, when those contract breaches took place; and with what procedures G4S failed to comply.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26793","26793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452101","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy to ensure that West Cumbria Magistrates' Court is not closed.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26710","26710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452102","2016-02-22","Leader of the House","2016-02-10","To ask the Leader of the House, when he plans to announce the parliamentary timetable for the rest of 2016.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26892","26892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452103","2016-02-29","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assurance the Government has given to (a) former members of Irish terrorist organisations and (b) former service personnel on any continuing liability to prosecution for alleged crimes committed during the Troubles; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26923","26923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452104","2016-02-29","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans the Government has to ensure comparable treatment in respect of (a) immunity from prosecution and (b) prosecution for former service personnel who served in Northern Ireland during the Troubles and for former members of paramilitary and terrorist organisations during that period.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26903","26903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452105","2016-02-22","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will make representations to Rt Hon Tony Blair to request that he accede to requests from the Northern Ireland Affairs Committee to give oral evidence on compensation for victims of IRA violence.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26768","26768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452106","2016-02-22","Northern Ireland Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many staff in her Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26823","26823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452107","2016-02-22","Cabinet Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in 10 Downing Street receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26824","26824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452108","2016-02-22","Scotland Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many staff in his Department receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26825","26825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452109","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many staff in his Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26826","26826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452110","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2015 to Question 18956, if he will provide details of the new Access fund for sustainable travel.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26794","26794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452111","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects Highways England operatives to attend to the day burning street lamps on the M67 between Denton and Hyde in Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26873","26873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452112","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost was to the public purse of graffiti removal across the (a) Highways England and (b) Network Rail networks in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26847","26847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452113","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the benefits to passengers with sight problems of requiring all new buses to have audio-visual next stop and final destination announcements.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26835","26835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452114","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to reduce the costs of (a) travel by road and train to airports in the UK and (b) airport parking.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26769","26769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452115","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with people who run airports on excessive VAT charging in retail outlets based in airports.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26770","26770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452116","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in the numbers of driving examiners in England on waiting times for tests; and what steps he is taking to encourage more examiners to qualify.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26790","26790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452117","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average wait for driving tests is in each English region.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26791","26791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452118","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the pass rates in driving tests were in each region and constituent part of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26789","26789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452119","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he plans to take to ensure that dualling of the A1079 between Barnby Moor and Wilberfoss goes ahead; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26748","26748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452120","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what changes the UK is discussing with its European partners to the EU Framework Directive in respect of commercial vehicle body building and conversion; what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to amend UK law on this matter; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26749","26749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452121","2016-02-23","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects the first on-road UK trial of zero-emission transport refrigeration units to take place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26750","26750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452122","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of recent changes to funding of bus services on the provision of those services.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26741","26741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452123","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much of the Access Fund he expects to be spent on cycling in each year to 2020-21.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26736","26736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452124","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2015 to Question 18101, at what stage he plans to be able to predict the geographical distribution of funding for cycling outside of London and the eight cycling ambition cities; and what steps he is taking to identify that geographical distribution.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26733","26733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452125","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce details of the new Access Fund.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26734","26734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452126","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans for there to be a period between the Local Sustainable Transport Fund ending in March 2016 and the commencement of the new Access Fund.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26735","26735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452127","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, by what proportion the rent for premises leased by Network Rail has increased for businesses based in (a) Bethnal Green and Bow constituency, (b) London and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26725","26725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452128","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to include additional road surface noise reduction measures, a sound barrier and home noise insulation measures in the contract specifications for the M60 smart motorway extension through Denton.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26868","26868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452129","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he expects residents adjoining the M60 in Denton to qualify for monetary compensation for the extension of the smart motorway scheme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26869","26869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452130","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which body is responsible for enforcement of aircraft noise abatement requirements.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26895","26895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452131","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to update the Heathrow Airport London (Noise Abatement Requirements) Notice 2010 to require higher minimum rates of climb for aircraft taking off from Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26896","26896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452132","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the rates of climb of aircraft taking off from Heathrow Airport compared to other (a) UK and (b) European airports.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26882","26882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452133","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answers of 18 November 2015 to Question 16782 and of 11 December 2015 to Questions 19723 and 19724, if he will estimate how many miles of local authority road are in poor structural condition in England.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26880","26880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452134","2016-02-22","Wales Office","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many staff in his Department receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26828","26828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452135","2016-02-22","Women and Equalities","2016-02-10","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many staff in the Government Equalities Office receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26818","26818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452136","2016-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff in his Department and non-departmental public bodies receive (a) home to work travel allowance, (b) a car allowance and (c) subsidised health insurance.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26829","26829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452137","2016-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who will begin receiving the new state pension in April 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26967","26967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/452138","2016-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the duration and value is of his Department's contract with Monster Worldwide Ltd for the management of Universal Jobmatch; and on what basis payments to Monster Worldwide Ltd are made under that contract.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26960","26960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451435","2016-02-11","HM Treasury","2016-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the loan guarantee facility offered by his Department to EDF Energy for construction of the twin Hinkley Point C nuclear power plants will be conditional on the prior successful operation of the same model elsewhere in the world before entering into force.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26672","26672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451436","2016-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 4 February 2016 to Question 903457, when the Spending Review settlement to her Department will be fully allocated.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26558","26558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451437","2016-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to ban the use of whips for encouragement in horse racing.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26556","26556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451438","2016-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effect on employment levels in the Syrian textile industry of the application of sanctions on Syria; and if he will estimate the number of Syrian textile workers and their families who have left Syria due to the loss of employment arising from application of economic sanctions.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26671","26671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451439","2016-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made on the test launch by North Korea of a long-range ballistic missile on 7 February 2016; and what representations the Government has received on the UK maintenance of the its long-range Trident ballistic missile system since 7 February 2016.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26670","26670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451440","2016-02-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans her Department has to ensure that the smart meter roll-out is used as an opportunity to engage with householders on the issue of carbon monoxide safety.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26495","26495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451441","2016-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward proposals to require private landlords to fit carbon monoxide alarms in any property that contains a fuel-burning appliance.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26526","26526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451442","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has received on the implications for aid of the 1955 tax treaty between the UK and Malawi.","Biography information for Richard Arkless","Richard  Arkless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26450","26450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451443","2016-02-11","Department of Health","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in which countries aspartame has been banned; and for what reason each such ban has been enacted.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26682","26682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451444","2016-02-11","Prime Minister","2016-02-09","To ask the Prime Minister, whether he has had discussions with the Prime Minister of the Czech Republic on the sale of Czech war planes to Iraq.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26378","26378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451445","2016-02-11","HM Treasury","2016-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to assist middle-income families with their pension planning.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26383","26383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451446","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans the armed forces have to commemorate the Battle of the Somme.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26404","26404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451447","2016-02-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the amount of wind energy that will be generated in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26403","26403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451448","2016-02-11","Department of Health","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to measure the effectiveness of his Department's work to tackle obesity.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26382","26382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451449","2016-02-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the re-offending rate was for (a) men and (b) women who left prison in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26402","26402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451450","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of cars he estimates will be electric in the UK in 2020.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26401","26401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451451","2016-02-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who are in receipt of benefits he estimates will be in full-time work after the roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26405","26405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451452","2016-02-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2016 to Question 25444, whether she has made an estimate of the proportion of coal that may have been mined by children.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26431","26431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451453","2016-02-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the coal burnt in UK coal-fired power stations originated in the USA in the first nine months of 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26410","26410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451454","2016-02-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the coal burnt in UK coal-fired power stations originated in Russia in the first nine months of 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26411","26411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451455","2016-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to ensure the powers of intervention over Local Government Pension Scheme funds' non-financial investment policies do not conflict with (a) Article 18 of EU Directive 41/2003 and (b) Occupational Pension Scheme Investment Regulations 2005.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26432","26432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451456","2016-02-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any personnel from Reaper Squadrons 39 or 13 are currently embedded with US forces.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26409","26409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451457","2016-02-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, within what timeframe his Department is able to deploy Reaper drones to Libya.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26528","26528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451458","2016-02-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what sanctions can be taken against the Office of the Independent Adjudicator if it misses the 90-day target in issuing complaint outcomes set by the European Directive on Alternative Dispute Resolution.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26674","26674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451459","2016-02-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what additional resources his Department plans to make available to the Office of the Independent Adjudicator to ensure it meets the 90-day target in issuing complaint outcomes set by the European Directive on Alternative Dispute Resolution.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26675","26675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451460","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what metrics of performance he used to measure the performance of the Government's Productivity Plan, entitled Fixing the foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation, published in 2015.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26506","26506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451461","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the performance against its aims of the Government's productivity plan, entitled Fixing the foundations: Creating a more prosperous nation, published in July 2015.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26507","26507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451462","2016-02-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of employee involvement in the workplace on productivity levels.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26420","26420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451463","2016-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much was spent on flood defence schemes in the Calder Valley area in (a) 1997 to 2010, (b) 2010 to 2015; and what the projected spend on such schemes is for 2015 to 2020.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26487","26487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451464","2016-02-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the current projections used by the Environment Agency on the expected frequency of extreme flooding in the Calder Valley in any given year are for a (a) 1.5 , (b) two and (c) four degree rise in average temperatures.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26417","26417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451465","2016-02-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has decided on a date for the conclusion of the public sector spectrum release.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26461","26461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451466","2016-02-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much revenue received from previous spectrum sales has been reinvested into digital infrastructure.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26460","26460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451467","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of (a) premises in the Highlands and Islands he estimates will have indoor 4G coverage, (b) the Highlands area he estimates will have complete not-spots for voice and SMS text by 2017.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26497","26497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451468","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he estimates the sale of 5G licences will take place; what estimate his Department has made of the revenue from the sale of the 5G spectrum; and whether he plans to invest the revenue from the sale of the 5G spectrum in digital infrastructure.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26474","26474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451469","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to carry out a full ratio frequency allocation review; and whether he plans to coordinate future allocation of bandwidth with EU member states.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26475","26475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451470","2016-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Indian counterpart on the treatment of Sikhs campaigning for human rights in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26563","26563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451471","2016-02-11","Department of Health","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent progress has been made on access to Translarna in discussions between NICE, NHS England and the relevant pharmaceutical company.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26414","26414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451472","2016-02-11","Department of Health","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to announce a decision on access to Translarna after the NICE Highly Specialised Technology Committee meeting on 17 February 2016.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26415","26415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451473","2016-02-11","Department for Education","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional funding her Department is providing to Bradford Council to help schools with essential repairs.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26653","26653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451474","2016-02-11","HM Treasury","2016-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the cost was of paying child benefit to EU nationals in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26484","26484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451475","2016-02-11","HM Treasury","2016-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the annual cost of paying child benefit to EU nationals under the terms of the renegotiation proposed by the EU Council President.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26485","26485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451476","2016-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offences of each type were committed by (a) sentenced female prisoners and (b) female prisoners held on remand who had their children with them in prison in each of the last three years; and which such offences were of each type in the violence against the person category.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26651","26651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451477","2016-02-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) women and (b) men held in prison in each of the last five years had been born in a prison.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26652","26652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451478","2016-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy to sign the Safe Schools Declaration to protect schools from being attacked or occupied for military purposes.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26564","26564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451479","2016-02-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many times the Minister of State for Culture and the Digital Economy has visited each region in the last year.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26509","26509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451480","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will direct Ofsted to undertake re-inspections of (a) Parley First School and (b) Ferndown Upper School within two years of their last inspections.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26624","26624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451481","2016-02-22","Department for Education","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will place in the Library a copy of the application made by Twynham Learning Federation to establish a new primary academy in West Christchurch which is proposed to open from September 2016 and a copy of her response.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26625","26625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451482","2016-02-11","Department for Education","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the proposed location is for the new primary academy to be opened in West Christchurch from September 2016 by Twynham Learning Foundation; and what financial contribution her Department plans to make to that academy's premises.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26622","26622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451483","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the status is of the 2003 Le Touquet Treaty in international law.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26572","26572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451484","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Prime Minister's Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25906, if he will place in the Library a copy of the analysis carried out by the Department for Work and Pensions and HM Revenue and Customs on benefit and tax credit claims by recently arrived EEA migrants.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26619","26619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451485","2016-02-11","HM Treasury","2016-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how the Government determines the Scottish Government's allocation of non-cash departmental expenditure budget for student loans.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26657","26657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451486","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will maintain the policy that payments made by Alliance House in relation to infected blood are disregarded for the purpose of tax or benefit assessments once the reformed system of payments is introduced.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26511","26511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451487","2016-02-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to incentivise developers to co-fund the deployment of local fibre broadband networks to properties which are not scheduled for connection free of charge.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26552","26552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451488","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will commission a study into the effect on bird and marine life of off-shore windfarms; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26456","26456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451489","2016-02-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department has taken to ascertain the reason for a large number of whales becoming stranded on the east coast of the UK in 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26471","26471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451490","2016-02-22","Department for Transport","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons a high-sided heavy goods vehicle which overturned on the Humber Bridge on 1 February 2016 was permitted to cross the bridge while the bridge was closed to all high-sided vehicles due to high winds; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26457","26457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451491","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether a security assessment has been made of the potential use of non-HM Passport Office (HMPO) sites for interviews when HMPO plans to replace face-to-face interviews with video-link interviews.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26498","26498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451492","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether staff working at the HM Passport Office site in Dundee will be (a) offered alternative employment or (b) made redundant.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26499","26499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451493","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the property lease contract on the HM Passport Office site in Dundee ends; and if she will extend the proposed timeframe for closure of this site.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26500","26500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451494","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether lease contracts on buildings currently housing HM Passport Office interview offices that are facing closure would allow for the proposed timeframe of office closures to be extended.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26501","26501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451495","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, under what criteria the 2016 to 2017 local government funding settlement was decided; and if he will publish the distributional effect of that settlement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26504","26504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451496","2016-02-11","HM Treasury","2016-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the amount paid in child benefit to parents of children residing outside the UK who have died since a claim was set up in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26565","26565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451497","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax credit claimants in work reported income rises of (a) more than £2,500, (b) more than £2,500 but less than £5,000 and (c) more than £5,000 in the most recent 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26604","26604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451498","2016-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what safeguards his Department plans to put in place to ensure that people who leave their council homes as a result of the proposed pay to stay scheme are able to afford private rented property in the same area.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26459","26459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451499","2016-02-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of private rented properties are priced above the local housing allowance in the (a) UK and (b) West Midlands.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26467","26467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451500","2016-02-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how the Transitional Grant available to certain local authorities was calculated and allocated.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26616","26616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451501","2016-02-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans she has to increase investment in home insulation.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26458","26458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451502","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 November 2015 to Question 16435, when his Department expects to publish the Impact Assessment on changes to reduce costs in medical negligence mitigation.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26546","26546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451503","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average patient waiting times for A&E departments at hospital sites that have introduced a (a) co-located urgent care centre and (b) model that integrates primary care staff within the A&E department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26472","26472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451504","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure of walk-in centres on patient waiting times in local A&E departments.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26473","26473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451505","2016-02-11","Department for Transport","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department plans to hold with colleagues in the Scottish Government on the environmental proposal for ship-to-ship oil transfers in the Cromarty firth.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26448","26448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451506","2016-02-11","Department for Education","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25404, which of the (a) academies, (b) academies which were previously maintained schools and (c) free schools have been subject to complaints about admissions decisions.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26683","26683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451507","2016-02-11","Department for Education","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25400, which academies and free schools made those applications to her Department to vary admissions requirements.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26684","26684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451508","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2016 to Question 25816, what the ceiling trajectory on agency spend is as a proportion of expenditure on nursing staff for all NHS trusts in England.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26424","26424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451509","2016-02-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many Article 4 directions to restrict the application of permitted development rights in local areas have been made by (a) local planning authorities and (b) the Secretary of State in the last three years; how many times he has restricted or amended those developments by local planning authorities in that time; and how many such cases relate to planning permission for the construction of basements.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26570","26570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451510","2016-02-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many refugee applications from migrants living in the Sovereign Base Areas started before 1 December 2008 had not been determined on 8 August 2014; how many such applications were determined as failed following the enactment of the Refugees (Amendment) Ordinance 2014; and how many migrants have been removed from the Sovereign Base Areas as a consequence of the enactment of that ordinance.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26568","26568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451511","2016-02-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people living in the Akrotiri and Dhekelia RAF Sovereign Base Areas have applied for asylum since October 1998; how many such applications have been (a) accepted and (b) rejected; and how many such people have been removed from the Sovereign Base Areas.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26569","26569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451512","2016-02-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many calls the Pay and Work Rights helpline received in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16; and how much funding that helpline received in each year between 2010-11 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26567","26567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451513","2016-02-11","Home Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December 2015 to Question 19716, what proportion of oral appeals were not represented in each month of the last three years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26685","26685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451514","2016-02-22","Home Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many US Department of Homeland Security officials are based at Heathrow, Gatwick and Manchester airports; and how long each such official has been based at each airport.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26610","26610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451515","2016-02-11","Department for Education","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her announcement of 2 November 2015 Introducing greater emphasis on literacy and numeracy at key stage 2, what representations she has since received on that policy; and approximately how many such representations were (a) against and (b) in favour of that statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sheryll Murray","Mrs Sheryll Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26643","26643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451516","2016-02-11","Department of Health","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of local authorities in carrying out their duties under the new commissioning arrangements to ensure that the needs of people living with HIV in their areas are met.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26434","26434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451517","2016-02-22","Department of Health","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many HIV support services are planned to be affected by changes in funding from April 2016; and how many people used each of those services in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26442","26442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451518","2016-02-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what obligations Openreach and BT have under contracts with the Government to provide prior warning to residents of planned maintenance or improvement work to junction boxes and other infrastructure that involves the temporary disconnection of services.","Biography information for Sir Alan Duncan","Sir Alan Duncan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26494","26494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451519","2016-02-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he received a document on UK Sikhs from the Indian delegation during the Indian Prime Minister's recent visit to the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26562","26562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451520","2016-02-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the county of origin of manufacture is of the PCS clothing solution.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26543","26543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451521","2016-02-22","Department for International Development","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many civil servants were loaned or seconded from the (a) Department for International Development to the Ministry of Defence, (b) Ministry of Defence to the Department for International Development, (c) Department for International Development to the Foreign and Commonwealth Office, (d) Foreign and Commonwealth Office to the Department for International Development, (e) Department for International Development to the Department of Energy and Climate Change, (f) Department of Energy and Climate Change to the Department for International Development, (g) Cabinet Office to the Department for International Development and (h) Department for International Development to the Cabinet Office in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26539","26539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451522","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people who have used the Business Premises Renovation Allowance scheme have also been subject to investigation by HM Revenue and Customs for tax avoidance or tax evasion.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26540","26540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451523","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what total value of tax relief has been granted under the Business Premises Renovation Allowance scheme in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26541","26541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451524","2016-02-22","HM Treasury","2016-02-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Business Premises Renovation Allowance scheme is planned to close.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26542","26542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451525","2016-02-11","Cabinet Office","2016-02-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he expects to receive the report and recommendations of the investigation headed by Sir Eric Pickles on electoral fraud.","Biography information for Sir Alan Campbell","Mr Alan Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26483","26483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451526","2016-02-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of whether China has met all of the technical Market Economy Status criteria as set by the EU.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26486","26486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/451527","2016-02-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-02-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the expenditure has been on the new National Living Wage advertising campaign to date.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 26640","26640"
