"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882201","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of foster care allowances in covering the cost of raising children.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135272","135272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882202","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people aged under 18 are awaiting assessment for attention deficit or hyperactivity disorder in (a) Kent, (b) West Yorkshire and (c) Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135273","135273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882203","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of people aged under 18 who are awaiting assessment for attention deficit or hyperactivity disorder by clinical commissioning group level.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135274","135274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882204","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of people aged over 18 who are awaiting assessment for attention deficit or hyperactivity disorder by clinical commissioning group level.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135275","135275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882205","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has undertaken an assessment of the potential effect of the Welsh Government's proposed investment in the Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon project on the (a) level of the average strike price and (b) tenure of contract requested by the prospective developer.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135276","135276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882206","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the level of addictive gambling of placing restrictions on the amount people can spend on online gambling games.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135277","135277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882207","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 April 2018 to Question 134169, what steps he is taking to help ensure that local authorities have sufficient provision and adequate criteria in place to provide sufficient financial support to kinship carers.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135278","135278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882208","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 30 January 2018 to Question 124848, when his Department plans to complete its consideration of the implications of the Walker v. Innospec Limited judgment for public service schemes.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135229","135229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882209","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons he rejected the application by West Bromwich Albion Football Club to pilot a safe-standing scheme at The Hawthorns in the 2018-19 season; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135230","135230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882210","2018-04-18","Department for International Trade","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the annual salary is of the Director General for Exports.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135231","135231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882211","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which schools are in the 20 per cent most deprived areas.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135232","135232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882212","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of pupils permanently excluded from schools in Derbyshire at key stage (a) 1, (b) 2, (c) 3 and (d) 4 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135233","135233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882213","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government plans to provide funding for the building of new care homes for elderly people.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135234","135234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882214","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his policy is on encouraging people in the health sector to enter general practice.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135235","135235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882215","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure soldiers back from deployment are given support to re-integrate into civilian life.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135236","135236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882216","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will take steps ensure the full implementation of the Military Covenant in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135237","135237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882217","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has plans to increase the maintenance loan for students to help prevent them going in to overdrafts.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135238","135238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882218","2018-04-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse was of legal aid in 2017.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135239","135239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882219","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have (a) signed up to the help to buy scheme and (b) received their bonus under that scheme.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135240","135240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882220","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many people have bought social housing properties since 2012.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135241","135241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882221","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are in receipt of housing benefit in the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135242","135242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882222","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to reduce (a) regional and national oversight, (b) quality assurance, (c) evaluation (d) central marketing and (e) other non-core operational delivery costs for the National Citizen Service.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135243","135243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882223","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, by what criteria his Department measures the value for money of applications for funding for research into Complex Regional Pain Syndrome.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135244","135244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882224","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to (a) publish torture guidance protocols and (b) consult (i) human rights organisations and (ii) others on protocols and guidelines relating to the torture of detainees.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135245","135245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882225","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in the US administration on UK nationals who have been refused entry to the US for business or tourism under the visa waiver programme because of dual citizenship with a country on the US travel ban list.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135246","135246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882226","2018-04-18","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure good cyber security practices are followed for the systems that support the delivery of UK elections ahead of local government elections in May.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135247","135247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882227","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to measure the effect of the removal of the NHS bursary on application rates to undergraduate nursing courses.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135248","135248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882228","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Airdrie and Shotts constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK received Access to Work grants (a) in total and (b) for a mental health condition in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135249","135249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882229","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Airdrie and Shotts constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK were referred to the Mental Health Support Service through Access to Work in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135250","135250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882230","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Airdrie & Shotts constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK received mental health support through (i) the Mental Health Support Service and (ii) an access to work award in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135251","135251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882231","2018-04-18","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the local statutory orders for the proxy and postal voting pilots in Peterborough, Slough and Tower Hamlets.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135252","135252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882232","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will review the guidance for police forces on recording and publishing statistics on knife crime to provide more specific figures than the force-wide level of knife crime.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135253","135253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882233","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department is assessing measures to increase the efficiency of public sector procurement; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135223","135223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882234","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, within what timeframe he plans to implement the proposed integrated communities strategy.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135224","135224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882235","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department plans to take to aid the development of the Integrated Communities Strategy.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135225","135225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882236","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on public safety of driverless vehicles.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135226","135226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882237","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) recent assessment his Department has made of and (b) further steps his Department is taking to tackle the threat to UK Armed Forces of chemical weapons.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135227","135227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882238","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of using local enterprise (a) zones and (b) partnerships to help support the UK's space launch industry.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135228","135228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882239","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has agreed a date by which it will accept or decline the offer of investment into Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon by the Welsh Government.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135333","135333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882240","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of investment into Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon by the Welsh Government on the required (a) strike price and (b) length of contract.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135339","135339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882241","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the letters of 16 February 2018 referenced M2579/18 and M2417/18 from the hon. Member for West Lancashire.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135341","135341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882242","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to assess whether (a) students and (b) parents of students with (i) autism and (ii) specific learning difficulties are satisfied with the accommodation by education providers of the educational needs of those students.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135342","135342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882243","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on the provision of study coaches for students with (a) autism and (b) specific learning difficulties.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135344","135344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882244","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of educational attainment of students with (a) autism and (b) specific learning difficulties since 2010.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135346","135346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882245","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that charities have access to clear advice on the effect of the provisions of the Transparency of Lobbying, Non-Party Campaigning and Trade Union Administration Act 2014.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135348","135348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882247","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to his Oral Answer of 20 March 2018, Official Report, column 156, on motor neurone disease, which projects received that £52 million investment; and which 24 clinical trials are being recruited to.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135354","135354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882248","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of granting indefinite personal independence payment awards to people diagnosed with motor neurone disease.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135356","135356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882249","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to make primary and secondary schools autism friendly.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135358","135358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882250","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what records are held of how much was owed to NHS trusts in the Yorkshire and Humber region in unpaid medical bills incurred by foreign nationals since 2010.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135360","135360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882251","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answers of 27 March 2018 and 3 April 2018 to Questions 133873 and 133719, whether any (a) Ministers, (b) officials, (c) special advisers and (d) others representing his Department have been in contact with (i) Cambridge Analytica, (ii) SCL Group and (iii) Strategic Communication Laboratories by (A) telephone, (B) email, (C) letter and (D) other form of communication on the statement on the Cambridge Analytica website that its methodology has been approved by his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135361","135361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882252","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department has collected to identify growth in county lines activity across the UK.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135362","135362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882253","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.32 of his Department's consultation document entitled Maritime 2050: Call for evidence, published on 27 March 2018, when he plans to make the changes required to extend entitlement to national minimum wage rates of pay for merchant seafarers working on ships in territorial waters and on one port voyages.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135363","135363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882254","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 3.32 of his Department's consultation document entitled Maritime 2050: Call for evidence, published on 27 March 2018, what assessment he has made of the changes required to the legislative framework to extend entitlement to national minimum wage rates of pay to all merchant seafarers working on commercial vessels in UK territorial waters and on one port voyages to offshore energy installations.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135365","135365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882255","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's policy paper, Autumn Budget 2017: government action to tackle tax avoidance, evasion, non-compliance and aggressive tax planning, published on 22 November 2017, if he will provide a list of the anti-avoidance measures the Government has introduced since 2010 which have raised an additional £160 billion in revenue; and how that figure of £160 billion was calculated.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135367","135367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882256","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 3.32 of his Department's consultation document entitled Maritime 2050: Call for evidence, published on 27 March 2018, what assessment he has made of the changes required to the legislative framework to (a) apply and (b) enforce entitlement to national minimum wage rates of pay for all merchant seafarers working on commercial vessels in UK territorial waters and on one port voyages to offshore energy installations.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135369","135369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882257","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 3.32 of his Department's consultation document entitled Maritime 2050: Call for evidence, published on 27 March 2018, what assessment he has made of the changes required to his Department’s service level agreement with HMRC for national minimum wage enforcement to (a) apply and (b) enforce entitlement to national minimum wage rates of pay to all merchant seafarers working on commercial vessels in UK territorial waters and on one port voyages to offshore energy installations.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135370","135370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882258","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.32 of his Department's consultation document entitled Maritime 2050: Call for evidence, published on 27 March 2018, what assessment he has made of the changes required to the legislative framework to extend entitlement to national minimum wage rates of pay to all merchant seafarers working in territorial waters and on one port voyages to offshore energy installations.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135372","135372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882259","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 3.32 of his Department's consultation document entitled Maritime 2050: Call for evidence, published on 27 March 2018, what the timetable is for making the changes required to the legislative framework to extend entitlement to national minimum wage rates of pay to all merchant seafarers working in territorial waters and on one port voyages to offshore energy installations.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135374","135374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882260","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to support a national roll-out of carer passport schemes.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135375","135375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882261","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to support children with autism at school.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135393","135393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882262","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve the educational experience for children with autism.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135380","135380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882263","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an assessment of the fire resilience of flats in timber-framed residential buildings.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135381","135381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882264","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of revenue to the Exchequer from fixed-odds betting terminals if the maximum stake on such terminals was reduced to £20.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135302","135302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882265","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve support for children with special educational needs in schools.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135383","135383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882266","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people addicted to online gambling services.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135378","135378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882267","2018-04-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effectiveness of the Legal Ombudsmen's review process.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135388","135388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882268","2018-04-18","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish his Department's report entitled Public Family Law Pressures - what do we know and what can be done.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135390","135390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882269","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many non-medical help providers have had (a) no referrals, (b) fewer than five referrals and (c) fewer than 10 referrals since the introduction of the Disabled Students Allowance Quality Assurance Group list in April 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135391","135391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882270","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with references to Technical Issues in Charity Law, published by the Law Commission in September 2017, whether he plans to take steps in response to the recommendations in that report.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135395","135395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882271","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were informally excluded from schools in academic year 2016-17; and how many of those informal exclusions related to SEND children.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135397","135397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882272","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment his Department has made of the feasibility of introducing a centralised national electoral register.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135385","135385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882273","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of ambulance handovers at Wirral University Teaching Hospital NHS Foundation Trust were delayed by more than (a) 30 minutes and (b) 60 minutes in the last three months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135399","135399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882274","2018-04-18","Scotland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what information his Department holds on the (a) amount of social housing stock there was in Glasgow North East constituency in each year from 1999 to date and (b) projected amount of social housing stock in that constituency for each year to 2020.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135401","135401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882275","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government has made an assessment of whether statutory minimum breaks remain sufficient for people working long shifts, including care workers.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135403","135403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882276","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve (a) diagnosis rates and (b) access to treatment for lymphoedema in (i) Oxfordshire and (ii) England.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135405","135405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882277","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of households affected by the replacement of Support for Mortgage Interest with a new loan were still to be informed of that change by Serco as of 31 March 2018.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135406","135406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882278","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many modern slavery operations were led by Immigration Enforcement Crime teams in each of the past three years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135408","135408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882279","2018-04-17","Women and Equalities","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when the consultation on proposals to reform of the Gender Recognition Act 2004 will be launched.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135410","135410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882280","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many potential cases of modern slavery were encountered by Immigration Enforcement Compliance teams in each of the past three years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135416","135416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882281","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many potential cases of people trafficking or modern slavery were identified during the course of Operation Magnify; and by which agencies such cases were identified.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135421","135421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882282","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many potential cases of people trafficking or modern slavery identified during the course of Operation Magnify resulted in victims entering National Referral Mechanism support accommodation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135423","135423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882283","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of how annual bonuses affect the payments recipients of such bonuses are required to make through Child Maintenance Service arrangements.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135386","135386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882284","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints her Department has received in relation to the effect on the calculation of child maintenance payments of annual bonus payments.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135424","135424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882285","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of eligible brain tumour patients with a glioma had their tumour tissue sample tested for 1p/19q co-deletion biomarker between 1 January 2016 and 31 December 2016.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135425","135425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882286","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to reduce road congestion on A-roads in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135427","135427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882287","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether steps are being taken to prevent the closure to new patients of the Lower Urinary Tract Services Clinic in north London.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135429","135429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882288","2018-04-18","House of Commons Commission","2018-04-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what the total cost is of the proposed Visitor Services Academy programme scheduled to commence in October 2018.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135433","135433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882289","2018-04-18","House of Commons Commission","2018-04-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what qualifications will be required of the staff responsible for training tour guides under the new Visitor Service Academy programme scheduled to commence in October 2018.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135434","135434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882290","2018-04-17","House of Commons Commission","2018-04-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what estimate has been made of the total cost of the Tour Guides Project proposed to commence in October 2018.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135436","135436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882291","2018-04-18","House of Commons Commission","2018-04-13","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what the timetable is for the delivery and operation of the (a) Tour Guides Project and (b) Visitors Services Academy Programme.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135437","135437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882292","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether Baroness Cumberlege plans consult patient groups and affected people before the Medicines and Medical Devices Review commences; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135439","135439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882293","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps he has taken to increase the take-up of free school meals among eligible pupils.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135441","135441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882294","2018-04-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will press for an early recall of the UN Security Council in order to seek a resolution to the conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135443","135443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882295","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue accrued to the public purse through corporation tax in (a) 2016-17 and (b) 2017-18.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135445","135445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882296","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate his Department has made of the number of young women who were absent from school as a result of not being able to afford feminine hygiene products.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135447","135447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882297","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has put in place to ensure that the National Citizen Service (NCS) Trust has the governance, leadership and expertise necessary to deliver the expansion of the NCS programme; and if he will publish the NCS Trust’s full action plan on governance and capabilities improvements.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135454","135454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882298","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent steps his Department has taken to ensure that developers meet their quotas for affordable housing.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135430","135430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882299","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions has he had with his Egyptian counterpart on the effect of the introduction of laws on the (a) Protest Law and (b) Assembly Law on human rights in that country.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135431","135431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882300","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will ensure applications for Legal Aid for victims of domestic violence are not means tested against the victim's partner's income; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135432","135432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882301","2018-04-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent steps the Government has taken to ensure the maintenance of the Good Friday Agreement in negotiations for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135435","135435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882302","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how the £86 million to support innovators and the NHS in overcoming barriers to getting new, innovative technologies to patients as part of the Accelerated Access Review will be allocated.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135438","135438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882303","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Royal Mint supplies wholesalers outside the UK, including other EU nations.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135440","135440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882304","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the wind speed required to disperse (a) PM 0.1, (b) PM 1, (c) PM2.5 and (d) PM10 particles from the source from which they are emitted.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135442","135442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882305","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) funding and (b) other support his Department makes available for improving major road junctions.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135444","135444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882306","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department plans to change the 12 week pay reference period used to calculate paid annual leave; and whether his Department plans to implement the recommendation of the Taylor Review of a 52 week pay reference period for annual leave.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135407","135407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882307","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority on exploitation of labour in the nail bar industry.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135446","135446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882308","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with the Gangmasters and Labour Abuse Authority on exploitation of labour in the car wash industry.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135409","135409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882309","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he has plans to extend private fostering arrangements to children up to the age of 18 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135411","135411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882310","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the advertising industry promotes positive body images.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135448","135448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882311","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the standard of care at Alder Hey Children's Hospital in respect of Alfie Evans.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135412","135412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882312","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of progress on the ICE Benchmark Association project to reform the LIBOR Benchmark Methodology; whether the new system will be implemented across all panel banks; and what the communication strategy for that project is.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135413","135413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882313","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of families whose benefit entitlement exceeds the benefit cap as a result of looking after children under child arrangements orders.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135414","135414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882314","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what incentives the Government provides for whistleblowers to come forward with information before an incident has occurred; and what steps he is taking to tackle the practice of penalising whistleblowers.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135415","135415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882315","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he had made of the merits of a US-style system for whistleblowing whereby whistleblowers are given incentives to come forward.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135417","135417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882316","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of exempting children under child arrangement orders from the benefit cap.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135382","135382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882317","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's policy is on schools requiring children to eat a lunchtime meal in a separate room as a result of their parents being unable to pay a minimum advance payment to cover meals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135384","135384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882318","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make his policy to require the National Infrastructure Commission to analyse the distributional effect of different infrastructure options by geographical area, income group, gender, and ethnicity.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135418","135418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882319","2018-04-18","Department for International Trade","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many applications to the (a) Export Control Joint Unit and (b) Export Control Organisation which were referred up to ministerial level were (a) approved and (b) denied for each and every year from year since 2010.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135387","135387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882320","2018-04-17","Prime Minister","2018-04-13","To ask the Prime Minister, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of creating at Cabinet level a Minister for older citizens .","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135419","135419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882321","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to Autumn Budget 2017, if he will list the 25 new schemes that will receive a share of the £36 million funding for flood protection; and what criteria his Department used to allocate that funding.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135420","135420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882322","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much road tax was collected from vehicles owned by people living in (a) Bury North constituency, (b) Bury and (c) the North West in each of the last five years.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135389","135389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882323","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department (a) commissioned and (b) received data from UCAS on the number of applicants for university nursing courses in England in the current 2018 undergraduate cycle by (i) by field of nursing and (ii) English region.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135422","135422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882324","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will publish the criteria his Department uses to assess the effect of the Government's reforms to nursing education.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135355","135355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882325","2018-04-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many councils have (a) requested and (b) received funding from the public purse for urgent fire safety work after the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135392","135392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882326","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2018 to Question 133651 on Mental Health Services: North West, how many specialist in-patient mental health beds there were on 31 December 2017 in (a) Bury, (b) North West and (c) England.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135357","135357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882327","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the Mobile Concrete Batching Plant industry of the announcement made by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State on 5 April 2018 on operating weight arrangements for Volumetric Concrete Mixers.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135449","135449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882328","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hours of training on complex regional pain syndrome are included in the syllabus for (a) a medical degree, (b) GP training, (c) a nursing degree and (d) a physiotherapy degree.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135359","135359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882329","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hours of training on Fibromyalgia are included in the syllabus for (a) a medical degree, (b) GP training (c) a nursing degree and (d) a physiotherapy degree.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135426","135426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882330","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hours of training on Chronic Pain are included in the syllabus for (a) a medical degree, (b) GP training, (c) a nursing degree and (d) a physiotherapy degree.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135364","135364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882331","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer on 2 February 2018 to Question 125524, on Complex Regional Pain Syndrome, for reason that data is not available.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135394","135394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882332","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he last met with representatives of (a) British Gas and (b)  Ofgem to discuss future pricing policy.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135450","135450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882333","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office, pursuant to Answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 133654, on Syria: Armed Conflict, which armed Syrian opposition groups the UK has trained since 2012; and what was included in that training.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135396","135396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882334","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made is of the (a) financial risks (b) liabilities to the public purse of the Government's new nuclear programme.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135451","135451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882335","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office, pursuant to Answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 133652, on Syria: Peacekeeping Operations, how many UK ground troops have been operating in Syria, including those embedded with US forces; from which regiments those troops came from; and where in Syria they were based.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135366","135366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882336","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Foreign and Commonwealth Office, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 133664 on Syria: Overseas Aid, what support the UK has provided (a) directly and (b) indirectly, to Ahrar al-Sham.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135398","135398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882337","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer  of 28 March 2018 to Question 133666 on Syria: armed conflict, what the breakdown of the £32 million support for opposition groups was for each year in the period 2011-17.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135368","135368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882338","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 3 April 2018 to Question 133853 on Occupied Territories, what assessment he has made of whether trade between British businesses and Israeli entities in the Occupied Territories is consistent with UN Security Council Resolution 2234.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135452","135452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882339","2018-04-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government helped Libyan exiles or British Libyans living in the UK to travel to Libya in 2011.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135371","135371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882340","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government was in communication with (a) Liwa al-Ummah and (b) the Tripoli Brigade during the war in Libya in 2011.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135400","135400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882341","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many discussions involving which officials his Department had with the Financial Conduct Authority and the UK Listing Authority on the stock market listing of EN+.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135329","135329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882342","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to African migrants in migrant camps in Yemen.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135330","135330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882343","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many discussions involving which officials his Department had with the Financial Conduct Authority and the UK Listing Authority on the stock market listing of EN+.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135331","135331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882344","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the (a) employment, (b) training, (c) housing and (d) health outcomes of vulnerable 16 and 17-year-olds who are cared for by local authorities.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135332","135332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882345","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, against which criteria the Government is measuring the effectiveness of the Bahraini Ministry of the Interior Ombudsman.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135334","135334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882346","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, by which benchmarks the Government plan to assess the fairness and outcome of the Bahraini elections due to take place in 2018.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135428","135428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882347","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on trends in the prison conditions for (a) the Bahrain 13 and (b) other prisoners in Bahrain.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135335","135335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882348","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Government of Bahrain on its failure to comply with the recommendations of the Bahrain Independent Commission of Inquiry in the matter of the release of people tortured in that country.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135336","135336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882349","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Saudi Government on the implications of its reform programme for Saudi Arabia's influence in Bahrain.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135337","135337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882350","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's budget is allocated to tackling chronic poverty and malnutrition in Central African Republic.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135338","135338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882351","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any people in Scotland have been refused a Support for Mortgage Interest (SMI) loan since the conversion of SMI from a benefit to a loan.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135340","135340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882352","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress the Government has made on reducing the extent of employer discrimination against people with (a) criminal records and (b) mental health problems.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135373","135373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882353","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government is going to meet its target date of April 2018 for moving the management of the National Citizen Service from a community interest company to a royal chartered public sector body.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135343","135343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882354","2018-04-18","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with her counterpart in Bangladesh on the (a) restricted humanitarian space in Bangladesh and (b) issuance of lFD6/7 permits and visas for international non-governmental organisations in Cox’s Bazar.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135402","135402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882355","2018-04-18","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, What plans she has to discuss the Rohingya crisis with her counterparts at the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in April.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135376","135376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882356","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to discuss the global refugee crisis with her Commonwealth counterparts at the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting in April 2018.","Biography information for Preet Kaur Gill","Preet Kaur Gill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135345","135345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882357","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what progress has been made on the recruitment of board members to the National Citizen Service Trust; and what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the time taken for that recruitment on the conversion of the trust to a royal charter body.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135453","135453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882358","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if the Government will make an assessment of the potential merits of including laparoscopic ventral mesh rectopexy within the ongoing review into medicines and medical devices safety.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135347","135347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882359","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made representations to clinical commissioning groups encouraging them to offer the Freestyle Libre blood glucose monitoring system to people living with diabetes as a result of the NHS Business Service Authority’s decision to approve the system for prescription on the NHS.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135404","135404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882360","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the position of Crown Representative to Interserve was vacant during any periods in the last two years.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135349","135349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882361","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of Support for Mortgage Interest claimants in each region in England.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135377","135377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882362","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will require the operators of waste incineration sites to (a) monitor the emissions of PM 10 and PM 2.5 particles at their sites and (b) publish the results of such monitoring.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135379","135379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882363","2018-04-18","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many live contracts Government departments and agencies have with Carillion and its subsidiary companies.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135351","135351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882364","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department knows which group was responsible for the killing of British soldier Sergeant Matt Tonroe in Manbij.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135352","135352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882365","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to engage with the digital currency industry.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135353","135353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882366","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to assess his Department's level of funding for universal infant free school meals in light of the rising cost of food.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135304","135304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882367","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an estimate of (a) how much the price of food will change over the next five years and (b) whether that change in price will have an effect on the provision of universal free school meals.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135305","135305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882368","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Department has made an assessment of the effectiveness of its policy on Universal Infant Free School Meals.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135306","135306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882369","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he will undertake an assessment of the effect on children of the universal infant free school meal policy.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135307","135307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882370","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils have been in receipt of universal infant free school meals since its introduction.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135308","135308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882371","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress has been made in the appointment of the (a) Chair and (b) board of the Social Mobility Commission.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135309","135309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882372","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of universal infant free school meals on children's health and nutrition.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135310","135310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882373","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of universal infant free school meals on children's attainment levels.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135311","135311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882374","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has plans to  devolve funding for hepatitis C services to Greater Manchester under the devolution agreement.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135312","135312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882375","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what powers are available to local authorities to award Blue Badges in the event that an application is not within his Department’s guidelines.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135313","135313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882376","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has allocated to Haiti in response to the (a) 2010 earthquake and (b) 2010-11 outbreak of cholera in that country.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135314","135314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882377","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, to which organisations her Department allocated funding to deliver aid to Haiti as a result of the (a) 2010 earthquake and (b) 2010-11 outbreak of cholera in that country.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135315","135315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882378","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to the public purse of repatriating UK citizens was after the collapse of Monarch airlines.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135316","135316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882379","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much and what proportion of the cost of repatriating UK citizens after the collapse of monarch airlines came from (a) the public purse, (b) the travel industry, (c) credit card companies, (d) insurance companies (e) other sources.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135317","135317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882380","2018-04-18","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what contingency plans his Department has put in place in the event of the collapse of Strategic Supplier Interserve.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135318","135318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882381","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of final cost to the public purse of costs not recharged after the collapse of Monarch airlines.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135319","135319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882382","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on what dates the quarterly supplier reviews were collected for Interserve; and when the next quarterly supplier review for that company will be due.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135320","135320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882383","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) people and (b) organisations have refused to contribute to repatriation costs after the collapse of Monarch airlines.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135321","135321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882384","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings have taken place between Interserve and (a) Government Ministers and (b) department officials in the last six months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135322","135322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882385","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to improve the transparency of Business Improvement District bodies.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135323","135323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882386","2018-04-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of sentences for each category of criminal offence resulted in suspended sentences.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135324","135324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882387","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage schools to use their budgets to provide sanitary products for children who are unable to afford them.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135325","135325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882388","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the reasons were for information on the (a) rape kit, (b) remarks made by the sentencing judge at Worboys’ trial and (c) new information that emerged as a result of the legal action against the Metropolitan Police, not being included in the dossier of evidence on the John Worboys case that was provided to the Parole Board.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135326","135326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882389","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of early service leavers were in employment six months after discharge from the armed forces in the most recent period for which information is available.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135327","135327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882390","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what changes to supplier checks have been made by Highways England as a result of the collapse of Carillion in January 2018.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135297","135297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882391","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, for what reason there is a variation in cost between National Citizen Service delivery partner providers for (a) the activity based residential from £201 to £725 and (b) the skills based residential from £100 to £1,040, in Cost Benchmark Report, National Citizen Service, Final Report of 7 February 2018.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135298","135298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882392","2018-04-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent progress has been made on Project Centurion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135299","135299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882393","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times her Department has requested a Statement of Reason from a tribunal after a tribunal has ruled in a personal independence payment claimant’s favour.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135300","135300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882394","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment tribunal decisions that have ruled in favour of the claimant have subsequently been appealed by her Department; and what the outcomes of those appeals have been.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135301","135301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882395","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment claimants with a primary condition of epilepsy who were awarded such payments after a tribunal ruling have (a) had a Statement of Reason requested by her Department, (b) had their tribunal decision appealed by her Department and (c) seen their award (i) decreased or (ii) removed as a result.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135303","135303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882396","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the protection of indigenous peoples' rights and culture worldwide.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135328","135328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882397","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of scheduled trains between Sheffield and Manchester Piccadilly were classed as having passengers in excess of capacity from the latest available data.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135459","135459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882398","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to make a decision on the Hope Valley Capacity Scheme submitted to his Department by Network Rail.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135460","135460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882399","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 111036, on Mobile Homes, if his Department will record net gain in new pitches.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135461","135461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882400","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of salary thresholds for work visas for non-EU nationals on NHS recruitment.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135462","135462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882401","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Queen's Speech 2017, whether her Department plans to publish the Immigration Bill only when the negotiations with the EU are complete.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135463","135463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882402","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations his Department has made to the Pakistani Government on ensuring that freedom of religion and belief commitments to education for religious minorities are upheld in that country.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135464","135464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882403","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will include paramedics in the list of healthcare students eligible for the NHS Learning Support Fund.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135465","135465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882404","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of claimants who moved from employment and support allowance to universal credit were found to be fit for work in their work capability assessment but were later found to be eligible for benefits at (a) mandatory reconsideration stage and (b) appeal stage.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135466","135466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882405","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to incentivise housing developers to ensure that all new homes can receive fast broadband.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135467","135467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882406","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of launching a new scheme, similar to Project Lightning, to ensure that more homes can provide usable broadband.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135468","135468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882407","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of the (a) financial and (b) staffing resources of (i) the UK Export Certification Partnership and (ii) that Partnership's beef certification team.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135469","135469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882408","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 March 2018 to Questions 130023, 130025, 130026, 130027, 130028, 130029 and 130030, what figure his Department uses for tax reliefs to estimate the cost to the Exchequer is negligible.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135470","135470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882409","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the Government’s policy is on hospitals sourcing food that is produced locally.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135471","135471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882410","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what role Public Health England will play in monitoring the effect of the implementation of a minimum unit price for alcohol in Scotland to inform any decision on that policy in England.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135472","135472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882411","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the ban on below-cost sales of alcohol on alcohol-related hospital admissions since the introduction of that ban.","Biography information for Dr Paul Williams","Dr Paul Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135473","135473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882412","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of or received legal advice on the implications for patients of non-compliance with part (9)(43)(3) of The National Health Service Commissioning Board and Clinical Commissioning Groups (Responsibilities and Standing Rules) Regulations 2012, which states that a relevant body must make arrangements to ensure that at the end of each data collection period not less than 92 per cent of the persons falling within paragraph 4 have been waiting to commence treatment for less than 18 weeks.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135474","135474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882413","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of recent underspending nationally on depreciation on (a) the NHS estate and (b) NHS equipment over the next (i) five, (ii) 10 and (iii) 15 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135475","135475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882414","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the variation between planned and actual spending on depreciation was nationally in each financial year since 2010-11; for what reason such variation occurred; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135476","135476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882415","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Unlocking Talent, Fulfilling Potential, what estimate he has made of the potential effect that increasing the number of early years practitioners in private, voluntary and independent nurseries will have on closing the early word gap.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135477","135477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882416","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the number of people who enrol in early years teacher training.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135478","135478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882417","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the Myanmar military to allow the safe, monitored and dignified return of the Rohingya people.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135479","135479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882418","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish information on the tasks on which children will be assessed under the forthcoming early years baseline assessment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135480","135480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882419","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to introduce changes to the Packaging Recovery Note system to strengthen producer responsibility before the publication of its Resources and Waste Strategy.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135481","135481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882420","2018-04-18","Scotland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many of his Department's social media campaigns have used the audience targeting filter, Exclude: Interests: Scottish independence since 2010.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135482","135482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882421","2018-04-18","Scotland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland,  which of his Department's social media campaigns used the audience targeting filter, Exclude: Interests: Scottish independence since 2010.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135483","135483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882422","2018-04-18","Scotland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on social media campaigns which used the audience targeting filter, Exclude: Interests: Scottish independence since 2010.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135484","135484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882423","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 119327, Revenue and Customs: ICT, whether HMRC remains on track to start migrating customers from the Customs Handling of Import and Export Freight system to the Customs Declaration Service system from August 2018.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135485","135485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882424","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will ensure that the forthcoming Consumer Green Paper sets out provisions to ensure that broadband exit fees are charged at a rate that is fair to consumers.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135486","135486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882425","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 1 February 2016 to Question 24633, whether his Department has collected data on the number of units of (a) housing and (b) affordable housing built on each parcel of NHS land sold in London since 2016.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135487","135487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882426","2018-04-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 20 March 2018 to Question 132489, on AWACS, whether he plans to assess the effect on the UK defence industrial base of agreeing a foreign military sale in respect of awarding a contract for the RAF's airborne early warning aircraft; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135488","135488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882427","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in Halton constituency were prosecuted for illicit drugs offences in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135489","135489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882428","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post boxes (a) have been removed from operation and (b) had their collection rates reduced since the Royal Mail was formally privatised.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135490","135490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882429","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department is providing to people unable to access the Pre-Exposure Prophylaxis (PrEP) Impact Trial due to sites being oversubscribed.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135491","135491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882430","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate he has made of the number of school-age children who live in the catchment area of only a state-funded faith school.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135492","135492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882431","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to give councils the flexibility to retain secure tenancies as standard in local tenancy strategies within the regulations under the Housing and Planning Act 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135493","135493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882432","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff were employed by HMRC at the Tax Credit Office in Preston as at 28 March 2018; and how many of those staff his Department (a) estimates will be employed at that Tax Credit Office by 1 January 2019 and (b) planned to offer redundancy to, make redundant or offer jobs at other HMRC offices in Lancashire, Merseyside or Greater Manchester to.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135494","135494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882433","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £49.4 million in EU exit funding for his Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135495","135495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882434","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £21.1 million in EU exit funding for his Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135496","135496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882435","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £29.6 million in EU exit funding for his Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135497","135497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882436","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £12.7 million in EU exit funding for his Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135498","135498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882437","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the introduction of the £200 self-contribution for disabled students who are in receipt of disabled student allowances on (a) the take-up of the equipment needed to study independently and (b) trends in the level of participation of disabled students; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135499","135499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882438","2018-04-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £17.3 million in EU exit funding for his Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135500","135500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882439","2018-04-17","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £0.4 million in EU exit funding for his Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135501","135501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882440","2018-04-17","Scotland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £0.3 million in EU exit funding for his Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135502","135502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882441","2018-04-17","Wales Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the Written Statement of 13 March 2018, Spring Statement, HCWS 540, if he will publish a list of where the £0.3 million in EU exit funding for his Department will be allocated.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135503","135503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882442","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has made representations to the Bangladeshi Government on its proposed transfer of Rohingya refugees to Bhasan Char island.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135504","135504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882443","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has provided consular assistance to the British human rights campaigner Andy Hall, who has been sentenced for defamation in Thailand.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135505","135505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882444","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect on the provision of services provided by sexual health clinics of moving responsibility for and funding of those clinics to local authorities.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135506","135506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882445","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he supports the creation of an independent body to (a) investigate, (b) document, (c) collect, and (d) analyse evidence of human rights violations in Burma.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135507","135507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882446","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the total payments made by parents direct to childcare providers due to technical issues experienced with HMRC's online service for tax-free childcare.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135508","135508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882447","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March 2018 to Question 134090, whether the previous interim chief officer will return to Halton Clinical Commissioning Group as interim chief officer after the end of the secondment.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135509","135509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882448","2018-04-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of extending badger culling on the effectiveness of vaccination schemes operating in those same areas.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135510","135510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882449","2018-04-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his Answer of 26 March  to Question 133676, how he proposes to take forward the garden city principles, other than those of design, now that those principles will no longer be included in the National Planning Policy Framework.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135511","135511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882450","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) men and (b) women aged (i) 10-20, (ii) 21-30, (iii) 31-40, (iv) 41-50, (v) 51-60, (vi) 61-70 and (vii) over 80 years were diagnosed with irritable bowel syndrome in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135512","135512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882451","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his South African counterpart on attacks against South African farmers.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135513","135513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882452","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 March 2018 to Question 129149 on Ministry of Defence Land,, whether the figure of 320 days given is based on a historical assessment or a future prediction.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135514","135514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882453","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the oral contribution of Lord Ahmed of Wimbledon, of 17 January 2018, House of Lords Official Report, column 701, when the review of the exchange of notes between the UK government and the British Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies expected to be published by the end of March will be published; and what the reasons are for the time taken to publish that report.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135515","135515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882454","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the level of participation among businesses in enabling their staff to engage in full-time social action projects and the National Citizen Service.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135516","135516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882455","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many cases referred to prosecuting authorities by HMRC for serious and complex tax crime by corporations have concluded with a criminal conviction since 2010.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135517","135517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882457","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been prosecuted under section 127 of the Communications Act 2003 for each year since 2013.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135519","135519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882458","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the level of successful asylum appeals since 2015.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135520","135520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882459","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the timetable is for a new double taxation treaty with Malawi to be signed.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135521","135521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882460","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many cases against (a) doctors, (b) nurses, (c) other medical professionals, (d) directors of NHS trusts and (e) other NHS staff relating to (i) fraud, (ii) violence, (iii) bribery, (iv) corruption, (v) criminal damage, (vi) theft, (vii) market-fixing and (viii) other unlawful action were being investigated in NHS Protect before it was superseded by the NHS Counter Fraud Authority in November 2017; how many such cases have been taken over by the NHS Counter Fraud Authority; and how many such cases are still current.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135522","135522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882461","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many investigations into NHS Trust directors the NHS Counter Fraud Authority has started (a) nationally and (b) in Yorkshire since it was established; and how many such investigations are still current.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135523","135523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882462","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people responded to her Department's consultation on air weapon licensing of 1 December 2017 to 6 February 2018 raising concerns about the shooting of animals such as cats by such weapons.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135524","135524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882463","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Public Health England report on deaths associated with neurological conditions in England 2001-14, what steps he is taking to reduce deaths associated with epilepsy.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135525","135525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882464","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many Medevac evacuations have taken place from St Helena in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135526","135526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882465","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of (a) access to healthcare and (b) socioeconomic inequality on epilepsy mortality rates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135527","135527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882466","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much in total was invested in the UK under the Tier 1 Investor Visa scheme between 2008 and Q1 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135528","135528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882467","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many politically exposed persons were successful under the Tier 1 Investor Visa scheme between 2008 and Q1 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135529","135529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882468","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to carry out retrospective checks on people that were successful under the Tier 1 Investor Visa scheme between 2008 and Q1 2015 and the source or sources of wealth invested by those such people.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135530","135530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882469","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the compensation criteria is for parents who miss out on tax-free childcare payments as a result of technical problems experienced with the online childcare service.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135531","135531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882470","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reasons her Department does not publish the names of people who are successful under the Tier 1 Investor Visa scheme.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135532","135532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882471","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 26 March 2018 to Question 133807, on Universal Credit, by what means his Department determines how much of a claimant's income has been or will be invested in a personal or occupational pension.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135533","135533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882472","2018-04-23","Department for International Trade","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the effect on the protection of human rights of arbitration clauses in Free Trade Agreements.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135534","135534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882473","2018-04-23","Department for International Trade","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will make it is policy to include clauses to protect human rights and the environment in negotiations on future bilateral trade agreements.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135535","135535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882474","2018-04-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that UK companies operating in (a) Colombia and (b) Peru comply with international standards on preventing negative social and environmental impacts of their operations on local communities.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135536","135536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882475","2018-04-18","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people previously convicted of (a) murder and (b) other killings have subsequently been convicted of carrying out additional killings after being released from prison in each year since 2010; and how many of those people had been serving (i) life and (ii) indeterminate sentences before being so released.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135537","135537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882476","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing the number of stopping services at East Midlands Parkway to support the growth of (a) the East Midlands Airport and (b) the economy in that region; and if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of specifying an increase in the number of stopping services at that station in the upcoming tender for that franchise in order to better serve passengers using East Midlands Airport.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135538","135538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882477","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of congestion on A-roads in the East Midlands.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135539","135539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882478","2018-04-17","Women and Equalities","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will provide a timeframe for the publication of the consultation on reform of the Gender Recognition Act 2004.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135540","135540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882479","2018-04-18","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 120003, how many photovoltaics installations through Green Deal plans provided by Home Energy Lifestyle Management Systems were undertaken in the Paisley and Renfrewshire North constituency.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135541","135541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882480","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many households in Paisley and Renfrewshire have accessed green deal finance through Home Energy Lifestyle Management Systems.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135542","135542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882481","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2018 to Question 134171, if he will publish every individual response to his Department's consultation, A democracy that works for everyone: British citizens overseas, in addition to the published summary of the responses received on 8 February 2018 in A democracy that works for everyone: British citizens overseas - Response to feedback to policy proposals.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135543","135543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882482","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of visits to accident and emergency departments were for minor ailments (a) in total, (b) by each strategic health authority until their abolition and (c) by each clinical commissioning group since they were set up in England in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135544","135544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882483","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of GP appointments for minor ailments that could have been treated at home or with advice from a pharmacy (a) in total, (b) by each strategic health authority until their abolition and (c) by each clinical commissioning group since they were set up in England in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135545","135545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882484","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on (a) how many occasions and (b) which class of train there have been reports of camera failure since the introduction of driver only operation services on Southern train services.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135546","135546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882485","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to add the maternal six week postnatal check to the General Medical Contract as recommended by the National Childbirth Trust.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135547","135547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882486","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he has taken to ensure that students with (a) autism and (b) specific learning difficulties are adequately accommodated by education providers at each level of their education.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135548","135548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882487","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what date the 1964 London Fisheries convention will cease to apply to the UK; and from that date all EU fishing vessels will be excluded from the UK's 6 to 12 nautical miles zone.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135549","135549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882488","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received from consumer rights organisations on reports of gas providers overcharging consumers and providing inadequate compensation and redress to those consumers.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135550","135550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882489","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the Government will review the system for redress and compensation to consumers who have been overcharged by energy companies.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135551","135551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882490","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received from sector organisations on reports of gas providers overcharging consumers and providing inadequate compensation and redress to those consumers.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135552","135552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882491","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with (a) sector organisations and (b) consumer rights organisations on reports of gas providers overcharging consumers and providing inadequate compensation and redress to those consumers.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135553","135553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882492","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of whether the funds invested under the Tier 1 Investor Visa scheme between 2008 and Q1 2015 remain in the UK financial system.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135554","135554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882493","2018-04-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether a formal risk register has been completed for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135555","135555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882494","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department's phone number for employment support allowance related queries will be changed to a freephone number.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135556","135556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882495","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many apprentices his Department directly employs.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135557","135557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882496","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to conclude its analysis of the offer of investment into Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon by the Welsh Government.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135558","135558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882497","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of eligible brain tumour patients with a glioma had their tumour tissue sample tested for 1p/19q co-deletion biomarker between 1 January 2017 and 31 December 2017.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135559","135559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882498","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of eligible brain tumour patients with a glioblastoma had their tumour tissue assessed for MGMT promoter hypermethylation status between 1 January 2016 and 31 December 2016.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135560","135560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882499","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of eligible brain tumour patients with a glioblastoma had their tumour tissue assessed for MGMT promoter hypermethylation status between 1 January 2017 and 31 December 2017.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135561","135561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882500","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has made representations to the Government of the UAE on the case of the Emirati human rights activist, Ahmed Mansoor.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135562","135562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882501","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of the increase in the state pension age for women on the entitlement to pension credit of men who are (a) married to and (b) live with those women.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135563","135563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882502","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 45 of the Government response to the First Report of the Justice Committee, Session 2017-19, HC 416, which Departments have reported on exemptions to the Ban the Box scheme in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135564","135564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882503","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the Government's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135565","135565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882504","2018-04-17","Attorney General","2018-04-13","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135566","135566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882505","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department has allocated to the Knife Crime Community Fund for 2018.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135567","135567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882506","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135568","135568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882507","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135569","135569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882508","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135570","135570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882509","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135571","135571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882510","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135572","135572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882511","2018-04-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135573","135573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882512","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of job roles advertised within her Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135574","135574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882513","2018-04-17","Department for International Trade","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135575","135575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882514","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135576","135576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882515","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of job roles advertised within her Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135577","135577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882516","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135578","135578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882517","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135579","135579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882518","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135580","135580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882519","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of job roles advertised within her Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the ban the box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135581","135581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882520","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135582","135582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882521","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135583","135583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882522","2018-04-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135584","135584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882523","2018-04-17","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of job roles advertised within her Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135585","135585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882524","2018-04-17","Scotland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135586","135586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882525","2018-04-17","Wales Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of job roles advertised within his Department in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 excluded the box under the Ban the Box initiative.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135587","135587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882526","2018-04-17","Wales Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135588","135588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882527","2018-04-17","Scotland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135589","135589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882528","2018-04-17","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what her Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135590","135590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882529","2018-04-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135591","135591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882530","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135592","135592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882531","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135593","135593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882532","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135594","135594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882533","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135595","135595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882534","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135596","135596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882535","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135597","135597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882536","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135598","135598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882537","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport,what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135599","135599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882538","2018-04-17","Department for International Trade","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135600","135600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882539","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135601","135601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882540","2018-04-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135602","135602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882541","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135603","135603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882542","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135604","135604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882543","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135605","135605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882544","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135606","135606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882545","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135607","135607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882546","2018-04-17","Attorney General","2018-04-13","To ask the Attorney General, what his Department's implementation plan is for banning the box on job applications.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135608","135608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882547","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many out-of-time visa applications were (a) processed within the standard service time (b) processed after six months and (c) processed after twelve months in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135609","135609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882548","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, on what date did each NHS trust in the North West sign up to NHS England's voluntary scheme to reduce the sale of sugar sweetened drinks in NHS canteens, shops and vending machines introduced in 2018; and which NHS trusts in that region have yet to sign up to that initiative.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135610","135610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882549","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many page views the online Civil Society Strategy consultation form has received since the start of that consultation.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135611","135611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882550","2018-04-18","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many responses his Department has received in respect of its consultation paper, Civil Society Strategy, published in February 2018.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135612","135612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882551","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what role his Department played in the UK Industrial Strategy Defence Sector deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135613","135613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882552","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for the conclusion of the UK Industrial Strategy Defence Sector deal; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135614","135614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882553","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the (a) sustainability and (b) competitiveness of the the UK defence radar sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135615","135615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882554","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has plans to support the expansion of the UK defence radar industrial footprint; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135616","135616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882555","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent discussions she has had with her counterparts at the United Nations on the inclusion of provisions on protection for internally displaced people in UN compacts on refugees and migration.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135617","135617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882556","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to support the long-term viability of the UK defence industrial sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135618","135618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882557","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of procuring a deployable long range air-defence radar; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135619","135619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882558","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to upgrade or replace the radar system to ensure a long range air-defence radar; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135620","135620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882559","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the economic effect of the Apprenticeship Levy on businesses in (a) England (b) the East Midlands (c) Mansfield constituency, since the levy was introduced.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135621","135621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882560","2018-04-18","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason the role of Crown Representative for the Voluntary, Community and Social Enterprise Sector was vacant between September 2014 and February 2018.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135622","135622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882561","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate he has made of the number of pupils in England who are (a) eligible and (b) not registered for free school meals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135623","135623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882562","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department plans to adopt the Scottish model of tariff-setting for specials.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135624","135624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882563","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the process is for setting the Specials Drug Tariff; and who is responsible for implementing that tariff.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135625","135625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882564","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Health Service Medical Supplies (Costs) Act 2017, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to regulate the costs of specials dispensed in community pharmacies.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135626","135626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882565","2018-04-17","Scotland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on land prices in rural areas throughout Scotland.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135627","135627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882566","2018-04-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to end the use of food labels which are likely to mislead consumers; and whether his Department plans to introduce mandatory labelling on the farming method used for (a) meat, (b) milk and (c) dairy products.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135628","135628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882567","2018-04-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what applications he has received from Milton Keynes Council for funding for (a) homelessness and (b) rough-sleeping projects since May 2014.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135629","135629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882568","2018-04-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for a Main Gate decision to be made on the Mechanised Infantry Vehicle programme.","Biography information for Nia Griffith","Nia Griffith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135630","135630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882569","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of  constituency enquiries by hon Members to the Complaints Resolution Team were not resolved within 15 working days.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135631","135631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882570","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when his Department plans to publish the findings of the investigation into the fridge identified as the seat of the fire at Grenfell Tower.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135632","135632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882571","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions his Department has had with Vertex on the cost supplying the drug Orkambi to the NHS.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135633","135633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882572","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to publish his Department's response to the consultation on accelerated degrees.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135634","135634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882573","2018-04-17","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with the Attorney General of Northern Ireland on the (a) efficiency and (b) effectiveness of the Public Prosecution Service of Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135635","135635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882574","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to tackle the falling rates of breast cancer screening across England, in patients aged between 50 and 70 years old.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135636","135636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882575","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to Question 126030 tabled on 31 January 2018, and Question 128803 tabled on 21 February 2018  by the hon. Member for Manchester Gorton.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135637","135637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882576","2018-04-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to prevent food retailers from using labelling to indicate that animals not reared outdoors were reared outside.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135638","135638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882577","2018-04-18","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that food labelling accurately indicates that  animals used to produce the meat were raised (a) indoors and (b) outdoors.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135639","135639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882578","2018-04-18","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies on UK aid to the Palestinian Authority of the decision by that Authority to pay directly the salaries of convicted terrorists.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135640","135640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882579","2018-04-18","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking in response to the Palestinian Authority’s announcement that it will revert to directly paying the salaries of convicted terrorists.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135641","135641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882580","2018-04-18","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the Palestinian Authority on the decision by that Authority to revert to paying directly the salaries of convicted terrorists.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135642","135642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882581","2018-04-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the revenue accrued to the public purse from Fibre Tax in each tax year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135643","135643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882582","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to abolish the Fibre Tax.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135644","135644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882583","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what provisions the Government plans to put in place to help people who have Lymphedema.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135645","135645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882584","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what support the Government provides to people who have Lymphedema.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135646","135646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882585","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for work commencing on the proposed duelling of the A1 road between Morpeth and Ellingham in Northumberland.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135647","135647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882586","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress has been made by the Government on the proposed re-opening of the Ashington, Tyne and Blyth train line in Northumberland.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135648","135648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882587","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for how long households will receive Support for Mortgage Interest as a benefit, if they have not been contacted by the Department about its change in policy by 5 April 2018.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135649","135649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882588","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure the effective operation of the Central Equine Database.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135650","135650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882589","2018-04-18","Scotland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department has spent on hospitality in each of the last eight years.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135651","135651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882590","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people whose income has increased above the standard minimum guarantee threshold for pension credit as a result of the April 2018 state pension increase.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135652","135652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882591","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to support vulnerable people who will become ineligible for pension credit and other passported benefits as a result of the April 2018 state pension increase taking their income above the standard minimum guarantee threshold for pension credit.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135653","135653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882592","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the affordable housing budget was in each of the last five years; and what proportion of that budget in each year was allocated to London.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135654","135654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882593","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much time it took on average to complete an assessment of an individual's social care needs (a) nationally, (b) in West Yorkshire and (c) in Hemsworth constituency in 2018.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135655","135655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882594","2018-04-18","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will respond to EDM 925, Professionalism and value of the British Civil Service.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135656","135656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882595","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 120003 on Home Energy and Lifestyle Management, how many photovoltaics installations through Green Deal plans provided by Home Energy Lifestyle Management Systems were undertaken in Airdrie and Shotts Constituency.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135657","135657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882596","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what controls are in place to protect customers from the use of formaldehyde in the production of MDF used for furniture.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135658","135658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882597","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of the published acceptable limits for formaldehyde released from MDF wood used in furniture.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135659","135659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882598","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of the published acceptable limits for formaldehyde in MDF furniture.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135660","135660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882599","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what service level agreements her Department has entered into with the UK Men's Sheds Association.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135661","135661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882600","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all eligibility decisions for continuing healthcare funding are made within 28 days.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135662","135662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882601","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to tackle variations in the number of people assessed as eligible to receive continuing healthcare funding in different regions of the UK.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135663","135663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882602","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March 2017 to Question 133491, what guidance her Department has issued to jobcentre staff to ensure that access to toilet facilities is available for customers with a disability.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135664","135664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882603","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the value of assets transferred was from each school under the control of the Wakefield City Academy Trust in each year that the Trust was responsible for the running of those schools.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135665","135665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882604","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what dates transfers of assets from budgets of schools under the control of the Wakefield City Academy Trust to the Trust were made.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135666","135666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882605","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when his Department was notified of concerns about the financial stability of the Wakefield City Academy Trust by the Schools Commissioner.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135667","135667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882606","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 March 2017 to Question 133491 on Government Departments: Disability, how many and what proportion of job centres have dedicated toilet facilities for customers with a disability.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135668","135668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882607","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether assets transferred from school budgets to the Wakefield City Academy Trust have been returned to schools as a result of the re-brokering of academy contracts.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135669","135669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882608","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to improve the scrutiny of (a) finances and (b) academic performance at academies as a result of the collapse of the Wakefield City Academy Trust.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135670","135670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882609","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will undertake a review of her Department's policy to only recognise implicit consent to act on peoples' behalf from MPs and their offices; and if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending that recognition further to (a) welfare rights groups (b) and Citizens Advice.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135671","135671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882610","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to strengthen the UN Verification and Inspection Mechanism for Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135672","135672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882611","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government has provided to the UN Verification and Inspection Mechanism for Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135673","135673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882612","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of people (a) applied for and (b) were granted continuing healthcare in 2017.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135674","135674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882613","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the economic merits of (a) maintaining and (b) improving the rail infrastructure in Merseyside.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135675","135675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882614","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the take-up of Healthy Start vouchers in England, and if he will published the ten local authorities with the (a) lowest and (b) highest rates of take-up of those vouchers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135676","135676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882615","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the publication of the Rail Accident Investigation Branch's investigation into the stranding of trains at Lewisham on the 2 March 2018.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135677","135677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882616","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure the sharing of best practice among local authorities on maximising the take-up of Healthy Start vouchers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135678","135678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882617","2018-04-17","Attorney General","2018-04-13","To ask the Attorney General, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135679","135679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882618","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals to the National Referral Mechanism for children aged under 18, had ticked criminal services (i.e. involved the commission of an offence by the victim) under section D of the referral form, in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135680","135680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882619","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals to the National Referral Mechanism for children aged under 18, had ticked yes for involvement in criminality highlighting involvement of adults under section E of the referral form in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135681","135681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882620","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals for children aged under 18 to the National Referral Mechanism had ticked the box suspicions for involvement in criminality highlighting involvement of adults under section E of the referral form in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135682","135682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882621","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals for children aged under 18 to the National Referral Mechanism had ticked yes for going missing and being found in areas where they have no known links under section E of the referral form in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135683","135683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882622","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135684","135684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882623","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135685","135685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882624","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135686","135686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882625","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135687","135687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882626","2018-04-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135688","135688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882627","2018-04-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union,  how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135689","135689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882628","2018-04-17","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) her Department and (ii) agencies of her Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135690","135690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882629","2018-04-17","Department for International Trade","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135691","135691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882630","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he will take steps to ensure that the Rail Accident Investigation Branch's investigation into the incident outside of Lewisham station on the 2 March 2018 will also investigate the incident which took place on the 5 April 2018 outside Lewisham station.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135692","135692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882631","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135693","135693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882632","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135694","135694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882633","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135695","135695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882634","2018-04-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135696","135696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882635","2018-04-17","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135697","135697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882636","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) her Department and (ii) agencies of her Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135698","135698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882637","2018-04-18","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his Department's press release, Defence Secretary boosts Britain's chemical defence capability as threat intensifies, published on 15 March 2018, how much of the £48m investment in a new Chemical Weapons Defence Centre is for (a) capital and (b) revenue spending.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135699","135699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882638","2018-04-17","Ministry of Defence","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135700","135700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882639","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135701","135701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882640","2018-04-17","Ministry of Justice","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135702","135702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882641","2018-04-17","Northern Ireland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) her Department and (ii) agencies of her Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135703","135703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882642","2018-04-17","Scotland Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135704","135704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882643","2018-04-17","Wales Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many (a) direct employees, (b) agency staff and (c) outsourced staff working for (i) his Department and (ii) agencies of his Department are paid less than the living wage, as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135705","135705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882644","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the under-spend in the Flexible Support Fund in each of the last five financial years for which data is available; and to where those funds were reallocated.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135706","135706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882645","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress her Department has made on enabling new legacy benefit claimants to submit their supporting documents electronically via a secure online portal.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135707","135707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882646","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of enabling travel expenses for claimants of the flexible support fund to be paid up front instead of in arrears.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135708","135708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882647","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many postal signers for universal credit there were in the last 12 months for which data is available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135709","135709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882648","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government has taken to tackle owners of empty residential properties relabelling those properties as second homes to avoid the empty home Council Tax surcharge.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135710","135710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882649","2018-04-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to Written Statement of 21 December 2017 on Leasehold and Commonhold Reform, HCWS384, what progress he has made on the actions outlined in that Statement; and whether a review of estate charges will be part of this work.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135711","135711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882650","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of the (a) timeliness and (b) effectiveness of the processing of Hardship Payments for sanctioned claimants.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135712","135712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882651","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to stop claimants on low incomes from being charged by GPs for the supply of supporting medical information for claims for benefit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135713","135713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882652","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of introducing a grace period for (a) vulnerable and (b) homeless claimants of (i) jobseekers allowance and (ii) employment support allowance during which the requirements placed on them are eased at times of transition or acute difficulty.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135714","135714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882653","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to (a) track and (b) record the destinations of claimants who have been sanctioned.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135715","135715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882654","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps she is taking to ensure that (a) disentitled and (b) sanctioned claimants of (i) jobseekers allowance and (ii) employment support allowance retain their entitlement to Housing Benefit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135716","135716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882655","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of expenditure of local authorities on local welfare assistance schemes.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135717","135717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882656","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many Section 215 (Town and Country Planning Act 1990) notices have been issued by local authorities in the past year; and what proportion of those notices resulted in successful (a) remedial action and (b) direct action for non-compliance.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135718","135718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882657","2018-04-17","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that children registered for free school meals access a hot meal each day; and which agency is responsible for the enforcement of the standards of free school meals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135719","135719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882658","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that local authorities are able to use Council Tax data effectively for the enforcement of (a) the empty home Council Tax surcharge, (b) Empty Dwelling Management Orders and (c) other enforcement measures.","Biography information for Alex Chalk","Alex Chalk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135720","135720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882659","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost was to the public purse of the New Enterprise Allowance in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016/17 and (c) 2017/18; and what estimate she has made of the projected cost for 2018-19.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135721","135721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882660","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the Government's policy is on the pension rights of senior civil servants who have been convicted of a criminal offence connected to their work and subsequently dismissed from the civil service.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135722","135722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882661","2018-04-18","Treasury","2018-04-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the cost to public purse of the wedding between Prince Harry and Meghan Markle.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135723","135723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882662","2018-04-18","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to her Department's press release, Explaining British support for Palestinian education, published on 1 April 2018, how her Department plans to conduct the assessment of the Palestinian curriculum; and what plans she has to publish that assessment.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135724","135724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882663","2018-04-18","Department for International Development","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to her Department's press release, Explaining British support for Palestinian education, published on 1 April 2018, what steps her Department plans to take if there is evidence of material that incites violence in the Palestinian curriculum.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135725","135725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882664","2018-04-18","Department for International Trade","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many UK arms export licenses have been granted to Israel in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135726","135726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882665","2018-04-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what progress the Government is making in securing the maintenance of mutual recognition of professional qualifications after the UK leaves the EU and the expiry of the implementation period.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135727","135727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882666","2018-04-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what recent steps the Government has taken to secure a formal agreement with Euratom after the UK leaves the EU and the expiry of the implementation period.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135728","135728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882667","2018-04-17","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what progress the Government is making in negotiations with the European Union on reciprocal arrangements for health care in the UK and the EU after the (a) UK leaves the EU and (b) expiry of the implementation period.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135729","135729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882668","2018-04-17","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government plans to continue to participate in the European Reference Networks for patients with complex or rare medical conditions after the UK leaves the EU and the expiry of the implementation period.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135730","135730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882669","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the article entitled Tory housing minister Dominic Raab warns that immigration has pushed up house prices, published by the Times on 8 April 2018, if he will publish the analysis conducted by his Department on the effect of immigration on property prices in the last 25 years.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135731","135731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882670","2018-04-17","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if the Government will make an assessment of the effect of the youth full-time social action programme on social mobility.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135732","135732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882671","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the conclusions and recommendations of the Age UK report entitled Why call it care when nobody cares?, published in March 2018.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135733","135733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882672","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of people (a) with hearing loss and (b) who list their primary medical condition as difficulty in hearing who were (i) in employment, (ii) economically inactive and (iii) unemployed in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135734","135734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882673","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of people (a) with hearing loss and (b) who list their primary medical condition as difficulty in hearing who were recorded as being economically inactive for the reason of (i) being a student, (ii) looking after family or home, (iii) being temporarily sick, (iv) being long-term sick, (v) being a discouraged worker, (vi) being retired and (vii) other reasons in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135735","135735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882674","2018-04-17","Cabinet Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of people (a) with hearing loss and (b) who list their primary medical condition as difficulty in hearing in employment who were in employment as (i) an employee, (ii) self-employed, (iii) unpaid family workers and (iv) part of a Government supported training and employment programme in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135736","135736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882675","2018-04-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will place a copy of any unpublished evidence held by his Department on the effect of immigration on house prices in the Library of the House of Commons.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135737","135737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882676","2018-04-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of immigration on house prices.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135738","135738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882677","2018-04-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pension, what estimate she has made of the cost incurred by (a) Jobcentre Plus, (b) her Department and (c) any other public agency in the preparation for the roll-out of the now aborted cut to housing benefit for 18-21 year olds.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135739","135739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882678","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to review hate crime legislation to tackle social media hate speech directed towards ethnic minority groups.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135740","135740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882679","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 29 March 2018 to Question 134184, whether his Department has plans to start collecting data on the number of children sent out of area to receive mental health treatment.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135741","135741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882680","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of men entitled to shared parental leave have taken such leave since its introduction.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135742","135742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882681","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government on the relationship between planning and the identification of minerals as a productivity foundation as set out in the Industrial Strategy.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135743","135743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882682","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of which is the cheapest form of electricity generation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135744","135744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882683","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children born in the UK are ineligible to access public funds as a result of their parents having no recourse to public funds.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135745","135745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882684","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children in the UK are ineligible to access public funds a result of their parents having no recourse to public funds.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135746","135746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882685","2018-04-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made the political situation in Sierra Leone’s since the presidential elections in April 2018; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure peace and stability in that country.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135747","135747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882686","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimates he has made of the financial costs to leaseholders in tower blocks as a result of incurring charges to (a) fund continuous waking watch fire patrols as a result of unsafe aluminium composite material cladding and (b) replace such cladding.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135748","135748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882687","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to support leaseholders of tower blocks incurring costs to replace unsafe aluminium composite material cladding installed by local government or housing association freeholders.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135749","135749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882688","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to support leaseholders in tower blocks who are unable to afford requested charges to (a) fund continuous waking watch fire patrols as a result of unsafe aluminium composite material cladding and (b) replace such cladding.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135750","135750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882689","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that aluminium composite material cladding on tower blocks that has failed Building Research Establishment tests is replaced.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135751","135751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882690","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what (a) procedures and (b) funding his Department has in place to provide alternative accommodation to leaseholders in a tower block in the event that that tower block is evacuated as a consequence of unsafe aluminium composite material cladding.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135752","135752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882691","2018-04-17","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what (a) procedures and (b) funding his Department has in place to provide alternative accommodation to social housing tenants in a tower block in the event that that tower block is evacuated as a consequence of unsafe aluminium composite material cladding.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135753","135753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882692","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the soft drinks industry levy on diabetics who may regularly buy drinks that are high in sugar.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135754","135754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882693","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of tier 4 visa applications for students have been processed within the service level agreement timescales in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135755","135755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882694","2018-04-17","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many tier 4 applications that have not been processed within the timescale set out in the service level agreement for processing such applications have caused students to miss university start dates in the latest academic for year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135756","135756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882695","2018-04-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to deter fraudulent applications for state benefits.","Biography information for Lee Rowley","Lee Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135757","135757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882696","2018-04-18","Department for Education","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to increase the uptake of physics and chemistry at A-level.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135758","135758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882697","2018-04-18","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the studies from Deloitte, Frontier Economics and LaingBuisson on the effect of sleep-in back payments on the social care sector will (a) include and (b) publish information on the financial impact for the Brighton and Hove Council area.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135759","135759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882698","2018-04-17","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits enabling people with autism to qualify as Blue Badge holders.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135760","135760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882699","2018-04-18","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many affordable homes have been built as part of Ebbsfleet Garden City; and how many of those home are for (a) social rent, (b) shared ownership, (c) affordable rent and (d) other affordable housing.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135761","135761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882700","2018-04-18","Home Office","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of personal robberies in each London boroughs, in each of the last twelve months for which information is available.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135762","135762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882701","2018-04-18","Department for Transport","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will make an assessment of the adequacy of funding provision for the electrification of rail services operating through West Lancashire.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135763","135763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/882702","2018-04-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-04-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for the Cabinet Office and Paymaster General of 2 November 2016, Official Report, column 879, what progress his Department has made in using the 2011 census classifications that differentiate Gypsies and Travellers.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135764","135764"
