"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425464","2015-11-04","Prime Minister","2015-11-02","To ask the Prime Minister, what recent discussions he has had with President Xi of China on joint multilateral initiatives the UK and China can take towards nuclear disarmament.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14432","14432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425465","2015-11-04","Scotland Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14375","14375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425466","2015-11-05","Scotland Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2015 to Question 13632, on what dates in September 2015 he met (a) the Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) other ministers in HM Treasury to discuss the potential effects in Scotland of a carbon price support exemption scheme.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14337","14337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425467","2015-11-05","Scotland Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2015 to Question 13632, on what dates in June 2015 he met (a) the Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) other ministers in HM Treasury to discuss the potential effects in Scotland of a carbon price support exemption scheme.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14338","14338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425468","2015-11-05","Scotland Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2015 to Question 13632, on what dates in July 2015 he met (a) the Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) other ministers in HM Treasury to discuss the potential effects in Scotland of a carbon price support exemption scheme.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14339","14339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425469","2015-11-05","Scotland Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2015 to Question 13632, on what dates in August 2015 he met (a) the Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) other ministers in HM Treasury to discuss the potential effects in Scotland of a carbon price support exemption scheme.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14340","14340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425470","2015-11-05","Scotland Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2015 to Question 13632, on what dates in May 2015 he met (a) the Chancellor of the Exchequer and (b) other ministers in HM Treasury to discuss the potential effects in Scotland of a carbon price support exemption scheme.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14341","14341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425471","2015-11-05","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-11-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what plans are in place for monitoring the EU referendum.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14326","14326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425472","2015-11-05","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-11-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how many people on the electoral register on 7 May 2015 were (a) registered under individual electoral registration, (b) data matched and (c) carried over from the old register in each London borough.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14321","14321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425473","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the current shortage of Certificate of Professional Competence qualified drivers is for the logistics industry; and what the shortage forecast for such drivers is expected to be in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2016-17 and (c) 2017-18.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14319","14319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425474","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will ensure that the bidding process for the Great Eastern Main Line franchise includes increased service frequency and improved train capacity.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14342","14342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425475","2015-11-04","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) passenger vehicles, (b) vans, (c) public service vehicles and (d) heavy goods vehicles are licensed; and how many vehicles in each such category (i) use petrol, (ii) use diesel and (iii) are hybrid.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14349","14349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425476","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the cost of acquiring a Certificate in Professional Competence on access to such certificates for young people.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14308","14308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425477","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on businesses in the Humber area of the shortage of Certificate of Professional Competence qualified drivers.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14309","14309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425478","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the economic cost of the shortage of Certificate of Professional Competence qualified drivers.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14310","14310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425479","2015-11-04","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the reduction was in his Department's support for bus funding in England in 2014-15.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14281","14281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425480","2015-11-04","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14376","14376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425481","2015-11-04","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Office of Road and Rail (ORR) monitoring framework; and what guidance he has provided to the ORR as it develops its enforcement plan.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14400","14400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425482","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Highways England on the appointment of a programme management partner; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14426","14426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425483","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the respective roles of (a) Highways England and (b) its proposed programme management partner in the delivery of the Road Investment Strategy Programme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14425","14425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425484","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what publications his private office subscribes to.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14418","14418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425485","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) his Department's and (b) HS2 Ltd's capital and resource expenditure has been on High Speed 2 in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14447","14447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425486","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2015 to Question 13286, whether any additional projects have been paused but not announced by Network Rail.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14449","14449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425487","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what framework of work Highways England is negotiating with the CH2M Hill/Mace/PwC consortium.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14446","14446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425488","2015-11-05","Department for Transport","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2015 to Question 4759, if he will update the benefit-cost ratio for Great Western electrification given in that Answer to reflect the revised cost estimate for that electrification project confirmed in oral evidence by Mark Carne of the Committee of Public Accounts, on Network Rail: planning and delivery of 2014-19 rail investment programme, HC473, Q1, on 21 October 2015.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14462","14462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425489","2015-11-04","Wales Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on the proposed Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14435","14435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425490","2015-11-04","Wales Office","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14378","14378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425491","2015-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the value of stationery that has been (a) lost and (b) stolen from his Department in each of the last five fiscal years; and what the cost was of replacing such stationery.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14379","14379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425492","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September 2015 to the hon. Member for Inverness, Nairn, Badenoch and Strathspey to Question 9852, by when his Department will be able to form a reliable estimate of the number of disability living allowance recipients who are Motability users who will not qualify for the enhanced rate of the personal independence payment mobility component.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14444","14444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425493","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that small and medium-sized businesses are aware of their obligations relating to workplace pensions.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14445","14445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425494","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his oral evidence to the Work and Pensions Committee of 28 October 2015, for how long a welfare rights adviser has been placed in the Birkenhead food bank; and when he plans to roll-out the placement of such advisers to all food banks.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14467","14467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425495","2015-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time is for a disability benefit appeal to reach a tribunal; and what steps he is taking to reduce that average time.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14287","14287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425496","2015-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the average time it takes in Birmingham for a disability benefit appeal to reach a tribunal; and what assessment he has made of the effect of that average time on the financial position of appellants.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14288","14288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425497","2015-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many delays to benefit payments there were in (a) Gloucester, (b) the South West and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14329","14329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425498","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department has given to micro-businesses in adapting to new automatic enrolment pension schemes.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14316","14316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425499","2015-11-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of his proposals for automatic enrolment of employees in pension schemes on businesses with fewer than 10 employees.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14313","14313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425689","2015-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect on air quality of levels of emissions from motor vehicles.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902028","902028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425690","2015-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to promote regional food and drink.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902020","902020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425770","2015-11-05","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2015-11-02","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what discussions the Speaker's Committee has had on the extent of electoral fraud; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902013","902013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426371","2015-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she has taken to ensure that dairy farmers receive a fair and sustainable price for their produce.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902032","902032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/426372","2015-11-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-11-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the National Pollinator Strategy since its publication in November 2014.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 902034","902034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425052","2015-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what material and financial support his Department is providing to people made redundant in the steel industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14187","14187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425053","2015-11-04","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Government's proposal to freeze the earnings threshold for plan 2 student loans on the cost of attending university.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14204","14204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425054","2015-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the finding of the Equality and Human Rights Commission in its report, Is Britain Fairer, published in October 2015, that the employment gap between the oldest and youngest age groups has increased.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14195","14195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425055","2015-11-03","Women and Equalities","2015-10-30","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the finding of the Equality and Human Rights Commission in its report, Is Britain Fairer, published in October 2015, that there are persistent gender pay gaps among graduates.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14197","14197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425056","2015-11-03","Women and Equalities","2015-10-30","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the findings of the Equality and Human Rights Commission in its report, Is Britain Fairer, published in October 2015, that (a) there are persistent gender pay gaps among graduates and (b) employment and earnings premiums among graduates are lower for women than for men.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14196","14196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425057","2015-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the finding of the Equality and Human Rights Commission in its report, Is Britain Fairer, published in October 2015, that up to 2013 there was a decline in both earnings and full-time employment for younger workers, despite them being more likely to be better qualified than previous generations.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14198","14198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425058","2015-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 5.2 of the Equality and Human Rights Commission report, Is Britain Fairer, published October 2015, what steps he plans to take to address that report's conclusion that the employment rate for young people has fallen and the unemployment rate has risen, even accounting for increased participation in education.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14203","14203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425059","2015-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much centrally-provided capital funding has been provided to each further education college in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14240","14240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425060","2015-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to investigate companies which sell improperly trained dogs as special guide dogs for disabled children.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14244","14244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425061","2015-11-04","Cabinet Office","2015-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, in what circumstances major Government programmes are exempted from the requirement for Gateway Reviews.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14168","14168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425062","2015-11-04","Cabinet Office","2015-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, in what circumstances major Government programmes are subjected to Project Assessment Reviews instead of Gateway Reviews; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14169","14169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425063","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will (a) incorporate natural capital into the national infrastructure plan, (b) take steps to ensure that new man-made infrastructure projects do not deplete the UK's natural capital asset base and (c) prioritise investment in natural capital.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14161","14161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425064","2015-11-03","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps HM Revenue and Customs has taken to shorten waiting times for customers.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14163","14163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425065","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to assess, mitigate and monitor macro-economic risks associated with trends in (a) environmental degradation, (b) resource scarcity, (c) climate change and (d) other aspects of the natural environment.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14156","14156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425066","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what work his Department is undertaking to contribute to the development of the Government's 25 year plan for nature.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14157","14157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425067","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Government's report, Fixing the Foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, Cm9098, published July 2015, what steps he has taken to increase the quantity and quality of apprenticeships in accordance with that report's recommendations.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14236","14236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425068","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish his Department's Business Tax Roadmap.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14254","14254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425069","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish an update on the delivery of the National Infrastructure Plan.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14255","14255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425070","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the interim recommendations of Sir Charles Bean's review of the quality, delivery and governance of local statistics.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14256","14256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425071","2015-11-03","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department allocated to pay staff of HM Revenue and Customs to deal with enquiries from hon. Members relating to constituents' concerns about tax credits in (a) 2015-16 and (b) each of the three previous years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14225","14225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425072","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the effect on revenue to the Exchequer of allowing devolved local authorities to keep 100 per cent of the business rates raised from car parks in (a) the UK, (b) England and (c) Wiltshire in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14260","14260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425073","2015-11-03","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the earnings from UK overseas assets were in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14215","14215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425074","2015-11-03","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the likely level of earnings from UK overseas assets over the next 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14214","14214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425075","2015-11-04","HM Treasury","2015-10-30","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to encourage manufacturing.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14171","14171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425076","2015-11-04","Department for Transport","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will improve access to pavements for wheelchair users.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14207","14207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425077","2015-11-04","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure the delivery of superfast broadband to the remaining five per cent of properties which do not have access to it in (a) Northamptonshire and (b) England.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14263","14263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425078","2015-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of his Department's likely civilian personnel strength on 1 April (a) 2016 and (b) 2020 for each top level budget.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14252","14252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425079","2015-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's (a) 2015 and (b) 2020 liability baseline is for service personnel for each top level budget.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14253","14253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425080","2015-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when his Department last completed an assessment of the whole life cost of the Successor programme.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14158","14158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425081","2015-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library copies of the service capitation rates for (a) Navy, (b) Army and (c) Air Command.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14210","14210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425082","2015-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which category (a) A, (b) B, and (c) C projects are managed by (i) Navy Command, (ii) Army Command, (iii) Air Command, (iv) Joint Forces Command and (v) the Strategic Programmes Directorate.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14212","14212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425083","2015-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the crew complement by (a) rank and (b) specialisation is for the (i) A400M, (ii) C-17, (iii) C-130J and (iv) Voyager.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14213","14213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425084","2015-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library the most recent quarterly assessment of the Force Elements at Readiness.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14211","14211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425085","2015-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the Commonwealth War Graves Commission on transferring to that Commission responsibility for the maintenance of military graves currently maintained by his Department.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14258","14258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425086","2015-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to transfer responsibility for military graves maintained by his Department to the Commonwealth War Graves Commission.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14259","14259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425087","2015-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the annual average cost to the Ministry of Defence of (a) maintaining each grave for which it is responsible and (b) the value of the grant made to the Commonwealth War Graves Commission in respect of each grave maintained by that Commission.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14257","14257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425088","2015-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which ongoing operations are funded by the core defence budget; and what the expenditure on each such operation was in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14223","14223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425089","2015-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place a copy of his Department's JSP 892 Risk Management in the Library.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14224","14224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425090","2015-11-04","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of UK military activity in Syria in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14221","14221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425091","2015-11-03","Department for Education","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of teacher training degrees incorporate modules on working with children aged 0 to 5 years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14154","14154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425092","2015-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what meetings she has had with Jobcentre Plus to discuss measures to help redundant onshore wind workers back into employment; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14155","14155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425093","2015-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what meetings she has had with Jobcentre Plus to discuss measures to help redundant onshore wind workers back into employment; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14199","14199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425094","2015-11-04","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the likely proportion of total UK energy production which will be solar energy in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14235","14235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425095","2015-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research her Department is funding on the effects of climate change on agricultural production in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14219","14219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425096","2015-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many greyhounds have been euthanized upon completion of their racing career in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14227","14227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425097","2015-11-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2015 to Question 13690, what estimate she has made of the cost of implementing her Department's Great Britain Invasive Non-native Species Strategy, published August 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14234","14234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425098","2015-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, at what intervals her Department receives accident and injury data on (a) racing and (b) retired greyhounds from (i) the Greyhound Board of Great Britain and (ii) individual greyhound tracks.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14228","14228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425099","2015-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate her Department has made of the number of (a) licensed and (b) unlicensed dog breeders operating in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14229","14229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425100","2015-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of dogs that have been put to sleep for meeting the physical characteristics of a banned breed under section 1 of the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14230","14230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425101","2015-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance her Department provides to dog legislation officers on enforcing section 1 of the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14231","14231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425102","2015-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect of the Dangerous Dogs Act 1991 on the number of pitbull terriers in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14232","14232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425103","2015-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information her Department holds on the number of greyhounds which retired from racing in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14233","14233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425104","2015-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she expects work on a long-term strategy for UK food and farming to conclude; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14216","14216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425105","2015-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the most significant key risks to the UK's food security; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14217","14217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425106","2015-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much and what proportion of UK agricultural output was used in the production of biofuels in each year from 2000-01 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14218","14218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425107","2015-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the (a) Iraqi and (b) Iranian authorities on the missile attack on Camp Liberty, Baghdad, on 29 October 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14159","14159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425108","2015-11-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to publish the report of the review into the Muslim Brotherhood; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14208","14208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425109","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on treating age-related macular degeneration in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14193","14193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425110","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what arrangements are in place for assessing a patient's eye health on discharge from hospital.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14194","14194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425111","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on treating patients with glaucoma in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14190","14190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425112","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on treating patients with diabetic retinopathy in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14191","14191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425113","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether standard patient health assessments by GPs include assessing eye health.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14192","14192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425114","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted to mental health hospitals outside of their home local authority area in (a) England and (b) London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14188","14188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425115","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will request that NICE publishes its reasons for including a recommendation on the use of C-reactive protein testing for patients presenting with lower respiratory tract infection in primary care in its guidance on pneumonia but not in its pneumonia draft quality statement.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14209","14209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425116","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average bed occupancy rate was in each mental health hospital in London in each month since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14181","14181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425117","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many admissions there were to psychiatric inpatient wards for psychosis in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14182","14182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425118","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average bed occupancy rate was in each hospital trust in London in each month since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14183","14183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425119","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions bed occupancy rates reached (a) 85, (b) 90, (c) 95 and (d) 100 per cent in each mental health hospital in London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14184","14184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425120","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions patients were granted weekend leave in each mental health hospital in London in each month since 1 January 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14185","14185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425121","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of people likely to have age-related macular degeneration in 2050.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14226","14226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425122","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the (a) potential effect on the number of antibiotic and (b) potential change in annual prescription and dispensing costs prescriptions of using C-reactive protein testing for patients presenting with respiratory tract infections in primary care.","Biography information for Maggie Throup","Maggie Throup","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14222","14222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425123","2015-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the proportion of medical research spending which is spent on eye disease.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14200","14200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425124","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of trends in the costs of treating sight loss and eye health problems.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14201","14201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425125","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent tackling the effects of sight loss in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14202","14202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425126","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the availability of comparative information on and screening for prostate cancer.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14175","14175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425127","2015-11-04","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the recommendations of the Lancet Commission on liver disease, published in November 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14170","14170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425128","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to increase awareness of prostate cancer.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14178","14178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425129","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of an annual screening programme on early detection of prostate cancer.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14176","14176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425130","2015-11-16","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to support prostate cancer awareness campaigns and screening programmes.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14177","14177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425131","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reasons are for the time taken to inform families involved in Selective Dorsal Rhizotomy procedures that funding for those procedures will cease.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14238","14238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425132","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons funding for Selective Dorsal Rhizotomy is due to cease in March 2016.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14239","14239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425133","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of funding special guide dogs for children with autism.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14245","14245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425134","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 21 of his Department's Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme, published in December 2013, when he plans to publish information on the comparative use of medicines in the NHS referred to in that document; by which channels he plans that information to be published; what plans he has to communicate that information proactively through the NHS; whether he intends to communicate that information to patients; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14247","14247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425135","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 21 of his Department's Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme, published in December 2013, when he plans to refresh the annual indicators arising from the Pharmaceutical Industry Competitiveness Taskforce referred to in that document; if he will make it his policy to include (a) medicines expenditure per head of population, (b) market sales as a percentage of GDP and (c) average pricing and reimbursement delays in the set of those indicators; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14248","14248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425136","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what payments have been made to the devolved administrations under the 2014 Pharmaceutical Price Regulation Scheme to date; on which date each such payment was made; what methodology is used to calculate the level of such payments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14249","14249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425137","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 21 of the Pharmaceutical Price Regulations Scheme, what steps he is taking to encourage academic health science networks to translate research into practice.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14250","14250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425138","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to publicise the innovation scorecard to (a) NHS organisations and (b) members of the public.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14251","14251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425139","2015-11-03","Home Office","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many historic crimes will feature in this year's crime figures.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14165","14165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425140","2015-11-03","Home Office","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will ensure that at least 1,000 refugees are resettled in the UK before Christmas 2015.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14166","14166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425141","2015-11-04","Home Office","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2015 to Question 12246, how many criminal operations have been smashed by the Organised Immigration Crime Task Force to date.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14162","14162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425142","2015-11-04","House of Commons Commission","2015-10-30","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, if he will take steps to ensure that the parliament.uk website states the country in which hon. Members' constituencies are located.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14160","14160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425143","2015-11-03","House of Commons Commission","2015-10-30","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what estimate the Commission has made of the savings from ending the printing of Acts of Parliament on vellum; and what proportion of those savings arises from (a) William Cowley and (b) other costs from the use of vellum.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14164","14164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425144","2015-11-06","Department for International Development","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, on what grounds UK aid is given to countries on the EU Commission tax haven blacklist.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14172","14172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425145","2015-11-06","Department for International Development","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many countries on the EU Commission tax haven blacklist, or identified as zero tax jurisdictions, received UK aid in financial years 2013-14 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14173","14173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425146","2015-11-06","Department for International Development","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much UK aid was provided to countries on the EU Commission tax haven blacklist or identified as zero tax jurisdictions in the financial years 2013-14 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14174","14174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425147","2015-11-04","Home Office","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) search and (b) surveillance warrants issued by a judge have been subject to judicial review in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14186","14186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425148","2015-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which three EU countries have the largest number of foreign nationals in UK prisons; and how many such prisoners there are from each of those countries.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14264","14264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425149","2015-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will request that the Parole Board publish the basis on which it took the decision to release Harry Roberts from prison in October 2014.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14246","14246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425150","2015-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when his Department plans to answer Question 13074, on Ministry of Justice: Public Expenditure, tabled by the hon. Member for Hammersmith on 22 October 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14261","14261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425151","2015-11-04","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to answer Question 12150, on HM Courts and Tribunals Service: Procurement, tabled by the hon. Member for Hammersmith on 15 October 2015.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14262","14262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425152","2015-11-04","Cabinet Office","2015-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy that no Department be permitted to (a) employ staff at wages below the living wage and (b) sign a contract with contractors who pay their staff less than the living wage.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14179","14179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425153","2015-11-04","Scotland Office","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, for what reason his Department's three most recently published quarterly returns were all published on the same day.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14206","14206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425154","2015-11-04","Department for Transport","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it is his policy to require the new TransPennine Express franchise to include direct Hull, Leeds and Manchester services at the same frequency as is currently provided.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14205","14205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425155","2015-11-04","Department for Transport","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the contribution that the Hoo Green to Bamfurlong spur of High Speed 2 is likely to make to reducing capacity constraints on the West Coast Main Line; and what account that estimate takes of (a) rail freight and (b) passenger services to Warrington Bank Quay and elsewhere.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14180","14180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425156","2015-11-03","Department for Transport","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of how many (a) drivers and (b) drivers under 25 were using black box technology in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14189","14189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425157","2015-11-04","Department for Transport","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has for replacement of the HST 125 trains on the Midland mainline.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14265","14265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425158","2015-11-03","Department for Transport","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of emissions containing organo-phosphates produced by aircraft engines on airline and airport staff and passengers.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14237","14237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425159","2015-11-04","Department for Transport","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to increase the frequency of train services to north-east Essex along the Great Eastern Main Line.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14220","14220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425160","2015-11-03","Department for Transport","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of how many subsidised bus routes have been withdrawn since 2010.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14242","14242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425161","2015-11-03","Department for Transport","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to fund Bikeability beyond 2015.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14243","14243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425162","2015-11-03","Department for Transport","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's plans are for long-term local sustainable transport funding.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14241","14241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425163","2015-11-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-30","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason the universal credit programme was subject to Project Assessment Reviews instead of Gateway Reviews.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14167","14167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425164","2015-11-04","Cabinet Office","2015-10-30","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress the Government has made on increasing the rate of employment in (a) Northamptonshire and (b) England since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14266","14266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424837","2015-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the annual budget for the Employment Agency Standards Inspectorate was in 2011-12.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14006","14006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424838","2015-11-03","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many primates were imported into the UK for scientific research purposes in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14011","14011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424839","2015-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to encourage retailers to reduce the amount of food waste they produce; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14012","14012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424840","2015-11-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of progress by the Aerospace Technology Institute on reaching its goal of reducing fuel emissions by 20 per cent over the next 20 years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14031","14031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424841","2015-11-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the 2013 Lough Erne G8 Leaders' Communiqu, published on 18 June 2013, what progress has been made on implementing the commitments in paragraph 9 of that document; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14089","14089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424842","2015-11-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what average time his Department took to respond to Freedom of Information requests in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14057","14057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424843","2015-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent progress he has made on publishing a statutory code for pub companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14115","14115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424844","2015-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what he plans for the size of the stake which the Government will retain in the Green Investment Bank to be after that bank's privatisation.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14148","14148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424845","2015-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans his Department has for the 1.8 billion of uncommitted Green Investment Bank funds following privatisation of that bank.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14149","14149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424846","2015-11-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he, his ministers and his officials have had with the European Commission on the situation in the steel industry.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14150","14150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424847","2015-11-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what ability the Government plans to retain to ensure that the Green Investment Bank operates according to its original purposes after that body's privatisation.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14108","14108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424848","2015-11-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans the Government has for potential financial proceeds from the privatisation of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14109","14109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424849","2015-11-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Government intends to raise from privatisation of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14107","14107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424850","2015-11-03","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who has been appointed to the Community Engagement Forum; what criteria were used to make those appointments; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14141","14141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424851","2015-11-02","Cabinet Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2015 to Question 13434, on Cabinet Committees: Airports, under what circumstances (a) full minutes, (b) dates of and (c) other information about such meetings would be published.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14044","14044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424852","2015-11-02","Cabinet Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what attacks have been made against the Government Gateway system to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14047","14047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424853","2015-11-03","Cabinet Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the Written Statement of 16 July 2015 by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary, Cabinet Office, HCWS 127, on individual electoral registration, how much of the funding referred to in that statement has been allocated to each electoral registration office in England.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14037","14037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424854","2015-11-03","Cabinet Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the potential sale of information stolen during the cyber-security breach of the Government Gateway system.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14038","14038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424855","2015-11-03","Cabinet Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he plans to take to contact people whose personal details have been stolen as a result of the cyber-security breach of the Government Gateway system.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13981","13981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424856","2015-11-03","HM Treasury","2015-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs spent on (a) IT systems and (b) cyber-security in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14, (v) 2014-15 and (vi) 2015-16 to date.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14000","14000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424857","2015-11-03","HM Treasury","2015-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what alternative sources of advice there are for people exercising pension freedoms who do not access Pension Wise guidance.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14018","14018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424858","2015-11-03","HM Treasury","2015-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2015 to Question 12045, on tax credits, if he will publish that data in the form in which it is available.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14126","14126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424859","2015-11-03","HM Treasury","2015-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many independent tribunals have been brought to challenge mandatory reconsiderations of tax credits by Concentrix in each month since that company has been under contract with his Department.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14147","14147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424860","2015-11-03","HM Treasury","2015-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2015 to Question 12791, on married people: tax allowances, what the best telephone number is for customers to use; and what rate that telephone line charges.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14045","14045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424861","2015-11-03","HM Treasury","2015-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the 2013 Lough Erne G8 Leaders' Communiqu, published on 18 June 2013, what progress has been made on implementing the commitments in paragraphs (a) 1, (b) 2, (c) 3, (d) 8 and (e) 10 of that document; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14136","14136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424862","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to increase participation in all-employee tax-advantaged share plans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14111","14111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424863","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will ensure that save-as-you-earn and share incentive plan savings limits are increased in line with inflation on an annual basis.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14112","14112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424864","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of how many low and middle income earners save and invest in a save-as-you-earn employee share plan.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14113","14113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424865","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking encourage the Prudential Regulation Authority to assist credit unions in expanding the services they offer to their members; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14104","14104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424866","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-29","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to permit private equity-backed companies to offer tax-advantaged all employee share plans; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14110","14110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424867","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department has allocated to each local authority in London per head of population in each year since 2010-11; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14105","14105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424868","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has made to ensure that the homelessness prevention grant is being used effectively.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14099","14099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424869","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to allocate the homelessness prevention grant in proportion to the level of need in each local authority.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14097","14097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424870","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department has taken to safeguard the size of the homelessness prevention grant in the period up to the 2020 spending review.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14098","14098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424871","2015-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in East Sussex Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14127","14127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424872","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will designate airfields as greenfield sites.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14076","14076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424873","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of airfields on land designated as brownfield sites.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14077","14077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424874","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will introduce further proposals to protect airfields from redevelopment.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14075","14075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424875","2015-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in Gloucestershire Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14128","14128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424876","2015-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in Buckinghamshire Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14129","14129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424877","2015-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in Wiltshire Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14130","14130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424878","2015-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in Dorset Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14131","14131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424879","2015-11-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2015 to Question 12248, what the gross cost to the Planning Inspectorate was of the examination into the planning consent application for the Navitus Bay Wind Park; and how much of that cost was paid by Navitus Bay Development Ltd.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14046","14046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424880","2015-11-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what funding is available to assist the development and promotion of long distance walks.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13976","13976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424881","2015-11-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make representations on reducing the gender pay gap at the BBC during forthcoming discussions on the BBC Charter.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14082","14082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424882","2015-11-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to improve the broadband speed in the Bristol West area.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14100","14100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424883","2015-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of serving personnel who have received continuity of education allowance in the last five years were (a) serving overseas and (b) in the UK at the time of claiming that allowance.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13988","13988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424884","2015-11-03","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to his Department was of the recent visit to the MFA Tidespring by Lady Boyce; and whether his Department plans for Lady Boyce to make further such visits.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14014","14014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424885","2015-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment the Government made of the risks associated with the deployment of Royal Navy personnel on active duty in the Seychelles.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13990","13990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424886","2015-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the criteria are for serving armed forces personnel to be eligible to claim the continuity of education allowance.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14087","14087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424887","2015-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel of each rank have claimed the continuity of education allowance in the last five years.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14027","14027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424888","2015-11-03","Department for Education","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how  much funding her Department provided for the McAuley Free School project in Hull.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14009","14009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424889","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of recruitment levels of new teachers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14021","14021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424890","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of senior civil servants in her Department attended (a) non-selective state schools, (b) state selective schools, (c) independent schools, fee assisted and (d) independent schools, not fee assisted.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13971","13971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424891","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how she plans for her Department's reception baseline assessment to take account of pupils that move school.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13982","13982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424892","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for how long a pupil must be present at a school to be included in its reception baseline assessment.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13983","13983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424893","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the finding of the report by Sense, entitled The case for play, on the importance of play for the development of children with disabilities and complex needs.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14073","14073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424894","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of provision of play opportunities for children with disabilities and complex needs.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14072","14072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424895","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of teachers who will be trained in each of the next five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14081","14081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424896","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will ensure that spending on play is protected in the forthcoming Comprehensive Spending Review.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14074","14074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424897","2015-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the cost of establishing and running her extended ministerial office has been since its introduction.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14119","14119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424898","2015-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2015 to Question 11214, what guidance her Department offers to potential investors on comparing the costs of different electricity technologies in order to inform investment decisions.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14023","14023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424899","2015-11-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she plans to make a decision on the strike price for the proposed Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13998","13998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424900","2015-11-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many responses she has received to the recent consultation on proposed cuts to the feed-in tariff; how long she plans for her Department to spend on evaluating those responses; and when she plans to make public the Government's proposed next steps on this matter.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13989","13989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424901","2015-11-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations she has received from the Welsh Government on the Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14036","14036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424902","2015-11-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent representations she has received on the potential effect on jobs and investment in the solar industry of reductions in feed-in tariff subsidies.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14118","14118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424903","2015-11-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answers of 6 July 2015 to Question 4551 and 12 October 2015 to Question 10567, if she will request that Ofgem estimates what the cost is to SSE of generating conventional hydro-electric power.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14092","14092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424904","2015-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to prevent illegal timber entering Europe.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14056","14056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424905","2015-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to help achieve a 100 per cent legal and sustainable timber trade in the UK by 2020.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14101","14101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424906","2015-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Indonesian counterpart on the recent persecution and violence against Christians in Aceh Province.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14084","14084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424907","2015-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Federal Minister of Family Affairs, Senior Citizens, Women and Youth in the German government on meeting with the Thalidomide Trust's National Advisory Council on financial compensation for people with thalidomide.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14151","14151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424908","2015-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Lithuanian government against plans for a convention centre to be built in the Jewish Cemetery in Piramont, Vilnius; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14143","14143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424909","2015-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Turkish counterpart on concluding the trial of five men accused of murdering three Christian missionaries in 2007.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14083","14083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424910","2015-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his European counterparts encouraging them to oppose Lithuanian government plans to erect a convention centre in the Jewish cemetery in Piramont, Vilnius; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14144","14144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424911","2015-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government considers that Burma's Rohinga minority are subject to genocide.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13977","13977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424912","2015-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the Burmese Rohinga people.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13978","13978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424913","2015-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions the Government has had with the Russian government on cultural events.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14117","14117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424914","2015-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Russian government on strengthening cultural links between Russia and Scotland.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14116","14116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424915","2015-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Israeli authorities on the attempted murder of the Palestinian activist, Mustafa Barghouti.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14028","14028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424916","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors have requested a certificate of current professional status in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14020","14020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424917","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure the provision of high quality urgent care in Brighton and Hove.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14043","14043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424918","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of GP retention in the North East Essex Clinical Commissioning Group area; and what steps he is taking to improve GP retention.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14026","14026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424919","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received from mental health charities on the adequacy of mental health provision in NHS services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14034","14034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424920","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of elderly people experiencing loneliness.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14035","14035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424921","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much NHS England spent on agency nurses in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14090","14090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424922","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the merits of including GPs on the occupation shortage list.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14058","14058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424923","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what regions he has identified as having a shortage of GPs; and what steps he is taking to address those shortfalls.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14059","14059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424924","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage young people from disadvantaged backgrounds to pursue a career in medicine.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14060","14060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424925","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what analysis his Department has conducted or commissioned on the number of doctors likely to retire in the next five years; and what assessment his Department has made of whether sufficient numbers of doctors are in training to maintain current service levels.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14061","14061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424926","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the potential numbers for junior doctors who may leave the NHS should a new contract for that role be imposed.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14062","14062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424927","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of drugs available on the NHS for the treatment of people diagnosed with (a) MS and (b) Alzheimer's disease.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13997","13997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424928","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many licences the Government has secured for off-patent drugs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13996","13996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424929","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to secure licences for existing off-patent drugs.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13994","13994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424930","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to support and promote the (a) use and (b) continued production and purchase of existing off-patent drugs.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13995","13995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424931","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ring-fence the budget of the National Institute for Health Research in the forthcoming Spending Review.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14016","14016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424932","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether it is his policy for NHS England to require individual funding requests to be made when treatment is permitted by the relevant commissioning policy.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14029","14029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424933","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the closure of Goodwood Court medical practice in Hove on patient access to primary care in that town.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14039","14039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424934","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that people in Hove have access to GP surgeries offering seven-day primary care.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14040","14040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424935","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the suitability of individual funding requests for preventive treatments and the criteria to demonstrate exceptional clinical circumstances in relation to such requests.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14030","14030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424936","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on patient safety of the project on how emergency calls were dealt with run by South East Coast Ambulance Service NHS Foundation Trust between December 2014 and February 2015.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14041","14041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424937","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of provision of urgent care in Brighton and Hove.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14042","14042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424938","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of cases of hypothermia diagnosed in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) Yorkshire and Humber and (c) the UK in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13979","13979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424939","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of cases of frostbite diagnosed in (a) Barnsley Central constituency, (b) Yorkshire and Humber and (c) the UK in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13980","13980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424940","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England plans to publish guidance to commissioners on their duty to pay excess treatment costs.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13975","13975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424941","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding was allocated to each clinical commissioning group area in London per head of population since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14140","14140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424942","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on advanced nurse practitioners of proposed adjustments of GPs working hours.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14070","14070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424943","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on advanced nurse practitioners of his plans for a seven-day NHS.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14069","14069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424944","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's definition is of an advanced nurse practitioner.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14067","14067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424945","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to support advanced nurse practitioners in the NHS.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14068","14068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424946","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost to the NHS is of educating and training a junior doctor.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14065","14065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424947","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will hold discussions with the devolved administrations on sharing best practice on steps to reduce (a) self-harm and (b) suicide rates.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14086","14086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424948","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many advanced nurse practitioners were employed by the NHS in each region of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14071","14071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424949","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many new cases of psychosis were diagnosed in (a) the UK, (b) London, (c) each London borough and (d) each health trust in London in each year between 2010 and 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14122","14122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424950","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions in each of the last five years bed occupancy rates reached (a) 85, (b) 90, (c) 95 and (d) 100 per cent in each hospital trust in London.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14125","14125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424951","2015-11-03","Department of Health","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) lesbian, gay, bisexual or transgender and (b) black and minority ethic people were diagnosed with mental health problems in (i) the UK, (ii) London, (iii) each London borough and (iv) each health trust in London on 1 October (A) 2010, (B) 2011, (C) 2012, (D) 2013, (E) 2014 and (F) 2015.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14121","14121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424952","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much it costs her Department to process an application for a Certificate of Travel.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14053","14053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424953","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason people with indefinite leave to remain have been granted certificates of travel with validity of less than five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14078","14078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424954","2015-11-03","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to the Freedom of Information Request, CTS reference M12288/15, submitted by the hon. Member for Preston and received by her Department on 30 August 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14146","14146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424955","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department gave to (a) the Commissioner of Police of the Metropolis, (b) constables and (c) sergeants ahead of the visit of Xi Jinping to the UK about potential protests during that visit.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14106","14106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424956","2015-11-03","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employees of Border Force are seconded to Frontex; and in what locations such staff are deployed.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14153","14153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424957","2015-11-03","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employees of Border Force are seconded to Kos and Lesbos; and what their (a) powers and (b) duties are.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14152","14152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424958","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of substantive replies to hon. Members her Department has answered within the targets it has set for such correspondence since May 2015.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13972","13972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424959","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many certificates of travel with a validity of 12 months or less were granted to people with indefinite leave to remain in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13993","13993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424960","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost is to her Department of processing an application for a certificate of travel.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13992","13992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424961","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will reduce the cost of an application for a certificate of travel to the same levels as for a convention travel document.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13991","13991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424962","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions her Department had with its Chinese counterparts prior to the recent visit of the Chinese President Xi Jinping on policing and protests during that visit.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14096","14096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424963","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Wilson Doctrine has been consistently applied to the parliamentary communications of the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross; and whether that hon. Member has been subject to surveillance.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14063","14063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424964","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what involvement her Chinese counterpart had in the planning of the policing operation for the recent visit of the Chinese President.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14094","14094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424965","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she was informed that warrants were being obtained to search the homes of the three protestors arrested during the visit of the Chinese President.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14095","14095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424966","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for what reason people with indefinite leave to remain are granted certificates of travel with validity of less than five years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14091","14091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424967","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many certificates of travel with a validity of 12 months or less were granted to people with indefinite leave to remain in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14054","14054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424968","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will reduce the cost of an application for a Certificate of travel so that it is the same cost as a Convention travel document.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14032","14032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424969","2015-11-03","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of changes to stop and search guidelines on the level of knife crime in (a) north east Essex and (b) other areas with a higher than average incidence of such crime.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14025","14025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424970","2015-11-02","Department for International Development","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that protective clothing is provided to hospital workers treating victims of Ebola in (a) Sierra Leone and (b) Liberia.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13973","13973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424971","2015-11-02","Department for International Development","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department takes to ensure that overseas development aid spent via the EU is used for its intended purposes.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13974","13974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424972","2015-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the 2013 Lough Erne G8 Leaders' Communiqu, published on 18 June 2013, what progress has been made on implementing the commitments in paragraph (a) 5, (b) 6 and (c) 7 of that document; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14088","14088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424973","2015-11-02","Department for International Development","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the World Health Organisation's Global Tuberculosis Report 2015, published on 28 October 2015, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the findings of that report; and what steps her Department is taking to contribute to the global eradication of tuberculosis.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14093","14093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424974","2015-11-02","Department for International Development","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to encourage the European Commission and the World Bank to promote road safety in their infrastructure funding; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14102","14102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424975","2015-11-02","Department for International Development","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to promote steps to tackle HIV/Aids; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14103","14103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424976","2015-11-02","Department for International Development","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support women's reproductive healthcare in Liberia.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14052","14052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424977","2015-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress the sentencing council has made on producing guidelines for sentencing serious motoring offences; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14123","14123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424978","2015-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he expects the consultation on the review of driving offences will be launched.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14124","14124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424979","2015-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review the adequacy of his Department's guidance on the care and management of transsexual prisoners.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14134","14134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424980","2015-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to review the requirement for a diagnosis of gender dysphoria in the application criteria for the gender recognition certificate.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14132","14132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424981","2015-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will reduce the (a) bureaucratic burden and (b) cost of the fee structure for the gender recognition certificate.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14135","14135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424982","2015-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that (a) transgender and (b) transsexual prisoners are placed in prison accommodation that is appropriate to their gender.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14133","14133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424983","2015-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make representations to the Criminal Cases Review Commission on reviewing the case of James Thompson.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14066","14066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424984","2015-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what training was provided to the people who assessed bids for legal aid duty solicitor contracts in administering and assessing such contracts.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14004","14004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424985","2015-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of the procurement process for legal aid duty solicitor contracts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14005","14005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424986","2015-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what weighting was given to the (a) disciplinary records of and (b) number of signatures of ongoing complaints against bidders in the procurement process for legal aid duty solicitor contracts.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14003","14003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424987","2015-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many temporary agency staff were recruited by the Legal Aid Agency to work on the procurement process for crime duty provider contracts; and what proportion of staff assessing the bids for such contracts were external staff.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14001","14001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424988","2015-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of staff assigned to work on the procurement process for crime duty provider contracts had no previous experience of working on public sector procurement.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14002","14002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424989","2015-11-03","Cabinet Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the daily rate or fee will be for members of the proposed review committee on securing the decisive role of the House of Commons on financial matters and secondary legislation.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14022","14022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424990","2015-11-02","Leader of the House","2015-10-29","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will consult political parties on proposals to change the sitting days of the House during party conferences.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14085","14085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424991","2015-11-03","Prime Minister","2015-10-29","To ask the Prime Minister, when he last discussed the issue of state aid for the UK steel industry with (a) the President of the European Commission, (b) the Presidency of the European Council and (c) other EU member state governments.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14024","14024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424992","2015-11-03","Prime Minister","2015-10-29","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will publish the minutes of the Prime Minister's Community Forum meeting on 13 October 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14142","14142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424993","2015-11-02","Department for Transport","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the efficiency savings his Department has gained from the reorganisation of the Highways Agency to Highways England; and what the budget of that body was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14064","14064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424994","2015-11-03","Department for Transport","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to involve disabled people in the design of better access to public transport.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14145","14145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424995","2015-11-03","Department for Transport","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he expects new rolling stock to be introduced on the forthcoming Transpennine Express franchise; and whether that rolling stock is planned to be diesel or electric powered.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14008","14008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424996","2015-11-03","Department for Transport","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate his Department has made of the forecast return on investment from the High Speed 2 project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14007","14007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424997","2015-11-03","Department for Transport","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make representations to his Danish counterpart on reopening the inquest into the death of commercial driver Stephen O'Malley in 2012.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14010","14010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424998","2015-11-03","Department for Transport","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to ensure that direct rail services between Hull, Leeds and Manchester continue regardless of which parts of that route are electrified.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14013","14013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424999","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans for portable evidential breath-test machines to be made available for use by the police to tackle drink driving.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14033","14033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425000","2015-11-02","Department for Transport","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what provisions are in place to enable airports to ban passengers from their premises; under what circumstances such provisions may be used; and how many passengers were banned from (a) Leeds Bradford International, (b) Belfast International, (c) East Midlands, (d) Edinburgh, (e) Glasgow International, (f) Manchester, (g) Newcastle International, (h) London Gatwick, (i) London Luton, (j) London Stansted and (k) London Heathrow Airport in each year from 2010 to 2015 to date.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13987","13987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425001","2015-11-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the application of working time regulations to aircraft maintenance engineers.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13986","13986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425002","2015-11-02","Department for Transport","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish a national road safety strategy.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13984","13984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425003","2015-11-02","Department for Transport","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will set road casualty reduction targets.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13985","13985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425004","2015-11-02","Wales Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which non-party political organisations he has worked with in developing the proposed Wales Bill.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14017","14017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425005","2015-11-02","Wales Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with which non-party political organisations he has met to discuss the proposed Wales Bill since March 2015.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14080","14080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425006","2015-11-02","Wales Office","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, from which non-party political organisations he has received representations on the proposed Wales Bill.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14079","14079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425007","2015-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made in piloting reasonable adjustments to the work capability assessment for people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14051","14051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425008","2015-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made in extending reassessment periods for claimants in the employment and support allowance support group (a) generally and (b) who have degenerative brain conditions.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14120","14120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425009","2015-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeals by claimants in the work related activity group of employment and support allowance have resulted in subsequent placement in the support group of employment and support allowance in each quarter since 2013.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14048","14048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425010","2015-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of appeals against fit for work decisions since January 2013 have involved people whose primary medical condition is a mental health condition.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14049","14049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425011","2015-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average cost to his Department is of an appeal against a fit for work decision.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14050","14050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425012","2015-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria he will use to decide whether to extend the placement of jobcentre advisers in food banks beyond the current pilot.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14139","14139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425013","2015-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the Multiple Sclerosis Society's recent findings that almost half of the people with multiple sclerosis surveyed who had had a work capability assessment declared that it had caused their condition to deteriorate or relapse.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14138","14138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425014","2015-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the Multiple Sclerosis Society's recent findings that 36 per cent of people with multiple sclerosis surveyed who had had a PIP face-to-face assessment declared that it had caused their condition to deteriorate or relapse.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14137","14137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425015","2015-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce poverty in (a) Barnsley Central constituency and (b) other former mining communities.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14019","14019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425016","2015-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that (a) health workers, (b) Jobcentre Plus staff and (c) his Department's staff have received adequate training to respond to the needs of people with Crohn's disease and Colitis, which meets the six main standards set out in the Standards for the Healthcare of People who have Inflammatory Bowel Disease, 2013 update.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14015","14015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425017","2015-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many appeals by claimants in the work related activity group of employment and support allowance whose primary medical condition is a mental health condition have resulted in subsequent placement in the support group of employment and support allowance in each quarter since 2013.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14055","14055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425018","2015-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the duration will be of the pilot project placing jobcentre advisers in food banks.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 14114","14114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/425019","2015-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-10-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on (a) IT systems and (b) cyber-security in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14, (v) 2014-15 and (vi) 2015-16 to date.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13999","13999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424458","2015-10-30","Attorney General","2015-10-28","To ask the Attorney General, how many civil servants in the Law Officers' Departments are members of trades unions; how much working hours facility time is claimed by each such civil servant; and what the cost of that facility time is to the Law Officers' Departments.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13895","13895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424459","2015-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of how many small businesses have been started in (a) Bristol, (b) London and (c) England in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13933","13933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424460","2015-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions his Department has had with the Ministry of Defence on the potential implications of the closure of steel plants in the UK for the UK defence industry and infrastructure.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13939","13939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424461","2015-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the evidential basis is for the proposition that freezing the repayment threshold for plan 2 student loans is likely to result in student loans being repaid to a greater extent than under the current terms.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13854","13854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424462","2015-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effects of the Government's proposal to freeze the repayment threshold for plan 2 student loans on the amount of money likely to be paid back over the 30 year repayment period.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13855","13855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424463","2015-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many civil servants in his Department are members of trades unions; how much working hours facility time is claimed by each such civil servant; and what the cost of that facility time is to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13894","13894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424464","2015-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment has been made of the effect of incorporating the function of the Pay and Work Rights Helpline into ACAS on outcomes for workers.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13746","13746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424465","2015-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to eliminate UK Export Finance investments in coal plants and coal mining overseas.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13744","13744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424466","2015-10-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will hold discussions with motor trade associations on steps to ban the sale of devices that are used to illegally reduce car mileages on vehicles for resale.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13758","13758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424467","2015-11-02","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 62 of the Government's consultation document, Tackling Exploitation in the Labour Market, published in October 2015, what limitations currently exist on data sharing between labour market enforcement bodies.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13810","13810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424468","2015-11-02","Cabinet Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward proposals to add the (a) Surveillance Camera Commissioner and (b) Office of the Biometrics Commissioner to Schedule 1 of the Freedom of Information Act 2000.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13811","13811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424469","2015-11-02","Cabinet Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the cost of using external agencies for recruitment to the Senior Civil Service across all Government departments in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13767","13767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424470","2015-10-30","Cabinet Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will contact those people whose personal details have been stolen as a result of the cyber security breach of the Government Gateway system.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13776","13776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424471","2015-11-02","Cabinet Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure that personal information housed on the Government Gateway system is better protected.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13799","13799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424472","2015-10-30","Northern Ireland Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many and what proportion of (a) 18 and (b) 19 year-olds in Northern Ireland were registered to vote on 30 June 2014; what the average number was of 18 and 19 year-olds in Northern Ireland so registered as a proportion of the mid-year population estimate made by the Office for National Statistics for 2014; and how that figure differs from (i) Electoral Commission and (ii) Cabinet Office estimates of the number of registered 18 and 19 year-olds in (A) Northern Ireland and (B) Great Britain in 2014.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13739","13739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424473","2015-10-30","Cabinet Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Independent Commission the Freedom of Information on the number of occasions it plans to meet in order to finalise its report.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13743","13743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424475","2015-10-30","Cabinet Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Office for National Statistics plans to include in quarterly migration figures the number of Syrian refugees resettled in the UK under the Government's relocation scheme.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13823","13823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424476","2015-10-30","Cabinet Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of government IT spending was spent with small and medium sized (SME) enterprises in 2014-15; and what estimate  he has made of the proportion of that spending that will be with SMEs in 2015-16.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13931","13931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424477","2015-11-02","Cabinet Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of (a) which personal details and (b) how many individual profiles were hacked as a result of the cyber security breach of the Government Gateway system.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13924","13924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424478","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many registered financial advisers are sole traders.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13942","13942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424479","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's impact assessment on the Tax Credits (Income Threshold and Determination of Rates) (Amendment) Regulations 2015, what the (a) income brackets are for each decile and (b) equivalent levels are for the proportions in Chart 1.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13929","13929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424481","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average (a) duration and (b) cost to the caller of a telephone call to HM Revenue and Customs' tax credit telephone lines was in the most recent 12 months for which data is available; and how much revenue was generated from these calls.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13966","13966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424482","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff have been employed to cover HM Revenue and Customs' tax credit telephone lines in each of the past five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13967","13967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424483","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the Exchequer of paying to foreign nationals (a) child and (b) other tax credits in 2015-16.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13969","13969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424484","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many requests have been made for paper copies of tax return forms in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Joanna Cherry","Joanna  Cherry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13960","13960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424485","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average time taken for HM Revenue and Customs to respond to a request for a paper tax form was in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Joanna Cherry","Joanna  Cherry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13961","13961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424486","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the implementation of the recommendations on money laundering and terrorism financing of the G7 Financial Action Task Force.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13835","13835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424487","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many regulated Retail Financial Advisory firms there are; and how many have five or more financial advisers working for them.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13913","13913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424488","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of armed forces veterans are in receipt of tax credits.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13737","13737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424489","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials of his Department are responsible for work directly relating to the Department for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13740","13740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424490","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to revise the Office for Budget Responsibility's (OBR) memorandum of understanding to permit the Government to request changes to OBR publications over and above factual comments on the presentation of analysis and forecasts; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13752","13752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424491","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2015 to Question 10809, how many enforcement actions involving victims of modern slavery have been undertaken since February 2015.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13786","13786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424492","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what tax revenue was lost as a result of illegal fuel laundering and smuggling in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13778","13778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424493","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what tax revenue was lost as a result of illegal fuel laundering and smuggling in Northern Ireland in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13779","13779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424494","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what tax revenue was lost as a result of tobacco smuggling in the UK in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13780","13780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424495","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what tax revenue was lost as a result of tobacco smuggling in Northern Ireland in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13781","13781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424496","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps HM Revenue and Customs are taking to stop illegal fuel laundering and smuggling in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13782","13782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424497","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps HM Revenue and Customs are taking to stop tobacco smuggling in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13783","13783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424498","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of working families in Northern Ireland who will be affected by proposed changes to working tax credits; and what estimate he has made of the average change in the amount that will be received by such families in the year commencing April 2016.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13755","13755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424499","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what data his Department collects on people who have exercised new pension freedoms who have not accessed the Pension Wise service.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13770","13770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424500","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what data his Department collects on the (a) demographics, (b) pension pot size and (c) decisions taken after the consultation of people accessing the Pension Wise service.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13771","13771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424501","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to gather data on people accessing the Pension Wise service.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13772","13772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424502","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have accessed the Pension Wise service through the (a) face-to-face service provided by the Citizens Advice Bureau and (b) telephone service provided by the Pensions Advisory Service to date.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13773","13773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424503","2015-11-02","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will hold discussions with Lloyds Bank on that company prioritising the payment of dividends to encourage small shareholders to retain shares for the long term, in advance of further sales of the Government's stake in that company.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13762","13762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424504","2015-10-30","HM Treasury","2015-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, following his decision to reduce the lifetime allowance for those saving with personal pensions, what assistance the Government plans to offer to people whose additional pension provision is likely to breach the reduced lifetime allowance for personal pensions but would not have breached the previous limit.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13757","13757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424505","2015-11-03","Department for Transport","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the level of democratic oversight of road safety partnerships; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13832","13832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424506","2015-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to change how take-away food delivery drivers are regulated.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13753","13753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424507","2015-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) starter and (b) affordable homes the Government plans to build over the next five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13738","13738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424508","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many Youth Diversion events were undertaken by English fire and rescue services in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13914","13914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424509","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many statutory Fire Safety Inspections were carried out by English fire and rescue services in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13915","13915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424510","2015-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new homes for affordable rent were completed in Bristol South constituency in each year from 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13872","13872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424511","2015-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many new homes for social rent were completed in Bristol South constituency in each year from 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13873","13873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424512","2015-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will change planning procedures for local authorities to speed up the construction of new affordable homes to buy.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13874","13874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424513","2015-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will provide exemptions from the pay to stay scheme for tenants in affordable rent-to-buy properties.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13875","13875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424514","2015-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes were completed in Bristol South constituency in each year from 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13941","13941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424515","2015-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what change there has been in the number of firefighter posts was in Devon and Somerset Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13938","13938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424516","2015-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many civil servants in his Department are members of trades unions; how much working hours facility time is claimed by each such civil servant; and what the cost of that facility time is to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13896","13896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424517","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many road traffic collisions English fire and rescue service attended in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13947","13947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424518","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in Cornwall Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13946","13946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424519","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the change in the number of firefighter posts was in Avon Fire and Rescue Service in 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13948","13948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424520","2015-11-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2015 to Question 12790, whether the licence obligation on Telefonica to provide indoor 4G coverage to 98 per cent of UK premises by 2017 includes coverage in tunnels.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13926","13926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424521","2015-10-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many civil servants in his Department are members of trades unions; how much working hours facility time is claimed by each such civil servant; and what the cost of that facility time is to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13897","13897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424522","2015-10-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that small businesses are able to access high speed broadband.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13876","13876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424524","2015-10-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to reform the Electronic Communications Code following the closure of the consultation on 30 April 2015.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13839","13839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424525","2015-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to commemorate the 350th anniversary of the passage into law of the Five Mile Act 1665.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13859","13859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424527","2015-11-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will discuss with the four home nations football associations allegations of corruption within FIFA and steps to rebuild public confidence in the administration of international football.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13760","13760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424528","2015-10-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold discussions with each of the devolved administrations on ensuring that the roll-out of superfast broadband benefits people across the UK uniformly.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13756","13756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424529","2015-11-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate the cost to businesses of inconsistent broadband coverage in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13814","13814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424530","2015-11-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans his Department has to improve access for children in rural areas to high-quality cultural and historical exhibits.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13812","13812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424531","2015-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of senior civil servants in his Department are from a lower socio-economic background.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13768","13768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424532","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to hold discussions with the Canadian government on future Royal Canadian Air Force procurement policy.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13819","13819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424533","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what training is provided to officials of his Department working on the Ministry of Defence Saudi Armed Forces Programme and the Saudi Arabia National Guard Communications Project on responding to whistleblowers from the private sector.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13794","13794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424534","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what arrangements are in place to monitor Babcock's performance and safety record.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13845","13845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424535","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to safely store or treat nuclear contaminated material arising from the decommissioning of nuclear-powered submarines at Rosyth by Babcock.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13846","13846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424536","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to his Department was of maintenance of facilities at (a) Prestwick, (b) RAF Benbecula, (c) RAF Buchan, (d) RAF Lossiemouth, (e) RAF Tain, (f) RRH Saxa Vord, (g) HMNB Clyde, (h) Redford Barracks, (i) Dreghorn Barracks, (j) Glencorse Barracks, (k) Fort George (l) Kinloss and (m) Leuchars in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steven Paterson","Steven Paterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13847","13847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424537","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2015 to the hon. Member for Reigate to Question 12151, whether he plans for the boats built to replace the nuclear submarine fleet to be built with steel manufactured in the UK.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13886","13886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424538","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the consequences for the UK's capability of the retirement in 2018 of the 53 Typhoon aircraft purchased in tranche 1; and if he will reverse this decision in the 2015 Strategic Defence and Strategic Review.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13893","13893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424539","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the costs of infrastructure improvements at RAF Waddington were in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13889","13889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424540","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian staff support operations at RAF Waddington; and what their payroll costs were in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13890","13890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424541","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the command structure at RAF Waddington is; and what the total payroll costs for senior officers were in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13891","13891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424542","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many RAF service personnel are based at RAF Waddington; and what their payroll costs were in each year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13892","13892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424543","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civil servants in his Department are members of trades unions; how much working hours facility time is claimed by each such civil servant; and what the cost of that facility time is to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13898","13898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424544","2015-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make it his policy to allow UK citizens who have been awarded the NATO Africa Medal for efforts against piracy to wear that medal in public; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13951","13951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424545","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which of the items of equipment referred to in UK Defence in Numbers, published by his Department in August 2015, are (a) not capable of use on the front line and (b) have been retired.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13934","13934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424546","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the annual running costs of RAF Waddington are; and what assessment he has made of RAF Waddington's contribution to the local economy.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13932","13932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424547","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to UK Defence in Numbers, published by his Department in August 2015, in what capacity the seven Jet Provost training aircrafts referred to in that document may be used; and when those aircraft were last used for that purpose.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13937","13937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424548","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to UK Defence in Numbers, published by his Department in August 2015, how many of the 125 Tornado Combat aircraft referred to in that document are combat ready.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13935","13935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424549","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to UK Defence in Numbers, published by his Department in August 2015, in what capacity the four Wessex Combat support helicopters referred to in that document may be used.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13936","13936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424550","2015-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assets his Department has assigned to (a) Standing NATO Maritime Group 1, (b) Standing NATO Maritime Group 2, (c) Standing NATO Mine Countermeasures Group 1 and (d) Standing NATO Mine Countermeasures Group 2 since February 2015; and for how long each such asset has been so assigned.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13956","13956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424551","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the accessibility of the Sevenoaks Annex of Weald of Kent Grammar School to school-age people living in the community served by the original school.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13968","13968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424552","2015-10-30","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2015 to Question 13005, whether the decrease in the take-up of free school meals includes children now entitled to universal infant free school meals.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13930","13930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424553","2015-10-30","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many civil servants in her Department are members of trades unions; how much working hours facility time is claimed by each such civil servant; and what the cost of that facility time is to her Department.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13899","13899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424554","2015-10-30","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with how many headteachers currently recruiting teachers internationally her Department is discussing its STEM international recruitment programme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13848","13848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424555","2015-10-30","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the budget is of her Department's STEM international recruitment programme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13849","13849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424556","2015-10-30","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers her Department has recruited through its STEM international recruitment programme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13836","13836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424557","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) guidance she has provided and (b) information her Department holds on which age groups the Sevenoaks Annexe of Weald of Kent Grammar School, recently approved by her Department plans to serve.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13867","13867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424558","2015-10-30","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the target countries are of her Department's STEM international recruitment programme; and how many teachers have been recruited from each target country.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13837","13837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424559","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) guidance she provides and (b) information her Department holds on the admissions arrangements for the Sevenoaks Annexe of Weald of Kent Grammar School, recently approved by her Department.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13868","13868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424560","2015-10-30","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with how many headteachers who would like to recruit teachers through its STEM international recruitment programme her Department is discussing that programme.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13838","13838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424561","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what grounds she decided that the recently approved annexe to the Weald of Kent grammar school is in an area that is easily accessible to the community that the school serves.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13861","13861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424562","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost was of (a) external and (b) internal legal advice on the approved and rejected proposals for an annexe to the Weald of Kent Grammar School.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13862","13862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424563","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how long officials in her Department spent considering proposals for an annexe to the Weald of Kent Grammar School.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13863","13863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424564","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) applications and (b) requests for decisions in principle her Department has received on proposals for expansions of grammar schools on new sites in the last five years; and when each was received by her Department.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13864","13864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424565","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, why the Weald of Kent Grammar School was not able to expand on its existing site.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13865","13865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424566","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will introduce teaching about the Five Mile Act 1665 and other sections of the Clarendon Code, and that code's repeal, to the curriculum on fundamental British values of freedom and religious tolerance.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13866","13866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424568","2015-10-30","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what mechanisms are in place to facilitate regular engagement with her counterparts in the devolved administrations on policy development.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13820","13820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424569","2015-11-02","Department for Education","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much time pupils will spend at each site of Weald of Kent Grammar School when its new site is open; by what mode of transport they will move and how that will be funded; what estimate she has made of the amount of time that it will take pupils to move between sites; and whether the school day will be extended to make up that time.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13797","13797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424570","2015-11-02","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2015 to Question 11214, what measure her Department considers to be an adequate comparator for costs of different electricity technologies in the future.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13809","13809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424571","2015-10-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of changes in employment in the renewable energy sector as a result of changes in policy towards feed-in tariffs.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13784","13784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424572","2015-10-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to support the increased use of wind and solar power.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13785","13785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424573","2015-10-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent steps she has taken to increase the UK's energy self-sufficiency and reduce reliance on imported fuel sources; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13824","13824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424574","2015-10-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many civil servants in her Department are members of trades unions; how much working hours facility time is claimed by each such civil servant; and what the cost of that facility time is to her Department.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13900","13900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424575","2015-10-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent steps she has taken to support carbon capture and storage technology to achieve commercial deployment; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13940","13940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424576","2015-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many civil servants in her Department are members of trades unions; how much working hours facility time is claimed by each such civil servant; and what the cost of that facility time is to her Department.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13901","13901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424577","2015-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has made to the European Commission on difficulties faced by milk farmers because of the low price of milk.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13754","13754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424578","2015-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department spent on tackling the illegal wildlife trade in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13745","13745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424579","2015-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to control the number of badgers in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13761","13761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424580","2015-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect of the EU Water Framework Directive on the level of water available in London.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13830","13830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424581","2015-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on creating a North-South water pipeline to bring water to London.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13831","13831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424582","2015-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on security of Mdecins Sans Frontires clinics in areas of conflict.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13795","13795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424583","2015-10-30","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with UNESCO on ensuring that world heritage sites (a) are protected from development by extraction industries and (b) encourage eco-tourism.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13775","13775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424584","2015-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will undertake a review into how his Department advises British citizens on the ethical rating of nations in line with performing to international standards on the illegal wildlife trade.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13747","13747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424585","2015-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will work with his international counterparts to request that the UN Secretary General appoint a Special Envoy for Sustainable Development.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13748","13748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424586","2015-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many diplomatic staff whose work includes tackling the illegal wildlife trade are based in (a) China, (b) Vietnam, (c) Laos, (d) Malaysia, (e) Botswana, (f) Mozambique, (g) Gabon, (h) South Africa, (i) Thailand and (j) India.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13749","13749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424587","2015-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many civil servants in his Department are members of trades unions; how much working hours facility time is claimed by each such civil servant; and what the cost of that facility time is to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13902","13902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424588","2015-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with NATO and EU governments on implementation of UN Security Council Resolution 2178 on foreign terrorist fighters.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13834","13834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424589","2015-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the efficacy of capacity building assistance in the area of strategic communications for (a) Georgia, (b) Moldova, (c) Ukraine and (d) other NATO partner countries.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13841","13841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424590","2015-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Russian authorities about an international tribunal to investigate the destruction of the Malaysia Airlines Flight MH17.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13842","13842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424591","2015-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Russian government on full implementation of its obligations under the Minsk agreements.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13843","13843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424592","2015-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had about access to all areas of East Ukraine for the OSCE Special Monitoring Mission.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Mr Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13844","13844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424593","2015-10-30","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of instances of a newborn baby being sent home from hospital with a woman other than that baby's biological mother in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13851","13851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424594","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons NHS England is proposing to have only two cancer centres using stereotactic radiosurgery to treat the most complex brain tumours.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13805","13805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424595","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospitals in the North East are treating brain tumour patients with stereotactic radiosurgery; and how many patients have been treated in each such hospital in each year since NHS England was created.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13806","13806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424596","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the findings of the report, Prevent, Reduce, Delay: Are councils meeting their new duties to support unpaid carers, published by the Carers Trust in October 2015, on the level of compliance by councils with their duty under the Care Act 2014 to prevent carers developing a need for support.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13857","13857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424597","2015-10-30","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Mayor of London on the London Assembly's report, Tackling TB in London, published on 27 October 2015.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13878","13878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424598","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time was for patients assigned to cognitive behavioural therapy on 1 October in each year since 2010 in (a) the UK, (b) London, (c) each London borough and (d) each health trust in London.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13798","13798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424599","2015-10-30","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of Government funding for research into stem cell transplantation.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13877","13877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424600","2015-10-30","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many civil servants in his Department are members of trades unions; how much working hours facility time is claimed by each such civil servant; and what the cost of that facility time is to his Department.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13903","13903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424601","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 2.21 of the Summer Budget 2015, what arrangements he has put in place to enable the funding provided for defibrillators to be disbursed.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13925","13925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424602","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 October 2015 to Question 11110, how much the NHS spent on cancer services in each year since 2012-13; and what the year-on-year change in that amount was in real terms.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13970","13970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424603","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many in-patient NHS beds for mental health patients Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust provided on its own premises on 1 June (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012, (d) 2013, (e) 2014 and (f) 2015; and what the locations of those beds was on each such date.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13826","13826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424604","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospitals in England treat arteriovenous malformations and pituitary ademomas with stereotactic radiosurgery.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13807","13807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424605","2015-10-30","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for NHS policies of the use of a regional eye inspection liaison officer in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13822","13822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424606","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs in London were aged 60 or over on 1 October 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13800","13800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424607","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many vacancies there were for GPs in (a) London and (b) each London borough on 1 October in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13801","13801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424608","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions for anti-depressants were issued in each year since 2010 in (a) the UK, (b) London, (c) each London borough and (d) each health trust in London.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13802","13802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424609","2015-11-02","Department of Health","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were (a) receiving and (b) on the waiting list to receive cognitive behavioural therapy on 1 October in each year since 2010 in (a) the UK, (b) London, (c) each London borough and (d) each health trust in London.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13803","13803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424610","2015-10-30","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people resident in Bristol South constituency were deported in each year from 2005 to 2014.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13817","13817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424611","2015-10-30","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's consultation document on Tackling Exploitation in the Labour Market, published in October 2015, what plans she has to use data gathered by labour market enforcement agencies in immigration enforcement activities.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13787","13787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424612","2015-10-30","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 September 2015 to Question 10048, if she will take steps to ensure that the Criminal Injuries Compensation Authority collects data in a way that would allow information about compensation awarded to victims of modern slavery to be identified.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13788","13788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424613","2015-10-30","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2015 to Question 10040, whether she plans that the Protocol to the 2014 Forced Labour Convention will be ratified before the end of 2015.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13789","13789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424614","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to reduce the Gangmasters Licensing Authority's Grant-In-Aid budget over the next 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13766","13766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424615","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will publish its strategic plan for housing Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13769","13769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424616","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Syrian refugees she expects to be housed in the UK by December 2015.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13774","13774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424617","2015-10-30","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on ensuring that policy and border staff share information on the illegal wildlife trade with Interpol, Europol and World Customs Organisation.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13750","13750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424618","2015-10-30","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many seizures of illegal animal wildlife products have been made at UK ports of entry in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13751","13751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424619","2015-10-30","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugees the Government plans to resettle in the Bristol City Council area.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13954","13954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424620","2015-10-30","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers the Government plans to resettle in the Bristol City Council area.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13955","13955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424621","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Question 1 of the consultation, Tackling exploitation in the labour market, published by her Department and the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills in October 2015, what the legal definition is of organised labour market exploitation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13916","13916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424622","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to Question 1 of the consultation, Tackling exploitation in the labour market, published by her Department and the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills in October 2015, what account of international law her Department took in defining labour market exploitation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13917","13917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424623","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many students from India were granted a visa to study in Britain in 1990.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13943","13943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424624","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many students from India were granted a visa to study in Britain in 2014.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13944","13944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/424625","2015-11-02","Home Office","2015-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many students from India were granted a visa to study in Britain in 2000.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 13945","13945"
