"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391539","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what measures he plans to use to assess progress towards full employment.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7954","7954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391540","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children experiencing material deprivation in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7955","7955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391541","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects to meet the four targets for eradicating child poverty as set out in the Child Poverty Act 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7956","7956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391542","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Scotland who will be claiming universal credit in April (a) 2016, (b) 2017, (c) 2018, (d) 2019 and (e) 2020.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8002","8002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391543","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will undertake an annual review of the effect in Scotland of the welfare changes announced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8018","8018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391544","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people living in Tooting constituency who are likely to move home because of a reduction in the benefit cap to £23,000.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8107","8107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391545","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of children living in households in Tooting constituency likely to be affected by a reduction in the benefit cap to £23,000.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8105","8105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391546","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of children living in households in London likely to be affected by a reduction in the benefit cap to £23,000.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8106","8106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391547","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who would remain unemployed when full employment is achieved under (a) the Non-Accelerating Inflation Rate of Unemployment, (b) the definition of full employment set out in the Europe 2020 Strategy, (c) the definition of full employment as the highest employment rate in the G7 and (d) the definition of full employment as the lowest rate of unemployment in the G7.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8078","8078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391548","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2015 to Question 6479, if he will make it his policy to collect such data in future.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8067","8067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391549","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Clause 4 of the Welfare Reform and Work Bill, what steps he plans to take to ensure that incidence of children living in poverty in households where at least one adult in work is recorded and reported.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8054","8054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391550","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of households in Scotland which will be affected by the proposed decrease in the household benefit cap.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8003","8003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391551","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, who he plans will be exempt from the removal of automatic entitlement to housing benefit for people aged 18 to 21.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8004","8004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391552","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department provides to claimants with dyslexia who need additional assistance when completing forms and applications.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8050","8050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391553","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many people in Tooting constituency have moved home as a result of the implementation of the benefit cap.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8108","8108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391554","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people living in London who are likely to move home because of a reduction in the benefit cap to £23,000.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8109","8109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391555","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of the gross value of all housing benefit payments was allocated to claimants in (a) England, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) Scotland and (d) Wales in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8099","8099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391556","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to reply to the letter to him dated 11 June 2015 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton, with regard to Mr R Koudsi.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 8121","8121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390913","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with representatives of Royal Mail on the adequacy of the postal compensation scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7762","7762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390914","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to the adult skills budget on the long-term financial stability of the further education sector.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7768","7768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390915","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proposals his Department have put forward for projects under the EU Fund for Strategic Investments.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7807","7807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390916","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on whether any British-licenced weaponry has been used by Saudi Arabia to bomb Saada province in Yemen.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7824","7824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390917","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2015 to Question 6219, which local spending bodies in the city of Birmingham spend money voted to his Department.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7816","7816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390918","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students (a) were in receipt of a full, (b) were in receipt of a partial and (c) did not receive a maintenance grant in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7850","7850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390919","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2015 to Question 6219, which local spending bodies spend money for which the Permanent Secretary in his Department is the accounting officer.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7815","7815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390920","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2015 to Question 6219, whether his Department holds information on (a) further education colleges, (b) apprenticeships providers, (c) local economic partnerships and (d) other local bodies which draw upon funds voted to his Department.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7817","7817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390921","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many regulations were (a) introduced and (b) removed in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7861","7861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390922","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the cost of (a) introducing and (b) removing regulations in each financial year from 2010-11 to 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7862","7862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390923","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to implement a whole-of-Government approach to export support: and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7863","7863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390924","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on which dates and in what locations British precision-guided missiles, licensed for export, have been used in the current conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7820","7820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390925","2015-07-21","Cabinet Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if the Government will assess the vulnerability of the UK to economic and financial warfare when developing the National Security Strategy.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7870","7870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390926","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the vulnerability of the financial system to terrorist actions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7869","7869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390927","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he has taken to reduce speculation in and improve the transparency and supervision of the oil futures market; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7871","7871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390928","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value was of grants approved by his Department under section 64 of the Health Services and Public Health Act 1968 in each of the last five years; and what assessment his Department has made of the value for money and effectiveness with which funding so awarded has been spent.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7826","7826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390929","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the job title is of the (a) official and (b) Minister in his Department with responsibility for approving grants made under section 64 of the Health Services and Public Health Act 1968; against what criteria such grants are awarded; and what the process is for considering applications for such grants.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7827","7827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390930","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the additional annual costs to councils of paying the National Living Wage to care workers employed by private firms to provide adult social care services for local authorities from April 2016.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7771","7771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390931","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue has been raised from the fixed-odds betting terminals tax.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7798","7798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390932","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many bee hives are sited on land and buildings owned by local authorities in the North West of England.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7843","7843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390933","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much each district and unitary council in the North West of England obtained in animal licensing fees in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7846","7846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390934","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will introduce legislative proposals to place a legal responsibility on local authorities to notify their neighbouring authorities when they place 16 to 21 year olds leaving (a) care and (b) young offender institutions in that area.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7808","7808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390935","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many families with children living in bed and breakfast accommodation have been so accommodated for more than six weeks; and how many families with children live in bed and breakfast accommodation in (a) each parliamentary constituency in the East Midlands and (b) England.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7855","7855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390936","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) homes and (b) affordable homes have been built in each local authority area in Cumbria in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7777","7777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390937","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2015 to Question 6223, which groups were awarded money for integration projects.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7872","7872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390938","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2015 to Question 6223, what measures he has used to assess the results and performance of the £50 million invested through the integration strategy.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7873","7873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390939","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to sections 33 to 41 of the Deregulation Act 2015, when he expects to make the commencement order on retaliatory evictions.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7875","7875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390940","2015-07-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with sensory loss can share in the benefits of (a) on-demand television services and (b) new social media.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7874","7874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390941","2015-07-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department has spent on sport in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire, (c) East Midlands and (d) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7849","7849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390942","2015-07-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many fixed-odds betting terminals there were in Copeland constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7797","7797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390943","2015-07-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the total prize money dispersed in horse racing in each of the last five years; and what estimate he has made of how much the betting industry has contributed to horse racing through (a) levy payments, (b) media rights and (c) sponsorship in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7767","7767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390944","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports he has received since 30 April 2013 on involvement of British military personnel in actions in Syria.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7791","7791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390945","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he was informed of the deployment of British military personnel in military action in Syria prior to the debate on Britain and International Security on 2 July 2015.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7841","7841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390946","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2015 to Question 5927, if he will commission a lessons learned post-Afghanistan review to inform future military strategy.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7772","7772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390947","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many operations British armed forces personnel have been involved in Syria since 30 August 2013; and from which branch of the armed forces each such personnel was deployed.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7778","7778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390948","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many British combat aircraft have been deployed in Syria since 30 August 2013.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7779","7779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390949","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many British ground assets have been deployed in Syria since 30 August 2013.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7780","7780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390950","2015-09-07","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the contribution of the hon. Member for Sutton Coldfield of 15 July 2015, Official Report, column 887, what his policy is on deployment of armed drones outside of designated war zones; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7838","7838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390951","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils eligible for free school meals achieved five GCSEs at A* to C including English and mathematics in (a) Ashfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7856","7856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390952","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils achieved five GCSEs at A* to C including English and mathematics in (a) Ashfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7857","7857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390953","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils were eligible for free school meals in secondary schools in (a) Ashfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7858","7858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390954","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils eligible for free school meals in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England subsequently attended a Russell Group university in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7830","7830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390955","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teaching assistants there were in schools in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) the East Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7854","7854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390956","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools and academies in (a) Ashfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England did not meet the standard of 60 per cent of pupils achieving five GCSEs at A* to C including English and mathematics, and also had a below median score for the proportion of students making expected progress, in (i) 2010-11, (ii) 2011-12, (iii) 2012-13, (iv) 2013-14 and (v) 2014-15.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7851","7851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390957","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much revenue has accrued to the public purse through the sale of sports fields in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire, (c) the East Midlands and (d) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7852","7852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390958","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the schools and academies assessed by Ofsted in (a) Ashfield and (b) Nottinghamshire in each of the last five years were rated as (i) outstanding, (ii) good, (iii) requiring improvement and (iv) inadequate.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7848","7848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390959","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils eligible for free school meals in (a) Ashfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England subsequently attended a university in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7831","7831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390960","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Sure Start children's centres closed in each of the last three years in (a) England and (b) Copeland constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7878","7878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390961","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils in (a) Ashfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England progressed to a Russell Group university in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7833","7833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390962","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils in (a) Ashfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England progressed to university in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7834","7834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390963","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of pupils were eligible for free school meals in primary and infant schools in (a) Ashfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7859","7859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390964","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the current status is of schools placed in special measures in (a) Copeland constituency and (b) Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7794","7794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390965","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools rated outstanding or good in (a) Ashfield and (b) Nottinghamshire (i) did not meet the 60 per cent standard pupils achieving five GCSEs at A* to C including English and mathematics and (ii) had a below median score for the proportion of students achieving expected progress in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7832","7832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390966","2015-09-08","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many bee hives are sited on land owned by her Department.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7845","7845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390967","2015-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether windfarms that were subject to appeal or judicial review at the time of her announcement on ending the onshore wind subsidy on 18 June 2015 will qualify for that subsidy.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7883","7883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390968","2015-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will estimate the average annual energy bill for a typical family in Ashfield constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7853","7853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390969","2015-09-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many bee hives are sited on land owned by her Department.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7844","7844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390970","2015-07-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many incidences of avian influenza have been reported in each of the last 36 months.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7796","7796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390971","2015-07-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether any members of staff involved in the sale of land by the New Covent Garden Market Authority have left that Authority and subsequently been employed by the land purchaser.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7761","7761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390972","2015-07-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what options other than demolition and rebuilding her Department considered for the redevelopment of the car park in New Covent Garden Market; and what the estimated cost was of each such option.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7884","7884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390973","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many precision guided missiles have been exported from the UK to Saudi Arabia since the start of the recent conflict in Yemen.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7888","7888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390974","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government is providing to the Saudi Arabian coalition operations in Yemen; and in what circumstances that support would be withdrawn.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7889","7889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390975","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his US counterpart urging President Obama to raise the case of detained British national Andargachew Tsege with the Ethiopian government during President Obama's forthcoming visit to that country.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7789","7789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390976","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the conflict in Yemen with Al-Qaeda on (a) global security and (b) security in the Arabian Peninsula; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7887","7887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390977","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of sanctions against Russia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7860","7860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390978","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to commission a national audit of continence care for young and elderly people.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7842","7842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390979","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish its Excellence in Continence Care Commissioning Framework.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7840","7840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390980","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS Trust chief executives hold a qualification in healthcare management; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7868","7868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390981","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library copies of the syllabus and teaching materials for the (a) Edward Jenner, (b) Nye Bevan, (c) Mary Seacole, (d) Elizabeth Garrett Anderson, (e) The Director, (f) Ready Now, (g) Senior Operational Leaders and (h) Intersect systems leadership programme.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7867","7867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390982","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct NHS England to place an obligation on clinical commissioning groups to contractually deliver quality continence care in England.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7877","7877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390983","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that Public Health England promotes good continence care via a national awareness campaign.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7876","7876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390984","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the co-ordination and efficiency of health and social care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7865","7865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390985","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of cross-charging in reducing bed-blocking; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7866","7866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390986","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data his Department collects on the state and quality of health and social care co-ordination; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7864","7864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390987","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 5566, on what basis his Department reached its conclusion that Action on Smoking and Health was the only charity in this area with the appropriate national record and forms; whether his Department gave consideration to organisations or bodies within (a) the NHS and (b) local government providing such services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7776","7776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390988","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 5566, what steps his Department took following receipt of the Freedom of Information requests in May and June 2014 on the use of grant funding by Action on Smoking and Health.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7774","7774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390989","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in what month in each of the last 10 years a decision to award a grant under Section 64 of the Health Services and Public Health Act 1968 to Action on Smoking and Health has been made.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7814","7814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390990","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 5566, if he will place in the Library a copy of the assessment undertaken in the awarding of all grants to Action on Smoking and Health by his Department; and what the job title is of the official responsible for making recommendations to Ministers on the awarding of such grants.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7775","7775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390991","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with NHS England on the performance of NHS trusts in implementing NICE guidance.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7825","7825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390992","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were registered with NHS dentists in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7828","7828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390993","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June 2015 to Question 2842, what the average yearly earnings of GPs on (a) General Medical Services, (b) Personal Medical Services and (c) Alternative Provider Medical Services contracts were in (i) England, (ii) London, (iii) the London Borough of Islington and (iv) Islington South and Finsbury constituency in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7836","7836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390994","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were on waiting lists to be registered with NHS dentists in (a) Ashfield constituency, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7829","7829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390995","2015-09-07","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that the Care Quality Commission's regulatory standards include verification of continence care treatment standards in (a) hospitals and (b) care homes.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7839","7839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390996","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to (a) close and (b) reduce services at the pediatric department at Ealing Hospital.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7769","7769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390997","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of GP practices in (a) England, (b) London, (c) the London Borough of Islington and (d) Islington South and Finsbury constituency have received funding from (i) the Prime Minister's Challenge Fund and (ii) the Primary Care Infrastructure Fund.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7782","7782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390998","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people applied for free NHS sight test vouchers in each of the last five years; and how many such applications were successful.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7809","7809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390999","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to improve (a) access to and (b) facilities for phlebotomy services for elderly and vulnerable people at Solihull Hospital.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7813","7813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391000","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps her Department has taken to (a) identify and (b) support young carers.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7795","7795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391001","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time was between referral to secondary care and the beginning of treatment in (a) England, (b) London, (c) the London Borough of Islington and (d) Islington South and Finsbury constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7784","7784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391002","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of UK-trained GPs who opted to practice overseas on completing their training in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7785","7785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391003","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any application for grant funding from Action on Smoking and Health has been refused in the last five years; and what the date and reasons for such refusal were in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7806","7806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391004","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people and what proportion of patients in each region of England have not seen a dentist in the last two years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7810","7810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391005","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) male and (b) female GPs who left the profession, for reasons other than retirement, in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7786","7786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391006","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many new (a) General Medical Services, (b) Personal Medical Services and (c) Alternative Provider Medical Services contracts were agreed with GP practices in (i) England, (ii) London, (iii) the London Borough of Islington and (iv) Islington South and Finsbury constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7783","7783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391007","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to monitor the introduction in Wales of an 18-month training placement for general practice during which trainees will be salaried directly by the Welsh NHS; and whether he plans to introduce such measures in England.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7787","7787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391008","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS dentists were registered in (a) Ashfield, (b) Nottinghamshire and (c) England in each year since 2008.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7835","7835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391009","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the number of burglaries in Copeland in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7800","7800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391010","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2015 to Question 5979, whether any files relating to child abuse have been destroyed by the intelligence and security services since 1 September 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7773","7773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391011","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the number of domestic violence reports in Copeland in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7799","7799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391012","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which organisations have received funding from the (a) Sexual Abuse Support Fund and (b) Child Abuse Inquiry Support Fund.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7792","7792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391013","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the financial support her Department provides to community organisations who provide specialised support services to victims of child sexual abuse; and if she will increase such funding.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7805","7805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391014","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will place in the Library copies of the assessment criteria used to determine applications received to the (a) Sexual Abuse Fund and (b) the Child Abuse Inquiry Support Fund since the launch of each such fund.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7812","7812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391015","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the number of offences of violence against a person in Copeland constituency in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7802","7802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391016","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the number of incidence of arson in Copeland constituency in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7803","7803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391017","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children under 16 in asylum-seeking families receive financial support from the Government.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7781","7781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391018","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of trends in the number of criminal damage reports in Copeland constituency in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7801","7801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391019","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was paid to panel members of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse in the 2014-15 financial year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7763","7763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391020","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was paid to (a) Dame Fiona Woolf and (b) Baroness Butler-Sloss for their work on the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7764","7764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391021","2015-07-21","Department for International Development","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the progress towards achieving the Millennium Development Goals.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7804","7804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391022","2015-07-21","Department for International Development","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with her international counterparts on the eradication of polio.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7818","7818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391023","2015-07-21","Department for International Development","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of how many people are at risk of death arising from the current conflict in Yemen; and what steps she is taking to protect such people.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7821","7821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391024","2015-07-21","Department for International Development","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the economic effects of the conflict in Yemen; and what steps she is taking to help people affected by that conflict.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7823","7823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391025","2015-07-21","Department for International Development","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has allocated to the UN humanitarian appeal for Yemen; and what information her Department holds on how much aid has been allocated by other countries.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7822","7822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391026","2015-07-21","Department for International Development","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to encourage other countries to donate to the Global Polio Eradication Initiative.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7819","7819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391027","2015-07-21","Department for International Development","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what information her Department holds on how many people have been displaced by the coalition bombing of Saada province in Yemen.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7890","7890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391028","2015-07-21","Department for International Development","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that donors' funds provided to UN and other non-governmental humanitarian agencies for use in Yemen will be delivered impartially to civilians in that country based on established humanitarian principles without political interference.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7891","7891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391029","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what arrangements have been made to distribute the £25 million of additional compensation to people infected with contaminated blood; when he plans to report progress on this matter to the House; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7788","7788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391030","2015-07-21","Prime Minister","2015-07-17","To ask the Prime Minister, when he was first informed of the involvement of British military personnel in military actions in Syria after the vote against military action in Syria on 30 August 2013.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7790","7790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391031","2015-07-21","Scotland Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy on a further referendum on Scottish independence of the Scottish Parliament election in 2016 delivering a majority for political parties committed to the holding of such a referendum.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7765","7765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391032","2015-07-21","Scotland Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what contingency plans his Department has prepared for the possibility of a further referendum on Scottish independence being the policy of the Scottish Government after the Scottish Parliament election in 2016.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7766","7766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391033","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will conduct a feasibility study on improving the trunk road section of the A595.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7770","7770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391034","2015-09-08","Department for Transport","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many bee hives are sited on land owned by his Department.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7847","7847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391035","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent on rail services per head of population in each region of England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7811","7811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391036","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what factors were taken into account in setting the application fee for the Child Maintenance Service at £20.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7793","7793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391037","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he intends to publish the next edition of the Low Income Dynamics analysis.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7837","7837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391038","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of children living in poverty in (a) Copeland and (b) Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7879","7879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391039","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Copeland constituency participated in the Work Programme scheme in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7880","7880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391040","2015-07-21","Cabinet Office","2015-07-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people are employed on zero hours contracts in Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7881","7881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391041","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the Government's policy is on 18 to 21 year olds in need of housing support.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7882","7882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391042","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many higher-rate telephone numbers his Department operates for new and existing claimants, and for which benefit categories; and what the average cost and duration is of each call to each of those numbers by benefit category.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7892","7892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391043","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Tooting constituency have been affected by the benefit cap.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7893","7893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391044","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been affected by the benefit cap in Greater London since April 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7894","7894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391045","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been affected by the benefit cap in the London Borough of Wandsworth since April 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7895","7895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391046","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an exemption to his proposed reduction in housing benefit for young people aged 21 and younger who cannot live with their parents and are at risk of homelessness.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7885","7885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391047","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what information his Department collects on the number of people who die after having their benefit withdrawn following being sanctioned.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7886","7886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390646","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will request the Royal Mail to review the (a) effectiveness and (b) fairness of its postal compensation scheme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7536","7536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390647","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 8.3 of the document Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, what areas and markets are of strategic importance and potential to the UK economy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7582","7582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390648","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage greater business participation in the Horizon 2020 research and innovation framework programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7566","7566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390649","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people who completed an apprenticeship programme in (a) Copeland constituency and (b) Cumbria received a full-time job within six months of completion of their apprenticeship in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7626","7626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390650","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprenticeship starts there were in each business sector in (a) Copeland constituency and (b) Cumbria in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7627","7627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390651","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what military hardware and components the UK has sold to Israel in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7621","7621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390652","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what military hardware and components the UK has imported from Israel in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7622","7622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390653","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many arms export licences have been issued for exports to Israel in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7623","7623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390654","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people were employed in the aerospace, defence, security and space industry in (a) each country of the UK and (b) each region of England in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7676","7676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390655","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the contribution to the UK economy of the cyber-technology sector within the aerospace, defence, security and space industry.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7677","7677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390656","2015-09-07","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what advice he has received from Islamic scholars on the writing off of sharia compliant student loans.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7681","7681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390657","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will review his Department's policy on arms export licence agreements with Israel.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7704","7704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390658","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the statutory requirements are for local enterprise partnerships on the transparency of their operations and responsibilities; and what guidance he has issued on those requirements.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7718","7718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390659","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to increase the transparency of the operations of local enterprise partnerships.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7719","7719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390660","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what qualifications other than NVQs are required as part of apprenticeships.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7711","7711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390661","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to enhance support for opportunity entrepreneurs to set up their own businesses.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7714","7714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390662","2015-07-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of further education colleges reported a financial deficit in 2014-15.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7745","7745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390663","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civil servants have filed and subsequently withdrawn HR Form 034 since 27 October 2014.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7735","7735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390664","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civil servants filed and subsequently withdrew HR Form 034 in each of the last four financial years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7736","7736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390665","2015-07-20","Cabinet Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much each Department spent on each method of advertising in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7634","7634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390666","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the value of wine in the Government wine cellar.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7637","7637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390667","2015-07-21","Cabinet Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 2556, whether, under his plans, digital illiteracy will stay above the target of 10 per cent of the population until 2026.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7666","7666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390668","2015-07-21","Cabinet Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which digital inclusion programmes central government departments and non-departmental public bodies are (a) funding or (b) participating in.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7667","7667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390669","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he next plans to publish an updated National Infrastructure Plan.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7528","7528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390670","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the value is of UK pension fund (a) equity assets, (b) fixed income assets, (c) real estate assets, (d) private equity assets, (e) private equity assets (f) infrastructure assets, (g) hedge fund assets and (h) cash held in (i) the UK and (ii) overseas.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7580","7580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390671","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what additional responsibilities he intends to give to the Office for Tax Simplification; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7581","7581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390672","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, at what level he intends to set the apprenticeship levy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7579","7579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390673","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce the current account deficit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7624","7624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390674","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what Barnett consequential will accrue to Wales as a result of the planned saving of £2.5 billion of the decision to replace maintenance grants with maintenance loans for students in England.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7618","7618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390675","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average length of time is between the date of receipt by HM Revenue and Customs of correspondence about inheritance tax liability and a response being given.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7586","7586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390676","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to include cities in the North East in the Northern Powerhouse initiative; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7614","7614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390677","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to improve competition in small and medium-sized enterprise bank lending; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7615","7615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390678","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which firms have relinquished a banking licence in the last 30 years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7617","7617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390679","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claimants will receive a net reduction in (a) tax credits, (b) disability living allowance and (c) housing support as a result of measures in the 2015 Summer Budget.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7561","7561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390680","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies will be required to pay the apprenticeship levy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7551","7551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390681","2015-07-20","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what changes he intends to make to the funding arrangements for Network Rail; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7552","7552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390682","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he intends to (a) maintain, (b) increase or (c) decrease scientific and medical research spending in real terms over the next (i) one year and (ii) five years.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7611","7611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390683","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of households in Scotland which will experience a reduction in tax credits as a result of measures announced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7652","7652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390684","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the effect on the (a) NHS budget and (b) Barnett formula of reductions in the eligibility criteria for the NHS tax credit exemption certificate.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7609","7609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390685","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the number of people that received dividends of £5,000 or more in 2014.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7599","7599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390686","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was raised from the sale of radio spectrum in each financial year since 2010-11; and how much he expects to accrue to the public purse in such ways in each financial year to 2019-20.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7641","7641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390687","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which firms have been granted a banking licence since April 1985.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7642","7642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390688","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number of single earner married couples and (b) proportion of all married couples who are single earner married couples in each country of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7643","7643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390689","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidance his Department has issued on how tax credit claimants can calculate how much their tax credit entitlement will change as a result of changes to tax credit entitlement announced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7590","7590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390690","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to improve the UK's attractiveness to private investment in infrastructure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7616","7616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390691","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the total reduction in credits to households in Scotland that will arise in the next financial year as a result of measures announced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7595","7595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390692","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate what the cost to each local authority in England and Wales will be of paying staff the new National Living Wage in April (a) 2016 and (b) 2020.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7737","7737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390693","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has commissioned on the effect on local authority budgets of paying the new National Living Wage to external staff commissioned by local authorities to provide adult social care.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7738","7738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390694","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of proposed changes to tax credits and housing benefit in the Summer Budget 2015 on long-term trends in family size.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7688","7688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390695","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the average change in income for (a) women and (b) households with children of the tax credit changes outlined in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7732","7732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390696","2015-09-07","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will establish a tax-free savings vehicle specifically designed to save for funerals.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7682","7682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390697","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what payments have accrued to the Exchequer from the New Covent Garden Market Authority in the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7708","7708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390698","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials in his Department are working on the Scottish rate of income tax.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7754","7754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390699","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much tax relief was granted (a) to higher rate taxpayers and (b) in total in respect of (i) defined contribution and (ii) defined benefit pension schemes in 2014-15.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7717","7717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390700","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what research his Department has carried out on the effect of the National Living Wage on local authority staffing costs; and if he will place a copy of such research in the Library.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7739","7739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390701","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Paragraph 2.103 of the Summer Budget 2015, if he will estimate the number of women who will be affected by the limit of child tax credits; and how many such women will be covered by exceptional circumstances.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7734","7734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390702","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Local Government Association on providing financial support for local authorities to assist meeting any costs of paying staff the National Living Wage.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7740","7740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390703","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of paying the National Living Wage for adult social care commissioned by local authorities over the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7741","7741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390704","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.15 of Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, if he will issue guidance on the term zonal system, used in connection with brownfield sites; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7726","7726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390705","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.10 of Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, how much time his Department will allow local authorities to put in place local plans where they have not yet done so before his Department will intervene to enforce this.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7728","7728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390706","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect of a rise in mortgage rates on future levels of house building.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7729","7729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390707","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.10 of Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, what steps he plans to take to ensure that there is adequate consultation with local people when imposing local plans on behalf of local authorities.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7727","7727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390708","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2015 to Question 5575, how the four-year residency of EU migrants is to be proven; upon whom the onus of proof that the residency criterion is met will lie; and what measures social housing providers will take to verify any proof they are given that residency criteria are met.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7747","7747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390709","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.21 of Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, whether height restrictions will apply in the policy to remove the need for planning permission for upwards extensions.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7722","7722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390710","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 917 of Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, whether under these proposals local authorities could be required to allow new building on greenbelt sites in cases where the Government imposes a local plan on their behalf.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7758","7758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390711","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.17 of Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, how he will implement a dispute resolution mechanism for section 106 agreements.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7723","7723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390712","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.17 of Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, how he plans to adequately resource local authorities to ensure planning decisions are made on time where they are currently failing to do so.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7725","7725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390713","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.21 of the document Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, what assessment his Department has made of additional infrastructure needs as a result of removing the need for planning permission for upwards extensions.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7720","7720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390714","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 921 of Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of removing the need for planning permission for upwards extensions on building safety.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7756","7756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390715","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.21 of Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, whether the policy of allowing extra storeys to be built on neighbouring properties in London will apply to (a) residential and (b) commercial property.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7721","7721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390716","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 917 of Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, what the scope is of those projects with an element of housing development which can be fast tracked through the Nationally Significant Infrastructure Projects regime.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7757","7757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390717","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) social and (b) affordable homes were built in (i) London and (ii) each London borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7671","7671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390718","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department has issued to local authorities on the aesthetic effect of loft extensions on residential areas.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7693","7693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390719","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) children and (b) adults were living in overcrowded accommodation in (i) London and (ii) each London borough in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7674","7674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390720","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the reduction in rent payment rates amongst social sector tenants upon moving to a direct payment scheme.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7675","7675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390721","2015-07-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the level of building on greenbelt sites in each year since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7663","7663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390722","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the effects on housing supply and affordability of the practice of investors selling on a house at a higher price to another investor immediately after purchase; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7625","7625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390723","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what weight he gave to the likely effect on commuter train services of the work needed to the Elstree Tunnels when approving the Radlett Rail Freight Terminal.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7545","7545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390724","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will extend the Internet of Things competition for UK cities launched on 13 July 2015 to rural communities.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7651","7651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390725","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage more young people in rural communities to pursue careers in the arts.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7632","7632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390726","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will introduce a UK Community of Culture Award to allow non-cities to experience the same benefits as cities awarded UK City of Culture awards.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7631","7631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390727","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of (a) children and (b) adults in Cumbria who swim.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7635","7635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390728","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to promote the legacy of the 2012 London Olympic and Paralympic Games in the North West.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7636","7636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390729","2015-07-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether regulations are in place on the length and frequency of internet advertising; and whether Ofcom or his Department has had discussions with the Advertising Standards Authority on the regulation of such advertising.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7668","7668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390730","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many serving members of the Fleet Air Arm have given notice of their intention to leave before serving the time that they signed up for in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7605","7605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390731","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of the level of morale amongst military personnel on the front line.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7606","7606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390732","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many migrants his Department has rescued from the Mediterranean sea each week since (a) HMS Bulwark and (b) HMS Enterprise commenced operations in that area.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7650","7650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390733","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the recent contract awarded to Raytheon Systems Ltd for Paveway IV bombs is intended to (a) replenish or (b) increase stock.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7544","7544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390734","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2015 to Question HL1125 on Saudi Arabia: Yemen, how many precision-guided weapons of what type are being provided to Saudi Arabian armed forces; what procedures are in place to monitor the use of such weapons by Saudi Arabian armed forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7584","7584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390735","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to develop the UK's technological edge in military capabilities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7548","7548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390736","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on (a) intermural and (b) extramural research in each financial year between 2010-11 and 2014-15.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7550","7550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390737","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the balance between NATO and Russian (a) naval, (b) air, (c) ground and (d) nuclear forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7549","7549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390738","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 9 September to Question 207819 on Saudi Arabia, what roles British personnel stationed in Saudi Arabia are carrying out in support of the Saudi armed forces military operations in Yemen; what steps he has taken to ensure that such military operations are not in breech of international humanitarian law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7583","7583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390739","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the 21 concurrent operations in which UK armed forces are presently engaged, together with (a) their location, (b) their planned duration and (c) the numbers of personnel involved in each such operation.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7746","7746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390740","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 23 of the Ofsted report, Children looked after placements by English authorities, published on 14 July 2015, how many of the 29 Chinese children who were missing from care on 31 March 2014 had gone missing from (a) foster care, (b) children's homes, (c) independent living, (d) secure units, young offenders' institutions or prisons and (e) residential schools.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7574","7574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390741","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 23 of the Ofsted report, Children looked after placements by English authorities, published on 14 July 2015, in the care of which local authorities were the 33 children missing for six months or longer on 31 March 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7575","7575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390742","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 23 of the Ofsted report, Children looked after placements by English authorities, published on 14 July 2015, how many of the 33 children missing for six months or longer on 31 March 2014 were (a) male and (b) female; and how many such children were (i) under 10, (ii) aged between 10 and 12, (iii) aged between 13 and 15 and (iv) aged between 16 and 18 years old when they went missing.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7576","7576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390743","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 23 of the Ofsted report, Children looked after placements by English authorities, published on 14 July 2015, how many of the 29 Chinese children who were missing from care on 31 March 2014 had been missing for (a) less than six months, (b) between six months and one year and (c) more than one year.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7577","7577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390744","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 23 of the Ofsted report, Children looked after placements by English authorities, published on 14 July 2015, how many of the 33 children were missing from (a) foster care, (b) children's homes, (c) independent living, (d) secure units, young offenders' institutions or prisons and (e) residential schools.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7578","7578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390745","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will introduce lessons on managing the risk of injuries related to digital screen use to school curriculums.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7555","7555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390746","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many legal cases are being brought against schools in the UK related to injuries caused by digital screen use.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7556","7556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390747","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many days of absence were reported to her Department on grounds of musculoskeletal injury in the (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15 school year.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7557","7557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390748","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what research her Department has undertaken on the potential effect of digital screen use on students in the last five years.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7558","7558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390749","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent meetings she has had with civil society groups on potential adverse health effects of introducing more technology in schools.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7542","7542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390750","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on (a) tablet computers and (b) other new information technology for students in schools in (i) 2012-13 and (ii) 2013-14.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7554","7554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390751","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in care have been placed in children's homes outside their local authority area in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7603","7603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390752","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken to reduce the number of children in care placed out of their home local authority area.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7604","7604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390753","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on introducing chartered teacher status within the education profession; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7638","7638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390754","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve skills within the teaching profession; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7639","7639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390755","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve the leadership skills of head teachers; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7640","7640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390756","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children in Copeland constituency have been identified as gifted and talented in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7633","7633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390757","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to make Ofsted inspections of (a) children's centres and (b) other early years settings as rigorous as inspection of primary and secondary schools.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7687","7687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390758","2015-07-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what guidance her Department has published on the effect of loft extensions on the installation of solar roof panels.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7692","7692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390759","2015-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress has been made on (a) negotiation on and (b) preparations for the November 2015 climate change conference; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7679","7679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390760","2015-07-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential use of the River Ouse as a source of renewable energy.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7547","7547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390761","2015-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to ensure that the fuel poverty strategy benefits people living in park homes.","Biography information for Seema Kennedy","Seema Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7569","7569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390762","2015-07-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the World Nuclear Industry Status Report 2015 published on 15 July 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7564","7564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390763","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to section 9.17 of Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published on 10 July 2015, Cm 9098, what impact assessment his Department has made of any impact assessment of reducing net regulation on housebuilders on meeting climate change targets.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7724","7724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390764","2015-07-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she intends to bring forward legislative proposals to prohibit the use of wild animals in circuses.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7749","7749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390765","2015-07-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on the discard of fish which can no longer be discarded lawfully at sea on land, and the potential utilisation of such fish; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7585","7585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390766","2015-07-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has received from tenants of the New Covent Garden market Authority on that market's redevelopment in the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7620","7620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390767","2015-07-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the (a) positions and (b) pay were of the principal officers of the New Covent Garden Market Authority in the last five years; and what consultation process will take place before any pay increases are awarded.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7755","7755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390768","2015-07-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what receipts the New Covent Garden Market Authority has received from the sale of land in the last five years; who bought the land in each such case; and for what purpose the land was sold in each such case.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7712","7712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390769","2015-07-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the demolition and rebuilding of the car park in New Covent Garden Market is forecast to cost.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7707","7707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390770","2015-07-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what expenses have been claimed by the directors of the New Covent Garden Market Authority in the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7644","7644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390771","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department is able to grant special mission immunity status to a person in the UK subject to an European arrest warrant.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7645","7645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390772","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what powers he has to re-assess special mission immunity status after entry; and on what grounds such a request made prior to entry can be refused.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7649","7649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390773","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many people from which countries were granted special mission immunity status in 2015 after entering the UK without that status.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7646","7646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390774","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what criteria are used to assess a request for special mission immunity status for a person who entered the UK without that status.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7647","7647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390775","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department can grant special mission immunity status to a person who entered the UK without that status.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7648","7648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390776","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to build sustainable peace in the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7613","7613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390777","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which teams from which countries is the UK Preventing Sexual Violence Initiative expert team working in partnership with.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7597","7597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390778","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the compliance of signatories to the Declaration of Commitment to End Sexual Violence in Conflict with the terms of that declaration.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7598","7598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390779","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy of the Human Rights Watch report, One passport, two systems, China's restrictions on foreign travel by Tibetans and others; and when he last raised the subject of the treatment of China's religious minorities with the Chinese government.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7607","7607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390780","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support his Department has provided to Ministers of the Scottish Government undertaking overseas travel in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7752","7752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390781","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many Consular (a) hubs and (b) spokes there are in each region; and what criteria his Department has set for deciding those numbers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7669","7669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390782","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Irish counterpart on the implications of a potential UK vote to leave the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7686","7686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390783","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the EU Trust Fund for the Central African Republic supports reconciliation and peacebuilding activities.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7697","7697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390784","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to fulfil its Responsibility to Protect in the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7698","7698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390785","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons the offence provisions in schedules 1 and 2 of the European Referendum Bill provide for the same custodial penalty whether an accused person is convicted on indictment or on summary complaint.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7703","7703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390786","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department plans to continue to publish detailed analysis of the human rights situation in countries of concern in an annual human rights report.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7689","7689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390787","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he proposes to change the (a) length and (b) format of his Department's annual report on human rights and democracy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7690","7690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390788","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the humanitarian situation in Yemen's Saada province and (b) whether British arms and equipment exported to Saudi Arabia have been sued by Saudi-armed forces in Saada province; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7565","7565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390789","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the budget was of the Preventing Sexual Violence Initiative (PSVI) in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15; and what budget has been allocated for the PSVI in 2015-16.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7559","7559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390790","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's human rights priorities are for the current Parliament.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7537","7537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390791","2015-07-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, to which countries the UK Prevention Sexual Violence Initiative experts were deployed in 2014-15; and to which countries that team will be deployed in 2015-16.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7533","7533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390792","2015-07-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support the Central African Republic in its preparations for national elections in 2015.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7539","7539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390793","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when care.data will be rolled out nationally; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7540","7540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390794","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many representations he has received from (a) individuals and (b) groups (i) in favour of and (ii) against care.data in the last six months.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7541","7541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390795","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of variations in the length of time NHS trusts take to implement NICE guidance.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7529","7529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390796","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made in developing a HIV prevention strategy; and what timetable he has set for the development of that strategy.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7527","7527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390797","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 6279, on accident and emergency departments: working hours, where the information is held and how it can be accessed.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7530","7530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390798","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of older people experiencing loneliness.","Biography information for Seema Kennedy","Seema Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7567","7567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390799","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve rates of early diagnosis of breast cancer.","Biography information for Seema Kennedy","Seema Kennedy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7568","7568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390800","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of (a) closing 450 beds at the Royal Bournemouth Hospital and replacing them with 450 new beds at Poole General Hospital and (b) closing 450 beds at Poole General Hospital and replacing them with 450 beds at the Royal Bournemouth Hospital.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7587","7587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390801","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) NHS establishments, (b) private and medical establishments and (c) registered medical practitioners operate in the UK; how many such establishments or practitioners process personal data for which notification or registration with the Information Commissioner is required; and what estimate he has made of how much revenue has been generated by registered medical practitioners in the UK from processing personal data in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7702","7702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390802","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support and guidance has been provided by his Department and the NHS to ensure that (a) NHS establishments, (b) private and medical establishments, (c) registered medical practitioners and (d) medical practitioner regulatory bodies are aware of their obligations under the Data Protection Act; and what plans he has to provide such support and guidance to each of those entities.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7701","7701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390803","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were treated using the drug Fampyra in (a) the UK, (b) each English region, (c) each parliamentary constituency and (d) each Clinical Commissioning Group.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7680","7680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390804","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to provide funding for projects and research on aetiology and the treatment of Fibromyalgia.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7759","7759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390805","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have opted out of the care.data scheme in each of the pathfinder areas.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7710","7710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390806","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessments he has made of the deliverability of care.data during the pathfinder stage.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7709","7709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390807","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether devolution of health commissioning to combined authorities will have any effect on the Government's plan for real terms increases in NHS spending in each year of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7601","7601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390808","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps (a) his Department, (b) Public Health England and (c) NHS England are taking to ensure that local antibiotic stewardship policies and prescribing practices are driven by the perceived value of antibiotics.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7592","7592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390809","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of the unbundling of new and emerging antibiotics from the national tariff to address the perceived cost barrier impeding optimal prescribing.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7593","7593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390810","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps (a) his Department, (b) Public Health England and (c) NHS England are taking to improve antibiotic stewardship and promote the optimal prescribing of antibiotics in the secondary and primary care settings.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7594","7594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390811","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the allocation of commissioning resources for 2015-16, for what reason the allocation for (a) NHS Oldham is 49 per cent below target, (b) Greater Manchester is two per cent below target, (c) NHS Isle of Wight is 18.02 per cent above target, (d) NHS West London is 31.52 per cent above target and (e) NHS Westminster is 26.24 per cent above target; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7596","7596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390812","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of health and care professionals registered with the (a) General Chiropractic Council, (b) General Dental Council, (c) General Medical Council, (d) General Optical Council, (e) General Osteopathic Council, (f) General Pharmaceutical Council, (g) Health and Care Professions Council, (h) Nursing and Midwifery Council and (i) Pharmaceutical Society of Northern Ireland in each of the last five years is from overseas.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7591","7591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390813","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 25 November 2014 to Question 215524, when Public Health England intends to publish data on the mortality rate for deaths in 2013 involving (a) C. difficile and (b) MRSA in (i) England and (ii) each NHS trust.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7619","7619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390814","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to initiate a public awareness campaign before the national rollout of care.data.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7629","7629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390815","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP practices in each pathfinder area have signed up to care.data.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7630","7630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390816","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) children and (b) adults in (i) Copeland constituency, (ii) Cumbria and (iii) England are classed as (A) overweight, (B) obese and (C) morbidly obese.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7628","7628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390817","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential reasons for changes in the number of recipients of Healthy Start in the last year; and what steps he is taking to ensure that all those who are eligible are encouraged to apply for that benefit.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7612","7612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390818","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that patients with chronic myeloid leukaemia in England have access to (a) Ponatinib and (b) other innovative new medicines.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7658","7658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390819","2015-07-20","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merit of the production of NICE evidence summaries for new and emerging antibiotics as a means of supporting the decisions of local stewardship and medicines management committees.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7608","7608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390820","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of potential delays for patients in access to medicines as a result of changes to the National Cancer Drugs Fund in March 2016.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7656","7656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390821","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal Colleges on the future of the National Cancer Drugs Fund beyond March 2016.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7657","7657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390822","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the cost of medical indemnity cover required by GP practices to operate outside regular out of hours services on the availability of out of hours provision.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7653","7653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390823","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will pay the costs of medical indemnity cover required by GP practices when providing an out of regular hours service.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7654","7654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390824","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce smoking-related deaths in areas where there is higher than average incidence of such deaths.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7743","7743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390825","2015-07-21","Department of Health","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy of the red risk rating of the care.data programme by the Major Projects Authority.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7744","7744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390826","2015-07-21","Cabinet Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many births were recorded at (a) West Cumberland Hospital and (b) Cumberland Infirmary, Carlisle in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7742","7742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390827","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints of racism were (a) made and (b) upheld against Metropolitan Police officers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7672","7672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390828","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints of racism upheld against Metropolitan Police officers resulted in (a) no action taken, (b) suspension, (c) other disciplinary measures and (d) dismissal in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7673","7673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390829","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of applications for visitor visas from each country were accepted in the last year for which records are available.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7602","7602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390830","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, under what circumstances a non-British parent of a young child based in the UK, who is not allowed to stay in the country for periods longer than six months, stops being considered as a primary care giver for immigration purposes as a result of siblings filling that role.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7600","7600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390831","2015-07-20","Home Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to speed up the repatriation of Grzegorz Kowalski; and when Mr Kowalski will be repatriated.","Biography information for Chloe Smith","Chloe Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7715","7715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390832","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in each local authority district in Lancashire hold gun licences.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7684","7684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390833","2015-09-07","Home Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the date was of the most recent gun amnesty in each police force area in England; and how many firearms were handed-in in each such amnesty.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7683","7683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390834","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has made an assessment of the potential merits of wider use of identity documentation to assist in the detection of illegal immigrants living in the UK.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7562","7562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390835","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2015 to Question 5846, what (a) proportion and (b) number of applications for a passport for a child overseas take longer than eight months to process.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7531","7531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390836","2015-07-21","Home Office","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2015 to Question 5849, how many complaints she has received on slow service at HM Passport Office in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7532","7532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390837","2015-07-21","House of Commons Commission","2015-07-16","To ask the Rt. Hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what estimate he has made of the change in the cost of electronic upgrades for recording divisions arising from proposed changes to Standing Orders on English votes on English laws.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7760","7760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390838","2015-07-20","House of Commons Commission","2015-07-16","To ask the Rt. Hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what progress has been made on developing device independent applications for the distribution of select committee papers.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7713","7713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390839","2015-07-20","House of Commons Commission","2015-07-16","To ask the Rt. Hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, if the Commission will take steps to allow door-keeping staff a summer uniform made from lighter materials to reduce discomfort in hot weather.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7716","7716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390840","2015-07-21","Department for International Development","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the level and sustainability of public and private debt in emerging African economies.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7670","7670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390841","2015-07-20","Department for International Development","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to support women's rights and help victims of sexual and gender-based violence in the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7534","7534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390842","2015-07-20","Department for International Development","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to implement the commitment in the June 2015 G7 Leaders' declaration to invest in the prevention and control of neglected tropical diseases.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7535","7535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390843","2015-07-20","Department for International Development","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect of her Department's expenditure in the Central African Republic on that country's economic prospects.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7538","7538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390844","2015-07-20","Department for International Development","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government plans to support the target on ending violence against women and girls at the UN General Assembly in September 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7543","7543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390845","2015-07-20","Department for International Development","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the status is of her Department's Framework on Health Systems Strengthening; what the timeline is for its publication; and how civil society will be consulted during its development.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7553","7553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390846","2015-07-21","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average time taken is by bailiffs at Wandsworth County Court to execute possession orders; and if he will make it his policy to ensure that all applications made for the execution of county court possession orders by county court bailiffs are carried out within seven days of that application being made.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7588","7588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390847","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants in Scotland are in the Work Related Activity Group.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7751","7751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390848","2015-07-20","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what procedures are in place to ensure aircraft maintenance crews are (a) fit to work and (b) not overtired.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7699","7699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390849","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Ministers in his Department approved or were consulted on the instruction made in late March 2015 that Network Rail should undertake a fuller assessment of its emerging cost estimates.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7730","7730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390850","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his contribution in the House of 16 July 2015 in response to the hon. Member for Colne Valley, what restriction will prevent the next operator of the Northern franchise from running refurbished London Underground trains on routes previously served by Pacers.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7731","7731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390851","2015-07-20","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what reports he has requested from the Civil Aviation Authority on the recent incident at Heathrow Airport when errors in aircraft maintenance procedures caused an emergency landing.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7700","7700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390852","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what average number of pilings per night was achieved by Network Rail's High Output Plant System train during (a) October to December 2014, (b) January to March 2015 and (c) April to June 2015.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7665","7665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390853","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on establishing a separate Devon and Cornwall rail franchise.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7664","7664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390854","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the number of journeys by hauliers from Scotland that have been delayed as a result of (a) closures to the Channel Tunnel and (b) ferry delays due to disruptions at Calais in the last three months.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7662","7662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390855","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of converting a Class 801 Intercity Express Programme unit to bi-mode diesel operation.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7660","7660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390856","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what internal assessment Network Rail is undertaking of its capacity to deliver major enhancement projects.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7661","7661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390857","2015-07-20","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department plans to allocate to achieving its target of 55 per cent of children walking to school; and how his Department arrived at that figure.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7610","7610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390858","2015-07-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his policy is towards global frequency allocation from the International Telecommunications Union at the World Radiocommunication Conference in November 2015 for the support of satellite based automatic dependant surveillance broadcast.","Biography information for Graham Stringer","Graham Stringer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7659","7659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390859","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department will publish the shortlist of applications for the next round of funding for the Regional Air Connectivity Fund.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7570","7570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390860","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Prime Minister on the (a) safety of cyclists and existing regulations on HGVs and (b) Cycling and Walking Investment Strategy.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7563","7563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390861","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department intends to announce the recipients of awards from the next round of funding for the Regional Air Connectivity Fund.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7571","7571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390862","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the budget is for the next round of funding for the Regional Air Connectivity Fund; and for how long that funding round will last.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7572","7572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390863","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of past awards from the Regional Air Connectivity Fund in establishing new routes; and what recent assessment he has made of whether such routes would remain viable if unsubsidised.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7573","7573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390864","2015-07-21","Women and Equalities","2015-07-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what steps she is taking to improve the representation of women in Parliament.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7733","7733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390865","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Schedule 6 of the Welfare Reform Act 2009, when he expects the Government to implement equal birth registration.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7678","7678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390866","2015-09-07","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many medical assessment centres there are for (a) employment and support allowance applicants and (b) personal independence payment claimants living within 90 minutes travelling time by public transport from the PR1 8UQ postcode.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7685","7685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390867","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will extend the special rules for attendance allowance to include those suffering from significant brain injuries.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7696","7696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390868","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much child maintenance was not collected in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7691","7691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390869","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the effect of the measures in the Summer Budget 2015 on foodbank use in Scotland.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7750","7750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390870","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure self-employed people claiming child maintenance declare their income in full.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7694","7694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390871","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to improve the collection of child maintenance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7695","7695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390872","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with Ministers in the Scottish Government on legislation to replace the Child Poverty Act 2010.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7705","7705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390873","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Scottish households have backdated housing benefit claims in excess of four weeks.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7753","7753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390874","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Scottish households will be affected by a reduction in the benefit cap to £20,000 per year.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7706","7706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390875","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of self-employed people made regular pension contributions in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7655","7655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390876","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy not to require those undergoing radiotherapy to undertake fit-for-work assessments.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7589","7589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390877","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) England, (b) Cumbria and (c) Copeland receive employment and support allowance in the work-related activity group.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7560","7560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390878","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to increase the £30,000 threshold for the Local Government Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7546","7546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390879","2015-07-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2015 to Question 5750, when figures for after August 2014 will be available.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7748","7748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390145","2015-07-20","Attorney General","2015-07-15","To ask the Attorney General, what guidance he provides to Government Legal Service (GLS) personnel on compliance with the Data Protection Act by (a) the Government, (b) agencies and (c) clients of the GLS to ensure that (i) data is not sent to a data controller who is not registered under the Data Protection Act, but ought to have done so and (ii) secure data handling procedures are operated by both the GLS and any external data controller to whom data is sent.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7382","7382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390146","2015-07-20","Attorney General","2015-07-15","To ask the Attorney General, who in the Government Legal Service (GLS) has operational lead responsibility for ensuring that training is provided to officials of the GLS on compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998 ICO guidance and Treasury Solicitor and GLS information security and data protection related policies and procedures; and what assessment (a) has been and (b) will be made on what date and by whom of the effectiveness of that training provision.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7444","7444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390147","2015-07-20","Attorney General","2015-07-15","To ask the Attorney General, what guidance he provides to (a) Government Legal Service personnel and officials in his Department and (b) others on the steps they (i) can and (ii) must take if they are or should reasonably be aware that data has been unlawfully processed by a data controller because that controller has not notified the Information Commissioner's Office.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7445","7445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390148","2015-07-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what obligations (a) people with reporting obligations in the regulated sector and (b) others have to ensure that a data controller who has processed personal data when not entitled to do so because of lack of notification does not benefit from any proceeds that may have been received as a consequence of that processing; and what sanctions can be taken against people who fail to fulfil those obligations.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7446","7446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390149","2015-07-20","Attorney General","2015-07-15","To ask the Attorney General, what data protection training has been given to (a) the Treasury Solicitor, (b) the Head of Litigation, (c) the Head of the Bona Vacantia Division, (d) the Ministry of Justice Advisory SCS1 Team Leaders, (e) the Ministry of Justice Legal SCS2 Team Leaders and (f) Legal Aid Agency Senior Lawyers at Grade 6 or above since 1 July 2013.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7506","7506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390150","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much was paid in bonuses to Met Office staff in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7507","7507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390151","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 17 June 2015 to Question 2127, how many Growth Vouchers were not redeemed by the deadline of 30 June; and what the total value was of those unredeemed vouchers.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7500","7500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390152","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish an updated assessment of the RAB charge taking into account announcements in the Summer Budget 2015; and what estimate he has made since that Budget on the level of RAB charge in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7501","7501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390153","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what research he has (a) commissioned and (b) examined on the potential effects of announcements in the Summer Budget 2015 on the number of students (i) applying to and (ii) taking up places at universities.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7502","7502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390154","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what forecast his Department or its agencies has made of the number of (a) applications to and (b) numbers taking up places at universities in each of the next five years; and whether those forecasts have been changed as a result of announcements in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7503","7503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390155","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) formal and (b) informal support is being provided by the Government to the local enterprise partnership network.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7504","7504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390156","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of staff of his Department were based in each region of the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7522","7522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390157","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) provision he has made and (b) guidance he plans to issue on the development of Science and Innovation Audits in areas which are part of more than one local enterprise partnership.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7430","7430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390158","2015-07-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of businesses in the UK process personal data for which registration with the Information Commissioner is required; and what estimate he has made of how much revenue is generated by businesses in the UK in each year from processing of personal data.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7442","7442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390159","2015-07-20","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what support and guidance (a) has been and (b) will be provided by his Department to (i) new and (ii) established businesses on their obligations under the Data Protection Act 1998.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7443","7443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390160","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 3.13 of the report Fixing the foundations: creating a more prosperous nation, published in July 2015, what qualifications he intends to abolish; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7458","7458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390161","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the net economic contribution of non-EU university students to the UK economy.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7467","7467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390162","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of likely changes in the number of non-EU national students studying at UK universities over the next five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7468","7468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390163","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the proportion of UK university funding contributed by non-EU nationals.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7469","7469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390164","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make representations to UCAS on releasing anonymised individual data on applications and admissions to universities for the purpose of research on access to higher education.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7408","7408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390165","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent progress he has made on publishing a statutory code for pub companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7357","7357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390166","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will endorse the Charter for Sustainable British Steel and amend his Department's procurement policies accordingly.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7260","7260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390167","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of zombie companies on national productivity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7261","7261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390168","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of employee ownership on national productivity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7262","7262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390169","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many and what proportion of those eligible to receive university maintenance grants were (a) women, (b) men, (c) black and minority ethnic, (d) white British and (e) disabled in the last financial year.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7296","7296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390170","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the likely default rate of the new university maintenance loans; and what provisions he has made to cover that cost.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7297","7297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390171","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Student Loans Company on the level of complaints it receives.","Biography information for Edward Argar","Edward Argar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7190","7190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390172","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on (a) the number of monitoring stations which recorded the reported temperature of 36.7 degrees Celsius on 1 July 2015 and (b) for how long each such monitoring station recorded that temperature that day.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7239","7239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390173","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on the number of sources from which data was gathered by the Meteorological Office to demonstrate that 1 July 2015 was the hottest July day recorded in the UK.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7238","7238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390174","2015-07-20","Cabinet Office","2015-07-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many complaints have been logged by his Department on the performance of Capita in relation to their administration of the recruitment of the Civil Service Apprenticeship Scheme.","Biography information for Sir Alan Duncan","Sir Alan Duncan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7176","7176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390175","2015-07-20","Cabinet Office","2015-07-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what mechanisms his Department has for gauging the performance of Capita in relation to its administration of the recruitment of the Civil Service Apprenticeship Scheme.","Biography information for Sir Alan Duncan","Sir Alan Duncan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7177","7177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390176","2015-07-20","Cabinet Office","2015-07-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what representations he has received on the removal of the contract for Civil Service Apprenticeship recruitment from Capita.","Biography information for Sir Alan Duncan","Sir Alan Duncan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7178","7178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390177","2015-07-20","Cabinet Office","2015-07-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the performance of Capita in administering the recruitment of the Civil Service Apprenticeship Scheme.","Biography information for Sir Alan Duncan","Sir Alan Duncan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7175","7175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390178","2015-07-20","Home Office","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding the Government has allocated to the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse for this financial year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7352","7352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390179","2015-07-20","Cabinet Office","2015-07-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of staff of all Government departments were based in each region of the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7523","7523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390180","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 5989, what estimate he has made of the cost of estimating the number of employees who receive more in tax credits than they pay in tax and national insurance contributions.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7519","7519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390181","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.213 of the Summer Budget 2015 and paragraph 1.252 of the Autumn Statement 2014, what steps he plans to take to ask the tobacco industry to make a greater contribution to the costs imposed by smoking on society.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7521","7521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390182","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will conduct a public consultation on the HM Revenue and Customs Building our Future programme.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7449","7449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390183","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment HM Revenue and Customs has made of the effectiveness of the Codentify tracking and tracing system in preventing illicit trade in tobacco; and whether his Department plans to commission an independent assessment of the potential for that system to meet the requirement for a tracking and tracing system under the EU Tobacco Products Directive.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7477","7477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390184","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.10 of the Government's response to the independent review of the Money Advice Service, published in March 2015, when his Department plans to publish the terms of reference for and objectives of the review of the case for providing consumers with a breathing space.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7490","7490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390185","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of the proposed increase in inheritance tax thresholds on property prices (a) nationally and (b) in each region of the UK.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7483","7483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390186","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people will no longer be eligible for a NHS Tax Credit Exemption Certificate as a result of changes in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7459","7459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390187","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.171 of the Summer Budget 2015, whether the £800 million investment in tackling tax non-compliance and evasion has been diverted from other business areas.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7457","7457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390188","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 2.111 of the Summer Budget 2015, who the vulnerable groups are; and what criteria he uses to decide those groups are vulnerable.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7456","7456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390189","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 14 July 2015 to Question 6473 and with reference to Tables 2.5 and 2.3 in the March and Summer Budget books, how the £1 billion reduction in the Department for International Development's Resource Department's Expenditure Limit has been reallocated.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7359","7359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390190","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the answer of 14 July 2015 to Question 6473 and with reference to Tables 2.5 and 2.3 in the March and Summer Budget books, why there is a £1 billion reduction in the Department for International Development's Resource Department's Expenditure Limit.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7360","7360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390191","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 1.153 of the Summer Budget 2015, if he will publish the criteria to decide who the most vulnerable housing benefit claimants are.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7395","7395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390192","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 1.153 of the Summer Budget 2015, what estimate he has made of the proportion of the £800 million each local authority will receive.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7396","7396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390193","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the compatibility of changes to (a) child tax credits, (b) working tax credit reductions, (c) working tax credit restrictions and (d) restriction of working tax credit to two children with the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7409","7409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390194","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the compatibility of changes to (a) child tax credits, (b) working tax credit reductions, (c) working tax credit restrictions and (d) restriction of working tax credit to two children with the European Convention on Human Rights.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7410","7410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390195","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the compatibility of changes to (a) child tax credits, (b) working tax credit reductions, (c) working tax credit restrictions and (d) restriction of working tax credit to two children with the International Covenant on Economic, Social and Cultural Rights.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7411","7411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390196","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on reform of capital gains tax in relation to compulsory purchase.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7383","7383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390197","2015-07-20","Cabinet Office","2015-07-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people between the ages of 16 and 24 in (a) West Yorkshire and (b) Leeds earning less than £7.20 per hour.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7400","7400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390198","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the financial statement by the Chancellor of the Exchequer on 8 July 2015, Official Report, column 334, what the value will be of the new funding to provide additional support to help employment and support allowance claimants return to work; and what form this additional support will take.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7292","7292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390199","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria he plans to apply when assessing which businesses will be required to pay the new apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Michelle Thomson","Michelle  Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7312","7312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390200","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an estimate of the number of businesses in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK that will be required to pay the new apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Michelle Thomson","Michelle  Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7313","7313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390201","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of level of revenue that will be raised from the new apprenticeship levy; and what additional funding he plans will be available for apprenticeships in England.","Biography information for Michelle Thomson","Michelle  Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7314","7314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390202","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to make available to the Scottish Government additional resources as a result of plans to increase funding for apprenticeships in England.","Biography information for Michelle Thomson","Michelle  Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7315","7315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390203","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of moving HM Revenue and Customs services online on people using such services who are without access to the technology required for online access.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7332","7332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390204","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people previously in receipt of tax credits will no longer receive them following changes covered in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7188","7188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390205","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Table 1.8 of the Summer Budget 2015, which Office for Budget Responsibility inflation forecast was used to calculate the data in that table.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7196","7196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390206","2015-07-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans for the National Living Wage announced in his Summer Budget 2015 to apply to apprentices over the age of 25.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7222","7222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390207","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding will be allocated to the Joint Security Fund in each year up to 2020.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7223","7223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390208","2015-07-20","HM Treasury","2015-07-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Summer Budget 2015, what criteria he plans to use to determine which employers are affected by the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7240","7240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390209","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many social housing tenants aged under 25 are (a) women, (b) men, (c) black and minority ethnic, (d) white British and (e) disabled.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7333","7333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390210","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to provide additional funding to support local authorities' to take account of changes in the Summer Budget 2015 which will (a) increase the minimum wage and (b) reduce the rents paid by social tenants.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7334","7334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390211","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, (a) how much each local authority in England received in rent from its social housing tenants in each year from 2010 to 2015 and (b) how much each local authority in England will receive in rent from its social housing tenants in 2019-20 following the announcement in the Summer Budget 2015 of a one per cent cut in each year of this Parliament.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7335","7335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390212","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2015 to Question 4550, what estimate his Department made of the (a) cost and (b) timescale of work needing to be carried out on the Elstree Tunnels prior to his approval of the planning application for the Radlett Strategic Rail Freight Terminal.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7328","7328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390213","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2015 to Question 4550, what estimate his Department made of what the source of the funding would be for the work required on the Elstree Tunnels prior to his approval of the planning application for the Radlett Strategic Rail Freight Terminal.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7329","7329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390214","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate the number of social homes in London occupied by non-UK residents.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7289","7289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390215","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to improve service delivery by local authorities in rural areas; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7268","7268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390216","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average time was for an appeal to the Planning Inspectorate to be heard following validation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7406","7406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390217","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has for the future of the homelessness gold standard programme.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7389","7389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390218","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the average time was for an appeal to the Planning Inspectorate to be validated in each of the last (a) 12 months and (b) five years.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7405","7405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390219","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people are designated as homeless in (a) West Yorkshire and (b) Leeds; and what proportion of them are aged (i) under 18 and (ii) between 18 and 21.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7394","7394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390220","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Minister for Local Government has met (a) pub-owning companies, (b) the British Beer & Pub Association, (c) CAMRA, (d) the Pubs Advisory Services, (e) Fair Pint and (f) other people or bodies to discuss the statutory pubs code and the Government's policy towards pubs since 7 May 2015.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7486","7486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390221","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to HM Treasury's press release, Chancellor announces £4.5 billion of measures to bring down debt, published on 4 June 2015, what amount of the £30 million additional savings from his Department will consist of (a) underspends within the DCMS group, (b) reduction in core budget and (c) reductions in funding to arms-length bodies.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7431","7431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390222","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department made of projected BBC expenditure in each of the next years before the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7342","7342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390223","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information his Department holds on the number of journalists employed (a) in total and (b) at national newspapers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7343","7343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390224","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether any of the funding for rollout of superfast broadband top sliced from the television licence fee has been retained for phase 3 of the rollout programme.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7341","7341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390225","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information he holds on how the BBC will enforce payment of the licence fee by people watching iPlayer.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7340","7340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390226","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he plans to take in response to Ofcom's Third Review of Public Sector Broadcasting, published in July 2015.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7339","7339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390227","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraph 1.325 of the Summer Budget 2015, whether the Government plans to provide financial support for the move of the Museum of London.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7338","7338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390228","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the Minister of State for Culture and the Digital Economy plans to respond to the letter to him of 29 June 2015 from the hon. Member for Inverness, Nairn, Badenoch and Strathspey.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7243","7243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390229","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions he has had with (a) the Secretary of State  for Scotland and (b) Ministers in the Scottish Government on the provision of 4G mobile telephone coverage in Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7219","7219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390230","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what projections his Department has made of the target strength of the Royal Air Force Regiment of the Royal Air Force in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7224","7224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390231","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the civilian operational costs were of the Force Development Training Centre at Fairbourne in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7230","7230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390232","2015-07-21","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to reach a decision on the future of the Force Development Training Centre at Fairbourne.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7229","7229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390233","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to modernise the (a) Challenger II tank and (b) Warrior armoured fighting vehicle; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7350","7350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390234","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library copies of his Department's Chart of Account for 2014-15 and 2015-16.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7269","7269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390235","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the out of service date is for the (a) Typhoon Tranche 1, (b) Typhoon Tranche 2, (c) Typhoon Tranche 3 and (d) Tornado GR4.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7270","7270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390236","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to establish a Scout specialist vehicle assembly line in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7271","7271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390237","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Scout specialist vehicles he plans to procure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7272","7272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390238","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the planned crew complement by (a) rank and (b) specialisation is for the Type 23 Global Combat Ship.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7267","7267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390239","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Lightning IIs he intends to procure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7349","7349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390240","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many working hours each week are provided by staff from (a) Bechtel, (b) PwC and (c) CH2M Hill under the managed service provider contracts to facilitate Defence Equipment and Support's transition to a trading entity.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7355","7355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390241","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 9 June 2015 to Question 1249, whether his Department has targets for army strength for each year up to 2020.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7353","7353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390242","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff from (a) Bechtel, (b) PwC and (c) CH2M Hill have been seconded to work full-time in Defence Equipment and Support as part of the managed service provider contracts to facilitate its transition to a trading entity.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7358","7358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390243","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff in each salary band from (a) Bechtel, (b) PwC and (c) CH2M Hill are working under the managed service provider contracts to facilitate Defence Equipment and Support's transition to a trading entity.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7356","7356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390244","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) length and (b) value is of his Department's managed service provider contracts with (i) Bechtel, (ii) PwC and (iii) CH2M Hill related to Defence Equipment and Support's transition to a trading entity.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7351","7351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390245","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has been allocated from the Joint Security Fund in each year up to 2020.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7367","7367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390246","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many external consultants are employed in Defence Equipment and Support by his Department.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7384","7384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390247","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff work for Defence Equipment and Support at the Abbey Wood site; and how many of those staff are militarily trained.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7385","7385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390248","2015-07-20","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what projections his Department has made of the target strength of the Royal Marines in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7368","7368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390249","2015-07-20","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans the Government has to include representations from the Polish forces and other countries at the 2015 Remembrance Day ceremony at the Cenotaph; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7432","7432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390250","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will launch an immediate consultation into securing the future of examinations in (a) Turkish, (b) modern Greek and (c) other community languages.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7421","7421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390251","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she has taken in response to the recommendations of the Independent Review on Poverty and Life Chances, published in 2010.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7422","7422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390252","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many pupils were entered into (a) GCSE and (b) A-levels in (i) Turkish, (ii) modern Greek, (iii) Spanish, (iv) French and (v) German in the last five academic years.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7418","7418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390253","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has received from (a) schools, (b) community groups and (c) other organisations on the future of examinations in (i) Turkish, (ii) modern Greek and (iii) other community languages.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7419","7419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390254","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department (a) has made and (b) plans to make of the benefits of pupils learning (i) Turkish, (ii) modern Greek and (iii) other community languages.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7420","7420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390255","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of early years educators qualified to Level 6 were working with children aged (a) two, (b) three and (c) four in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7480","7480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390256","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the disparity in reading ability between different socio-economic groups at age four in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Kendall","Liz Kendall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7481","7481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390257","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will estimate the proportion of two year old children receiving their full entitlement of free childcare (a) nationally, (b) in each region, (c) in each socio economic group and (d) in each ethnic group.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7473","7473"
