"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748164","2017-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce the incidence of nitrogen dioxide levels exceeding the legal limit of 40 micrograms per cubic metre.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2976","2976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748165","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Commissioners of Irish Lights will remain responsible for lighthouses and other marine navigational aids in and in waters around Northern Ireland when the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2964","2964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748166","2017-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Government of the Bolivarian Republic of Venezuela on reported human rights violations in that country.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2711","2711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748167","2017-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many protected disclosures were made by staff in his Department in each of the last three years for which figures are available; how many such disclosures were found to be valid; how many staff alleged detriment as a result of making such a disclosure; and how many staff who (a) made such a disclosure and (b) alleged detriment as a result of a disclosure subsequently left the employment of the Department.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2832","2832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748168","2017-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last spoke to the President of Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2796","2796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748169","2017-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of relations between the UK and Qatar; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2795","2795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748170","2017-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to visit Qatar.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2794","2794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748171","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he or the Minister for Africa has to meet Workneh Gebeyehu, the Ethiopian Foreign Minister.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2824","2824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748172","2017-07-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he or the Minister for Africa plan to visit the (a) African Union in Addis Ababa and (b) Ethiopian Government.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2825","2825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748173","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to increase funding for addiction services in England.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2783","2783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748174","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many protected disclosures were made by staff in his Department in each of the last three years for which figures are available; how many such disclosures were found to be valid; how many staff alleged detriment as a result of making such a disclosure; and how many staff who (a) made such a disclosure and (b) alleged detriment as a result of a disclosure subsequently left the employment of the Department.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2833","2833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748175","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on patient care of reductions in the number of NHS nurses and midwives since 2008.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2848","2848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748176","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received from representatives of nurses and midwives on staffing levels in the NHS.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2849","2849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748177","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure all patients have a named GP.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2845","2845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748178","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on patient care of the cap on staff pay in the NHS.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2847","2847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748179","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, where England was ranked compared to other European countries for breastfeeding in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2855","2855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748180","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the GP Forward Review published in April 2016, how many of the 3,000 new mental health therapists referenced in that review have been appointed.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2846","2846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748181","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Independent Mental Health Taskforce report entitled Five Year Forward View on Mental Health published in February 2016, what the timetable is for the establishment of a care pathway for autism.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2861","2861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748182","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital social workers have been employed by the NHS in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2853","2853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748183","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on preventing escalating clinical negligence costs in the NHS.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2889","2889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748184","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence on the forthcoming consultation on guidelines for treating depression in adults.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2874","2874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748185","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) requirements for and (b) costs to nurses trained in Australia and New Zealand are who wish to register for work within the NHS.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2902","2902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748186","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the potential cost to the NHS of longer (a) treatment times and (b) hospital stays as a result of prescribing less powerful antibiotics as a result of the international shortage of the antibiotic piperacillin-tazobactam.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2903","2903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748187","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress the Government has made in implementing recommendation 52 of the Five Year Forward View for Mental Health on undertaking a review of existing regulations of the Health and Social Care Act to identify disparities and gaps between provisions relating to physical and mental health services.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2952","2952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748188","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS mental health patients were treated in non-NHS institutions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2924","2924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748189","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS beds were available for mental health patients in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2925","2925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748190","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure that any spare land sold off by the NHS is used to build affordable homes for low-paid NHS staff.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2926","2926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748191","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government provides guidance to GP surgeries on whether they should provide supporting letters for disability benefit claims if patients request them.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2927","2927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748192","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospitals have been identified which are clad with (a) material similar to the Grenfell Tower and (b) other fire-risk material; what remedial work has been carried out on those hospitals; and whether additional funding will be provided by the Government to ensure remedial work on those hospitals is not met from existing NHS budgets.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2936","2936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748193","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when magnetic implants to improve eyesight will be available on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2707","2707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748194","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that mental health patients can receive treatment closer to where they live.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2708","2708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748195","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to continue the reduction in the number of HIV cases in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2709","2709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748196","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the occurrence of post-natal illness.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2710","2710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748197","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of how many suicides involving (a) 10 to 14-year olds and (b) 15 to 19-year olds were the result of online bullying.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2721","2721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748198","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether East and North Hertfordshire NHS Trust is required to consult on proposed changes to delivery of acute services in South-West Hertfordshire.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2702","2702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748199","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual administration costs are for the NHS in Hertfordshire.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2703","2703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748200","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the annual administration costs are of each clinical commissioning group in Hertfordshire.","Biography information for Sir Mike Penning","Mike Penning","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2704","2704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748201","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce pre-eclampsia in pregnant women.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2673","2673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748202","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that MRI scans can better detect cancer tumours.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2677","2677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748203","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal Colleges on any connection between Parkinson's disease and faulty immune cells.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2680","2680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748204","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to further reduce the incidence of still births.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2681","2681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748205","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal Colleges on the potential effect of pregnant women taking paracetamol and its effect on unborn boys.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2682","2682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748206","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of (a) online and (b) offline bullying on the incidence of suicide among children and young people.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2728","2728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748207","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the Government's response to the Accelerated Access Review, published in October 2016.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2743","2743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748208","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, why expenditure on adult drug misuse services in England has fallen by over £42 million since 2013-14.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2963","2963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748209","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to secure an affordable price for Orkambi, to make it available to people with cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2960","2960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748210","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors from the EU countries newly registered with the General Medical Council in each month in the last two years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2940","2940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748211","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what instructions his Department have provided to NHS bodies related to fire safety checks; and whether all hospitals in England have been fire assessed.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2941","2941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748212","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure future supplies of the Tazocin brand of the antibiotic piperacillin-tazobactam.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2915","2915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748213","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data the Government collects centrally on whether standard fire safety checks around building structures, escape routes, fire alarms and sprinklers are up to date across all NHS sites.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2937","2937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748214","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 7 March 2017 to Question 66131, on carers, what plans he has to publish the national carers strategy.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2923","2923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748215","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) nurses and (b) midwives from other EU countries newly registered with the Nursing and Midwifery Council in each month in the last two years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2939","2939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748216","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answers to the hon. Member for East Ham of 23 March 2017 to Questions 68535 and 68460, whether the Government plans to bring forward legislation to (a) control the sale and purchase of products with high acidic content and (b) restrict by age of consumer the sale and purchase of such products.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2974","2974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748217","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to publish a report on the funding of extremist activities in the UK by foreign governments, entities or individuals.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2977","2977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748218","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate she has made of the average time taken to process changes to passports for women holding dual nationality after those women have notified a name change after their marriage; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2980","2980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748219","2017-07-06","Cabinet Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many non-UK EU citizens, by country of origin are currently living in the UK.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2776","2776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748220","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much of the 2017-18 Counter Terrorism Policing and Protective Security Grant budget has been allocated to (a) regional units and (b) national units.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2787","2787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748221","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much of the 2017-18 Counter Terrorism Policing and Protective Security Grant budget has been allocated to (a) North West CTU, (b) North East CTU, (c) SE CTU, (d) WM CTU, (e) London (SO15), (f) South West CTIU, (g) Wales CTIU, (h) Eastern CTIU, (i) East Midlands CTIU, (j) Scotland CTIU and (k) Northern Ireland CTIU.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2788","2788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748222","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people applied for a visa through the fast track immigration service in the UK since 1 January 2017; and how many of those visa applications were granted on the same day that the application was made.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2777","2777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748223","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether non-UK EU citizens living in the UK whose applications for settled status are refused will be required to leave the UK when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2790","2790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748224","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have contacted the Right to Rent check service in each month since that service has been in operation.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2778","2778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748225","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the (a) salary and (b) terms of employment of each of the Director-Generals in her Department.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2779","2779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748226","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were employed in (a) UKVI, (b) UKBA and (c) passport services as at 1 July 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2780","2780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748227","2017-07-11","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to tackle provision of terrorist and extremist propaganda through social media, the internet and other online sources.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2759","2759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748228","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the annual operating cost of IT systems for each police force in England and Wales.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2749","2749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748229","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from chief constables in relation to frontline police officer numbers.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2685","2685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748230","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police and crime commissioners have used the full two per cent council tax precept in each financial year since 2012-13.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2686","2686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748231","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to review guidance on single crewing by police officers.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2675","2675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748232","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish the police funding formula review.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2676","2676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748233","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to tackle violent sex abuse against women from Asian and Pakistani groups in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2672","2672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748234","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what long-term assistance is available for victims of terrorism in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2669","2669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748235","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) how many applications her Department has received for special grants and (b) what amount has been given in such grants in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2692","2692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748236","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when Stephen Shaw will begin his follow-up review into the welfare in detention of vulnerable persons.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2693","2693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748237","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from police forces in relation to the closure of police stations.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2689","2689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748238","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received about single crewing by police officers.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2690","2690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748239","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the reasons the Government is yet to achieve its target of reducing net migration to the tens of thousands.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2706","2706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748240","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police raids on care homes in (a) England, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland resulted in potential victims of human trafficking being taken by the police to reception centres in each of the last three years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2922","2922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748241","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the Government has to restrict access to websites that promote or encourage suicide or self-harm.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2872","2872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748242","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there has been an increase in the number of acid attacks in 2017.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2870","2870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748243","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of websites promoting, encouraging or selling products to assist with suicide.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2871","2871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748244","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of her Department's approved intervention providers for the Channel programme as located in each region of England.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2865","2865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748245","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she had made of the number of wanted suspects on the Police National Computer in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2944","2944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748246","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many and what proportion of each category of crime was committed by wanted suspects on the Police National Computer in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2945","2945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748247","2017-07-10","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of vacancies for detectives of any rank in each police force.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2946","2946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748248","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to waive the fee for those applications for settled status from non-UK EU citizens, as a result of the UK's decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2887","2887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748249","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many intervention providers for the Channel Programme are pending approval.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2885","2885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748250","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the Government has to restrict access to websites that sell suicide kits online.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2873","2873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748251","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding was allocated to the Research, Information and Communications Unit in her Department in each of the last three years; and what estimate she has made of the amount of funding that will be allocated to that unit in the next two years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2841","2841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748252","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many protected disclosures were made by staff in her Department in each of the last three years for which figures are available; how many such disclosures were found to be valid; how many staff alleged detriment as a result of making such a disclosure; and how many staff who (a) made such a disclosure and (b) alleged detriment as a result of a disclosure subsequently left the employment of the Department.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2834","2834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748253","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Government is taking to bring net migration to the UK to fewer than 100,000 people a year.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2805","2805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748254","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether it is her Departments policy to include student numbers in official migration statistics.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2807","2807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748255","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment has been made of the effectiveness of the Psychoactive Substances Act.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2808","2808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748256","2017-07-06","Department for International Development","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many protected disclosures were made by staff in her Department in each of the last three years for which figures are available; how many such disclosures were found to be valid; how many staff alleged detriment as a result of making such a disclosure; and how many staff who (a) made such a disclosure and (b) alleged detriment as a result of a disclosure subsequently left the employment of the Department.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2835","2835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748257","2017-07-06","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government is providing to ensure that historical and church buildings in Mosul are rebuilt.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2678","2678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748258","2017-07-06","Department for International Development","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support the Government is providing to help tackle cholera outbreaks in Yemen.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2746","2746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748259","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any community rehabilitation companies in England or Wales use bio-metric machines as a method of reporting for offenders.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2745","2745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748260","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases are awaiting determination by the First Tier Immigration Tribunal.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2781","2781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748261","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new immigration judges were appointed in 2017.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2782","2782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748262","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been murdered since February 2015 by offenders who at the time of the offence, were being supervised by community rehabilitation companies.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2744","2744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748263","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many probation staff were employed by each community rehabilitation company in England and Wales on (a) 1 April 2015, (b) 1 April 2016 and (c) 1 April 2017.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2785","2785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748264","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) anticipated and (b) actual caseload was for probation workers in community rehabilitation companies in 2016-17.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2792","2792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748265","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many serious further offence reviews were carried out for all probation areas in England and Wales in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2786","2786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748266","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any community rehabilitation company in England and Wales received additional funding above the agreed contract in 2016-17.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2738","2738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748267","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many serious further offence reviews were carried out in each community rehabilitation company area and for the National Probation Service in (a) 2015-16 and (b) 2016-17.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2737","2737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748268","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the review on the functioning of community rehabilitation companies was completed; and what the main recommendations of that review were.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2740","2740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748269","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the report Taking control: the need for fundamental bailiff reform, published by a consortium of debt advice agencies in March 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2716","2716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748270","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many protected disclosures were made by staff in his Department in each of the last three years for which figures are available; how many such disclosures were found to be valid; how many staff alleged detriment as a result of making such a disclosure; and how many staff who (a) made such a disclosure and (b) alleged detriment as a result of a disclosure subsequently left the employment of the Department.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2836","2836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748271","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people aged (a) over 65 and (b) over 75 are currently held in prison.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2818","2818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748272","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people who have been diagnosed with dementia are currently held in prison.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2819","2819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748273","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any offenders supervised by community rehabilitation companies in England or Wales report to call centres.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2799","2799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748274","2017-07-10","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers are employed in England and were employed in (a) 2010 and (b) April 2016.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2820","2820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748275","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the ownership of any community rehabilitation company has changed since February 2015.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2800","2800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748276","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increasing cost of clinical negligence cases.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2890","2890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748277","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times a nearest relative formally objected to the detention or transferral into detention of a person under the Mental Health Act 1983 in the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2950","2950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748278","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many applications to displace an unsuitable nearest relative under section 29 of the Mental Health Act 1983 have been made in England in the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2951","2951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748279","2017-07-06","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many protected disclosures were made by staff in his Department in each of the last three years for which figures are available; how many such disclosures were found to be valid; how many staff alleged detriment as a result of making such a disclosure; and how many staff who (a) made such a disclosure and (b) alleged detriment as a result of a disclosure subsequently left the employment of his Department.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2837","2837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748280","2017-07-10","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much has been spent on the (a) salaries and (b) allowances of (i) members of the Northern Ireland Assembly and (ii) their staff since January 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2966","2966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748281","2017-07-10","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, for what reasons the full salaries and allowances of members of the Northern Ireland Assembly are being paid in the absence of a functioning Assembly; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2967","2967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748282","2017-07-10","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions he had with the Electoral Commission before his statement to the House on 3 July 2017 on the publication of details of political donations made to parties in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2968","2968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748283","2017-07-10","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what mechanisms have been put in place to ensure that Northern Ireland Departments have sufficient funds available for its policies and programmes during the suspension of the Northern Ireland Assembly.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2973","2973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748284","2017-07-06","Prime Minister","2017-07-04","To ask the Prime Minister, when the Government plans to make available the findings of the Grenfell Tower fire inquiry.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2668","2668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748285","2017-07-06","Scotland Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the planned timeframe is for the introduction of new financial arrangements for the Scottish Parliament agreed in the Scotland Act 2016.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2732","2732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748286","2017-07-06","Scotland Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many protected disclosures were made by staff in his Department in each of the last three years for which figures are available; how many such disclosures were found to be valid; how many staff alleged detriment as a result of making such a disclosure; and how many staff who (a) made such a disclosure and (b) alleged detriment as a result of a disclosure subsequently left the employment of his Department.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2838","2838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748287","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many protected disclosures were made by staff in his Department in each of the last three years for which figures are available; how many such disclosures were found to be valid; how many staff alleged detriment as a result of those disclosures; and how many staff subsequently left his Department's employment.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2864","2864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748288","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Stagecoach Group PLC's press release dated 28 June 2017, preliminary results for the year ended 30 April 2017, what assessment he has made of the effect of Network Rails' reprioritised infrastructure programme on the finances of the InterCity East Coast franchise.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2860","2860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748289","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to his Department was of the Gibb Report, published on 22 June 2017 (a) in total, (b) on staffing and (c) on externally commissioned work.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2859","2859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748290","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government plans to take to encourage integration of bus services in the North East.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2772","2772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748291","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many houses in Stafford constituency have been purchased by (a) the High Speed 2 Exceptional Hardship Scheme and (b) other schemes since each such scheme was launched; and what the average cost is of each such purchase.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2888","2888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748292","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what work (a) has been done and (b) is ongoing, to analyse historical satellite surveys to assess the rate and magnitude of recent ground movements on the proposed route of HS2 Phase 2B in Eddisbury constituency.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2891","2891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748293","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce a decision on the delivery of a new train fleet for the Tyne and Wear Metro.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2756","2756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748294","2017-07-11","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Highways Agency is taking to remove ragwort from (a) roadsides and (b) other land from which it isresponsible.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2758","2758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748295","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2017 to Question 1331, whether bilateral air services arrangements with all EU member states will still apply in the event that the UK leaves the EU air travel regime.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2809","2809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748296","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions the Government has had with the North East Combined Authority on the delivery of a new train fleet for the Tyne and Wear Metro.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2773","2773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748297","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to relax or amend the regulations relating to the introduction of bus franchising by non-mayoral combined authorities.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2774","2774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748298","2017-07-10","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government plans to take to support the introduction of bus franchising in non-mayoral combined authorities.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2775","2775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748299","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's publication of 2 February 2017, Road accidents and safety statistics, for what reasons there has been a delay in the supply of data from data providers.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2978","2978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748300","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if any space-borne synthetic aperture radar surveys have been commissioned to assess ground movements on the proposed route of High Speed 2 phase 2B in Eddisbury.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2953","2953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748301","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the decision will be announced of the route of phase 2B of High Speed 2 from Crewe to Manchester and Leeds.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2954","2954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748302","2017-07-10","Wales Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for International Trade on securing tariff-free trade with the EU for the (a) agriculture sector and (b) steel sector in Wales after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2971","2971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748303","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to make a decision on the Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon before the summer recess; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2696","2696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748304","2017-07-06","Wales Office","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many protected disclosures were made by staff in his Department in each of the last three years for which figures are available; how many such disclosures were found to be valid; how many staff alleged detriment as a result of making such a disclosure; and how many staff who (a) made such a disclosure and (b) alleged detriment as a result of a disclosure subsequently left the employment of his Department.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2840","2840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748305","2017-07-10","Women and Equalities","2017-07-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions she has had with the House of Commons Commission on taking steps to ensure that the Parliamentary estate is fully accessible to people of differing physical ability.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2850","2850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748306","2017-07-10","Women and Equalities","2017-07-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to her letter of 29 June 2017 on funding for abortions for Northern Irish women in England, when the Government plans to make this service available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2815","2815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748307","2017-07-10","Women and Equalities","2017-07-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to her letter of 29 June 2017 on funding for abortions for Northern Irish women in England, whether the Government also intends to fund the costs of (a) private consultations in Northern Ireland, (b) travel and (c) accommodation for women who wish to access these services.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2816","2816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748308","2017-07-10","Women and Equalities","2017-07-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what plans she has to extend provisions in the Equalities Act 2010 related to protection against discrimination to mental health conditions that are episodic and fluctuating; and whether such provisions will include people with epilepsy.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2947","2947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748309","2017-07-06","Women and Equalities","2017-07-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she plans to bring forward legislative proposals to require companies with more than 250 employees to publish data on the pay gap between men and women.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2869","2869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748310","2017-07-10","Women and Equalities","2017-07-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to her letter of 29 June 2017 on funding for abortions for Northern Irish women in England, whether organisations which are not registered as pregnancy advice bureaux will be eligible to receive funding.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2763","2763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748311","2017-07-10","Women and Equalities","2017-07-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to her letter of 29 June 2017 on funding for abortions for Northern Irish women in England, how she plans to advertise the availability of such services in England.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2764","2764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748312","2017-07-10","Women and Equalities","2017-07-04","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to her letter of 29 June 2017 on funding for abortions for Northern Irish women in England, whether for women with complex medical needs that funding can be used to access NHS services.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2765","2765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748314","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward proposals to change the child maintenance calculations from gross to net income to assess the necessary parental contributions required under the new Child Maintenance Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2983","2983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748315","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what rationale the Government has used to decide the order of local authority areas for the Universal Credit Transition Schedule.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2930","2930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748316","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2017 to Question 1470, if he will publish the response to the Freedom of Information request referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2929","2929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748317","2017-07-10","HM Treasury","2017-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Social Mobility Commission report Time for Change, published on 28 June 2017, what steps he is taking to increase young people's wages.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2748","2748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748318","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many customers have used free wi-fi in (a) Govan Jobcentre Plus and (b) Pollock Jobcentre Plus in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2932","2932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748319","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions the Government has had with colleges and third sector organisations in Glasgow South West constituency to extend the availability of public access terminals.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2933","2933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748320","2017-07-10","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of GP surgeries refuse to provide supporting letters for disability benefit claimants; what proportion of surgeries charge for those letters; and how much surgeries charge to issue those letters.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2928","2928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748321","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the locations are of the 16 public access terminals available for claimants in Glasgow South West constituency.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2935","2935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748322","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many customers have been provided with an assisted service for additional support to use the 16 customer access terminals in Glasgow South West constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2934","2934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748323","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to progress the proposals set out in the Green Paper entitled Work, health and disability green paper: Improving Lives.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2905","2905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748324","2017-07-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to improve the understanding of mental health among personal independence payment and employment and support allowance assessors.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2949","2949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748325","2017-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time is for an employment and support allowance claim to reach the assessment stage in (a) England, (b) the West Midlands and (c) Birmingham, Yardley constituency.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2881","2881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748326","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average waiting time was for an ESA appeal hearing in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2884","2884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748327","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will meet representatives of the Disabled Children's Partnership to discuss its Secret life of us campaign for support for disabled children and their families.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2886","2886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748328","2017-07-06","HM Treasury","2017-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in (a) Wolverhampton and (b) Wolverhampton North East constituency qualified for (i) working tax credits and (ii) child tax credits in each financial year from 2009-10.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2806","2806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748329","2017-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of applications for employment and support allowance which are rejected are overturned at the appeals stage.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2883","2883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748330","2017-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many protected disclosures were made by staff in his Department in each of the last three years for which figures are available; how many of those disclosures were found to be valid; how many staff alleged detriment as a result of those disclosures; and how many staff subsequently left his Department's employment.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2863","2863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748331","2017-07-17","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the dates were on which the Coal Forum met in each of the last three years; and when he plans to call a further meeting of that forum.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2862","2862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748332","2017-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the one per cent public sector pay cap applies to employees of Direct Rail Services Ltd.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2858","2858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748333","2017-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential effect on the UK steel industry of the US Administration imposing a 20 per cent tariff on steel imports to the US.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2851","2851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748334","2017-07-06","HM Treasury","2017-07-04","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of eligible businesses have been referred to designated finance platforms under the Bank Referral Scheme since its implementation.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2784","2784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748335","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many protected disclosures were made by staff in his Department in each of the last three years for which figures are available; how many of those disclosures were found to be valid; how many staff alleged detriment as a result of having made a protected disclosure; and how many of those staff subsequently left the employment of the Department.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2878","2878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748336","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many GWh of electricity consumed in the UK in the last 12 months were supplied by interconnectors.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2893","2893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748337","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many TWh of electricity were consumed in the UK in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2892","2892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748338","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what operational interconnectors there are in the UK; and what the MW capacity is of each of those interconnectors.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2896","2896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748339","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many GWh of electricity were exported from the UK through interconnectors in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2894","2894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748340","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many TWh of electricity have been imported into the UK by individual interconnectors since 2012.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2895","2895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748341","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the T-4 capacity market auction for delivery in October 2021 will take place in February 2018; and and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2901","2901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748342","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the average cost is of transmission network costs for (a) interconnectors and (b) domestic generators of electricity.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2900","2900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748343","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many megawatts of new interconnector capacity are proposed by (a) 2020 and (b) 2025.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2897","2897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748344","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of electricity will be supplied by interconnectors in (a) 2020 and (b) 2025.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2898","2898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748345","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the average price of electricity supplied by (a) interconnectors and (b) other electricity generation was in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2899","2899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748346","2017-07-10","Department for Education","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to page 4 of the Social Mobility Commission report Time for Change, published on 28 June 2017, for what reasons more older than younger workers have obtained apprenticeships.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2750","2750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748347","2017-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether any planning applications have been submitted for new onshore wind farms since 9 June 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2753","2753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748348","2017-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on establishing a Shale Environmental Regulator; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2752","2752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748349","2017-07-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to further improve competition in the domestic gas industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2760","2760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748350","2017-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the role the Government is playing in facilitating technological transfer to smaller countries to grow their renewable energy sectors and reduce dependence on fossil fuels.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2761","2761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748351","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the risk that the UK's withdrawal from the European Atomic Energy Community would trigger compensation clauses in the investor agreement in relation to Hinkley Point C power station.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2729","2729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748352","2017-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to support the transfer of technology to Jamaica in relation to the renewable energy programme in that country.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2769","2769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748353","2017-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on how many households are on energy suppliers' standard variable rates.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2705","2705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748354","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect on UK energy security of any change in ownership of the NuGen power station at Moorside; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2718","2718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748355","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the completion date for the NuGen nuclear power station at Moorside; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2719","2719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748356","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what incentives his Department provides to the private sector to increase expenditure on research and development.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2975","2975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748357","2017-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK withdrawing from Euratom on cancer research in the UK.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2969","2969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748358","2017-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK withdrawing from Euratom on energy production in the UK.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2970","2970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748359","2017-07-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will take steps to ensure that the interests of people from diverse communities are represented during the negotiations on the UK exiting the EU.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2771","2771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748360","2017-07-10","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many civil servants has been employed by his Department as specialist lawyers since its creation; what the pay grades are of those officials; how many lawyers have been seconded to his Department, from which firms, since its creation; and how much has been spent on such external legal advice and services.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2904","2904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/748361","2017-07-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps he is taking to encourage diversity in his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2822","2822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749755","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he had with contractors on their delivery of service accommodation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz Twist","Liz Twist","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900314","900314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749756","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to expand the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900312","900312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749757","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on agreeing a contract for the Type 26 frigate.","Biography information for Andrew Bowie","Andrew Bowie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900309","900309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749758","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on his Department's policies of the draft treaty to prohibit nuclear weapons published by the UN in May 2017.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900315","900315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749759","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to strengthen the Armed Forces Covenant.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900317","900317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749760","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress he has made on bringing the Queen Elizabeth class aircraft carriers into service.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900316","900316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/749761","2017-07-10","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with the Armed Forces Pay Review Body on levels of pay for the armed forces.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 900313","900313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747454","2017-07-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he expects the lessons learned investigation across Whitehall co-ordinated by the National Security Adviser to report.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2445","2445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747455","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the Government's policy is on the legal status of (a) Spice, (b) Black Mamba and (c) the new highly potent and lethal crystalised form of Spice.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2406","2406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747456","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures are in place in (a) Greater Manchester and (b) the rest of the UK to test for the presence of the new crystalised form of the drug Spice.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2370","2370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747457","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Jewish places of worship from each denomination had applied for funding under the Places of Worship Security Funding Scheme by 1 June 2017 in each region.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2481","2481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747458","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on contingency planning for multiple fire incidents across London.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2475","2475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747459","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on contingency planning for multiple fire incidents across Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2476","2476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747460","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on contingency planning for multiple terrorist incidents across London.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2477","2477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747461","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on contingency planning for multiple terrorist incidents across Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2478","2478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747462","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Christian places of worship from each denomination in each region had applied for funding under the Places of Worship Security Funding Scheme, by 1 June 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2479","2479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747463","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Islamic places of worship from each denomination had applied in each region for funding under the Places of Worship Security Funding Scheme by 1 June 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2480","2480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747464","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers there have been in the South Yorkshire Police Service in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2405","2405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747465","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what costs have been (a) incurred to date and (b) committed for future periods for the development and management of the South Yorkshire and Bassetlaw Sustainability and Transformation Plan.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2652","2652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747466","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the success rate for appeals against decisions on (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment entitlement in Barnsley has been in the most recent 12-month period for which data is available.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2653","2653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747467","2017-07-06","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the new school funding formula on each school in Barnsley East constituency.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2654","2654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747468","2017-07-06","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much was spent per pupil on improving the condition of school buildings in (a) Barnsley East constituency and (b) the UK on average in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2655","2655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747469","2017-07-06","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that all pupils attending Kingsway Academy will have a school place in the next school year, after the closure of that school.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2494","2494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747470","2017-07-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether representations were made to his Department by representatives of the Building Research Establishment in 2016 on the presence of combustible materials in tall buildings not compromising relevant building regulations.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2394","2394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747471","2017-07-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether Sir Peter Bonfield, Chief Executive of the Building Research Establishment, approved the guidance document BR135 as part of the regulatory scheme set out in Fire Safety: Approved Document B: 2 under which Grenfell Tower was refurbished in 2016.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2395","2395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747472","2017-07-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to broaden the scope of combustibility testing as a result of the Grenfell Tower fire to include (a) insulation materials and (b) other materials used in the construction, refurbishment or maintenance of tall buildings in the UK.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2392","2392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747473","2017-07-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how the combustibility testing regime being used to test samples of building materials as a result of the Grenfell Tower fire was chosen.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2393","2393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747474","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of reported thefts of tools from trades vehicles has resulted in a prosecution in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2357","2357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747475","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received on the availability of lock-picking equipment on the internet; and what assessment she has made of the effect of its availability on thefts from trades vehicles.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2358","2358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747476","2017-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of safeguards for people living with Alzheimer's from those appointed with lasting power of attorney who act against their best interests.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2359","2359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747477","2017-07-05","Department for Transport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the efficacy of the enforcement of disabled parking bays in supermarket car parks.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2360","2360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747478","2017-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether an assessment is made of an individual's capacity in the appointment of an attorney with lasting power of attorney.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2367","2367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747479","2017-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department took legal advice on the target of upholding original decisions in 80 per cent of mandatory benefit reconsideration requests.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2401","2401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747480","2017-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his counterpart in Russia on recent reports of torture and murder of gay people in Chechnya.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2444","2444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747481","2017-07-05","House of Commons Commission","2017-07-03","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what information the Commission holds on the number of passwords belonging to Members of the House of Lords which were compromised in the recent cyber attack on Parliament.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2448","2448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747482","2017-07-06","Department for International Trade","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how the Government plans to ensure that the North East remains a national leader in exports.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2493","2493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747483","2017-07-05","Department for Transport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to increase capacity for rail freight in the Newcastle region.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2554","2554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747484","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government plans to take to expedite completion of planned upgrades to the A1 and A19.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2571","2571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747485","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government plans to take to remove capacity constraints on the East Coast Mainline.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2528","2528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747486","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is taking to support the delivery of a new train fleet for the Tyne and Wear Metro.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2527","2527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747487","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps the Government is planning to take to improve road and rail access to Newcastle International Airport.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2529","2529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747488","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that Greater Manchester Police have sufficient resources to reduce harm caused by the drug spice.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2572","2572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747489","2017-07-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he has taken to use the authority given to him in the Building Act 1984 to retroactively enforce the standards laid out in the Building Regulations England & Wales Part B (2006) Fire Safety in Dwelling Houses on all buildings and compel all building owners to undertake a fire safety check.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2649","2649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747490","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of how many people on the sex offenders register will be moved to a reactive management monitoring regime in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2388","2388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747491","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what offences people on the sex offenders register, who are due to be subject to a reactive management regime, have been convicted of.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2389","2389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747492","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of the people on the sex offenders register, who are due to be subjected to a reactive management regime, are on the Disclosure and Barring Services automatic barring list (i) with and (ii) without representations.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2390","2390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747493","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many individuals on the sex offenders register who are deemed low risk (a) committed offences whilst on the register and (b) breached their notification requirements in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2391","2391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747494","2017-07-05","Women and Equalities","2017-07-03","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to her letter of 29 June 2017 on funding for abortions for Northern Irish women in England, what assessment she has made of whether Northern Irish doctors will be able to (a) formally refer women to and (b) inform women of these abortion services in England without fear of prosecution.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2513","2513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747495","2017-07-05","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding was allocated to Music Education Hubs, by NUTS1 Territorial Units for Statistics for each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2524","2524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747496","2017-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to include (a) sports coaches and (b) youth leaders within the Positions of Trust provisions of section 21 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2525","2525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747497","2017-07-05","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 14 January 2013, Official Report, column 533W, on teachers: qualifications, how many people have obtained each type of school-based qualification in (a) music, (b) drama, (c) theatre-studies and (d) art in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2651","2651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747498","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her oral contribution of 3 July 2017, on the child sexual abuse inquiry, which police forces (a) are and (b) are not planning to implement a reactive management regime for some people on the sex offenders register in their areas.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2646","2646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747499","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the UK economy of the UK leaving the EU's Common Commercial Policy and Common External Tariff without a customs agreement between the UK and the EU.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2365","2365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747500","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the economy of reducing net immigration to the tens of thousands.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2363","2363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747501","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect on the UK economy of a customs agreement with the EU that includes participation in the Common External Tariff and Common Commercial Policy.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2364","2364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747502","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral evidence from the Chief Executive and Permanent Secretary of HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) to the Public Accounts Committee on the HMRC estate on 25 January 2017, Q14, HC 891, which eight principles HMRC used to determine the location of its regional centres.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2583","2583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747503","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral evidence from the Chief Executive and Permanent Secretary of HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) to the Public Accounts Committee on the HMRC estate on 25 January 2017, Question 14, HC891, which locations HMRC initially considered as possible regional centres.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2581","2581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747504","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the oral evidence from the Chief Executive and Permanent Secretary of HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) to the Public Accounts Committee on the HMRC estate on 25 January 2017, Question 4, HC891, on what date ministerial approval was given for HMRC's strategic outline case for regional centres; and if he will make a statement before the summer recess.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2582","2582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747505","2017-07-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what support her Department is providing to cities to grow their digital media industries.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2371","2371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747506","2017-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many farmers in (a) South Lakeland District Council area and (b) Cumbria have not yet received their full basic payment scheme payment for 2016.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2418","2418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747507","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2017 to Question 219, if she will publish the Home Office report on foreign funding of extremism and radicalisation in the UK.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2416","2416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747508","2017-07-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on utility bills for sites owned by his Department that have been officially closed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2417","2417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747509","2017-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made on the trial of in-work progression for universal credit claimants; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2379","2379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747510","2017-07-06","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 1 March 2017, HCWS 509, what the (a) timetable and (b) planned commencement date is for the consultation on the provision of relationships education.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2526","2526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747511","2017-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria his Department uses for determining the likelihood that child maintenance arrears will be collected.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2605","2605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747512","2017-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to collect child maintenance arrears, by category of collectability.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2606","2606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747513","2017-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will implement the recommendations in the Work and Pensions Select Committee report, Child Maintenance Service, HC587, published on 2 May 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2574","2574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747514","2017-07-05","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) cash and (b) per pupil funding has been provided to schools in Mid Sussex constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2544","2544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747515","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on reviewing UK National Screening Committee guidance on Group B strep prevention; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2421","2421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747516","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to improve productivity in British commerce and industry; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2569","2569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747517","2017-07-06","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the projected (a) cash and (b) per pupil funding is for schools for Mid Sussex constituency in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2570","2570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747518","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the National Institute for Health Research will begin the clinical trial comparing universal screening for Group B strep carriage in late pregnancy with usual risk-based care.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2419","2419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747519","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to review Group B strep prevention strategies to align the UK with international best practice in preventing early-onset Group B Strep.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2420","2420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747520","2017-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he plans to take to ensure that the Agriculture Bill is suited to the farming conditions in England.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2656","2656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747521","2017-07-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many businesses have successfully scaled up from being a start-up to having more than nine employees in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2435","2435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747522","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on equity investments in small and medium-sized enterprises by region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2442","2442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747523","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much financial support the European Investment Bank has contributed to the UK economy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2441","2441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747524","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to increase the availability of free and low-cost financial and business advice for small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2429","2429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747525","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the Government will publish a target for increasing equity investment in small and medium-sized enterprises.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2433","2433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747526","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on spending by small and medium-sized enterprises in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2434","2434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747527","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many loans between £10 million to £25 million the British Business Bank lent to small and medium-sized enterprises in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2436","2436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747528","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have invested through the (a) Enterprise Investment Scheme, (b) Seed Enterprise Investment Scheme and (c) venture capital trusts in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2437","2437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747529","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much was invested through (a) the Enterprise Investment Scheme, (b) the Seed Enterprise Investment Scheme and (c) venture capital trusts in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2438","2438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747530","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many companies received investment from (a) the Enterprise Investment Scheme, (b) the Seed Enterprise Investment Scheme and (c) venture capital trusts in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2439","2439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747531","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to maintain funding for British businesses following the UK's withdrawal from the EU and the possible loss of investment from the European Investment Bank.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2440","2440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747532","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information his Department holds on the level of funding for small and medium-sized enterprises provided through (a) equity investments, (b) peer-to-peer loans and (c) other forms of lending for each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2430","2430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747533","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much funding the (a) Government and (b) British Business Bank have contributed to the Angel CoFund in each of the last five years; and how much funding the Government plans to provide over the next two years.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2428","2428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747534","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many new entrant banks offering finance for small and medium-sized enterprises were established in each of the last five years; and how many of those banks continue to offer such finance.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2431","2431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747535","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to ensure  banks share customer data with new entrants to the finance market for small and medium-sized enterprises in good time.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2432","2432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747536","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government has made an assessment of the merits of granting credit reference agencies and authorised finance providers access to financial data in the VAT register.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2425","2425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747537","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to support challenger banks who have entered or are looking to enter the small and medium-sized enterprise lending market.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2426","2426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747538","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions the Government has had with businesses and finance providers on establishing schemes to provide advice to small businesses on how to secure finance.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2427","2427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747539","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what security assessments his Department has made since the acquisition of a majority stake in the National Grid by the consortium comprising the Qatar Investment Authority and others.","Biography information for John McNally","John McNally","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2580","2580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747540","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the net value of the European Geostationary Navigation Overlay System.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2505","2505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747541","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has paid for the medical treatment of UK citizens in other EU member states in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2506","2506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747542","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will recoup the capital invested by the Government in the European Investment Bank when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2507","2507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747543","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the financial value of EU construction projects which will not be completed until after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2502","2502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747544","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the net value of the European Space Agency.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2503","2503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747545","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the net value of the EU's Copernicus polar tracker satellite system.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2504","2504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747546","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to create a centrally-held funding source to local authorities who provide care and support to people from religious minorities requiring care from specialist providers.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2457","2457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747547","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to maintain at the same level or increase the annual grant to the Community Security Trust.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2455","2455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747548","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to introduce a special circumstance dispensation for people from religious minorities in relation to the payment of child benefit for a third or subsequent child.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2456","2456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747549","2017-07-05","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance her Department has published on preventing speakers intending to incite hate being given a platform on university campuses.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2454","2454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747550","2017-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications for universal credit have been closed as a result of an absence of agreement on claimant commitments.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2518","2518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747551","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the practice of developers selling new houses on a leasehold rather than a freehold basis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2575","2575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747552","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to investigate the fairness of charges levied by housebuilders and others on home owners seeking to buy the freehold of their property; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2576","2576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747553","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the number of developers selling on the leasehold of new-build homes to other companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2577","2577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747554","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on medical conditions experienced by homeless people in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2407","2407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747555","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the rooftop solar power market of the business rate rise for organisations investing in solar power for their own consumption.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2355","2355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747556","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to incentivise businesses to invest in rooftop solar.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2356","2356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747557","2017-07-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of resources available to the Information Commissioner's Office to support businesses in the implementation of changes to the General Data Protection Regulation.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2519","2519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747558","2017-07-05","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of schools funding in Cambridgeshire.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2520","2520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747559","2017-07-05","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve the retention of teachers in Cambridge constituency.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2521","2521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747560","2017-07-05","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of regional schools commissioners.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2522","2522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747561","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what comparative assessment his Department has made of the differences in (a) development, (b) manufacturing and (c) regulatory costs of biosimilar and generic medicines.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2523","2523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747562","2017-07-05","Department for Transport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the changes to Network Rail's renewals programme arising from the reduction in the High Output Track Renewals programme and the effect of those on (a) regular maintenance and (b) rail safety.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2368","2368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747563","2017-07-06","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the one per cent public sector pay cap on the levels of child poverty since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2608","2608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747564","2017-07-06","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy that no school in the London Borough of Newham will see a reduction in (a) cash and (b) per pupil funding in each of the next five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2612","2612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747565","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of the potential loss of access to Europol's Terrorism Situation and Trend Report system on the UK's ability to tackle cyber crime.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2613","2613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747566","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on the number of non-UK EU nurses working in the UK of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2566","2566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747567","2017-07-06","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to allow nursery schools to offer the 30 hours of free early education for three and four year olds from September 2017.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2408","2408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747568","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of homeless people in (a) Telford and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2512","2512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747569","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on proposed changes to the filing of tax returns for smaller businesses and people who are self-employed.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2617","2617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747570","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received from smaller businesses on the timeliness of the payment of invoices in the private sector.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2618","2618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747571","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to require the workforce to be represented on boards of public limited companies.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2614","2614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747572","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to announce the appointment of a Small Business Commissioner.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2615","2615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747573","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues on proposed changes to national insurance contributions for people who are self-employed.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2616","2616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747574","2017-07-06","Department for International Trade","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to encourage and facilitate trade cooperation between the UK and Israel in the (a) agricultural technology and (b) high-tech sector.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2645","2645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747575","2017-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons the Government has not given notice  of the UK's withdrawal from the London Fisheries Convention 1964.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2641","2641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747576","2017-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what waters the UK has historically exercised sovereign control over for management and access.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2642","2642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747577","2017-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what definition has been used to identify the waters the UK has historically exercised sovereign control over.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2643","2643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747578","2017-07-06","Department for International Trade","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether progress has been made on securing a trade agreement between the UK and Israel for when the UK is no longer part of the EU-Israel Association Agreement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2644","2644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747579","2017-07-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will ask the Electoral Commission to review political parties' compliance with regulations during the 2017 General Election.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2573","2573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747580","2017-07-05","Wales Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the delay to the Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon project.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2458","2458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747581","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the recommendation set out in The role of tidal lagoons, published in December 2016, to proceed with the Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon project.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2459","2459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747582","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress has been made on the Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon project.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2460","2460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747583","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made on the feasibility of the proposed Colwyn Bay Tidal Lagoon project.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2461","2461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747584","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made on the feasibility of the proposed Cardiff Bay Tidal Lagoon project.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2462","2462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747585","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with NHS England and other key stakeholders on putting in place support for families visiting relatives who are receiving out-of-area mental health treatment.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2530","2530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747586","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will offer support to Luke Dicker to allow him to access the Specialist Professor at Bath University, Mark Brosnan; whether Wiltshire Clinical Commissioning Group or Avon and Wiltshire Mental Health Care Partnership is responsible for that treatment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2578","2578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747587","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Vertex on the provision of Orkambi to people with cystic fibrosis; when he plans to respond to the Accelerated Access Review; what his policy is on the provision of Orkambi to people with cystic fibrosis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2562","2562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747588","2017-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Government of Nigeria on a strategy to reduce the number of abductions in the north of that country.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2621","2621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747589","2017-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what funding his Department has made available to aid the peace process in Southern Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2620","2620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747590","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much electricity was produced from (a) wind, (b) tidal, (c) biomass, (d) solar, (e) hydro and (f) geothermal power in (i) Gloucestershire and (ii) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2629","2629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747591","2017-07-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has plans to postpone the 2018 Boundary Commission Review.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2630","2630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747592","2017-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role his Department is playing to help bring peace and stability to Southern Sudan.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2619","2619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747593","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many community hospitals closed in each local authority in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2624","2624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747594","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has plans to reform the process for council tax banding appeals.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2633","2633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747595","2017-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance his Department is giving to the Government of Uganda to help restrict the activities of the Lord's Resistance Army.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2622","2622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747596","2017-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with each of the devolved administrations on his Department's plans for the reform of agriculture after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2631","2631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747597","2017-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to assess the adequacy of levels of capacity in the provision of the incineration of waste.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2632","2632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747598","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to put in place measures to prevent the closure of minor injury units in community hospitals.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2623","2623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747599","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many appeals have there been for council tax banding in (a) Stroud District and (b) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2634","2634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747600","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on amending the provision of local authority housing finance further to incentivise construction of council houses.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2635","2635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747601","2017-07-05","Department for International Development","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department has made available to (a) Sudan and (b) South Sudan for the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2636","2636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747602","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) Chief Superintendents, (b) Superintendents, (c) Chief Inspectors, (d) Inspectors, (e) Sergeants and (f) Constables there have been in Gloucestershire Constabulary in each year from  2010 to the latest year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2625","2625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747603","2017-07-05","Department for Transport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people have received driving bans in (a) Stroud District, (b) Gloucestershire and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2637","2637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747604","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of sums received from land taxation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2626","2626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747605","2017-07-05","Department for Transport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many cycling fatalities there have been in (a) Gloucestershire and (b) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2638","2638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747606","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on reevaluating the tax base for business rates.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2627","2627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747607","2017-07-05","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has plans to provide additional school places in (a) Stroud constituency and (b) Gloucestershire.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2639","2639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747608","2017-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) employment and support allowance and (b) personal independence payment appeals there have been in the Stroud District in each year since 2010; and how many such appeals were successful.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2628","2628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747609","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of successful applications to the Home Building Fund have been submitted by builders delivering less than 100 units per year since the introduction of that fund.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2558","2558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747611","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the Home Building Fund has been allocated to property developers in each region since October 2016.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2557","2557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747612","2017-07-06","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of the (a) maintained schools, (b) non-maintained schools, (c) independent schools, (d) providers on the Early Years Register and (e) providers registered with an early years childminder agency which provide early years foundation stage have been assessed as (i) outstanding, (ii) good, (iii) satisfactory and (iv) inadequate.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2607","2607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747613","2017-07-06","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of early years foundation stage providers have been assessed as (a) outstanding, (b) good, (c) satisfactory and (d) inadequate in (i) each region in England and (ii) England.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2533","2533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747614","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps are being taken to encourage householders to seek the cheapest energy deals available to them to help them to cut energy bills.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2376","2376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747615","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps are being taken to protect poorer households from fuel poverty caused by the high prices of pre-payment energy meters.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2377","2377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747616","2017-07-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, when he plans to disclose the cost of the Supreme Court case R (on the application of Miller and another) v Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2403","2403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747617","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how his Department will ensure that the Industrial Strategy Challenge Fund complements existing initiatives in Scotland to deliver an holistic approach to innovation.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2587","2587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747618","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure closer collaboration between the Government and the Scottish Government in relation to the Government's Industrial Strategy.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2586","2586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747619","2017-07-05","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how his Department is providing opportunities for Scottish businesses to feed into the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2584","2584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747620","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how the Government is addressing the regional productivity gap in each region and constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Stephen Kerr","Stephen Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2585","2585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747621","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the data from the BRC1/2 tests carried out by the UK Genetic Testing Network.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2423","2423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747622","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the two research studies into ovarian cancer awareness which the previous Government indicated it planned to publish in the summer of 2017.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2424","2424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747623","2017-07-05","Department for International Development","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when her Department expects that the air service contract between the St Helena Government and SA Airlink will be signed.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2514","2514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747624","2017-07-05","Department for International Development","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she has requested reports from the Governor of St Helena on the outcomes of the air service tender.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2515","2515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747625","2017-07-05","Department for International Development","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many responses the St Helena Government received on its tender for the air service.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2516","2516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747626","2017-07-05","Department for International Development","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what (a) discussions and (b) meetings her officials have had with SA Airlink on the future of the air service in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2517","2517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747627","2017-07-05","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) people applied and (b) applications were received for places on midwifery training courses by the January deadline in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2510","2510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747628","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many midwives working in the NHS in England were 70 or older in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2484","2484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747629","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many midwives have been in formal training in England in each six month period since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2482","2482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747630","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the age profile was of midwives working in the NHS in England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2483","2483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747631","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Capped Expenditure Process on (a) obstetrics, (b) mental health services and (c) waiting times for cancer treatment in (i) Cheshire and (ii) England.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2488","2488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747632","2017-07-05","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on the Government's policies for academy schools of the conclusions of the Sutton Trust report, Chain Effects 2017.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2489","2489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747633","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many social workers have been employed in the adult social care sector in the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2490","2490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747634","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many social workers are employed directly by the NHS in adult social care.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2491","2491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747635","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to Clinical Commissioning Groups on (a) workforce planning and (b) the number of social workers available on hospital wards.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2492","2492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747636","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has recouped from EU member states whose nationals have received emergency treatment from the NHS in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2509","2509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747637","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the annual growth in household income was in each of the last eight quarters for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2508","2508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747638","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many times (a) he, (b) Ministers of his Department have met with the Leasehold Knowledge Partnership in the last two years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2487","2487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747639","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Social Mobility Commission report, Time for Change: An Assessment of Government Policies on Social Mobility 1997-2017, what steps he plans to take to tackle low levels of social mobility in the medical profession.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2486","2486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747640","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure adequate consultation with social workers on its proposals for social care.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2485","2485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747641","2017-07-06","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to announce a final decision on Eastern Avenue Jobcentre closure following the consultation.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2410","2410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747642","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the budget is for the (a) Take Five, (b) Cyber Aware, (c) Cyber Essentials, (d) Scam Smart, (e) Not With My Name, (f) Urban Fraud Myths, (g) Avoiding Scams, (h) Get Safe Online, (i) Cyber Choices, (j) The Pensions Regulator's Scorpion Campaign, (k) 10 Steps to Cyber Security, (l) Date Safe and (m) Fighting Fraud programmes for 2017-18.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2411","2411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747643","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of fraud were reported to Action Fraud by each police force in each year from 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2412","2412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747644","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the planned budget is for special grants funding for 2017-18; and how much of that funding will be allocated to each police force.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2465","2465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747645","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether funding for the Commonwealth Heads of Government Conference will come from her Department's special grants budget.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2466","2466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747646","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications her Department received for special grants in 2016-17.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2467","2467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747647","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to issue guidance on the circumstances in which an adult with a mental disorder may be removed to a police station under section 81 of the Police and Crime Act 2017.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2409","2409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747648","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of special grants were allocated by her Department to cover legal fees in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2468","2468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747649","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department allocated in special grant funding to each recipient body in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2469","2469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747650","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people who have been reached by the (a) Take Five, (b) Cyber Aware, (c) Cyber Essentials, (d) Scam Smart, (e) Not With My Name, (f) Urban Fraud Myths, (g) Avoiding Scams, (h) Get Safe Online, (i) Cyber Choices, (j) The Pensions Regulator's Scorpion Campaign, (k) 10 Steps to Cyber Security, (l) Date Safe and (m) Fighting Fraud programmes during 2017-18.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2470","2470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747651","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) adults and (b) children with a mental disorder in each force area have been removed to police stations since January 2017.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2378","2378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747652","2017-07-05","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations she has made to the US Administration about (a) the strategic importance of the Fulbright programme to the special relationship and (b) the need to preserve funding for the programme in the years ahead.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2464","2464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747653","2017-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the US Administration on (a) the benefits of the Fulbright Scholarship programme to UK-US relations and (b) the level of funding required for that programme in the next five years.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2463","2463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747654","2017-07-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the proportion of people aged (a) 18 to 29, (b) 30 to 44, (c) 45 to 59, (d) 60 to 79 and (e) over 80-years old who have internet access in each parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2495","2495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747655","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the proportion of (a) 18 to 29, (b) 30 to 44, (c) 45 to 59, (d) 60 to 79 and (e) over 80 year olds  who use online banking in each parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2496","2496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747656","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the clarity of the guidance set out in paragraph 12.7 of Approved Document B on materials which can be used above and below 18 metres in high rise buildings.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2474","2474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747657","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure that (a) patients and (b) the public are consulted on the creation of Accountable Care Systems.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2542","2542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747658","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to amend the Building Regulations and the guidance contained in Approved Document B on fire safety.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2543","2543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747659","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department is giving to local authorities on the removal of cladding from high-rise buildings.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2450","2450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747660","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made on discussions with the US Administration on allowing the pre-clearance in the UK of passengers for immigration purposes.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2451","2451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747661","2017-07-18","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the armed forces are currently working in South Sudan; and what role those people are performing.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2386","2386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747662","2017-07-18","Department for International Development","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to ensure that humanitarian assistance can be delivered effectively in South Sudan.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2387","2387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747663","2017-07-18","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on progress on the creation of the Hybrid Court in South Sudan.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2385","2385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747664","2017-07-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will extend the membership of the Coordination Committee to be established between the Government and the Democratic Unionist Party to the hon. Member for North Down.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2657","2657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747665","2017-07-06","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, for what reasons he declined the request of the Electoral Commission to publish the details of donations since January 2014 to political parties operating in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2662","2662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747666","2017-07-05","Leader of the House","2017-07-03","To ask the Leader of the House, whether hon. Members elected for Sinn Fein receive any monies in funding analogous to Short Money provision to the Democratic Unionist Party.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2658","2658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747667","2017-07-06","Cabinet Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure publication of the minutes of meetings of the co-ordination committee to be established in accordance with the confidence and supply deal agreed on 26 June 2017 between the Democratic Unionist Party and the Government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2663","2663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747668","2017-07-05","Leader of the House","2017-07-03","To ask the Leader of the House, what estimate she has made of the amount of Short Money that the Democratic Unionist Party will receive as a result of the outcome of the June 2017 General Election.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2659","2659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747669","2017-07-06","Cabinet Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether ending the anonymity of political donations to parties in Northern Ireland was discussed with the Democratic Unionist Party (DUP) before the deal was signed between the Government and the DUP on 26 June 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2664","2664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747670","2017-07-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the (a) composition and (b) frequency of meetings is of the Co-ordination Committee agreed to be established on 26 June 2017 in the confidence and supply deal agreed between the Democratic Unionist Party and the Government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2660","2660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747671","2017-07-06","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Conservative Party publishes details of the donations made since January 2014 to the Conservative Party operating in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2665","2665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747672","2017-07-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the constitutional status of the Co-ordination Committee to be established between the Government and the Democratic Unionist Party in accordance with the deal agreed between them on 26 June 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2661","2661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747673","2017-07-06","Northern Ireland Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, for what reasons he did not make retrospective to January 2014 the end of anonymity for political donations to parties in Northern Ireland during his statement to the House of 3 July 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2666","2666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747674","2017-07-05","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2017 to Question 160, whether he plans to increase the number of women serving on his Department's senior negotiating team.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2369","2369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747675","2017-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the new Minister for Asia plans to visit Hong Kong during the current Parliamentary session.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2372","2372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747676","2017-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Chinese counterpart on the 20th anniversary of the handover of Hong Kong.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2373","2373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747677","2017-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to meet Lord Patten of Barnes to discuss the democratic situation in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2374","2374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747678","2017-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of climate change on Overseas Territories; and what measures are being put in place to protect biodiversity in Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2446","2446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747679","2017-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to visit Hong Kong during this parliamentary session.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2447","2447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747680","2017-07-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many of his senior negotiating team are from an ethnic minority background.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2609","2609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747681","2017-07-06","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 26 June 2017 to Question 160, whether he plans to increase the number of women in his senior negotiating team.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2610","2610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747682","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on public safety of decreasing the Counter Terrorism Policing and Protective Security Grant by 7.2 per cent in cash terms over the next two years.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2404","2404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747683","2017-07-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the potential long-term effect of providing financial support to smaller charities for fundraising training and support.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2471","2471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747684","2017-07-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues and (b) local authorities on support provided to smaller charities to raise funds through grants and commissioning processes.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2472","2472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747685","2017-07-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with charity-sector bodies and foundations on support provided to smaller charities for fundraising activities.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2473","2473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747686","2017-07-05","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2588","2588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747687","2017-07-05","Cabinet Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2589","2589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747688","2017-07-05","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2590","2590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747689","2017-07-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2591","2591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747690","2017-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2592","2592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747691","2017-07-05","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2593","2593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747692","2017-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2594","2594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747693","2017-07-05","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2595","2595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747694","2017-07-05","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2596","2596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747695","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2597","2597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747696","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2598","2598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747697","2017-07-05","Department for International Development","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2599","2599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747698","2017-07-05","Department for International Trade","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2600","2600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747699","2017-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2601","2601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747700","2017-07-05","Department for Transport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2602","2602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747701","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2603","2603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747702","2017-07-05","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the amount of manual processing on paper that it carries out and to make such processing digital.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2604","2604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747703","2017-07-06","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 18 April 2017 to Question 69488, if he will place in the Library the results of the research commissioned by his Department on the effect of current pricing structures used by foreign exchange providers on consumer value choices.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2375","2375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747704","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to publish new Immigration Rules and associated Guidance in response to the ruling in the Supreme Court case of MM & Ors v SSHD (2017).","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2402","2402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747705","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Written Statement of 3 July 2017, Official Report, WS 23, if the Government will increase the number of refugees to be resettled under the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Resettlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2647","2647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747706","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Written Statement of 3 July 2017, Official Report, WS 23, whether it is her policy that refugees who are (a) Palestinian and (b) stateless will eligible to be resettled in the UK under the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Resettlement Scheme.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2648","2648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747707","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical services contracts awarded to private providers in England are of a duration of longer than five years.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2531","2531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747708","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) median and (b) average length in years is of clinical service contracts awarded to private providers in England.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2532","2532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747709","2017-07-06","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much funding will be available through the UK Shared Prosperity Fund; and what mechanism will be used to distribute that funding.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2380","2380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747710","2017-07-06","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the Government's policy is on a devolved settlement for Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2381","2381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747711","2017-07-06","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the recommendations in the Social Mobility Commission's report, entitled The Time for Change, published 28 June 2017, what plans she has to develop and implement a new social mobility test for public policy.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2382","2382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747712","2017-07-06","Department for Education","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the recommendations in the Social Mobility Commission's report, entitled The Time for Change, published 28 June 2017, what plans she has to develop a strategic cross-departmental social mobility plan.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2383","2383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747713","2017-07-06","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the UK Shared Prosperity Fund will be allocated on the basis of a formula or following a bidding process.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2384","2384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747714","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the insurance industry on insurance for residents of tower blocks.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2497","2497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747715","2017-07-05","HM Treasury","2017-07-03","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of whether residents of tower blocks are encountering difficulties in renewing their home insurance after the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2498","2498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747716","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital admissions in England were categorized as assault by corrosive substance in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2366","2366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747717","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to collect and collate statistics on the age and gender of perpetrators of acid attacks.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2361","2361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747718","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of acid attacks resulted in prosecutions in each of the last five years; and what steps she is taking to improve the reporting of acid attacks.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2362","2362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747719","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the total sum of arrears recovered by HM Revenue and Customs was for non-compliance with the national minimum wage in 2016-17; how many (a) workers and (b) employers those arrears relate to; how much of that total sum of arrears was recovered through the self-correction mechanism introduced in 2015; and how many (i) workers and (ii) employers those self-corrected arrears relate to.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2413","2413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747720","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many financial penalties have been imposed to date on respondent employers for aggravated breach of employment law under section 16 of the Enterprise and Regulatory Reform Act 2013; how many such penalties (a) have been paid and (b) remain unpaid; and what the total value is of penalties (i) imposed, (ii) paid and (iii) not yet paid.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2414","2414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747721","2017-07-06","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 11 January 2017 to Question 58968, how many (a) warning letters and (b) financial penalty notices have been issued to respondent employers to date under section 150 of the Small Business, Enterprise and Employment Act 2015 for failure to pay an employment tribunal award; how many of those financial penalties (i) have been paid and (ii) remain unpaid; and how much in previously unpaid awards has been recovered by his Department following (A) the issuing of a warning letter only and (B) the issuing of both a warning letter and a financial penalty notice.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2415","2415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747722","2017-07-05","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library a copy of (a) the document circulated to NHS officials in London on 25 May 2017 on the effect of the capped expenditure process, (b) any equivalent document circulated to such officials in other areas affected by the capped expenditure process and (c) the letter referred to in the 27 June 2017 edition of the Health Service Journal.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2443","2443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747723","2017-07-06","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2017 to Question 1467, when the report of the review into the funding of Islamist extremism was (a) finalised and (b) submitted to ministers; and from which external sources advice is being provided to ministers on publication of the report.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2650","2650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747724","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how does a prison notify the next of kin of a prisoner's death in custody.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2564","2564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747725","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support is available for prisoners with mental health issues.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2565","2565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747726","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoner deaths attributed to suicide were recorded in prisons in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2567","2567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747727","2017-07-06","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoner deaths were recorded in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2568","2568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747728","2017-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the White Paper on Prison safety and reform published in November 2016, when he plans to publish a strategy to improve the treatment of female offenders in custody and in the community.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2500","2500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747729","2017-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the increase in the number of female prisoners in June 2017.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2499","2499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747730","2017-07-05","Ministry of Justice","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of women in prison.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2501","2501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747731","2017-07-05","Home Office","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Government's publication entitled The United Kingdom's Exit from the European Union: Safeguarding the Position of EU Citizens Living in the UK and UK Nationals Living in the EU, published on 26 June 2017, when the length of the grace period referred to in paragraph 24 will be specified for EU nationals resident in the UK at the time the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2449","2449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747732","2017-07-05","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many local libraries have been operating in each region of England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2553","2553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747733","2017-07-05","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the 25 year strategy for tackling bovine TB.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2579","2579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747734","2017-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2017 to Question 1033, what estimate his Department has made of the total cost to the public purse of court costs relating to air quality compliance cases in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2611","2611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747735","2017-07-06","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the future availability of seasonal labour in the agricultural sector.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2541","2541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747736","2017-07-06","Department of Health","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many social workers are directly employed by the NHS in adult social care in (a) the West Midlands and (b) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2534","2534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747737","2017-07-06","Department for International Trade","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will place in the Library studies produced by the Defence and Security Organisation and Defence Growth Partnership that examine the potential market landscape for UK naval exports in the five to 15-year market.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2535","2535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747738","2017-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans that the proposed RAF P-8A fleet take over overland surveillance roles currently performed by the Sentinel R1.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2555","2555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747739","2017-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to outsource any of its jobs and functions to the private sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2556","2556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747740","2017-07-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans are in place to dispose of Hyde Park Barracks.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2536","2536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747741","2017-07-06","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's plans are for the basing requirements for the Household Cavalry Mounted Regiment.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2537","2537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747742","2017-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many civilian jobs and functions within his Department have been outsourced to the private sector in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2552","2552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747743","2017-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of planned civilian redundancies within his Department on the operational capabilities of the armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2549","2549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747744","2017-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on wine in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2550","2550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747745","2017-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department plans to procure a new platform to enable the RAF to maintain its wide-area surveillance capability after the Sentinel R1 fleet is retired in 2021.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2551","2551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747746","2017-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department spent on hospitality for foreign (a) military personnel and (b) civilian defence officials in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2546","2546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747747","2017-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost was of recruiting foreign personnel into the Brigade of Gurkhas in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2547","2547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747748","2017-07-05","Ministry of Defence","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans are in place to outsource his Department's fire and rescue services on airfields and dockyards.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2548","2548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747749","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to require Highways England to publish the minutes of its board meetings.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2400","2400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/747750","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the one per cent public sector pay cap applies to employees of (a) Highways England, (b) Network Rail, (c) the Civil Aviation Authority, (d) the investigation branches for air, marine and rail accidents and (e) HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 2398","2398"
