"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777684","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to respond to the proposals contained in the Road Signs Task Force report, published in March 2017.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109526","109526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777685","2017-10-30","Wales Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if the Government will take steps to ensure that the cost for any extra facilities or infrastructure required by Welsh ports to meet their legal requirements at the UK's point of exit from the EU will be funded either directly by the Government or through additional funding to the Welsh Government for that purpose.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109487","109487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777686","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of claimants in (a) Barnsley and (b) the UK who were awarded employment and support allowance for under (i) one year, (ii) two years and (c) five years were re-assessed before the award expired.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109507","109507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777687","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of claimants in (a) Barnsley and (b) the UK who were awarded a personal independence payment for under (i) one year, (ii) two years and (c) five years were re-assessed before the award expired.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109508","109508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777688","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of claimants of universal credit did not receive the full payment within 10 weeks of submitting a claim.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109509","109509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777689","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claimants of universal credit did not receive the full payment within 10 weeks of submitting a claim.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109510","109510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777690","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of decisions on whether employment and support allowance claimants will not have to undergo further work capability assessments as a result of a lifelong, progressive, degenerative or incurable condition will be made as a result of a paper-based assessment.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109515","109515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777691","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support people in automatic enrolment pension schemes to make additional voluntary contributions to their pensions.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109482","109482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777692","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2017 to Question 107371, who drafted the document entitled Professor Dieter Helm - declaration of interest.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109477","109477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777693","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent progress he has made to simplify the number of tariffs offered by energy companies.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109514","109514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777694","2017-10-30","Department for International Trade","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether the revised tariff rate quotas for the UK that will be lodged with the WTO will constitute a technical rectification.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109483","109483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777695","2017-10-30","Department for International Trade","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK and EU's joint position on WTO schedules of commitments on other WTO member states.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109484","109484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777696","2017-10-30","Department for International Trade","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans he has to facilitate the implementation of the UK's schedules and quotas at the WTO under the modification procedure.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109485","109485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777697","2017-10-30","Department for International Trade","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the date when schedules and tariff rate quotas for the UK will be agreed at the WTO.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109486","109486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777698","2017-10-30","Attorney General","2017-10-25","To ask the Attorney General, whether the Law Officers' Departments were consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109528","109528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777699","2017-10-30","Cabinet Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109529","109529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777700","2017-10-30","Cabinet Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what research his Department has commissioned from Korn Ferry Hay Group in the last two years.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109638","109638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777701","2017-10-30","Cabinet Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government plans to bring forward the recommendations of the proposed Boundary Review 2018 in England.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109636","109636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777702","2017-10-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2017 to Question 108122, on cybercrime, how many registered consultancies of the Government's Cyber Essentials scheme had data exposed.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109582","109582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777703","2017-10-30","Cabinet Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many and what proportion of adults of voting age were not registered to vote in each year from 2010 to date.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109585","109585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777704","2017-10-30","Cabinet Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what contingency funding his Department has allocated in relation to the Government's negotiations on the UK leaving the EU for the (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20 financial years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109779","109779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777705","2017-10-30","Cabinet Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have died as a result of carbon monoxide poisoning in (a) England and (b) each English region in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109725","109725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777706","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the rent-to-buy sector assesses the ability of customers to repay their loans prior to signing contracts.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109763","109763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777707","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 113 of the HM Revenue and Customs Annual Report and Accounts 2016-17, what assessment he has made of the level of compliance with tax legislation of stores and retailers which offer discounts to HM Revenue and Customs employees.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109671","109671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777708","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to promote safer forms of credit for the most financially excluded.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109738","109738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777709","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure effective regulation of the rent-to-own sector in response to the Financial Conduct Authority's recent ruling on BrightHouse.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109739","109739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777710","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the costs incurred by his Department in the current financial year in preparation for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109624","109624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777711","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of bank branch closures in (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109593","109593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777712","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many recipients of in-work tax credits there are in the Vale of Clwyd; and how many and what proportion of those people will see their income (a) increase, (b) remain the same or (c) decrease as a result of the roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109618","109618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777713","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2017 to Question 108144, what the cost of each ticket was; to how many people those eight bookings related; and what the reasons were for that travel.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109570","109570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777714","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109549","109549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777715","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Financial Conduct Authority's findings on the proportion of over-55s who suspect that they have been contacted about a fraudulent investment in the last three years and did not report it, what steps his Department is taking to advise such people to report such fraudulent investment activity.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109552","109552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777716","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the economy of north-east Scotland of the proposed closure of all HM Revenue and Customs offices north of Glasgow and Edinburgh, including the office at Ruby House, Aberdeen.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109556","109556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777717","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will undertake a cost-benefit analysis of maintaining a third HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) office in Scotland, north of Glasgow and Edinburgh, by exempting the Ruby House office in Aberdeen from the proposed HMRC office closures.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109557","109557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777718","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-25","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have been registered as self-employed in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109560","109560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777719","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109530","109530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777720","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has sought legal advice on the appointment of a Sheffield City Region mayor.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109647","109647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777721","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of children in temporary accommodation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109682","109682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777722","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what meetings (a) he and (b) his Department has had with representatives of trades unions in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109732","109732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777723","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department publishes for (a) local authorities and (b) housing associations on providing a safe means of exit for disabled residents in the event of an emergency.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109733","109733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777724","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions his Department has had with the Local Government Association on improving standards of (a) electrical and (b) gas safety in the private rented sector.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109734","109734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777725","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2017 to Question 107742, on Department for Communities and Local Government: procurement, how many project managers employed by his Department have the authority to authorise projects of a value in excess of £10,000.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109674","109674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777726","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Regulatory Reform (Fire Safety) Order 2005 in ensuring that (a) adequate fire safety arrangements and (b) appropriate fire drills, including evacuations, are carried out for (i) hospitals, (ii) schools, (iii) care homes and (iv) women's refuges.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109675","109675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777727","2017-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the extent of contaminated land across each of the four Black Country boroughs; and what funding is available for remediation of such contamination.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109715","109715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777728","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Oral Answer of the Prime Minister, Official Report, column 300, of 25 October 2017, what discussions he has had with the Prime Minister on the proposals to be brought to Parliament on fracking.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109761","109761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777729","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of properties with carbon monoxide detectors installed in the (a) private and (b) social rented sector.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109716","109716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777730","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the Government's guidance on abandonment of properties under the provisions of the Housing and Planning Act 2016 is planned to come into force.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109730","109730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777731","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what contingency funding his Department has allocated in relation to the Government's negotiations on the UK leaving the EU for the (a) current, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20 financial year.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109778","109778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777732","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what funding his Department has set aside for contingencies relating to the UK leaving the EU in the (a) current and (b) 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109783","109783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777733","2017-10-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if her Department will increase funding for UK Anti-Doping.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109723","109723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777734","2017-10-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what contingency funding her Department has allocated in relation to the Government's negotiations on the UK leaving the EU for the (a) current, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20 financial year.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109777","109777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777735","2017-10-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 September 2017 to Question 7471, on broadband: universal service obligation, what estimate she has made of the proportion of (a) Hemsworth constituency and (b) West Yorkshire that will be able to access broadband speed of 10Mbps in (i) one month, (ii) six months and (iii) one year.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109558","109558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777736","2017-10-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 September 2017 to Question 7471, on broadband: universal service obligation, whether that timetable includes new housing developments in (a) Hemsworth constituency and (b) West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109559","109559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777737","2017-10-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109546","109546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777738","2017-10-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2017 to Question 107920, on S4C: Reviews, if she will publish the names of the key partners, stakeholders and parties interested in S4C who were invited to submit evidence to the independent review of S4C.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109569","109569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777739","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which NATO countries provided Maritime Patrol Aircraft for use in UK airspace on 24 and 25 October 2017.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109575","109575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777740","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the recent refit cost of HMS Scott was.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109633","109633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777741","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for the base-porting arrangements for the new Type 26 frigates.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109634","109634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777742","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the retirement dates are of each of the 13 Type 26 frigates.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109635","109635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777743","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government has indicated to the Governments of Brazil and of Chile that HMS Albion and HMS Bulwark may become available for purchase.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109639","109639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777744","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the base-porting arrangements are for the most recent Astute-class attack submarine.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109632","109632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777745","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons the decision to extend the out-of-service date for the Hawk T1 aircraft was made.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109555","109555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777746","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109531","109531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777747","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where the maintenance of the F-35B aircraft will take place.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109683","109683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777748","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many service personnel were based at Maindy Barracks in (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109600","109600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777749","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it is the Government's policy to purchase 138 F35 aircraft.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109656","109656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777750","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what financial assumptions his Department has made on the cost of (a) spare parts, (b) software upgrades and (c) logistics support for the F-35 programme; and whether those costs are borne by his Department or the supplier for that programme.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109657","109657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777751","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the unit cost is of the Generation III helmets being procured for pilots of the Lockheed Martin F-35 fighter jets.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109658","109658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777752","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to manage exposure to foreign currency fluctuations as part of his Department's F-35 programme.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109659","109659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777753","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to ensure that software bugs identified in the Autonomic Logistics Information System on the F-35 aircraft are remedied.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109660","109660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777754","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contingency or replacement policy his Department has in place if any F-35 variant is lost during operations.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109661","109661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777755","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contingency funding his Department has allocated in relation to the Government's negotiations on the UK leaving the EU for the (a) current, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20 financial year.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109776","109776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777756","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the current planned operational retirement date is for HMS Scott.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109631","109631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777757","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Regulatory Reform (Fire Safety) Order 2005 in ensuring that (a) adequate fire safety arrangements and (b) appropriate fire drills, including evacuations, are carried out for military bases in the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109676","109676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777758","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions officials of his Department have had with (a) their counterparts in the US Administration or (b) representatives of Lockheed Martin on production targets for the F35 variants falling behind schedule.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109736","109736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777759","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions officials of his Department have had with (a) their counterparts in the US Administration or (b) representatives of Lockheed Martin on cost reduction targets for the UK F35 variants in production batches 12, 13 and 14.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109737","109737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777760","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funding his Department has set aside for contingencies relating to the UK leaving the EU in the (a) current and (b) 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109781","109781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777761","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average contribution from the public purse to each Russell Group university is for 2017-18.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109692","109692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777762","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of making it compulsory for all schools to have sprinklers installed.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109693","109693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777763","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the change will be in funding to schools from baseline block funding allocation 2015-16 to academic year 2019-20 of the implementation of the National Funding Formula in (a) Tooting constituency, (b) Wandsworth Borough Council, (c) Greater London Authority and (d) the UK in (i) nominal and (ii) real terms.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109698","109698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777764","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to launch its careers strategy.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109699","109699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777765","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department plans to take to increase apprenticeship enrolment among people from lower-income backgrounds.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109701","109701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777766","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Oral contribution of the Minister of State for Education of 18 July 2017, Official Report, column 713, what discussions her Department has had with HM Revenue and Customs to resolve the issues identified with the digital childcare service; and what progress her Department has made on steps identified in those discussions to resolve those issues.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109758","109758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777767","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital spending was allocated from the public purse to each university technical college that has closed since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109764","109764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777768","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2017 to Question 107822, what steps she is taking to ensure that schools meet more than two Gatsby benchmarks of good practice in careers education, information, advice and guidance.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109667","109667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777769","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to appoint further ambassadors for the apprentice ambassador programme on a cross-party basis.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109668","109668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777770","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to announce further details of the review of tertiary education.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109669","109669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777771","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many inspectors are employed by Ofsted in each region of England.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109672","109672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777772","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the findings of the evaluation of the further education reform programme 2015 research report commissioned, by her Department, on the effect of student loans on learners from disadvantaged backgrounds.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109670","109670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777773","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on the budgets of Oxfordshire primary and secondary schools of (a) changes to business rates, (b) the apprenticeship levy, (c) changes to national insurance contributions and (d) the withdrawal of the education services grant.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109769","109769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777774","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of children live within three miles of three outstanding schools in each local authority in England.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109742","109742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777775","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Oral Statement of 17 July 2017, Official Report, columns 563 to 566, on schools update, whether the £10 million ringfenced from the soft drinks industry levy revenue to provide breakfast clubs will be affected by changes to the funding levels available through the healthy pupils capital budget.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109743","109743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777776","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Early Years Workforce Strategy, published in march 2017, what progress her Department has made on plans to conduct a feasibility study on the development of a programme to grow the graduate workforce in Opportunity areas.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109626","109626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777777","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which free schools have closed since 2010; and how much (a) revenue and (b) capital expenditure was disbursed on each of those schools.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109747","109747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777778","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of apprenticeships at companies benefiting from the apprenticeship levy by (a) household income, (b) region and (c) age.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109594","109594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777779","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to allow Ofsted to inspect multi-academy trusts.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109665","109665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777780","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to enhance collaboration between the (a) Network of Teaching Excellence in Computer Science and (b) other programmes in England and equivalent computing teacher support programmes in the devolved nations.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109646","109646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777781","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to publish the internal audit reports carried out by the Education and Skills Funding Agency on the Collective Spirit Free School, Oldham.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109586","109586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777782","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of employers that benefit from the apprenticeship levy; and how many apprentices have remained at their place of employment after their apprenticeship has concluded.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109596","109596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777783","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the apprenticeship levy increases social mobility.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109597","109597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777784","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of apprentices who have secured apprenticeships at a company benefiting from the apprenticeship levy in (a) Leigh, (b) Wigan and (c) Greater Manchester.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109598","109598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777785","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of Adult Community Learning funding has been spent on (a) English, (b) mathematics and (c) ESOL courses in (i) the UK and (ii) London.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109583","109583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777786","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many learners funded through the Adult Community Learning budget studied   (a) English, (b) mathematics and (c) ESOL courses in (i) the UK and (ii) London in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109584","109584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777787","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, further to her Department's publication on an open process to provide breakfast clubs in schools, how much of the funding from this process is additional to the ring fenced revenue from the Soft Drinks Industry Levy in schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109689","109689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777788","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of school funding in North Cornwall constituency after the implementation of the national funding formula.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109602","109602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777789","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of changes to Government policy on interest rates on graduate debt on her Department's revenue budget for (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109653","109653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777790","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109532","109532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777791","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what information her Department holds on the (a) number and (b) amounts of settlements paid to head teachers leaving schools in multi-academy trusts in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109561","109561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777792","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many head teachers (a) have registered and (b) been dismissed from schools within a multi-academy trust since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109562","109562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777793","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the relevance for public health policy of the recommendations in the What Works Centre for Wellbeing recent report, Happy people wear seat belts: wellbeing and risk-taking, published on 6 October 2017.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109611","109611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777794","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the amount of capital funding allocated to school building programmes by (a) local authority and (b) parliamentary constituency in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109610","109610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777795","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what targets she has for exports in education in each of the next three years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109572","109572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777796","2017-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of incorporating the assured breeder scheme into the new dog breeding regulations.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109640","109640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777797","2017-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that inspections carried out by assured breeder scheme inspectors are not duplicated by local authorities under the new dog breeding regulations.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109641","109641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777798","2017-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109533","109533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777799","2017-11-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the use of a small- scale cutter dredger brought from the Netherlands by the Environment Agency which operated on waterways in the UK in summer 2017; and what plans he has to use similar equipment on rivers and water courses elsewhere in the UK in future.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109637","109637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777800","2017-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with representatives of the archaeological profession on the future of farming policy, particularly with reference to heritage and conservation.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109643","109643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777801","2017-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of he availability of the BCG vaccine for badgers.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109644","109644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777802","2017-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he plans to put measures in place to boost UK horticultural production.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109645","109645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777803","2017-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many members of the board responsible for Cotswold Area of Outstanding Natural Beauty Conservation Area reside in Cotswold district; and how many members of that board are elected representatives of the residents of Cotswold district.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109770","109770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777804","2017-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the costs incurred by his Department in the current financial year in preparation for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109622","109622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777805","2017-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Oral Answer of the Prime Minister to the hon. Member for Edinburgh East of 25 October 2017, what discussions he has had with the Prime Minister on the proposals to be brought to Parliament on fracking.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109759","109759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777806","2017-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of leaving the EU on the security of supply of medicines for animals.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109731","109731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777807","2017-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent meetings and discussions he has had with the Colombian Ambassador to the UK on how the UK can effectively support the peace process in Colombia.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109599","109599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777808","2017-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received on the alleged involvement of a British company in supplying arms to the Government of South Sudan.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109605","109605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777809","2017-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109534","109534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777810","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of vacancies in the NHS diagnostic workforce; and what assessment he has made of the implications of that number of vacancies for (a) meeting cancer waiting time targets and (b) introducing FIT to bowel screening to the level planned.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109563","109563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777811","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with GPs and medical defence organisations on providing appropriate funding to meet additional costs incurred following changes to the discount rate in February 2017.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109551","109551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777812","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109547","109547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777813","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the availability of the BCG vaccine; what plans he has to secure supplies of that vaccine after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109580","109580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777814","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which prescription drugs had the highest increase in price to the NHS in the last 10 years for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109619","109619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777815","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have had the BCG vaccine in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109581","109581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777816","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance the Government offers to local authorities on the effect of the provisions in the Care Act 2014 on the minimum number of residential care homes such authorities are required to offer.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109571","109571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777817","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the variation in the levels of access to contraception from sexual health clinics in England.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109608","109608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777818","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding the NHS in Cornwall currently receives; and how that level of funding compares to levels in 2010.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109601","109601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777819","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the extent of the reduction in uptake of long-acting reversible contraception; and what assessment he has made of the implications of that reduction for his policies.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109588","109588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777820","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of funding for research on cervical cancer in the last five years.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109666","109666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777821","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted via accident and emergency departments with a primary diagnosis of laceration in each month of the financial years (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15, (f) 2015-16 and (g) 2016-17.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109662","109662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777822","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted via accident and emergency departments with a primary diagnosis of a sprain or ligament injury in each month of the financial years (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15, (f) 2015-16 and (g) 2016-17.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109663","109663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777823","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2017 to Question 107810, on general practitioners: Greater London, what estimate his Department has made of the GP-to-patient ratio in (a) the Enfield Clinical Commissioning Group and (b) clinical commissioning groups in London in each financial year since April 2013.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109664","109664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777824","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to provide safe and accessible transportation to and from hospitals for patients who are (a) too ill for public transport and (b) travelling to and from areas with poor quality patient transport services.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109726","109726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777825","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to help older patients facing long journeys get to and from hospital appointments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109727","109727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777826","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to address the downward trend in cervical cancer screening rates among women.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109728","109728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777827","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase cervical cancer screening uptakes among women in the 25 to 29 age group.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109729","109729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777828","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of additional unpaid carers there will be by (a) 2020 and (b) 2040.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109694","109694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777829","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the outcome of the recent pilot in Bradford and its surrounding area on improving NHS dental availability.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109686","109686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777830","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cases of neonatal (a) sepsis, (b) meningitis and (c) pneumonia have been treated in NHS hospitals in each region in the last five years.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109717","109717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777831","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the NHS of treating carbon monoxide poisoning in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109718","109718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777832","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people attended accident and emergency departments as a result of carbon monoxide poisoning in (a) England and (b) each English region in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109719","109719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777833","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been admitted to hospital as a result of carbon monoxide poisoning in (a) England and (b) each English region in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109720","109720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777834","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what average level of Units of Dental Activity were commissioned per capita in (a) Bradford South constituency, (b) Yorkshire and Humber and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109673","109673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777835","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on patients of the number of clinical commissioning groups that have introduced a threshold in access to hip and knee replacements in (a) West Yorkshire, (b) Yorkshire and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109627","109627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777836","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to (a) prevent violent crimes against pensioners and (b) support pensioners who have been victims of such crimes.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109772","109772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777837","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the interview for the new Chair of the College of Policing took place; and when the successful candidate for that role will be announced.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109630","109630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777838","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of attacks or assaults on people involving acid in each of the last five years; and what steps she is taking to prevent such attacks.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109629","109629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777839","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2017 to Question 108158, which external companies are involved in the administration or operation of the National Cyber Security Tracker survey.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109740","109740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777840","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions her Department has had with its French counterpart on plans in place to provide shelter and help to refugees who may have a legal right to claim asylum in the UK who are currently residing in the Grande Synthe refugee camp in Dunkirk.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109757","109757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777841","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many pensioners have been victims of violent crime in (a) the UK and (b) Sunderland Central constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109771","109771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777842","2017-11-03","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Ministers and officials of her Department have (a) received or (b) been offered data on non-compliance with section 54 of the Modern Slavery Act 2015.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109767","109767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777843","2017-11-03","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance she has issued on the proportion of local police budgets that should be devoted to (a) cyber crime and (b) counter-terrorism.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109766","109766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777844","2017-11-03","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department has taken to increase BAME representation in the police since May 2016.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109765","109765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777845","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in the UK have applied for dual UK-EU citizenship since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109768","109768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777846","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which organisations will contribute financially to the Emergency Services Network programme.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109695","109695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777847","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful applications her Department has received for two-year visit visas for Chinese nationals from China in each of the years that scheme has been operating.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109709","109709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777848","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications her Department has received for standard visitor visas from China in each of the last 10 years; and how many such applications were successful.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109705","109705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777849","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of overstayers who (a) are and (b) are not in detention from (i) all countries, (ii) India, (iii) China, (iv) Bangladesh and (v) Pakistan.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109706","109706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777850","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to increase the number of refugee families reunited under the Mandate scheme.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109687","109687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777851","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to reduce knife crime.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109595","109595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777852","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many British citizens have returned to the UK after fighting in Iraq and Syria since 2012.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109589","109589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777853","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any civilian target shooting club in the UK is approved by her Department to use armour piercing or explosive ammunition.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109587","109587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777854","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she has met representatives of the (a) FCSA UK club or (b) National Rifle Association to discuss her Department's proposals on banning .50 calibre rifles.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109591","109591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777855","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria her Department uses to formally approve target shooting clubs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109592","109592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777856","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to ensure that UK Visas and Immigration has an adequate number of staff to process Tier 2 visa applications when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109649","109649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777857","2017-11-03","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many companies published a Modern Slavery Statement in accordance with the provisions of section 54 of the Modern Slavery Act 2015 in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109691","109691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777858","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the refugee family reunion rules on the capacity of refugees to integrate fully in the UK.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109651","109651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777859","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for family reunion visas under part 11 of the Immigration Rules were granted outside of those rules in (a) 2014, (b) 2015 and (c) 2016.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109652","109652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777860","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to introduce a licensing regime for air rifles.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109684","109684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777861","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether an assessment of the (a) number and (b) types of calls made to the modern slavery helpline has been made since that helpline was established.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109685","109685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777862","2017-10-30","Cabinet Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the number of non-UK EU citizens who have left the UK since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109607","109607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777863","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109536","109536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777864","2017-10-30","Department for International Development","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109537","109537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777865","2017-10-30","Department for International Development","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, under what circumstances the Government would consider increasing the percentage  of GDP allocated to official development assistance above 0.7 per cent.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109573","109573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777866","2017-10-30","Department for International Development","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department plans to take to support the Government of Uganda in supporting refugees in that country.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109606","109606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777867","2017-10-30","Department for International Development","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to support science and innovation in Africa.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109677","109677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777868","2017-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the current status is of the British Council's African Knowledge Transfer Partnerships pilot project; and whether there are plans to continue or to replicate that project in the near future.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109678","109678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777869","2017-10-30","Department for International Development","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2017 to Question 108856, on Developing countries: sexual harassment, how her Department defines adequate controls; and whether such controls were framed under the provisions of UK employment or in-country law.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109762","109762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777870","2017-10-30","Department for International Development","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2017 to Question 108856, on Developing countries: sexual harassment, if the Government will publish the details of the due diligence assessment that organisations funded by her Department are subject to.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109744","109744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777871","2017-10-30","Department for International Development","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2017 to Question 108856, on Developing countries: sexual harassment, whether her Department has terminated any funding projects due to (a) suppliers not fulfilling their obligations and (b) reasons concerning sexual harassment policies or cases.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109745","109745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777872","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate the Government has made of the proportion of prisoners who spend more than 22 hours per day in their cell.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109722","109722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777873","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders the Government projected would be referred to each community rehabilitation company in each quarter at the time of signing contracts with those companies.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109753","109753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777874","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the costs incurred by his Department in the current financial year in preparation for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109623","109623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777875","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of hours was that prisoners spent on purposeful activity in each day in (a) England and Wales and (b) each prison in England and Wales in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109756","109756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777876","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of offenders are managed by the National Probation Services; and what proportion of offenders the Government estimated would be so managed at the time of that body's creation.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109721","109721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777877","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect of its proposal to reduce the cap on the number of claimable pages under the Litigators' Graduated Fee Scheme on (a) historic sex abuse prosecutions and (b) other complex cases.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109755","109755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777878","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders have been referred to community rehabilitation companies in each quarter of the last two years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109754","109754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777879","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff worked in the (a) public and (b) private probation sector (i) in each year since 2010 and (ii) on the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109713","109713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777880","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners serving imprisonment for public protection sentences there are in each prison; and how many such prisoners have already served their minimum tariff.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109714","109714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777881","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests for registered intermediaries were made in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109707","109707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777882","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests for registered intermediaries were made for each age group of vulnerable witnesses by (a) the police, (b) the Crown Prosecution Service, (c) courts and (d) solicitors in 2017.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109710","109710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777883","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of probation assessments carried out by each community rehabilitation company were administered (a) by telephone and (b) face-to-face in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109711","109711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777884","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many registered intermediaries are available to cover each police force in England and Wales in 2017.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109704","109704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777885","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sexual offences were prosecuted which involved a person aged under 18-years old where that person was (a) matched and (b) unmatched with a registered intermediary in 2017.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109702","109702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777886","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests for registered intermediary support there were for witnesses (a) under and (b) over 18-years old by (i) the police, (ii) the Crown Prosecution Service, (iii) defence lawyers, (iv) judges and (v) police area in 2017; and what proportion of those requests were successfully fulfilled for each of such category of witness and requester.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109703","109703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777887","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce the number of self-inflicted deaths of prisoners.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109679","109679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777888","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the number of self-inflicted deaths in prisons.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109680","109680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777889","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect on people with autism of participating in a potentially stressful personal independence payment tribunal.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109609","109609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777890","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department spent on staff attending external courses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109681","109681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777891","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many British citizens who have returned to the UK after fighting in Iraq and Syria since 2012 have been prosecuted.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109590","109590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777892","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2017 to Question 107170 on magistrates: Warrington, when and for what reasons his Department decided to cease collection of data on the gender and residence of members of the magistracy.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109566","109566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777893","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many EU nationals (a) are in UK prisons and (b) have been transferred to prison in their own countries under the EU Prisoner Transfer Directive.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109565","109565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777894","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to build a new women's prison in Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109576","109576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777895","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to build a new women's prison in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109577","109577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777896","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109538","109538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777897","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in which prisons women who (a) gave a North Wales address and (b) were sentenced by a North Wales Court were held in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109550","109550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777898","2017-10-30","Leader of the House","2017-10-25","To ask the Leader of the House, whether her Office was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109539","109539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777899","2017-10-30","Northern Ireland Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109540","109540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777900","2017-10-30","Scotland Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109541","109541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777901","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109542","109542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777902","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to reduce the number of unnecessary road signs.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109527","109527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777903","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to release the outcome of the consultation on the site of the High Speed 2 depot on the eastern leg of its route.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109650","109650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777904","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to reduce overcrowding on the South West Mainline into London Waterloo.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109648","109648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777905","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the position and dates of employment by HS2 Ltd are of all former High Speed 2 staff who have received redundancy payments.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109786","109786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777906","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether rail operators will contribute to the airwave replacement programme for British Transport Police.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109696","109696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777907","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2017 to Question 108497, if his Department will undertake a study into journey times between Leigh and local High Speed 2 stations; and how such times can be reduced.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109697","109697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777908","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of air quality on the M6 between junctions 9 and 10a; and what steps his Department is taking to mitigate the effect of traffic on air quality on that section of that road.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109724","109724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777909","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase capacity on popular train routes between London and (a) Chester, (b) Greater Manchester and (c) major cities in the North of England.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109712","109712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777910","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who has sat on the (a) Exceptions, (b) People and (c) Management Panel of High Speed 2; and between what dates each such person served on those panels.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109752","109752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777911","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2017 to Question 4164, what proportion of the estimated life cycle costs for the emergency service network programme it is planned that the British Transport Police will pay.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109741","109741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777912","2017-10-30","Wales Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109543","109543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777913","2017-10-30","Wales Office","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people in Wales who have been participants in (a) INTERREG, (b) Horizon 2020, (c) EaSi, (d) COSME and (e) Erasmus+ in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109564","109564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777914","2017-10-30","Women and Equalities","2017-10-25","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether the Government Equalities Office was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109535","109535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777915","2017-10-30","Women and Equalities","2017-10-25","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she was first made aware of proposals by the Equality and Human Rights Commissioner to abolish the position of Disability Commissioner.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109708","109708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777916","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what funding his Department has set aside for contingencies relating to the UK leaving the EU in the (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2018-19 financial years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109784","109784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777917","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reasons the mother and baby unit at Eastwood Park Prison remains out of commission; and when the repair to that unit will be completed.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109775","109775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777918","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2017 to Question 108912, on Department for Work and Pensions: telephone services, where the income from telephone services referred to in that Answer is applied.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109746","109746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777919","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time was between an employment support allowance claim application and a decision being made on that claim, (a) nationality and (b) in Sunderland Central constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109773","109773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777920","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has estimated the potential savings to the public purse of the closure of Eastern Avenue jobcentre.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109774","109774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777921","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of disabled people who will be enrolled on to universal credit by 31 January 2018.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109750","109750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777922","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to publish monthly the number of disabled people receiving universal credit alongside other monthly statistics on universal credit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109749","109749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777923","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disabled people are in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109748","109748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777924","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobcentre clients have been assisted by an Armed Forces Champion in the Glasgow South West constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109655","109655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777925","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109544","109544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777926","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many items of correspondence he has received from people in Midlothian constituency on changes to the state pension age for women born in the 1950s.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109553","109553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777927","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will carry out an assessment of the effect on women in Midlothian constituency of changes to the state pension age for women born in the 1950s.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109554","109554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777928","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will release data to (a) local authorities and (b) housing associations on the claimants due to migrate from legacy benefits to universal credit on a daily basis.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109567","109567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777929","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 3 February 2017 to Question 62617, on food poverty, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that people in work do not experience food poverty resulting in a reliance on food banks.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109568","109568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777930","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints his Department has received from universal credit claimants in Midlothian constituency since its introduction.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109578","109578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777931","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people claiming universal credit in Midlothian constituency have contacted the universal credit helpline (a) by landline, (b) by mobile phone and (c) at a local jobcentre.","Biography information for Danielle Rowley","Danielle Rowley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109579","109579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777932","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people on benefits in the Vale of Clwyd who will be transferred to universal credit in (a) the next four months and (b) each year until 2022.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109615","109615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777933","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how representations from hon. members acting on behalf of constituents about benefit claim decisions are communicated to case managers and decision makers working for his Department.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109642","109642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777934","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which jobcentres in Wales have offered claimants free access to jobcentre (a) telephone lines and (b) computers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109612","109612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777935","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times jobcentre computers were accessed by claimants in each jobcentre in Wales in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109613","109613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777936","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many telephone calls were made by benefit claimants from within each jobcentre in Wales in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109614","109614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777937","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs that will be affected by the closure of jobcentres; and what the roles and functions of those jobs will be.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109688","109688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777938","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Weston-Super-Mare, of 11 August 2017, on behalf of Somerset Savings & Loans on the Credit Union Expansion Project.","Biography information for John Penrose","John Penrose","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109604","109604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777939","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time was between an employment and support allowance claim application and a first payment being made (a) nationally and (b) in Sunderland Central constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109735","109735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777940","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to assist universal credit claimants who are (a) illiterate or (b) innumerate.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109620","109620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777941","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time was for answering telephone calls for each category of claim handled by (a) jobcentres in Wales and (b) his Department's agencies in each year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109621","109621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777942","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the number of new claimants of universal credit his Department will process in the Vale of Clwyd in (a) the next four months and (b) each year until 2022.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109616","109616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777943","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in the Vale of Clwyd were receiving (a) employment and support allowance, (b) jobseeker's allowance, (c) housing benefit, (d) income support and (e) tax credits in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109617","109617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777944","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to respond to the recommendations of his Department's consultation on tips, gratuities, service and other charges; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109654","109654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777945","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109545","109545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777946","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Oral Answer of the Prime Minister, Official Report, column 300, of 25 October 2017, what discussions he has had with the Prime Minister on the proposals to be brought to Parliament on fracking.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109760","109760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777947","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, on what date he plans to publish the Consumer Green Paper.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109751","109751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777948","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the Industrial Strategy White Paper.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109628","109628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777949","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to publish his response to the Taylor Review of modern working practices, published in July 2017, before the November 2017 recess.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109625","109625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777950","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what funding his Department has set aside for contingencies relating to the UK leaving the EU in the (a) 2017-18 and (b) 2018-19 financial years.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109782","109782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777951","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what contingency funding his Department has allocated in relation to the Government's negotiations on the UK leaving the EU for the (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20 financial years.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109780","109780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777952","2017-10-30","Department for International Trade","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what funding his Department has set aside for contingencies relating to the UK leaving the EU in the (a) current and (b) 2018-19 financial year.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109785","109785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777953","2017-10-30","Department for International Trade","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department was consulted by the Department for Exiting the European Union on the economic impact assessments conducted for the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109548","109548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777954","2017-10-30","Department for International Trade","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what information his Department holds on the supply of arms by a British company to the Government of South Sudan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109574","109574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777955","2017-10-30","Department for International Trade","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans the Government has to bring forward a schedule of commitments on trade in IT equipment to be agreed with new trading partners after the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109690","109690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777956","2017-10-30","Department for International Trade","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of export opportunities in the dairy sector.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109603","109603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777957","2017-10-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what representations the Government has received from the aviation sector on priorities for its negotiations on the UK leaving the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109700","109700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776822","2017-10-26","Cabinet Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has assessed the findings and conclusions of the September 2017 report by the Joseph Rowntree Reform Trust, Elections for Sale?; and if he will implement that report's recommendations on reform of the current electoral spending rules.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109244","109244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776823","2017-10-26","Cabinet Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 12 October 2017 to Question 105664, on special constables: leave, whether it is the policy of all government departments to provide paid leave for employees to undertake special constable training and duties.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109258","109258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776824","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department takes to ensure that UK Official Development Assistance not spent under the provisions of the International Development Act 2002 is spent in a way that is likely to contribute to a reduction in poverty.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109259","109259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776825","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect the freeze in whisky excise duty in 2016 had on Government revenues.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109248","109248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776826","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to recent emergency funding for recovery from Hurricanes Irma and Maria, if he will take steps to guarantee contingency funding outwith Overseas Development Assistance for future events affecting British Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109262","109262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776827","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on compliance of the recent reforms to off-payroll working in the public sector; and what recent assessment he has made of the level and effects of non-compliance relating to the recent reforms to off-payroll working in the private sector.","Biography information for Jeremy Quin","Jeremy Quin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109236","109236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776828","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the net worth to the UK economy of the Scottish whisky industry.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109245","109245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776829","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what impact assessment was undertaken ahead of the March 2017 Budget on its effect on the whisky industry.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109246","109246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776830","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect the reduction in whisky duty in 2015 had on Government revenues.","Biography information for Douglas Ross","Douglas Ross","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109247","109247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776831","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the potential savings to the public purse from the proposed closure of the Ruby House HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) office in Aberdeen; and what account was taken in making the decision to close that office of the potential effect of that proposed closure on HMRCs' ability to collect tax.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109266","109266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776832","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the proposed closure of the Ruby House HM Revenue and Customs office in Aberdeen on the local economy.","Biography information for Ross Thomson","Ross Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109267","109267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776833","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the reasons are for Scotch whisky being taxed at a higher rate than wine; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109230","109230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776834","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the (a) number of people employed in, (b) volume of sales in and (c) amounts of duty levied from the Scotch whisky industry as a result of the March 2017 Budget.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109231","109231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776835","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the increases in excise duty on the levels of sales of Scotch whisky as a result of measures in the March 2017 Budget.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109232","109232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776836","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 7789, on children: daycare, whether there has been a change to the figures for those people signing up since that Answer; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109233","109233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776837","2017-11-06","Church Commissioners","2017-10-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what assessment the Church of England has made of whether to mark the 400th anniversary of imposition of the Five Articles of Perth by James I of England and VI of Scotland on the Church of Scotland.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109298","109298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776838","2017-10-30","Church Commissioners","2017-10-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what the policy is of the Church Commissioners on the playing of secular music in (a) St. Sepulchre-without-Newgate Church and (b) all churches.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109263","109263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776839","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his Department's policies of the Local Government Association's financial peer review of Northamptonshire County Council.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109261","109261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776840","2017-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his Oral contribution of 19 October 2017, Official Report, column 1002, on Grenfell Tower, what plans he has to audit the management, operation, facilities and safety of all social housing.","Biography information for Matt Western","Matt Western","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109260","109260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776841","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to advise homebuyers of the potential risks of buying leasehold properties; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109277","109277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776842","2017-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that new build homes are sold on as leasehold properties.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109239","109239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776843","2017-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 19 October 2017, Official Report, column 1001, on Grenfell Tower, what the total estimated cost to the public purse is of the work on those buildings identified as requiring remedial measures.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109304","109304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776844","2017-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 19 October 2017, Official Report, column 1001, on Grenfell Tower, for how many of the buildings in the Government's building safety programme the retrofitting of sprinkler systems has been identified as one of the remedial measures needed.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109305","109305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776845","2017-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 19 October 2017, Official Report, column 1001, on Grenfell Tower, how many tower block buildings, as part of the Government's building safety programme, have been (a) tested, (b) confirmed as fire safe and needing no interim or remedial measures, (c) confirmed as needing interim measures and (d) confirmed as needing remedial measures.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109306","109306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776846","2017-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 19 October 2017, Official Report, column 1001, on Grenfell Tower, how many buildings identified as needing interim measures have had that work (a) started and (b) completed.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109307","109307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776847","2017-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 19 October 2017, Official Report, column 1001, on Grenfell Tower, how many of the buildings in the Government's building safety programme are operated or owned by (a) local authority, (b) housing association and (c) private sector landlords.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109308","109308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776848","2017-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 19 October 2017, Official Report, column 1001, on Grenfell Tower, what the total estimated cost to the public purse is of the work on those buildings identified as requiring interim measures.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109309","109309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776849","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions he has had with house-builders on sales of (a) leasehold houses and (b) freeholds to other companies after purchases are completed.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109276","109276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776850","2017-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 19 October 2017, Official Report, column 1001, on Grenfell Tower, how many of his Department's officials have been allocated tower block buildings to follow as part of his Department's monitoring of the building safety programme.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109301","109301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776851","2017-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 19 October 2017, Official Report, column 1001, on Grenfell Tower, what has been the increase in the number of officials in his Department working on (a) the building safety programme and (b) other work related to the Grenfell Tower fire since that work commenced.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109302","109302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776852","2017-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to his oral contribution of 19 October 2017, Official Report, column 1001, on Grenfell Tower, how many buildings identified as needing remedial measures have had that work (a) started and (b) completed.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109303","109303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776853","2017-10-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate her Department has made of the number of local newspapers in the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109291","109291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776854","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Brimstone missiles have been sold by the UK to Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109284","109284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776855","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of Brimstone missiles used by Saudi Arabia in the conflict on Yemen.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109285","109285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776856","2017-10-30","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the criteria for an EU national applying to join the British Army take account of the applicant's parents having attained UK citizenship.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109283","109283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776857","2017-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how he defines the term growing Royal Navy.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109310","109310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776858","2017-10-30","Department for International Trade","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to UK Defence and Security Export Statistics for 2016, how much of the £5.9 billion that the UK exported, based on orders, was paid for by the Government of Iran.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109243","109243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776859","2017-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the recommended level of spare parts held by the armed forces for the UK's Typhoon squadrons is.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109227","109227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776860","2017-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the level of spare parts held by the armed forces for the UK's Typhoon squadrons was at the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109228","109228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776861","2017-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much has been spent by his Department and the armed services on Typhoon spare parts in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109229","109229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776862","2017-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) staff of his Department and (b) members of the UK armed forces were in attendance at the naming ceremony for RFA Tidesurge at DSME Shipyard in Okpo, South Korea on 1 September 2017.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109312","109312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776863","2017-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost to the public purse was of transporting the Lady Sponsor and accompanying guests to South Korea for the naming ceremony for RFA Tidesurge on 1 September 2017.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109313","109313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776864","2017-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the designated Fleet Ready Escort was on each day between 14 and 23 October 2017.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109314","109314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776865","2017-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's policy is on tackling unauthorised traveller encampments on his Department's land.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109323","109323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776866","2017-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on which dates the Red Arrows display team last performed in (a) Saudi Arabia, (b) Jordan, (c) Kuwait, (d) Qatar, (e) Oman, (f) Bahrain and (g) the United Arab Emirates; how many personnel from his Department attended each such performance; and what the cost to the public purse was of each such performance.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109315","109315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776867","2017-10-26","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of unfilled vacancies there are in private and voluntary-run nurseries and pre-schools; and what steps she is taking to ensure that those vacancies are filled.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109275","109275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776868","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she last met representatives of supply teachers to discuss their concerns about insecure working practices.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109278","109278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776869","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) applications and (b) admissions for initial teacher training courses specialising in the education of under-fives there were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109286","109286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776870","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 9 October 2017 to Question 105348, on children: day care, what the reasons are for the apparent discrepancy between the proportion of providers cited who were willing and able to offer the extended hours places and the data provided on that proportion in paragraph 3 on page 12 of her Department's paper, Evaluation of Early Rollout of 30 Hours Free Childcare, published on 31 August 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109254","109254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776871","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an estimate of the number of parents who are unable to access funded hours only places; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109242","109242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776872","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many two-year olds have received 15 hours free childcare in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109295","109295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776873","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of under-fives received early years education in maintained nursery schools in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109287","109287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776874","2017-10-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the timetable is for the introduction of legislative proposals to increase the maximum sentence for animal cruelty offences to five years imprisonment.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109235","109235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776875","2017-10-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to encourage landowners to erect owl and bat boxes on their land; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109264","109264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776876","2017-10-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding each national park in England has received in each of the last five financial years from the European Commission and its programmes and agencies.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109222","109222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776877","2017-10-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how UK fisheries will be managed after 30 March 2019; whether UK fisheries will be managed out to the Exclusive Economic Zone median line; and whether the UK will apply different rules to the area between the territorial sea and the Exclusive Economic Zone.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109211","109211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776878","2017-10-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to stop the dumping of dead fish in UK waters after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109212","109212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776879","2017-10-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2017 to Question 107602, on packaging, how many local authorities provide roadside collection of plastic wrap; how many tonnes of plastic wrap has been recycled in each of the last five years; and what proportion of plastic wrap used in the UK was recycled in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109317","109317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776880","2017-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the outcome of the Conference on Facilitating the Entry Into Force of the Comprehensive Nuclear Test Ban Treaty held on 20 September 2017.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109335","109335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776881","2017-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support the work of the Preparatory Commission for the Comprehensive Nuclear Test Ban Treaty Organization.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109336","109336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776882","2017-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his US counterpart on ratification by that country of the Comprehensive Nuclear Test Ban Treaty; and what assessment he has made of the prospects for such ratification under the current US Administration.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109333","109333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776883","2017-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help facilitate the entry into force of the Comprehensive Nuclear Test Ban Treaty.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109334","109334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776884","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information NHS England holds on the use of tasers in mental health units.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109217","109217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776885","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government will provide devolved administrations with increased funding to pay for lifting the cap on nursing pay in the NHS.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109218","109218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776886","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the cap on nursing pay will be lifted for all nursing staff working in the NHS at bands 5 to 9.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109219","109219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776887","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the pay award for nursing staff in the NHS will be at a higher level than inflation.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109220","109220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776888","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether additional funding will be made available to cover the increase in pay for nursing staff working in the NHS.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109221","109221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776889","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the budget surplus of (a) clinical commissioning groups in England and (b) Greater Manchester Clinical Commissioning Group for 2016-17.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109213","109213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776890","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the recording and sharing of NHS data to assist to improve care for patients and scientific research.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109214","109214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776891","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to improve the UK's clinical trials base capacity over the next five years.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109237","109237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776892","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted via accident and emergency departments with a primary diagnosis of local infection in each month of (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15, (f) 2015-16 and (g) 2016-17.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109249","109249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776893","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted via accident and emergency departments with a primary diagnosis where nothing abnormal was detected in each month of (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15, (f) 2015-16 and (g) 2016-17.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109250","109250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776894","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of the (a) English and (b) Welsh resident population who live within (i) five, (ii) 10 and (iii) 15 miles of a registered NHS or independent abortion clinic by NUTS 1 region.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109280","109280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776895","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of illegal (a) surgical and (b) medical abortions which took place before 24 weeks' gestation in each of the last five fiscal years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109282","109282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776896","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) NHS and (b) independent premises are regulated for (i) surgical abortions only, (ii) medical abortions only and (iii) both surgical and medical abortions.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109281","109281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776897","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding NHS England has allocated to specialised inpatient eating disorder services in each of the last six (a) financial and (b) calendar years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109294","109294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776898","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total cost to the public purse of NHS Direct has been in each year since its formation in March 1998.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109332","109332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776899","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the discount rate change on the indemnity costs of general practitioners.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109328","109328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776900","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to reply to the letter of 6 October 2017 from the hon. Member for Bridgend  on Kernow Clinical Commissioning Group's proposed withdrawal of transport for renal dialysis patients.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109316","109316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776901","2017-10-26","Home Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will commission the Migration Advisory Committee to produce an interim report on seasonal workers.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109326","109326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776902","2017-10-26","Home Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure the safe passage to the UK of child refugees sleeping rough in Calais who (a) meet the Dublin III Regulation family reunification criteria and (b) could be offered a place by local councils under the Dubs scheme.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109274","109274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776903","2017-10-26","Home Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the equity of the fee to apply for settled status in the UK; and whether she plans to waive the fee for applicants for settled status who are non-UK citizens and who apply because the UK is leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109331","109331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776904","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department has allocated to the Border Force; and how many people have been employed by that agency in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109293","109293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776905","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the use of tasers in mental health units; and whether this information will be collected as part of her Department's new requirement for police forces to record and publish data on their officers' use of force.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109215","109215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776906","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to ensure that appropriate local mechanisms have been implemented to scrutinise the use of tasers in mental health settings; and if she will set out the arrangements in each local area.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109216","109216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776907","2017-11-06","House of Commons Commission","2017-10-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, if the Commission will take steps to mark the 375th anniversary of the signing of the Solemn League and Covenant by both Houses of Parliament and the Scottish commissioners on 25 September 1643.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109300","109300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776908","2017-10-26","Department for International Development","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she has received from civil society organisations on the Government providing continued support to the International Citizen Service.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109321","109321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776909","2017-10-26","Department for International Development","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the International Citizen Service on educational outcomes in developing countries.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109322","109322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776910","2017-10-26","Department for International Development","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to fund the International Citizen Service programme in each of the next five financial years.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109325","109325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776911","2017-10-26","Department for International Development","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what percentage of UK humanitarian aid was spent on education in (a) 2012, (b) 2013, (c) 2014, (d) 2015 and (e) 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109226","109226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776912","2017-10-26","Department for International Development","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effect on global poverty reduction of the increasing proportion of the UK aid budget spent by Departments not subject to the International Development Act 2002.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109257","109257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776913","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of incidents of prisoners spitting at prison officers in 2016.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109311","109311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776914","2017-10-26","Home Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to support the police in tackling street drinking and anti-social behaviour.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109272","109272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776915","2017-11-06","Scotland Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether his Department plans to mark the 375th anniversary of the signing of the Solemn League and Covenant by both Houses of Parliament and the Scottish commissioners on 25 September 1643; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109299","109299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776916","2017-10-26","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the completion of the electrification of the rail line between Chippenham and Bristol Temple Meads.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109269","109269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776917","2017-10-26","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the completion of electrification of the rail line between Chippenham and Bristol Temple Meads.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109271","109271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776918","2017-10-26","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will undertake an assessment of the potential effect on levels of air pollution in Bath of the (a) completion and (b) non-completion of rail electrification between Chippenham and Bristol Temple Meads.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109270","109270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776919","2017-10-26","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the replacement of Pacer carriages covering local services with modern rolling stock on rail services in the North of England.","Biography information for Chris Green","Chris Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109238","109238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776920","2017-10-26","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the level of carbon emissions that will be caused by diesel bi-mode trains compared to electric trains on the Midland Mainline.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109327","109327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776921","2017-10-26","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the estimated cost is of the purchase and running of diesel bi-mode trains on the Midland Mainline.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109329","109329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776922","2017-10-26","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect on commuters from Hook and Winchfield of the proposed reduction in morning peak-period services in South Western Railway's new timetable.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109324","109324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776923","2017-11-01","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential effect on the viability of community transport organisations of the requirement for them as section 19 permit operators not to charge anyone and to require all drivers to have a PSV O-licence.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109297","109297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776924","2017-11-01","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if his Department will make an estimate of the cost to community transport organisations of ensuring that all their drivers have a PSV O-licence; and whether that requirement will effect their charitable status due to the capital reserve requirement involved.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109296","109296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776925","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants will be affected by the changes to the support for mortgage interest due to take place in April 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109223","109223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776926","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, following the support for mortgage interest changes in April 2018, with what frequency interest will be applied.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109224","109224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776927","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, who will be administering the support for mortgage interest changes due to take place in April 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109225","109225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776928","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the interest rate will be set, following support for mortgage interest changes in April 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109240","109240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776929","2017-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of whether Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe's rights under (a) Iranian and (b) international human rights laws have been violated; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109241","109241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776930","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 October 2017 to Question 105008, on personal independence payment (PIP): appeals, what his target is for the proportion of PIP decisions to be made correctly first time; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109255","109255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776931","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 9 October 2017 to Question 105008, on personal independence payment: appeals, what the average cost to his Department is of each appeal.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109256","109256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776932","2017-10-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department offers to people over 25-years old to re-enter the job market.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109268","109268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776933","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to prevent the dumping of Chinese steel in the UK.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109288","109288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776934","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish Professor Tim Dafforn's review of entrepreneurship; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109279","109279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776935","2017-10-30","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he plans to take to prevent the dumping of Chinese steel in the UK when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109289","109289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776936","2017-10-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many Scottish Limited Partnerships have been fined since the People with Significant Control register came into force.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Dame Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109251","109251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776937","2017-10-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to bring forward legislative proposals to provide for a register showing who owns and controls overseas legal entities that own UK property or participate in Government procurement.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Dame Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109252","109252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776938","2017-10-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which UK-based Trust and Company Service Providers have incorporated more than 20 Scottish Limited Partnerships.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Dame Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109253","109253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776939","2017-10-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on food prices in the UK of adopting World Trade Organisation tariffs when the UK leaves the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109292","109292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776941","2017-10-30","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on food prices in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109290","109290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776942","2017-10-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to his oral contribution of 17 October 2017, Official Report, column 744, on EU Exit negotiations, what the evidential basis is for his statement that UK inward investment is at record levels in the first half of 2017.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109265","109265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776943","2017-10-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many non-British EU nationals have been employed by his Department in each month since it was established.","Biography information for Damien Moore","Damien Moore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109273","109273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776944","2017-10-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2017 to Question 106266, on UK membership of the EU, by whom has such agreement been made that when the UK leaves the EU there is automaticity about the European Economic Area Agreement no longer operating in respect of the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109234","109234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776945","2017-10-26","Cabinet Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which government departments have freephone numbers for public use.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109359","109359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776946","2017-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the letter of 15 September 2017 from the Investigatory Powers Commissioner's Office summarising the findings of the 2017 BPD Audit, for how long data gathered from social media services is held by GCHQ before being deleted; and how large the bulk dataset holding that data is.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109364","109364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776947","2017-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the letter of 15 September 2017 from the Investigatory Powers Commissioner's Office summarising the findings of the 2017 BPD Audit, what methods are used by GCHQ to collect data from social media services; and whether GCHQ collects metadata and content from social media services.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109365","109365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776948","2017-10-30","Cabinet Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will bring forward proposals for automatic voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109371","109371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776949","2017-10-30","Cabinet Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions his Department has had with other Government Departments on the potential use of automatic voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109372","109372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776950","2017-10-30","Cabinet Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits to the electoral system of automatic voter registration for elections in the UK.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109373","109373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776951","2017-10-26","Cabinet Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2017 to Question 7512, on cybercrime, what the four services referred to in that Answer are.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109429","109429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776952","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will review the progressive beer duty regime to ensure that the excise duty system supports growth in British beer exports.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109467","109467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776953","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will review the operation of the Small Brewers Relief scheme to remove barriers to growth for the UK's small and medium-sized brewers.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109468","109468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776954","2017-10-26","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has considered the report from Europe Economics commissioned by the Small Brewer Duty Reform Coalition; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109469","109469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776955","2017-10-30","HM Treasury","2017-10-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what additional funds he plans to allocate to the Scottish Government to prepare for when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109356","109356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776956","2017-10-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the specific cause of the fire at Grenfell Tower has been identified; and what that cause was.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109354","109354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776957","2017-10-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the timetable is for the introduction of mandatory portable appliance testing for residential properties.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109392","109392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776958","2017-10-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans for the provisions of the Housing and Planning Act 2016 relating to client money protection to come into force.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109393","109393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776959","2017-10-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2017 to Question 9919, if her Department will make an analysis of the harm done by skin bleaching videos and options for regulation.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109399","109399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776960","2017-10-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she has taken to ensure that charities and social enterprises that receive funding from the EU can receive a similar level of funding after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109349","109349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776961","2017-10-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of the assets at the Olympic Park have been sold; what revenue those sales have yielded; and what further such sales of assets are planned.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109351","109351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776962","2017-10-30","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she has taken to ensure that charities and social enterprises can bid for funding from the proposed UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109353","109353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776963","2017-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what training and assistance the UK armed forces are providing to support anti-poaching patrols in other countries.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109460","109460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776964","2017-10-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress his Department has made on increasing the size of the Army Reserve to 30,000 personnel.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109458","109458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776965","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 1 March 2017, Sex and Relationships Education, HCWS 509, and pursuant to the Answer of 11 July 2017 to Question 2526, what the (a) timetable and (b) planned commencement date is for the consultation on the provision of relationships education.","Biography information for Stella Creasy","Stella Creasy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109340","109340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776966","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the Education Funding Agency plans to publish its report into Wakefield City Academies Trust; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109401","109401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776967","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department or any of its agencies hold reports that raise concerns on the financial situation in multi-academy trusts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109402","109402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776968","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department takes upon discovering concerns about the governance and financial management of multi-academy trusts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109403","109403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776969","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department took to ensure that there were no improper financial transfers from within the Wakefield City Academies Trust before that Trust collapsed; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109404","109404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776970","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether schools in Plymouth which accept children of servicemen and servicewomen will continue to receive the service pupil premium after April 2018.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109355","109355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776971","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will place in the Library a copy of the Education Funding Agency investigation into the Wakefield City Academies Trust produced in 2016.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109337","109337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776972","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to hold an inquiry into the operation of the Wakefield City Academies Trust.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109338","109338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776973","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2017 to Question 108171, whether her Department plans to seek information on the income of people accessing 30 hours of free childcare.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109339","109339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776974","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the announcement by her Department on 11 April 2017 on families to benefit from £55 million boost to childcare services, how many applications have been made to that fund; how much has been paid out from that fund; and how many childcare places that funding has established.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109407","109407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776975","2017-10-30","Department for Education","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Taylor Review of modern working practices, published in July 2017, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy to improve the working practices in the supply teaching profession.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109408","109408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776976","2017-10-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department allocated to scientific research in the UK on the environment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109461","109461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776977","2017-10-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department takes to update the public on new and scientific discoveries about challenges to ecosystems across the world.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109462","109462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776978","2017-10-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Foreign Secretary on the role of the UK in demonstrating global leadership on ocean conservation.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109463","109463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776979","2017-10-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to further the roll-out of marine sanctuaries in the Antarctic.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109464","109464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776980","2017-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to communicate with hon. Members and Members of the House of Lords plans for the Commonwealth Heads of Government Meeting 2018.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109465","109465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776981","2017-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has provided to private organisations that work to improve the UK's international relations in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109466","109466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776982","2017-10-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage the Governments of Uganda and Kenya to participate in the Intergovernmental Authority on Development-led High-Level Revitalisation Forum.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109389","109389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776983","2017-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Spanish counterpart on the violence that occurred during the Catalan independence referendum; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109475","109475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776984","2017-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when the Overseas Territories Joint Ministerial Council will be held in 2017; and what the agenda is for that meeting.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109343","109343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776985","2017-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterparts in other countries on ratification of the International Labour Organisation Convention on Domestic Workers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109367","109367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776986","2017-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has made with his US counterpart on that Government's current Nuclear Posture Review.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109368","109368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776987","2017-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on self-determination for the Biafran people in the Eastern Region of Nigeria.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109413","109413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776988","2017-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to help facilitate implementation by UN member states of their obligations under UN Security Council Resolution 1540.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109436","109436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776989","2017-10-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to support the work of the committee established pursuant to UN Security Resolution 1540.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109437","109437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776990","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what additional resources have been allocated to child and adolescent mental health services in Lancashire, outside the Greater Manchester region, since the Manchester area attack of 22 May 2017.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109318","109318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776991","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that GPs and nurses are able to access training to gain and maintain qualifications to fit long-acting reversible contraception.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109330","109330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776992","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of children waiting for mental health support services in (a) Hounslow, (b) London and (c) England.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109432","109432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776993","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of children on the waiting list for mental health support services in (a) Hounslow, (b) London and (c) England who have witnessed domestic abuse.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109433","109433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776994","2017-10-30","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital trusts in London have recorded budget deficits in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109341","109341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776995","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to update his Department's report, entitled A Framework for Sexual Health Improvement in England, published in March 2013.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109418","109418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776996","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many days locum GPs have been employed in each clinical commissioning group in England in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109390","109390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776997","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of GP locums in each clinical commissioning group in England in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109391","109391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776998","2017-10-26","Department of Health","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of reductions in public health budgets on open access sexual health services.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109394","109394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/776999","2017-10-26","Home Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 9 October 2017 to Question 105367, on motorcycles: helmets, what discussions she has had with the police on whether suspects being pursued should be included in the category of any road users.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109470","109470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777000","2017-10-26","Cabinet Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government's annual migration figures include seasonal workers.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109443","109443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777001","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of children growing up in homes which are experiencing domestic violence in each region and nation of the UK.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109434","109434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777002","2017-10-26","Home Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2017 to Question 108430, on asylum, how many decision makers her Department aims to maintain using rolling recruitment.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109366","109366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777003","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2017 to Question 108450, on police: finance; if she will publish the number of unsuccessful bids to the Police Transformation Fund and the value of each unsuccessful bid.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109414","109414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777004","2017-10-30","Home Office","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will ensure that all refugees in France refused transfer to the UK are informed that their application for transfer has been refused.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109449","109449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777005","2017-10-26","Department for International Development","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department provided for anti-poaching efforts in Africa in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109459","109459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777006","2017-10-26","Department for International Development","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of UK Aid's humanitarian funding has been allocated to local and national responders, to fulfil the UK's obligation to reach the global target of 25 per cent by 2020 as set out in the 2016 OECD World Humanitarian Summit's Grand Bargain.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109444","109444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777007","2017-10-26","Department for International Development","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans she has to regularly evaluate implementation of the Supply Partner Code of Conduct and to make such reports available to the public.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109431","109431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777008","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 October 2017 to Question 106123, if he will hold discussions with the Chair of the Sentencing Council on linking the length of custodial sentences to the acquisition of specified skills in prison.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109425","109425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777009","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department and its agencies hold on incidence of (a) anti-Semitism, (b) Islamophobia,(c) racism and (d) homophobia by prison guards and prisoners; and how such information is recorded.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109388","109388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777010","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the Legal Aid Agency paid to providers through grants of exceptional funding for representation at inquests before Coroners' Courts in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109424","109424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777011","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans his Department has to invest in the refurbishment of prisons  in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) HM Prison Liverpool in the next five years.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109441","109441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777012","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether his Department plans to close prisons in (a) the North West and (b) England in the next five years.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109442","109442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777013","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish the (a) running costs and (b) budget for HM Prison Liverpool in each of the last 12 years.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109455","109455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777014","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff at HM Prison Liverpool have suffered injury in each of the last 12 years.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109456","109456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777015","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on diverting offenders with mental health problems away from detention in prison.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109439","109439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777016","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons he or the Minister for Prisons have visited in (a) England and (b) the North West in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109440","109440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777017","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers were employed in (a) England, (b) the North West and (c) HM Prison Liverpool in each of the last 12 years.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109453","109453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777018","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to tackle (a) violence, (b) drug use, (c) use of drones and (d) use of mobile phones in prison.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109457","109457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777019","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total cost incurred by the Legal Aid Agency is in means testing applications for grants of exceptional funding in respect to representation at inquests before Coroners' Courts in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109423","109423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777020","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have died in HM Prison Liverpool in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109471","109471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777021","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners have died by suicide in HM Prison Liverpool in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109472","109472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777022","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what capital investment has been made to HM Prison Liverpool in each of the last 12 years.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109473","109473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777023","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to respond to the recent assessment by the HM Inspectorate of Prisons on HM Prison Liverpool that took place in September 2017.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109448","109448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777024","2017-10-30","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions his Department has had with the HM Inspectorate of Prisons on HM Prison Liverpool in the last three years.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109447","109447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777025","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of reconviction rates among women leaving prison.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109360","109360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777026","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to help mothers leaving prison rebuild family relationships.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109361","109361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777027","2017-10-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of trends in the level of homelessness among women leaving prison.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109362","109362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777028","2017-10-30","House of Commons Commission","2017-10-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, how many vacancies for specialist advisers to select committees have been advertised in each of the last five sessions of Parliament.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109412","109412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777029","2017-10-30","Prime Minister","2017-10-24","To ask the Prime Minister, whether the hon. Member for Daventry was acting on behalf of the Government when he wrote to university vice-chancellors requesting the names of academic staff who teach European affairs with a particular focus on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109352","109352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777030","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when and by whom his Department was informed that unauthorised redundancy payments of £1.76 million had been paid out by HS2 Ltd.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109374","109374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777031","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the job titles were of former HS2 Ltd employees who received unauthorised redundancy payments; and what the amount and date paid was of each such payment.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109375","109375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777032","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what arrangements have been made to recover unauthorised redundancy payments made by HS2 Ltd from recipients.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109376","109376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777033","2017-10-30","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of vehicles in the Government car service are ultra-low emission vehicles.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109377","109377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777034","2017-10-26","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's press release of 12 October 2017, when his Department plans to announce how the new £48 billion funding for Britain's railways will be allocated.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109319","109319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777035","2017-10-26","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to reduce the number of unnecessary road signs.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109454","109454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777036","2017-10-26","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that local councils enforce the removal of temporary road signs which have remained in place beyond the maximum permitted period of three months.","Biography information for Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","Mr Ian Liddell-Grainger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109452","109452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777037","2017-10-26","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many wrecks have been recovered in each of the Overseas Territories since the introduction of the Nairobi International Convention on the Removal of Wrecks by the UK in 2015.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109445","109445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777038","2017-10-26","Department for Transport","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has commissioned any work from First Class Partnerships; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109430","109430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777039","2017-10-26","Women and Equalities","2017-10-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what plans her Department has to mark the International Day of Persons with Disabilities on 3 December 2017.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109379","109379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777040","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which Department manages the Jointly Managed Engagement Team; and how many members of staff from (a) HM Treasury and (b) his Department work in that team.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109446","109446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777041","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the peak number of claimants is for universal credit via the link service.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109347","109347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777042","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants currently claim via the link service.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109348","109348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777043","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department takes to avoid errors in universal credit payments where the RTI data for a claimant is late, missing or incorrect.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109450","109450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777044","2017-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of people living in social tenancies have been in rent arrears in each financial year since 2012-13.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109451","109451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777045","2017-10-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2017 to Question 105738, how many people aged (a) between 100 and 105, (b) between 106 and 110, (c) between 111 and 115 and (d) over 116-years receive the UK state pension in each country outside the UK.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109320","109320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777046","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2017 to Question 107556, on universal credit, what the aims and nature of his Department's work is with the HM Revenue and Customs Jointly Managed Engagement Team; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109435","109435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777047","2017-10-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Taylor Review of modern working practices, published in July 2017, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on improving the pensions of workers subject to insecure working practices, including supply teachers.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109410","109410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/777048","2017-11-02","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-10-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of people living in social tenancies have downsized in each year since the introduction of the spare room subsidy.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109357","109357"
