"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657180","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what measures her Department has in place to support those of its staff who have mental health problems.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57127","57127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657181","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has received from payment of civil penalties under right to rent schemes.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57104","57104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657182","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many civil penalty notices issued under the right to rent legislation were (a) first-time penalties for the landlord concerned and (b) second or at subsequent penalty for a landlord.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57105","57105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657183","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many civil penalty notices issued under right to rent legislation have related to (a) lodgers and (b) tenants.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57106","57106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657185","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many appeals against a civil penalty notice under the right to rent provisions (a) have been successful, (b) have been unsuccessful and (c) are ongoing.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57107","57107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657186","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many civil penalty notices issued under right to rent provisions have been appealed by landlords or agents from (a) 1 December 2014 to 31 January 2016 and (b) since 1 February 2016.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57108","57108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657187","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Prime Minister's announcement during her visit to the Gulf of December 2016 on cooperation to end modern slavery, how many UK personnel will be allocated to help tackle such slavery in each of the six Gulf states.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57147","57147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657188","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many landlords and agents have been issued with a civil penalty as a result of renting a property to someone who does not have a right to rent from (a) 1 December 2014 to 31 January 2016 and (b) since 1 February 2016.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57109","57109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657189","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referral notices were issued to landlords or agents as part of the right to rent scheme between (a) 1 December 2014 to 31 January 2016 and (b) since 1 February 2016.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57110","57110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657190","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of civil servants based in her Department who work full-time on asylum casework; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57083","57083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657191","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the total cost has been of processing civil penalty appeals under the right to rent provisions.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57103","57103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657192","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 November 2016 to Question 52848, whether it was her Department's chief scientific adviser or the Government's Chief Scientific Adviser who expressed concerns about the scientific basis of the trial; and if she will place in the Library or otherwise publish copies of any correspondence outlining those concerns.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57161","57161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657193","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many undocumented migrants identified through the right to rent scheme have since been (a) granted discretionary leave to remain, (b) granted refugee status, (c) granted humanitarian protection and (d) recognised as a victim of trafficking or modern day slavery.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57151","57151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657194","2016-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will estimate the number of volunteers in the football industry who work unsupervised with children.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57150","57150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657195","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the highest-paid and lowest-paid full-time employee in her Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56990","56990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657196","2016-12-15","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will review the powers available to the police to tackle anti-social use of off-road bikes and mopeds.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56963","56963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657197","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to include worker representation on its departmental board.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57012","57012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657198","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the pay of full-time staff in the highest pay grade in her Department and average full-time pay in that Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57034","57034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657199","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people who have suffered torture abroad and are awaiting her Department's decision on their claim for asylum; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57045","57045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657200","2016-12-15","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to reduce knife crime in London.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57070","57070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657201","2016-12-15","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to protect the status of EU nationals living in the UK when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57072","57072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657202","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for criminal records checks have been received by the Disclosure and Barring Service from the Football Association in each year since 2009-10; and what proportion of those applications (a) passed and (b) failed.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57048","57048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657203","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people who have been granted asylum in the UK after being victims of torture abroad in each of the last six years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57054","57054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657204","2016-12-15","Department for International Development","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her strategic objectives are in relation to women and girls in developing countries.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56961","56961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657205","2016-12-14","Department for International Development","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the pay of full-time staff in the highest pay grade in her Department and average full-time pay in that Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57035","57035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657206","2016-12-14","Department for International Development","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans her Department has to include worker representation on its departmental board.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57013","57013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657207","2016-12-14","Department for International Development","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the highest-paid and lowest-paid full-time employee in her Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56991","56991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657208","2016-12-14","Department for International Development","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what measures her Department has in place to support those of its staff who have mental health problems.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57128","57128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657209","2016-12-14","Department for International Development","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what progress has been made on plans to improve nutrition-specific programmes in low and middle-income countries.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57092","57092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657210","2016-12-14","Department for International Development","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to support the Scaling Up Nutrition movement in its work on global malnutrition.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57094","57094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657211","2016-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the timetable is for the introduction of proposals for a British Bill of Rights.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56978","56978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657212","2016-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any member of the (a) National Tactical Response Group and (b) Tornado Team has been injured during a call-out in the last two years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57182","57182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657213","2016-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on how many occasions the (a) National Tactical Response Group and (b) Tornado Team have been called out to prisons in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57183","57183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657214","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of searches of (a) prison staff and (b) visitors when entering prisons on reducing the number of prohibited items being brought into prisons.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57129","57129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657215","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of current controls of mobile telephones in prisons.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57130","57130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657216","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what measures her Department has in place to support those of its staff who have mental health problems.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57124","57124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657217","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if her Department will publish all correspondence her and her predecessor had with (a) Hull City Council, (b) the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North and (c) constituent Tina Trowhill on baby ashes and cremation working practices.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57201","57201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657219","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people attempted to access legal aid and were declined in Wansbeck constituency in the last three years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57191","57191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657220","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the highest-paid and lowest-paid full-time employee in her Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56993","56993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657221","2016-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many extra days imprisonment have been given to prisoners for assaults committed on (a) fellow prisoners and (b) prison staff in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56955","56955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657222","2016-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many weapons have been confiscated in prisons in each year since 2010; and what (a) number and (b) proportion of such weapons were firearms.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56956","56956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657223","2016-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people in each prison in England and Wales have been accommodated in cells designed for (a) one person but occupied by two and (b) two people but occupied by three in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56954","56954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657224","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans her Department has to include worker representation on its departmental board.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57015","57015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657225","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the pay of full-time staff in the highest pay grade in her Department and average full-time pay in that Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57037","57037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657226","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of exonerating rather than pardoning gay and bisexual men convicted of now-abolished sexual offences; and if she will bring forward legislative proposals to exonerate gay and bisexual men of such offences.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57047","57047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657228","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many public interest transfers for each grade of staff have been approved within NOMS since January 2012; and what the cost was of those transfers.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57234","57234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657229","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total cost has been of capped public interest transfers to HM Prison Berwyn; and how many staff of each grade have been involved in such moves.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57235","57235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657230","2016-12-15","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisons in each category are (a) fitted and (b) not fitted with netting on outdoor areas to restrict drone access; and what other anti-drone techniques are being trialled in prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57249","57249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657231","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department holds a record of the meeting held by the then Secretary of State for Justice with the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North and constituent Tina Trowhill on 22 February 2016 on baby ashes and cremation working practices.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57202","57202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657232","2016-12-14","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether a civil servant was in attendance at the meeting held by the then Secretary of State for Justice with the hon. Member for Kingston upon Hull North and constituent Tina Trowhill on 22 February 2016 on baby ashes and cremation working practices.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57203","57203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657234","2016-12-14","Northern Ireland Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions his Department has had with the Irish government on the rights of Irish citizens in Northern Ireland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57282","57282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657235","2016-12-14","Northern Ireland Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the pay of full-time staff in the highest pay grade in his Department and average full-time pay in that Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57038","57038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657236","2016-12-14","Northern Ireland Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what plans his Department has to include worker representation on its departmental board.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57016","57016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657237","2016-12-14","Northern Ireland Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the highest-paid and lowest-paid full-time employee in his Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56994","56994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657238","2016-12-14","Northern Ireland Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what measures his Department has in place to support those of its staff who have mental health problems.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57137","57137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657239","2016-12-14","Northern Ireland Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what his policy is on maintaining the Common Travel Area border between the UK and the Republic of Ireland following the UK leaving the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57207","57207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657240","2016-12-14","Cabinet Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the highest-paid and lowest-paid full-time employee in 10 Downing Street.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56995","56995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657241","2016-12-14","Cabinet Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans 10 Downing Street has to include worker representation on its departmental board.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57017","57017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657242","2016-12-14","Cabinet Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the pay of full-time staff in the highest pay grade in 10 Downing Street and average full-time pay in that Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57039","57039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657243","2016-12-14","Scotland Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the pay of full-time staff in the highest pay grade in his Department and average full-time pay in that Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57040","57040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657244","2016-12-14","Scotland Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what plans his Department has to include worker representation on its departmental board.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57018","57018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657245","2016-12-14","Scotland Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the highest-paid and lowest-paid full-time employee in his Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56996","56996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657246","2016-12-15","Scotland Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what steps are being taken to secure the future of Gaelic broadcasting; and what discussions he plans to have with the BBC in ensuring the new BBC Charter delivers additional new programme investment into Gaelic television.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57238","57238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657247","2016-12-19","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce his final decision on implementing changes to the exemption from compulsory annual roadworthiness testing for vehicles of historic interest; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57251","57251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657248","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 56154, which local authorities have received funding allocated in the Autumn Statement 2016 from the Pothole Action Fund; and how much each such local authority has received.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57163","57163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657249","2016-12-15","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will introduce a formula to reduce rail ticket prices across the strike-affected southern region until normal service is resumed.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57223","57223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657250","2016-12-15","HM Treasury","2016-12-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any funding shortfall for the South Wales Metro resulting from the UK leaving the EU will be made up by the Government.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57224","57224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657251","2016-12-15","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 December 2016 to Question 56574, on Volkswagen, whether that payment will be made by 25 December 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57292","57292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657252","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the highest-paid and lowest-paid full-time employee in his Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56997","56997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657254","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to include worker representation on its departmental board.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57019","57019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657255","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the pay of full-time staff in the highest pay grade in his Department and average full-time pay in that Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57041","57041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657256","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will hold discussions with Govia Thameslink Railway on the action it might take to mitigate the financial effect on retail outlets in train stations of industrial action by employees of Southern Rail.","Biography information for Jeremy Quin","Jeremy Quin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56968","56968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657257","2016-12-15","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with coach and bus companies on provision of alternative routes for commuters living in Worthing during industrial action on the Southern rail line.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56944","56944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657258","2016-12-15","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with coach and bus companies on mitigating the effects of industrial action on the Southern rail line.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56947","56947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657259","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the devolved administrations on the modernisation of UK airspace.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56931","56931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657260","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the aviation industry on the Government's agenda for airspace modernisation.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56932","56932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657261","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much from the public purse is allocated to rail electrification in each NUTS 1 region of the country in each of the next five years; and how many miles of track are to be electrified in each such region in each such year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57210","57210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657262","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what measures his Department has in place to support those of its staff who have mental health problems.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57138","57138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657263","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57158","57158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657264","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much he plans to invest in the North East of England's highways to improve roads and to carry out essential maintenance up to 2020.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57194","57194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657265","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what reports he has received on Southern trains (a) being taken out of service and (b) skipping stations or suffering delays due to cameras on driver-only operation trains failing.","Biography information for Jeremy Quin","Jeremy Quin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56969","56969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657266","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the environmental benefits of modernising the UK's airspace.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57091","57091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657267","2016-12-14","Wales Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57159","57159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657268","2016-12-15","Wales Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department has spent on Christmas functions for hon. Members and Ministers in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56952","56952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657269","2016-12-15","Wales Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department plans to spend on Christmas functions for hon. Members and Ministers in 2016.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56953","56953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657270","2016-12-15","Wales Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on Christmas functions in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56957","56957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657271","2016-12-15","Wales Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department plans to spend on Christmas functions in 2016.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56958","56958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657272","2016-12-14","Wales Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what plans his Department has to include worker representation on its departmental board.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57021","57021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657273","2016-12-14","Wales Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the pay of full-time staff in the highest pay grade in his Department and average full-time pay in that Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57043","57043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657274","2016-12-14","Wales Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the highest-paid and lowest-paid full-time employee in his Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56999","56999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657275","2016-12-15","Women and Equalities","2016-12-12","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many civil servants worked in the Government Equalities Office in each of the last five years by grade; and how many at each grade were (a) women, (b) BAME and (c) disabled.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57185","57185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657276","2016-12-15","Women and Equalities","2016-12-12","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether there is an annual survey of staff in the (a) Government Equalities Office and (b) Equality and Human Rights Commission.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57244","57244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657277","2016-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which companies or organisations (a) hold and (b) own the lease for each of the 16 jobcentres in Glasgow; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57273","57273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657278","2016-12-14","HM Treasury","2016-12-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Written Statement of 14 November 2016, HCWS251, update on HM Revenue and Customs' contract with Concentrix, of those Mandatory Considerations against Concentrix tax credit decisions that are still outstanding, what the dates were on which the cases relating to those decisions were first lodged; and what the date was when the case longest awaiting consideration was lodged.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57162","57162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657279","2016-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an estimate of the number of people aged under 21 who will be affected by the planned removal of the housing benefit element of universal credit who have a mental health issue.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57250","57250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657280","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been sanctioned by his Department in (a) Wansbeck constituency, (b) the North East of England and (c) the UK in the last (i) six months and (ii) three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57281","57281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657281","2016-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the (a) number of people aged under 21 who will be affected by and (b) effect on the level homelessness of the planned removal of the housing benefit element of universal credit.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57290","57290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657282","2016-12-14","Department for Education","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to bring into force the parts of section 36 and Schedule 4 of the Equality Act 2010 that would enable residents to secure disability related alterations to the physical features of the common parts of let residential premises or premises owned on a commonhold basis; what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on that issue; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57146","57146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657283","2016-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2016 to Question 55249, by what date the Government anticipates that the Real Time Information function of universal credit will make it possible to track claimant earnings.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57078","57078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657284","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of future changes to housing benefit for claimants under 21 years of age on (a) claimants' labour mobility and (b) the wider economy.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57084","57084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657285","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57160","57160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657286","2016-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the monthly average response time was for calls to universal credit helplines in each year since the introduction of that credit; what the longest response time was in that period; how many such calls were recorded as abandoned; and how many complaints about response times for those helplines were made in that period.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57177","57177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657287","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what measures his Department has in place to support those of its staff who have mental health problems.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57139","57139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657288","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disability living allowance claimants in (a) Wansbeck constituency, (b) North East England and (c) the UK who have reapplied for personal independence payment have been unsuccessful in their applications.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57186","57186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657290","2016-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have used the services of jobcentre offices in (a) the UK, (b) Greater London, (c) the London Borough of Newham and (d) East Ham constituency in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57170","57170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657291","2016-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether British citizens returning from a period living in another EU country are fully entitled immediately to receive (a) NHS treatment, (b) access to public funds and (c) a full state pension.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57171","57171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657292","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, following changes to the weekly support for new work-related activity group (WRAG) claimants on employment support allowance effective from April 2017, whether any pre-April 2017 WRAG claimants will receive the lower weekly payment if they are re-assessed as still being in the WRAG following the end of their review period.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57149","57149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657293","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the highest-paid and lowest-paid full-time employee in his Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57000","57000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657294","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the pay of full-time staff in the highest pay grade in his Department and average full-time pay in that Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57044","57044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657295","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to include worker representation on its departmental board.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57022","57022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657296","2016-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, who owns the (a) Langside, (b) Castlemilk and (c) Newlands Jobcentre Plus offices.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57075","57075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657297","2016-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time equivalent staff currently work in the Child Poverty Unit.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57065","57065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657298","2016-12-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2016 to Question 55878, on social security benefits: children, whether his Department discussed that matter with the Public and Commercial Services trade union.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56948","56948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657299","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 December 2016 to Question 55878, on social security benefits: children, whether his Department discussed that matter with Unison.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56937","56937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657300","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make an assessment of the extent to which the recommendations of the report by the Executive Office of the President's National Science and Technology Council Committee on Technology, entitled Preparing for the future of artificial intelligence, published in October 2016, apply to the UK.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56940","56940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657301","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the highest-paid and lowest-paid full-time employee in his Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56979","56979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657302","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has to include worker representation on its departmental board.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57001","57001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657303","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the pay of full-time staff in the highest pay grade in his Department and average full-time pay in that Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57023","57023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657304","2016-12-15","HM Treasury","2016-12-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect changes in the value of sterling on export businesses since the referendum.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56972","56972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657305","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations he has received on the Government's decision to cancel the carbon capture and storage competition.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57067","57067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657306","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent representations he has received on the potential removal of coal-powered electricity generation from the UK's energy mix.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57068","57068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657307","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the public investment needed to maintain the UK's energy capacity in the next 20 years.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57069","57069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657308","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much he plans to financially invest in the steel industry in the UK in the next three years; and what plans he has to support steel workers.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57189","57189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657309","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people are classified as fuel poor in (a) Wansbeck constituency, (b) North East England and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57200","57200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657310","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what measures his Department has in place to support those of its staff who have mental health problems.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57220","57220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657311","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many people are registered as using a pre-payment meter to access their electricity and other utilities in (a) Wansbeck constituency, (b) the North East and (c) nationally.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57085","57085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657312","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he has taken to advance the green economy since his Department was established.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57076","57076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657313","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he had with Dame Julia Slingo in advance of her standing down from the Scientific Advice Mechanism High-Level Group of the European Commission; and what steps he has taken to replace her with another UK scientist.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57113","57113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657314","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether it is his Department's policy to increase the number of policy-making civil servants based outside London.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57184","57184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657315","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's policy is on underground coal gasification.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57181","57181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657316","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the European Commission on appointing a UK scientist to the Scientific Advice Mechanism High Level Group; and whether he plans to seek such an appointment before the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57180","57180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657317","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of (a) the Senior Civil Service and (b) policy-making civil servants in his Department are based in London.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57289","57289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657318","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many civil service apprentices have been appointed by his Department since it was created.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57283","57283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657319","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to (a) expedite the Government's application to the European Commission to exempt energy-intensive industries from the indirect costs of the Renewables Obligation and small-scale Feed-in Tariffs and (b) ensure that legislation on that exemption is in place before financial year 2017-18.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57227","57227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657320","2016-12-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what (a) mechanisms and (b) monitoring systems are in place to ensure that fuel pumps at filling stations deliver the correct amount of fuel so that motorists are not defrauded whether accidently or deliberately.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57252","57252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657321","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to secure contingency funding for the continuation of compensation for the indirect costs of the Renewables Obligation and small-scale Feed-in Tariffs for (a) the steel industry and (b) other energy-intensive industries beyond April 2017.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57226","57226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657322","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to outline his Department's strategy for promoting the use of sustainable and efficient energy measures in residential homes.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57241","57241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657323","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many complaints have been received on breaches of the Overseas Companies Regulations 2009 by overseas companies; and how many such complaints resulted in (a) compliance or (b) prosecution.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57242","57242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657324","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many interns are currently working in his Department; at what rate those interns are paid; and what the maximum length of an internship is.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57243","57243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657325","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of Innovate UK on (a) investment, (b) job creation and (c) the economy.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57264","57264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657326","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what redundancy schemes his Department is currently operating.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57232","57232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657327","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many civil servants in each unit of his Department are in the redeployment pool.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57233","57233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657328","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what Innovate UK's budget (a) was in each of the last five financial years and (b) will be in each of the next four financial years.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57263","57263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657329","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has for the future staffing of the Advisory, Conciliation and Arbitration Service.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57267","57267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657330","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what public appointments he has made in 2016.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57268","57268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657331","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his plans are for the future of UK Shared Business Services Ltd; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57265","57265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657332","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what annual staff surveys are carried out at the (a) Competition and Markets Authority, (b) Land Registry and (c) Ordnance Survey; and if he will place the results of each of those surveys in the Library.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57266","57266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657333","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the cost of using external agencies for recruitment of senior civil service posts in (a) his Department, (b) the former Department for Business, Innovation and Skills and (c) the former Department for Energy and Climate Change in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57260","57260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657334","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the location is of each office from which his Department operates; and which of those offices are planned for closure.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57277","57277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657335","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much (a) his Department, (b) the former Department for Business, Innovation and Skills and (c) the former Department for Energy and Climate Change spent on non-payroll staff in (i) 2015 and (ii) 2016.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57258","57258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657336","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many non-payroll staff are employed by his Department; and how many such staff were employed by the former Department for (a) Business, Innovation and Skills and (b) Energy and Climate Change in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57259","57259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657337","2016-12-15","HM Treasury","2016-12-12","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.36 of the Autumn Statement 2016, what budget has been allocated to the advisory panel on Patient Capital; and whether members of that panel will receive a wage or expenses.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57278","57278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657338","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the planned efficiency savings from his Department's administrative budget are in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57274","57274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657339","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many civil servants his Department employs; and how many such staff his Department plans to employ in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57275","57275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657340","2016-12-14","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate his Department has made of the level of exports from the UK in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57270","57270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657341","2016-12-14","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many bilateral trade deals he estimates the UK will sign by 2020.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57236","57236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657342","2016-12-15","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will make it his policy to prioritise a free trade agreement with (a) Israel and (b) the Palestinian Authority after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57291","57291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657344","2016-12-14","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of investor-state dispute settlement measures in supporting growth in international trade.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57190","57190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657345","2016-12-14","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many additional staff his Department plans to recruit in the next (a) year and (b) three years.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57133","57133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657346","2016-12-14","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential costs and benefits for the UK of membership of the European Free Trade Association; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57208","57208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657347","2016-12-14","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the pay of full-time staff in the highest pay grade in his Department and average full-time pay in that Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57036","57036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657348","2016-12-14","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans his Department has to include worker representation on its departmental board.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57014","57014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657349","2016-12-15","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of policy-making civil servants in his Department is based in London.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56960","56960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657351","2016-12-14","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the highest-paid and lowest-paid full-time employee in his Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56992","56992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657352","2016-12-15","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of the 26 million, referred to in paragraph 3.34 of the Autumn Statement 2016, to recruit additional policy staff to support international trade issues will be allocated to his Department.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56943","56943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657353","2016-12-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans his Department has to include worker representation on its departmental board.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57009","57009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657354","2016-12-15","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what proportion of policy making civil servants in his Department is based in London.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56959","56959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657355","2016-12-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the highest-paid and lowest-paid full-time employee in his Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56987","56987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657356","2016-12-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the percentage gap in earnings is between the pay of full-time staff in the highest pay grade in his Department and average full-time pay in that Department.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57031","57031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657358","2016-12-15","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the hourly rate is for employing additional non-governmental legal support for the court case R (Miller) v the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, relating to Article 50.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56974","56974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657359","2016-12-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, in what format and by what date he plans to publish his Department's plan for the UK's negotiations on exiting the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57211","57211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657360","2016-12-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of the UK remaining a member of the European Economic Area.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57213","57213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657361","2016-12-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what preparations his Department is making for the coordination with EU member states of efforts to tackle climate change after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57172","57172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657362","2016-12-15","Home Office","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what preparations her Department is making for the coordination of efforts with EU member states to support Syrian refugees after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57173","57173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657363","2016-12-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what measures his Department has in place to support those of its staff who have mental health problems.","Biography information for Helen Whately","Helen Whately","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57141","57141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657364","2016-12-15","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 24 November 2016 to Question 53514, on Brexit, what the cost to the public purse has been to date of the (a) Government's appeal to the Supreme Court on triggering Article 50 and (b) the court case R (Miller) v the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, relating to Article 50.","Biography information for Jenny Chapman","Jenny Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56975","56975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657365","2016-12-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether it is his policy to negotiate a transitional agreement with the EU so that existing trading arrangements for UK companies will be able to continue beyond 1 April 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 57205","57205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657824","2016-12-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to protect the UK's cultural heritage.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907916","907916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/658050","2016-12-15","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the level of SME business interest in the great.gov.uk digital platform.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907898","907898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/658052","2016-12-15","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU customs union on levels of employment.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907890","907890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/658053","2016-12-15","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether it is his policy to retain preferential access to the EU single market by continuing to make financial contributions to the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907900","907900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/658055","2016-12-15","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether it is his policy to retain preferential access to the EU single market by continuing to make financial contributions to the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907892","907892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/659402","2016-12-15","Department for International Trade","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to ensure that UK trade and investment agreements protect human rights.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907899","907899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/659403","2016-12-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support the future of Gaelic broadcasting.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907926","907926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/659404","2016-12-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on supporting Local Charities Day 2016.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907922","907922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/659405","2016-12-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions her Department has had with football authorities on tax avoidance by football clubs, managers and players.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907921","907921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/659406","2016-12-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to provide financial support for library provision.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907923","907923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/659407","2016-12-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps the Government is taking to support people affected by allegations of sexual abuse in football.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907925","907925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655671","2016-12-13","HM Treasury","2016-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what processes are required before the UK ratifies the World Health Organisation Protocol to Eliminate Illicit Trade in Tobacco Products.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56889","56889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655672","2016-12-13","HM Treasury","2016-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations the Government has received on the ratification of the World Health Organisation Protocol to Eliminate Illicit Trade in Tobacco Products.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56890","56890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655673","2016-12-13","HM Treasury","2016-12-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions the Government has had with the tobacco industry on the ratification of the World Health Organisation Protocol to Eliminate Illicit Trade in Tobacco Products.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56891","56891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655674","2016-12-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what mechanisms there are to ensure local authorities meet the required number of Travellers' sites in each local authority area.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56886","56886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655675","2016-12-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of local authority Travellers' sites that will be required in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56884","56884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655676","2016-12-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of Travellers' sites that are required in each local authority area.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56885","56885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655677","2016-12-13","Department of Health","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's budget was for dementia training for homecare workers in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56899","56899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655678","2016-12-13","Department of Health","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on dementia training for homecare workers in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56900","56900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655679","2016-12-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2016 to Question 50216, when he plans to provide a full reply to that Question.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56904","56904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655680","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her will make an assessment of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on funding for specialist women's services.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56927","56927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655681","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many times she has met (a) StubHub, (b) Viagogo, (c) Seatwave, (d) GetMeIn! and (e) representatives of each of those companies since her appointment as Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56921","56921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655682","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, who attended and from which organisations her Department's roundtable on the secondary market on 30 November 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56920","56920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655683","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what safeguards are in place to ensure that data held under the Investigatory Powers Act 2016 is secure; and what discussions she has had with internet service providers on that matter.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56901","56901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655684","2016-12-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, where the hon. Member for Berwickshire, Roxburgh and Selkirk can find reference to the consultation for a new voucher scheme for broadband which the Minister for Digital and Culture stated had been announced in the Autumn Statement 2016 in his oral contributions of 28 November 2016.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56913","56913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655685","2016-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the level of unemployment of former armed service personnel.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56922","56922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655686","2016-12-14","Department for Education","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has spent on evaluation studies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56914","56914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655687","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will require all universities in the UK to publish regular remuneration reports.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56874","56874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655688","2016-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the peace process in Papua New Guinea.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56887","56887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655689","2016-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to help resolve the frozen conflict in Trans-Dneister.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56878","56878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655690","2016-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance his Department provides towards helping the peace process in the Mano River region.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56879","56879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655691","2016-12-13","Department of Health","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on recruitment for a new paediatric neuromuscular consultant post at Birmingham Heartlands Hospital.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56867","56867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655692","2016-12-14","Department of Health","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the autism referral to treatment pathway announced in the Five Year Forward View on Mental Health is being developed; and for what reasons it was not included in NHS England's implementation plan for the Five Year Forward View.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56882","56882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655693","2016-12-14","Department of Health","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of changes in social care budgets on the length of time that older people spend in hospital.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56906","56906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655694","2016-12-14","Department of Health","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the morale of the NHS workforce.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56907","56907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655695","2016-12-14","Department of Health","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the changes in the cost of funded nursing care on the budgets of community care groups.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56902","56902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655696","2016-12-14","Department of Health","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the changes in the cost of funded nursing care on the commissioning decisions made by community care groups.","Biography information for Anne Marie Morris","Anne Marie Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56903","56903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655697","2016-12-13","Department of Health","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016 to Question 55157, how his Department plans to ensure that progress will be regularly and transparently monitored on the food industry's reduction of sugar in its products; who will be responsible for conducting such monitoring; and how and at what frequency the public will be made aware of the outcome of such monitoring.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56919","56919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655698","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Oral Answer of 5 December 2016, Official Report, column 4, on documentation relating to EU nationals resident in the UK, what options she is considering for that documentation; and what the estimated costs are of those options.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56918","56918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655699","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her European counterparts on strengthening EU-wide border controls, coast guard provision and asylum systems in order to treat people arriving in Europe swiftly and with due diligence on account of EU legislation.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56925","56925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655700","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the emergency services network masts will be designed and built to provide multi-occupancy sites from all four mobile network operators.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56909","56909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655701","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many emergency services masts are planned for construction in Berwickshire, Roxburgh and Selkirk constituency; and what steps she is taking to ensure that mobile phone services are provided from all four mobile network operators at emergency services network sites.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56911","56911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655702","2016-12-14","Home Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether geographic location data for the emergency services network sites built by (a) the Government and (b) EE will be published.","Biography information for Calum Kerr","Calum Kerr","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56912","56912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655703","2016-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance is issued to the Crown Prosecution Service and Crown Court judges on sentences for the offence of public nuisance; and how many guilty verdicts in such cases have led to custodial sentences in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56873","56873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655704","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions the Government had with the Scottish Government on proposals to require schools to carry out immigration checks and to propose changes to the prioritisation of illegal migrants in the school admissions process before the introduction of the Immigration Bill 2015-16.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56897","56897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655705","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2016 to Question 54294, what assessment she has made of whether the criteria for advanced security checks for the Registered Traveller Service are compatible with the Government's obligations under international law.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56868","56868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655706","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2016 to Question 54294, what criteria in advanced security checks allow the Border Force to assess whether an applicant is suitable to join or remain in the Registered Traveller Service.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56869","56869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655707","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2016 to Question 54294, whether the advanced security checks for the Registered Traveller Service include an assessment of whether the applicant has acted or has contributed to actions in contravention of the Geneva Convention or the Hague regulations.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56870","56870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655708","2016-12-14","House of Commons Commission","2016-12-09","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what discussions the Commission has had on providing hon. Members' staff based on the parliamentary estate and visitors with facilities to donate toiletries and non-perishable food to a food bank at the Palace of Westminster; whether plans are in place to provide such donation points; what facilities there are to donate surplus food from the parliamentary estate to foodbanks and other charities; and how much food was sent from the parliamentary estate to landfill in 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56880","56880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655709","2016-12-13","Department for International Trade","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help improve trade with Moldova.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56876","56876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655710","2016-12-13","Department for International Trade","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to help improve trade with Ukraine.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56877","56877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655711","2016-12-13","Department for International Development","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to prioritise projects that will provide electricity in countries that have limited access to electricity supply.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56928","56928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655712","2016-12-13","Department for International Development","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate her Department has made of the amount of research carried out into paediatric formulations of antiretrovirals within the pharmaceutical sector in developing countries; and if her Department plans to incentivise research into that area.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56929","56929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655713","2016-12-14","Scotland Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on planned jobcentre closures in Glasgow.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56910","56910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655714","2016-12-14","Scotland Office","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he was made aware of the proposed jobcentre closures in Glasgow that are planned for 2018 prior to the announcement of such closures on 7 December 2016.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56916","56916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655715","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the deficit is for the delivery of the Croxley rail link; and what plans his Department has for allocating additional funding required for that rail link.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56923","56923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655716","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information the Government holds on Transport for London's deficit for the delivery of the Croxley rail link; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56924","56924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655717","2016-12-14","Department for Transport","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the annual maintenance cost was of the Severn Bridges in the last year for which statistics are available; and how many toll paying vehicles in each vehicle category crossed the bridges in that year.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56881","56881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655718","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the economic effect on the (a) South West region and (b) UK of the lack of new rolling stock available to train companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56866","56866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655719","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the findings of the National Audit Office's report, Benefit sanctions, published on 30 November 2016, what plans he has to review or consult on the benefits sanction system.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56908","56908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655720","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on evaluation studies in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56915","56915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655721","2016-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what research his Department has conducted on the health effects on claimants of the imposition of benefit sanctions and the processes related to the mandatory reconsideration and appeal of such sanctions.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56883","56883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655722","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have used the services of jobcentre offices in each of the last five years in (a) Aberdeen, (b) Dundee, (c) Edinburgh, (d) Glasgow, (e) Inverness, (f) Perth, (g) Stirling, (h) Cardiff, (i) London, (j) Scotland, (k) England, (l) Wales and (m) the UK.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56917","56917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655723","2016-12-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 December 2016 to Question 56075, on pre-school education, how much funding his Department provided to the Early Years Intervention Foundation in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56896","56896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655724","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how his Department monitors the effect on existing commercial innovation facilities after an award of public funding has been made for new innovation facilities.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56926","56926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655725","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the effect on small businesses of the licensing enforcement regime for the use of music in public spaces.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56888","56888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655726","2016-12-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the evidential basis is for the Pubs Code Adjudicator's statement on the ITV documentary, The Great British Pub Revolution, screened on 8 December 2016, that many of the tenants he has met are supportive of him in his role.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56905","56905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655727","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make it her policy to exempt children's play centres from licensing requirements for the use of music.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56872","56872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655728","2016-12-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to consult on the recommendations of the Hendry review into tidal lagoons before a decision on the future development of such lagoons is taken.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56898","56898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655729","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures the Government plans to introduce to regulate pay increases granted by internal remuneration bodies to Chancellors and Vice Chancellors of universities.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56875","56875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655730","2016-12-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the proportion of known fossil fuels which need to be left in the ground to prevent global temperature change above two degrees centigrade.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56871","56871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655731","2016-12-14","Department for International Trade","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the average number of hours worked by civil servants in his Department since it was created; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56892","56892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655732","2016-12-14","Department for International Trade","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many employees in his Department have opted out of the EU working time directive; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56893","56893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655733","2016-12-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the average number of hours worked by civil servants in his Department since it was created; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56894","56894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/655734","2016-12-14","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many employees in his Department have opted out of the EU working time directive; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56895","56895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654780","2016-12-13","Attorney General","2016-12-08","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the charges for Government Car Services supplied ministerial cars between 2012 and 2015, published on 17 December 2017, what the (a) purpose, (b) distance travelled and (c) cost was of each journey booked by his Office.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56816","56816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654781","2016-12-13","HM Treasury","2016-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many additional staff have been allocated to assist with the implementation of the new EU Customs Code which was introduced on 1 May 2016.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56725","56725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654782","2016-12-13","HM Treasury","2016-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether it is his policy that 0.7 per cent of gross national income is the maximum amount to be allocated to overseas development assistance.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56726","56726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654783","2016-12-13","HM Treasury","2016-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many applications made pursuant to the implementation of the new EU Customs Code have been processed.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56733","56733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654784","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an assessment of the effect on (a) per capita GDP and (b) overall productivity of changes in the migrant share of the adult population.","Biography information for John Penrose","John Penrose","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56709","56709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654785","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many amateur sports clubs have lost their community amateur sports club status since 2002.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56712","56712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654786","2016-12-13","HM Treasury","2016-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what costs (a) have and (b) will accrue to the public purse as a result of the 2012 Franked Investment income judgment.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56757","56757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654787","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the Government has had to pay in tax rebates since the 2012 Franked Investment Income judgment.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56743","56743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654788","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Autumn Statement 2016, paragraph 5.14, how much of the 102 million support for armed forces and emergency services charities and other related good causes has been allocated to (a) facilities based at Ministry of Defence sites, (b) charities and organisations affiliated to the Ministry of Defence and (c) official Ministry of Defence-run charities and events.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56783","56783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654789","2016-12-13","HM Treasury","2016-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of Shell's sale of its North Sea field assets on the sustainability of UK jobs in that area.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56830","56830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654790","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.22 in the Autumn Statement 2016, whether he will make an announcement on the future of the Levy Control Framework in (a) the Spring Budget 2017 or (b) the Autumn Budget 2017.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56845","56845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654791","2016-12-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to publish the outcomes of his Department's consultation on Council Tax collection which closed in November 2015.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56835","56835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654792","2016-12-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many young people have received assistance from the Government's Help to Buy scheme in (a) the UK, (b) Greater London, (c) the London Borough of Newham and (d) East Ham constituency.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56836","56836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654793","2016-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister of State for Europe and the Americas of 17 November 2016, Official Report, column 387, what proportion of the 837 Chagossian people surveyed indicated that they wished to reside on the  Chagos islands before they were asked to take into consideration what life would be like on those islands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56763","56763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654794","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the health benefits of retirement housing and its potential in reducing local authority adult social care bills.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56754","56754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654795","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many meetings she has held with the UK Information Commissioner since her appointment.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56720","56720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654796","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made recent representations to the South Korean government on implications of the South Korean dog meat trade for countries due to participate in the next Winter Olympics.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56711","56711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654797","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2016 to Question 55347, on sports: equality, if she will promote the application of similar measures more generally throughout sport to address diversity at the top.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56803","56803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654798","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to support and promote the recommendations of the Parker Review on increasing the ethnic diversity of UK boards in appointments for which her Department is responsible.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56865","56865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654799","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department proposed candidates to Ofcom for vacant Channel 4 non-executive director posts in 2016.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56858","56858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654800","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, for what reason she rejected the appointment of Althea Efunshile as a non-executive director of Channel 4.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56859","56859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654801","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what account she took of the diversity of public appointments in her decision relating to the approval of Ofcom's candidates for vacant Channel 4  non-executive director posts.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56860","56860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654802","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many candidates for vacant Channel 4 non-executive director posts her Department has discussed the appointment process for those roles with on what dates in 2016.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56861","56861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654803","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many candidates for vacant Channel 4 non-executive director posts were interviewed by Ministers of her Department on what dates in 2016.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56862","56862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654804","2016-12-13","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with the Secretary of State for Education on including the subject of cyber resilience in the teaching of ICT in schools.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56828","56828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654805","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that housing benefit data is used by local authorities in England to identify and automatically register all children eligible for free school meals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56826","56826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654806","2016-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many letters his Department has sent in the last two years asking soldiers to come forward with any information that could help the Police Service of Northern Ireland in its historical investigations.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56837","56837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654807","2016-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Royal Navy submarines are due to be scrapped; and for how long those submarines have been decommissioned.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56838","56838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654808","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether it remains the Government's policy to restrict army applicants aged under 16 years and six months from enlisting for frontline combat and driving roles.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56737","56737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654809","2016-12-13","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent meetings he has held as part of his Department's review into the Government's policy on compensation for war widows who re-married between 1973 and 2005.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56722","56722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654811","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the process is for appointing the advisory panel of apprentices for the Institute for Apprenticeships and Technical Education; and how she plans to ensure that that panel's membership is drawn from different occupations, backgrounds and areas of the country.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56724","56724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654812","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans any office closures for her Department or its departmental agencies.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56731","56731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654813","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many civil servants are based at each office location in which her Department employs staff.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56732","56732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654814","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which locations her Department is assessing the potential merits of for the Institute of Apprentices.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56758","56758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654815","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government plans to take to protect state maintained schools in Bristol West from the effect on their budgets of rising (a) staff and (b) other costs and real-terms funding reductions in 2016-17 and in 2017-18.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56753","56753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654816","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for her policies on those units and agencies that were formally the responsibility of the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills of the recommendations in the McKinsey & Company BIS 2020 report.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56762","56762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654817","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to identify further actions the Government will take to ensure all children and young people have access to Sex and Relationships Education.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56782","56782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654818","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 1.102 of Budget 2016, what the planned timescale is for the review of Lifelong Learning.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56769","56769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654819","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many international students have been enrolled on (a) STEM and (b) Vocational Education and Training courses in each year since 2012; and how many such students took part in training or work placements as part of their course.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56770","56770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654820","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the number of (a) Russell Group graduates and (b) graduates with a first class degree working in (i) secondary schools and (ii) sixth form colleges in deprived communities.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56815","56815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654821","2016-12-13","Department for Education","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the provision of (a) health and nutrition advice and (b) personal finance advice in schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56818","56818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654822","2016-12-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) the process is and (b) permissions required are for a reservoir to be drained.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56819","56819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654823","2016-12-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of each of the 11 million trees the Government has committed it will plant in this Parliament.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56810","56810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654824","2016-12-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2016 to Question 40357, what progress has been made on the implementation of the protocol allowing pig trotters to be exported from the UK to China.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56814","56814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654825","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much cattle feed has been imported to the UK in the last five years; what proportion of the total amount was soya products; and from which countries those imports came.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56839","56839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654826","2016-12-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to ensure that the Groceries Adjudicator can take evidence of alleged breaches of the supermarket code from all producers and not just from the suppliers of supermarkets.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56817","56817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654827","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much British-grown wheat, of each grade type was (a) exported and (b) to which countries in the past five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56848","56848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654828","2016-12-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the main reasons were for non-payment of Basic Farm Payments to those who made claims that resulted in no payment in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56792","56792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654829","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff her Department has recruited in each month of 2016.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56748","56748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654830","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff are seconded to her Department from other companies or organisations; and from which organisations and companies they have been seconded.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56749","56749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654831","2016-12-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take further steps to prevent the sale of underage kittens.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56717","56717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654832","2016-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will hold discussions with the Azerbaijan authorities on recent reports of the persecution, arrest and fining of Christians in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56715","56715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654833","2016-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the authorities in Uzbekistan on reports of the prosecution of Christians and confiscation of religious material in that country.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56716","56716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654834","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will hold discussions with the South Korean authorities on transparency in dealing with allegations of corruption.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56708","56708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654835","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the South Korean government on dog meat trade in that country.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56710","56710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654836","2016-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information he holds on the raid of the publications office of the Ahmadi Muslim community headquarters in Rabwah, Pakistan on 5 December 2016.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56697","56697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654837","2016-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Pakistan on the detention of three Ahmadi Muslims arrested in Rabwah, Pakistan on 5 December 2016.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56698","56698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654838","2016-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Pakistan on freedom of religion for Ahmadi Muslims in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56699","56699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654839","2016-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if his Department will make available English translations of all foreign language articles or interviews which he provides for non-UK media outlets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56764","56764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654840","2016-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the transition team of the President-elect of the US.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56772","56772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654841","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with its allies on establishing an area in eastern Syria that could be controlled by non-Assad democratic forces.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56840","56840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654842","2016-12-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of freedom of (a) religion and belief and (b) association in Iran; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56850","56850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654843","2016-12-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to answer Question 53905, tabled on 21 November 2016 by the hon. Member for Edinburgh East.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56813","56813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654844","2016-12-13","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many outpatient and community contacts there were in adult secondary mental health and learning disabilities services, by team type, attendance rate and clinical commissioning group, in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56791","56791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654845","2016-12-13","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions (a) Ministers And (b) officials of his Department have had with the Royal Free Hospital on its new Streams app.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56827","56827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654846","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the 20 million budget cap on the number of available cancer treatments.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56852","56852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654848","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the timetable for availability of molecular PIM1 on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56853","56853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654849","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 November 2016 to Question 54228, whether he intends to respond to the finding of Breast Cancer Now that three in four UK Breast cancer oncologists are unable to prescribe bisphosphonates due to funding issues and the lack of a clear commissioning pathway.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56864","56864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654850","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of regulation of the cosmetics industry.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56857","56857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654851","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues to NHS Trusts on making payments to third parties in connection with data sharing agreements; and whether any such guidance has been issued to the Royal Free Hospital.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56846","56846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654852","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions Ministers or officials in his Department have had with the Royal Free Hospital on safeguarding the confidentiality of patient information.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56847","56847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654853","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the NHS has made an assessment of the potential effect of spinal tap on increasing the mobility of wheelchair-bound patients.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56856","56856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654854","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with clinical bodies on the use of electronic pulse treatment to reduce abdominal pain and mitigate against the other effects of Crohn's disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56854","56854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654855","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with pharmaceutical companies on the price structuring of medicines they supply to the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56855","56855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654856","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to establish ways of encouraging BME organ donations.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56780","56780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654857","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the difference between BME organ donations and the level of demand for such donations.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56779","56779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654858","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish details of the linear programming model that informed the refreshing of the Eatwell Guide.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56781","56781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654859","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the new cervical screening database will be ready in time for the rollout of HPV primary screening.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56799","56799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654860","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to commission the next Infant Feeding Survey.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56800","56800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654861","2016-12-13","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016 to Question 55192, whether the development of evidence-based treatment pathways in community mental health care will be subject to public consultation.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56804","56804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654862","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve cervical screening coverage.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56801","56801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654863","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding Health Education England has received in each year since 2012; and how much has been allocated for 2020-21.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56795","56795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654864","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many NHS trusts employed the maximum possible number of nursing agency staff within the spending limits set for 2015-16; and how many have done so to date in 2016-17.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56796","56796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654865","2016-12-13","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016 to Question 55193, what national minimum standards exist to ensure the provision of psychological therapy in adult secondary and tertiary mental health services.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56802","56802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654866","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2016 to Question 43855, whether Public Health England plans to publish its report on the revision of the Eatwell Guide before the end of 2016.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56797","56797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654867","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the Government has to fund and run national awareness campaigns on cervical cancer prevention.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56798","56798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654868","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what research his Department has conducted on the ability of people awaiting joint replacement surgery to participate in exercise.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56742","56742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654869","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the decision of the Vale of York Clinical Commissioning Group's policy to postpone surgery for patients who smoke or have a BMI over 30.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56741","56741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654870","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the criteria are for NHS Improvement to intervene in the governance of  NHS trusts.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56740","56740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654871","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent reductions in funding for smoking cessation services on rates of smoking.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56735","56735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654872","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on recruitment for the new paediatric neuromuscular consultant post to be based at Birmingham Heartlands Hospital.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56747","56747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654873","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will instruct the Vale of York Clinical Commissioning Group to end its policy on postponing surgery for patients who smoke or have a BMI over 30.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56738","56738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654874","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle inappropriate use of the GP appointment request process.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56752","56752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654875","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the findings of the Care Quality Commission in its quality reports on the Leeds and York Partnership NHS Foundation Trust, published in November 2016, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of governance arrangements at that NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56739","56739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654876","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on the (a) forthcoming Housing White Paper and (b) delivery of retirement housing across all tenures.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56755","56755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654877","2016-12-13","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the quality of food provided in care homes.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56718","56718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654878","2016-12-13","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides on standards of nutritional value for food provided in care homes.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56719","56719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654879","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of additional resources required for proposed changes in NICE's processes to consider highly specialised technologies to take place.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56702","56702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654880","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that patients do not face delays in obtaining access to treatments for rare and ultra-rare diseases.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56703","56703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654881","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that proposed delays to NICE's process for highly specialised technologies will not delay access to treatments for rare and ultra-rare diseases.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56704","56704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654882","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of how many treatments will be delivered under the new highly specialised technologies process to be introduced shortly by NICE.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56705","56705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654883","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many treatments for rare and ultra-rare diseases that have received orphan designation as part of their regulatory license from the European Medicines Agency have qualified for NICE's highly specialised technologies evaluation.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56706","56706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654884","2016-12-12","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many treatments for rare and ultra-rare diseases that have received orphan designation as part of their regulatory license from the European Medicines Agency have qualified for NICE's single technology appraisal.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56707","56707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654886","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy to grant short-term pastoral visas to Christian church ministers from countries where their members are suffering persecution for their faith.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56713","56713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654887","2017-01-09","Home Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much each constabulary in the North West raised through police auctions in 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56721","56721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654888","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will direct HM Passport Office to design a passport with a blue cover.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56701","56701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654889","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether approval orders for breath test measuring devices are statutory instruments, subordinate to primary legislation.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56787","56787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654890","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the use of drones in connection with rural crime.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56771","56771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654891","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people her Department has had on record as having no recourse to public funds in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56820","56820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654892","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department has provided in respect of the Kajaki Dam project in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56849","56849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654893","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what programmes her Department has supported in the last five years to delivery electricity to developing countries; and which of those programmes provided outcomes that met the International Energy Agency definition of 250 kwh electricity for rural households and 500 kwh for urban households.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56844","56844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654894","2016-12-12","Department for International Development","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate she has made of the effectiveness and value for money of projects to provide energy to developing countries in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56842","56842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654895","2016-12-13","Department for International Development","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding her Department (a) has given in the last year and (b) plans to allocate in 2017 for the support of democracy and political governance; and how organisations can bid for such funding.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56790","56790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654896","2016-12-13","Department for International Development","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many days she has spent abroad on government business since her appointment.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56775","56775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654897","2016-12-13","Department for International Development","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2016 to Question 55212, how she will assess the (a) value for money and (b) performance; and by when decisions will be made on project cancellations in the 2017-18 financial year.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56776","56776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654898","2016-12-13","Department for International Development","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2016 to Question 55212, on what previous occasions the Overseas Development Assistance budget has been reduced since 2010.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56777","56777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654899","2016-12-13","Department for International Development","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what projects her Department has agreed to fund in the 2017-18 financial year; and what the budget is for such funding for that year.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56727","56727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654900","2016-12-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to fully implement section 67 of the Serious Crime Act 2015 relating to sexual communication with a child.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56756","56756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654902","2016-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many concerted indiscipline incidents of each type have occurred in each prison establishment in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56821","56821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654903","2016-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) children under 18 years of age and (b) young people aged 18 to 24 were granted legal funding under the Exceptional Case Funding Scheme in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56825","56825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654904","2016-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents involving the use of drone technology have been recorded at each type of prison facility in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56823","56823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654905","2016-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prison officers have taken long-term sick leave and for what reasons in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56824","56824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654906","2016-12-13","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisoners have been diagnosed with a (a) mental health problem and (b) substance or alcohol addiction in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56812","56812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654907","2016-12-13","Ministry of Justice","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many hostage incidents in which a (a) prison officer and (b) prisoner was taken hostage there have been in each prison establishment in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56822","56822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654908","2016-12-13","Department of Health","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prisoners are receiving treatment for a (a) mental health problem and (b) substance or alcohol addiction in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56811","56811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654909","2016-12-13","Northern Ireland Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether he plans to take steps to resolve the ownership of the waters and seabed of Lough Foyle before 1 April 2019.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56714","56714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654910","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will include the provision of four fast trains per hour between St Pancras and Luton Airport Parkway in his Department's consultation on the new East Midlands franchise.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56734","56734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654911","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to ensure that the East Anglia rail franchise has integrated operating teams between train services and infrastructure.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56700","56700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654913","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department has received from (a) the Mayor of London and (b) Transport of London on the cost of the Croxley rail link; and whether the Government plans to provide additional funding to support the development of that link.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56736","56736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654914","2016-12-12","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether (a) public and (b) Area of Outstanding Natural Beauty (AONB) consultations will be held on potential visually appropriate designs for the Great Western Mainline modernisation of overhead line equipment through AONB.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56784","56784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654915","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 December 2016 to Question 55070, which funds are potentially available for redevelopment of Mirfield railway station.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56778","56778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654916","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what support his Department provides to communities seeking to establish their own not-for-profit bus operator.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56806","56806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654917","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the number of bus miles on English roads in (a) 2017, (b) 2018, and (c) 2019.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56807","56807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654918","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the benefits of not-for-profit delivery of community transport operators.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56808","56808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654919","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) benefits and (b) methods of increasing passenger involvement in bus service procurement.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56809","56809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654920","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons no regional Factsheet covering Buckinghamshire has been published by HS2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56833","56833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654921","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what insurance cover is in place on properties purchased by HS2 in Buckinghamshire.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56834","56834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654922","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what security arrangements have been put in place at properties in Buckinghamshire purchased by HS2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56831","56831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654923","2016-12-13","Department for Transport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what properties have been purchased by HS2 in Buckinghamshire.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56832","56832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654925","2016-12-12","Women and Equalities","2016-12-08","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether the six-month validity period for Gender Recognition Certificates will be reviewed as part of the commitment to review the Gender Recognition Act 2004.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56751","56751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654926","2016-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of additional sanctions likely to be issued in enlarged jobcentres in Glasgow as a result of increased travel distances and time for users relocated from centres that have closed.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56761","56761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654927","2016-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to met meet with his counterparts in the Scottish Government to discuss the Jobcentre Plus estate in Scotland before making any further announcements on the future of that estate.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56760","56760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654928","2016-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support will be made available to jobseekers in Glasgow who will face additional travel costs and time in the event of the closure of their current Jobcentre Plus office.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56759","56759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654929","2016-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the travel times to the nearest jobcentre from each of those eight jobcentres earmarked for closure in Glasgow; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56768","56768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654930","2016-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the equality impact assessment made on the proposals to close the Glasgow jobcentres that was announced on 7 December 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56767","56767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654931","2016-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria his Department uses to determine whether a jobcentre earmarked for closure should go out to public consultation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56766","56766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654932","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the (a) Jobseeker's Allowance (Habitual Residence) Amendment Regulations 2013 and (b) three month rule provisions of those regulations on UK nationals who have returned to the UK after undertaking short-term contracts abroad.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56744","56744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654933","2016-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many of the eight Glasgow jobcentres earmarked for closure will be subject to public consultation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56765","56765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654934","2016-12-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he had with his counterparts in the Scottish Government on the proposed closure of job centres in Glasgow before the announcement of those closures was made on 7 December 2016.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56723","56723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654935","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward proposals to ensure that jobseeker's allowance claimants who have worked abroad for more than 13 weeks but are normally resident in the UK are exempted from the three-month rule.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56745","56745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654936","2016-12-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants have been refused jobseeker's allowance upon returning to the UK after working abroad for more than 13 weeks but less than six months since January 2014.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56746","56746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654937","2016-12-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the average carbon capture capabilities of a single tree.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56805","56805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654938","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish (a) his industrial strategy and (b) consultation on industrial strategy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56788","56788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654939","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what main policy areas will be covered by his Department's forthcoming Emissions Reduction Plan; and when his Department plans to publish that plan.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56789","56789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654940","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to page 20 of the Northern Powerhouse Strategy, what the planned (a) locations and (b) delivery dates are of pilots of Intellectual Property Offices in the north of England.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56793","56793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654941","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the potential effect of climate change on the future contribution of the agriculture industry to the UK economy.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56785","56785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654942","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to maintain in force the Companies, Partnerships and Groups (Accounts and Non-Financial Reporting) Regulations 2016 after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56786","56786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654943","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much has been spent promoting British tourism in (a) Europe, (b) Asia, (c) North America and (d) total in (i) 2016, (ii) 2015 and (iii) 2014.","Biography information for Mr Mark Williams","Mr Mark Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56843","56843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654944","2016-12-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress his Department has made on developing a public register of UK property ownership.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56841","56841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654945","2016-12-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2016 to Question 55870, if he will assess the merits of retaining the ownership of North Sea assets to be sold by Shell in the UK.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56829","56829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654946","2016-12-13","Department for International Trade","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many days he has spend abroad on government business since his appointment.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56774","56774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654947","2016-12-12","Department for International Trade","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with reference to page 21 of the Northern Powerhouse Strategy, published in November 2016, when his Department plans to put in place sector and infrastructure and regeneration specialists in the north of England; and in which areas such specialists will be located.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56794","56794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654948","2016-12-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many days he has spent abroad on government business since his appointment.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56773","56773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654949","2016-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will respond to Early Day Motion 655, Triggering of Article 50.","Biography information for John Penrose","John Penrose","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56750","56750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654950","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what preparations her Department is making for the coordination of efforts to tackle human trafficking with EU member states after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56728","56728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654951","2016-12-13","Home Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what preparations her Department is making for the coordination of efforts to tackle weapons trafficking with EU member states after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56729","56729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654952","2016-12-13","HM Treasury","2016-12-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what preparations his Department is making for the coordination of efforts to tackle the financing of terrorism with EU member states in line with the aspirations of the G7 Financial Taskforce after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56730","56730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654953","2016-12-12","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what his policy is on matching funding from the EU for community and farming purposes as part of the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56851","56851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654954","2016-12-13","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-12-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the potential effect on European structural funding for each region of the UK of the UK leaving the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56863","56863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/657003","2016-12-14","Cabinet Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps to modernise the process of electoral registration.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907860","907860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/658117","2016-12-14","Cabinet Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to improve public and business awareness of cyber security.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907863","907863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/658118","2016-12-14","Cabinet Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure adequate civil service support for new government departments.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907865","907865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/658119","2016-12-14","Cabinet Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of the One Public Estate programme.","Biography information for John Stevenson","John Stevenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907870","907870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/658120","2016-12-14","Cabinet Office","2016-12-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to report on the inquiry into the leak of the Prime Minister's Resignation Honours list.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907864","907864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654288","2016-12-12","Attorney General","2016-12-07","To ask the Attorney General, what plans the Law Officers' Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56595","56595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654289","2016-12-12","Cabinet Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56596","56596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654290","2016-12-12","Cabinet Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what plans the Government has for reform of Government procurement after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56646","56646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654291","2016-12-12","Cabinet Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 6.7 of Budget 2016, what plans additional to the move of 5,700 staff from Whitehall to 10 South Colonnade, have been made to reduce significantly the number of civil servants working in Central London.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56649","56649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654292","2016-12-12","Cabinet Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to paragraph 6.7 of Budget 2016, what substantial savings for the taxpayer will result from moving civil servants from central London to 10 South Colonnade.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56650","56650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654293","2016-12-12","Cabinet Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will list the digital transformation projects (a) ongoing and (b) planned.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56675","56675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654294","2016-12-12","Cabinet Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of (a) the cost, (b) expected savings and (c) changes to overall civil service staff numbers of plans to move staff from locations in Whitehall to 10 South Colonnade.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56545","56545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654295","2016-12-12","Cabinet Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will take steps along with the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy to plan reform of public procurement rules in order to support strategic industries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56669","56669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654296","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of how much proposed simplification of reporting processes for petroleum revenue tax will save oil and gas companies each year.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56504","56504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654297","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when new reporting processes to reduce the administrative costs of petroleum revenue tax for oil and gas companies are planned to come into effect.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56505","56505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654298","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many tax avoidance cases HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) has settled prior to litigation in each of the last five years; and how many of those cases were settled (a) wholly or (b) in part in HMRC's favour.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56499","56499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654299","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 2 December 2016 to Question 55382, on what date the powers of the Tax Credits (Income Thresholds and Determination of Rates) (Amendment) Regulations 2016 were first used to change tax credit awards automatically.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56456","56456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654300","2016-12-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to paragraph 1.301 of Budget 2016, which schemes (a) have been and (b) are planned to be supported by the 150 million investment in flood defence schemes in Leeds, Cumbria, Calder Valley and York.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56683","56683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654301","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's announcement in 2012 on the proceeds from LIBOR fines to be used to support charities and related good causes, how much the Government has collected in such fines since 2012; and how much of that money has been provided to charities and related good causes.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56592","56592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654302","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps are being taken to prevent cases of false self-employment in the construction industry.","Biography information for Michelle Thomson","Michelle  Thomson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56633","56633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654303","2016-12-12","HM Treasury","2016-12-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56612","56612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654304","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department's policies of the recommendations of the New Economics Foundation's Blue New Deal Action Plan, published in November 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56580","56580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654305","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56597","56597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654306","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that private letting agencies do not (a) transfer costs to landlords and (b) redefine tenant fees.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56542","56542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654307","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release 2,000 new homes and thousands of jobs in Birmingham, Leeds and Manchester, published on 1 December 2016, if he will set out how the funding from the Government's new Home Building Fund for the construction of those purpose-built rental properties will be allocated.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56570","56570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654308","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release 2,000 new homes and thousands of jobs in Birmingham, Leeds and Manchester, published on 1 December 2016, what estimate he has made of the rent levels of those purpose-built rental properties.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56571","56571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654309","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release 2,000 new homes and thousands of jobs in Birmingham, Leeds and Manchester, published on 1 December 2016, whether his Department will play a role in how those purpose-built rental properties will be marketed to prospective tenants.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56572","56572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654310","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's press release 2,000 new homes and thousands of jobs in Birmingham, Leeds and Manchester, published on 1 December 2016, whether any further funding will be provided by (a) his Department and (b) any other bodies in addition to the funding from the Government's new Home Building Fund for the construction of those purpose-built rental properties.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56573","56573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654311","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the British values are, as referred to in the Casey Review: a review into opportunity and integration, published on 5 December 2016.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56682","56682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654312","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his current guidance to local authorities is on the priority given to different house types in section 106 agreements; and whether he plans to change that guidance.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56664","56664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654313","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 3.11 of the Autumn Statement 2016, in what way restrictions on grant funding will be released in order to allow providers to deliver a mix of housing types; and whether the Homes and Communities Agency's (a) whole programme, (b) affordable rented homes programme and (c) social rented homes is available for bids.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56665","56665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654314","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the long-term effect on (a) house prices and (b) private rents in the North East of the UK leaving the EU; and what steps he is taking to address any such effect.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56442","56442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654315","2016-12-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies on coastal communities of the recommendations contained in the New Economics Foundation's Blue New Deal Action Plan, published in November 2016.","Biography information for Caroline Ansell","Caroline Ansell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56483","56483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654316","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with Ministers of HM Treasury on the potential effect on freelance creative workers of HM Revenue and Customs proposals that self-employed workers update their tax quarterly.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56474","56474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654317","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraph 3.20 of the Autumn Statement 2016, what her timetable is for (a) tackling network not spot zones and (b) national roll-out of 5G.","Biography information for Dr Andrew Murrison","Dr Andrew Murrison","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56544","56544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654318","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to encourage secure web programming among web developers, software and hardware vendors and site administrators.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56443","56443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654319","2016-12-12","Cabinet Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent progress has been made on the incorporation of the Cyber Information Sharing Partnership into the remit of the National Cyber Security Centre.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56441","56441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654320","2016-12-12","Home Office","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that EE negotiates transparent commercial terms for multi-operator access to publicly funded sites for the emergency services network.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56437","56437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654321","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what vetting procedures were (a) carried out and (b) considered by her Department in relation to the candidates recommended by Ofcom for appointment to the Board of Channel 4; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56591","56591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654322","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings (a) she, (b) Ministers of her Department and (c) officials of her Department have had with each of the candidates recommended by Ofcom for appointment to the Channel 4 Board; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56590","56590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654323","2016-12-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans her Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56598","56598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654324","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to publish information on the gender pay gap among its employees.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56599","56599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654325","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many war widows who remarried between 1973 and 2005 have been denied compensation.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56546","56546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654326","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officials of his Department are working on potential options for compensation for war widows who remarried between 1973 and 2005.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56547","56547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654327","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timescale is for the review of the Government's policy on compensation for war widows who remarried between 1973 and 2005.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56548","56548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654328","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Defence Infrastructure Organisation (DIO) has reimbursed CarillionAmey for the purchase of 3,000 boilers approved by DIO to ensure winter boiler breakdown requirements are met in accordance with key performance indicators; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56549","56549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654329","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) staff of his Department and (b) members of the UK armed forces were in attendance at the naming ceremony for RFA Tiderace at DSME Shipyard in Okpo, South Korea, on 1 December 2016.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56630","56630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654330","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of refitting the six Type 45 destroyers with intercoolers capable of operating in warm climates.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56621","56621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654331","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the most recent timetable is for the weapons testing programme for the F35B Joint Strike Fighter with the (a) Raytheon Paveway IV, (b) MBDA ASRAAM and (c) MBDA AMRAAM; and if he will estimate the costs of integrating each of those systems.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56632","56632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654332","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the 3 billion in defence expenditure in the Gulf Region announced by the Prime Minister during her visit to Bahrain in December 2016 will be allocated.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56641","56641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654333","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who is the designated patron of RFA Tiderace.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56629","56629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654334","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the United States Marine Corps are seconded to HMS Queen Elizabeth.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56631","56631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654335","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which ballistic missile defence systems protect the UK; and whether the Government has considered the potential merits of the use of ship-based ballistic missile defence systems.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56517","56517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654336","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the planned out-of-service date is for the Tornado fast jet fleet.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56520","56520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654337","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many airprox incidents there have been by (a) category and (b) location in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56521","56521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654338","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date his Department learned of the disappearance of HMS (a) Exeter, (b) Encounter and (c) Electra.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56522","56522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654339","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to protect war graves in overseas waters.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56523","56523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654340","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations his Department has made to the Indonesian government on the disappearance of (a) HMS Exeter, (b) HMS Encounter and (c) HMS Electra.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56524","56524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654341","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many and what proportion of recruits enlisting into the Army (a) under and (b) over the age of 18 were enlisted into (i) the infantry and (ii) any other frontline role in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56526","56526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654342","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of extending the in-service date for the GWS 60 Harpoon beyond 2018.","Biography information for Jack Lopresti","Jack Lopresti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56471","56471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654343","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the British Army began its scoping study into GCSE provision for trainees; when it plans for the findings of that study to be published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56485","56485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654344","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of British Army trainees aged under 18 at (a) ATC Pirbright and (b) ITC Catterick achieved Functional Skills qualifications in English and mathematics during their training there; and at what levels those trainees achieved those qualifications.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56486","56486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654345","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the capabilities of the new Russian, T-14, Armata main battle tank.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56687","56687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654346","2016-12-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2016 to Question 47716, whether his Department plans that no UK F35B Joint Strike Fighter aircraft will have undertaken testing for shipborne rolling vertical landing before tests begin aboard HMS Queen Elizabeth in 2018.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56688","56688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654347","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on how many occasions in 2015 and 2016 Ofsted has required governors to sign a declaration that they will not share an Ofsted Report on their school or college with anyone else.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56671","56671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654348","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government plans to extend funding for maintained nursery schools beyond the two years proposed in her Department's consultation, Early years funding: changes to funding for three and four-year olds.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56489","56489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654349","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to consider funding maintained nursery schools under the school national funding formula.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56490","56490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654350","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many child contact centres operated in England in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56500","56500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654351","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations her Department has received on the availability and regularity of bus services for pupils travelling for Halewood to Cronton Sixth Form and Riverside College.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56472","56472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654352","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will place copies of all responses received to the Government's consultation on early years funding in the Library.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56507","56507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654353","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to (a) commission research into the early years gap in the north of England and (b) create an effective plan for closing that gap.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56530","56530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654354","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much was provided for English for speakers of other languages classes in (a) Yorkshire and the Humber, (b) Bradford district and (c) Bradford West constituency in (i) 2012, (ii) 2013, (iii) 2014 and (iv) 2015.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56462","56462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654355","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on funding for postgraduate education courses of the UK leaving the EU; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56457","56457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654356","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to improve the performance of pupils in England in the Trends in International Mathematics and Science Study.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56434","56434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654357","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of PE and Sports Premium funding on participation in competitive sport; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56628","56628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654358","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues and other stakeholders on increasing the role played by Premier League and Football League teams in supporting the Government's free school and academy programmes.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56627","56627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654359","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2016 to Question 49486, on apprentices, what plans she has to provide extra support for ex-offenders.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56579","56579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654360","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment she has made of the performance of school music hubs; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56623","56623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/654361","2016-12-12","Department for Education","2016-12-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many state schools offered History of Art A-level in academic year 2015-16; how many such schools were comprehensive schools; and if she will place a list of those schools in the Library.","Biography information for Michael Gove","Michael Gove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 56624","56624"
