"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595695","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which African countries her Department regards as unsafe to return political opposition supporters to.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47299","47299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595696","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in Eritrea on the increase in political asylum seekers from that country.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47300","47300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595697","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the reasons for unaccompanied children from Albania seeking to purchase tickets to fly to the UK in order to claim asylum.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47304","47304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595698","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government is giving to Egyptian and Italian authorities investigating the murder of Giulio Regeni.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47305","47305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595699","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 45588, what recent representations he has received from Saudi officials on their Joint Investigation Assessment Team and the timescale for the investigation.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47380","47380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595700","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff of his Department's resigned in each half of each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47368","47368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595701","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government plans to make to the international community on the alleged chemical weapons attacks in Dafur.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47289","47289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595702","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the report by Amnesty International, published on 29 September 2016, on the use of chemical weapon attacks against civilians in Darfur.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47294","47294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595703","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons the Government did not support proposals by the Netherlands for the UN Human Rights Council to set up an independent inquiry into civilian deaths in Yemen.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47354","47354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595704","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 20 September 2016 to Question 45858 and 2 August 2016 to Question 42407, whether Government assistance has been provided to the UK Thalidomide Trust on its proposal to allow collective compensation applications to Contergan Foundation established by the German government.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47353","47353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595705","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the government of Burundi on political violence in that country.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47259","47259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595706","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of the Democratic Republic of Congo on the next presidential election in that country.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47260","47260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595707","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the (a) number of Palestinians affected by the demolition over separate locations on 27 September 2016 of structures in the West Bank and (b) potential cost of the reconstruction of those structures.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47365","47365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595708","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to hold discussions with his EU counterparts on the potential inclusion of companies and significant people who are involved in the construction of the bridge from Russia to Ukraine on the Russia sanctions list.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Djanogly","Mr Jonathan Djanogly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47287","47287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595709","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, when he next plans to meet his US counterpart to discuss Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership proposals.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47268","47268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595710","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on a potential establishment of a no-fly zone over parts of Syria.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47343","47343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595711","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the potential implications for UK foreign policy of the President of the European Commission's State of the Union Address of 14 September 2016.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47447","47447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595712","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps he is taking to address the humanitarian crisis in sub-Saharan Africa.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47449","47449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595713","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of staff employed by his Department are non-UK nationals.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47415","47415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595714","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had discussions with representatives of Japanese businesses operating in the UK on the memorandum presented by the Japanese government to the Prime Minister at the recent G20 Summit.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47490","47490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595715","2016-10-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what research has been (a) commissioned and (b) carried out by his Department in the last three years on the reputation of the UK abroad; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47484","47484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595716","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of staff on the payroll of his Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47584","47584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595717","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of his Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47562","47562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595718","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of his Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47564","47564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595719","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans NHS England has to undertake a formal evaluation of the new Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47600","47600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595720","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to introduce financial incentives for physiological services to engage with and achieve IQIPS accreditation.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47534","47534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595721","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with CCGs to work with community pharmacies to develop a role in reducing hospital admissions, early identification or intervention services and patient ongoing monitoring services.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47553","47553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595722","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether there are plans for NICE to review the process of patient involvement in technology appraisals.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47601","47601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595723","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the progress of audiology services achieving IQIPS accreditation; and what plans he has to ensure that audiology services in NHS trusts and communities give priority to registering with IQIPS.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47533","47533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595724","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the 46th Report of the Public Accounts Committee, Session 2014-15, HC971, what steps he has taken to ensure that the public purse is not exposed to any losses in circumstances in which Circle Holding plc fails to fulfil its contractual obligations in the delivery of musculoskeletal services in Greenwich; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47488","47488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595725","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the 46th Report of the Public Accounts Committee, Session 2014-15, HC971, An update on Hinchingbrooke Health Care NHS Trust, what the cost is to the public purse of Circle Holdings Plc's withdrawal from delivery of its contract to run Hinchingbrooke Hospital; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47512","47512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595726","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to introduce mandatory accreditation of audiology services in England.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47535","47535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595727","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of (a) the performance of Circle Holdings Plc in the delivery of musculoskeletal services in Bedford and (b) whether Circle Holdings Plc is meeting its national access targets; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47513","47513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595728","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the readiness of Circle Holdings Plc to deliver musculoskeletal services in Greenwich from 1 December 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47514","47514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595729","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of staff on the payroll of his Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47586","47586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595730","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of the staff employed by his Department are non-UK nationals.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47416","47416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595731","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many newly qualified GPs are waiting to be added to the national list for medical performers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47437","47437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595732","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the article in The Lancet, Adjuvant bisphosonphate treatment in early breast cancer: meta-analyses of individual patient data from randomised trials, published in July 2015, what steps he has taken to ensure that bisphosphonates for the indication of preventing secondary breast cancer are routinely available to the patients who need them.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47436","47436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595733","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise public awareness of (a) pancreatic cancer and (b) other cancers for which symptoms can be non-specific and have similarities to other benign conditions.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47460","47460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595734","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many audiology services there are in England.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47464","47464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595735","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the drug used in HIV PrEP, Truvada to come off patent.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47429","47429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595736","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints NHS England has received in each year since 2010 on services in the NHS provided by Capita.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47455","47455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595737","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department has provided for research on pancreatic cancer in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47269","47269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595738","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce mortality rates for people diagnosed with pancreatic cancer.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47270","47270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595739","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many doctors from (a) EU countries and (b) countries outside the EU have applied to practice medicine in the UK in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47253","47253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595740","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many UK medical students entered undergraduate training in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47254","47254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595741","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 11 May 2016 to Question 36655, if he will direct NHS England to issue a directive through the Clinical Commissioning Group (CCG) bulletin that requires CCGs to communicate the risks of valproate medicines in female patients and to ensure that the Valproate Toolkit is used by pharmacists and GPs.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47333","47333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595742","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the recommendations in the UN High Level Panel on Access to Medicines report, published in September 2016, on stimulating research and development in underfunded areas and improving access to medicines; whether he has plans to take those recommendations forward; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47337","47337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595743","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has made to the Government on the potential effect on health of restricting television advertising for unhealthy food on programming likely to be watched by children.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47361","47361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595744","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on increasing the ability of GP practices in North Wales to attract locums since the Government responded to the Third Report of the Welsh Affairs Committee of Session 2014-15, HC 404, on Cross-border health arrangements between England and Wales.","Biography information for Dr James Davies","Dr James Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47359","47359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595745","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the career destinations of doctors who completed foundation training in August 2016 were.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47358","47358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595746","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many complaints his Department received in relation to vaccination against human papilloma virus in each month of 2016.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47258","47258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595747","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on work permits and immigration rules for EU citizens working in the NHS, health and pharmaceutical industries after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47298","47298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595748","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure consistency of provision in the quality of care in mental health services across England.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47291","47291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595749","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the process for GPs referring patients to mental health services.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47292","47292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595750","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to implement the changes to funding for community pharmacies, announced in December 2015.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47296","47296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595751","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on pharmacy services in (a) the North East, (b) County Durham and (c) Easington constituency of the Government's proposed changes to the budget for community pharmacy.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47370","47370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595752","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital-borne cases of sepsis in England were recorded in (a) 2000, (b) 2005, (c) 2010 and (d) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47400","47400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595753","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of introducing in the UK initiatives for people with (a) fibromyalgia and (b) other central sensitivity syndromes similar to those introduced in Spain.","Biography information for Jake Berry","Jake Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47302","47302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595754","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans routinely to offer screening tests for Group B Strep to pregnant women as part of their antenatal care.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47405","47405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595755","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 45660, for what reasons the cost of indemnity is rising for GPs.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47387","47387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595756","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital-borne infectious diseases were recorded in England in (a) 2000, (b) 2005, (c) 2010 and (d) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47404","47404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595757","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospital-borne cases of MRSA were recorded in England in (a) 2000, (b) 2005, (c) 2010 and (d) 2015.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47403","47403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595758","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many trainee GPs have been informed by Capita and Primary Care Support England that they are no longer allowed to practice as they are not currently on the national list for medical performers.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47438","47438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595759","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the budget for Health Education England (a) was in each year since 2012 and (b) will be for 2017-18.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47397","47397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595760","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 45660, what estimate he has made of the number of general practices that require assistance from the new practice resilience programme.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47425","47425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595761","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on behalf of local independent pharmacies in Warrington on their future funding.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46943","46943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595762","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received from the National Pharmacy Association on the potential effect of planned changes to Government funding of local independent pharmacies.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46944","46944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595763","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many health visitors were employed in each of the last three years.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46922","46922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595764","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44621, how investments made from the public purse for mental health services in the community are monitored for their effectiveness.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46904","46904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595765","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44621, what information his Department holds on levels of investment from the public purse into mental health services in the community between 2010 and 2015; and what level of funding his Department has committed to investing in mental health services in the community until 2020.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46905","46905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595766","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44396, what the overall cost to the public purse of administering the NHS Low Income Scheme in England has been in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46906","46906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595767","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many child patients as a relative proportion of the local population had an appointment with an NHS dentist in Yorkshire and Humber in (a) July 2015 to June 2016, (b) July 2014 to June 2015 and (c) July 2013 to June 2014.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46917","46917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595768","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adult patients as a relative proportion of the local population had an appointment with an NHS dentist in (a) Bradford Districts Clinical Commissioning Group (CCG) and (b) Bradford City CCG in (i) July 2015 to June 2016, (ii) July 2014 to June 2015 and (iii) July 2013 to June 2014.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46918","46918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595769","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many child patients as a relative proportion of the local population had an appointment with an NHS dentist in (a) Bradford Districts Clinical Commissioning Groups (CCG) and (b) Bradford City CCG in (i) July 2015 to June 2016, (ii) July 2014 to June 2015 and (iii) July 2013 to June 2014.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46919","46919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595770","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44481, what records NHS England keeps on the grounds for inadequate ratings given to clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46909","46909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595771","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44481, for what reasons the 26 clinical commissioning groups referred to were rated as inadequate for 2015-16.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46910","46910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595772","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44396, for what reason there has been a decrease in the number of HC3 certificates issued between 2008 and 2016.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46907","46907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595773","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many adult patients as a relative proportion of the local population had an appointment with a NHS dentist in Yorkshire and the Humber in (a) July 2015 to June 2016, (b) July 2014 to June 2015 and (c) July 2013 to June 2014.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46916","46916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595774","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the range of therapy available on the NHS to people with autism.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46957","46957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595775","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to engage with the Daily Mile to help implement the physical activity objectives of the childhood obesity strategy.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46791","46791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595776","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase understanding of dental care among young people.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46841","46841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595777","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, based on today's values, what the expected lifetime earnings are for a junior doctor starting in training in August 2016 if they become (a) a consultant, (b) a GP and (c) remain a junior doctor; and what assessment his Department has made of how those earnings compare to other (i) public and (ii) private sector professionals.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46829","46829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595778","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 June 2016 to Question 40810, on NHS Protect, what the categories of offence were for each of the prosecutions listed.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46817","46817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595779","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Law Commission as part of its scoping work on reform of surrogacy law.","Biography information for Robert Neill","Robert Neill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46831","46831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595780","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people (a) have access to and (b) use an insulin pump.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46832","46832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595781","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people use a continuous glucose monitor (a) provided by the NHS and (b) that they have funded themselves.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46833","46833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595782","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people use an insulin pump (a) provided by the NHS and (b) that they have funded themselves.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46834","46834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595783","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total cost to the NHS was of (a) aspirin, (b) ibuprofen and (c) equivalent medication prescribed by GPs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46851","46851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595784","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that mental health services are not deprioritised in the commissioning process for budgetary reasons.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46866","46866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595785","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS England is able to meet its aim of extending waiting time standards for mental health.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46867","46867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595786","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the mental health crisis care concordat in improving cooperation between mental health services, non-mental health NHS services and other government services.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46868","46868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595787","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase transparency in mental health service block contracts.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46869","46869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595788","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to incentivise the provision of higher quality mental health services.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46870","46870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595789","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of NHS England's decision not to fund second stem cell transplants on the long-term outcomes of patients.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46697","46697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595790","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to put in place measures to ensure that funding for atypical GP practices is ring-fenced.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46698","46698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595791","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to increase public involvement in decision-making by clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46699","46699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595792","2016-10-11","HM Treasury","2016-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the total funding that the Welsh Government will lose as a result of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46748","46748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595793","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the new junior doctors' contract on the average pay of junior doctors.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46747","46747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595794","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44420, how the Government is monitoring the extent to which the NHS is offering treatment in accordance with NICE guidelines across all areas of medicine; and what assessment the Government has made of the extent to which treatment is falling short of NICE guidelines for financial reasons.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46746","46746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595795","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the NHS staff and recruitment needs for (a) the North East, (b) County Durham and (c) Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46741","46741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595796","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the per capita funding for the (a) North West Surrey, (b) Guilford and Waverley, (c) Surrey Downs, (d) Richmond, (e) Hounslow, (f) Hillingdon, (g) Slough, (h) Windsor, Ascot and Maidenhead, (i) Bracknell and Ascot and (j) Surrey Heath clinical commissioning groups was in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46750","46750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595797","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much each NHS trust has recuperated by recharging insurance companies for the costs associated with the treatment of customers who are involved in road traffic accidents in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46735","46735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595798","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent GPs per 1000 patients there were in (a) the North East, (b) County Durham and (c) Easington constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46784","46784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595799","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to (a) improve access to and (b) increase funding of mental health services in (i) the North East, (ii) County Durham and (iii) Easington constituency.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46785","46785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595800","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the expansion of the Doctaly scheme on patients' access to GP services.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46807","46807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595801","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what additional earnings above base pay are received by consultants by decile.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46812","46812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595802","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on management and administration in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46814","46814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595803","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 28 June 2016 to Question 40810, on NHS Protect, when each of the prosecutions listed commenced.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46816","46816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595804","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to include (a) stem cell and (b) bone marrow donation alongside organ and blood donation options on NHS GP registration forms for new patients.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47070","47070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595805","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to educate people on the importance of hand-sanitising products in the prevention of infection in hospitals.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47067","47067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595806","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase registration for (a) blood and platelet, (b) stem cell, (c) bone marrow and (d) organ donation.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47068","47068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595807","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the annual cost to the NHS of the common cold.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47118","47118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595808","2016-10-18","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total budget is for dental care in England in each of the next five years; and how much of that budget is allocated to dental care education in (a) schools and (b) the community.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47349","47349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595809","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how his Department plans to raise awareness among young people of the dangers of so-called smart drugs.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47116","47116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595810","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the additional 1.25 billion made available in the March 2015 Budget for child and adolescent mental health services has been spent in Derby North constituency.","Biography information for Amanda Solloway","Amanda Solloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47121","47121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595811","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve East Midlands Ambulance Service NHS Trust response times for stroke victims for whom 999 emergency services are requested.","Biography information for Amanda Solloway","Amanda Solloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47123","47123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595812","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department is providing nursing homes facing closure.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47113","47113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595813","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Dental Contract Reform: Prototypes pilot in (a) improving the quality of dental care and (b) improving access to dental care.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47007","47007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595814","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure residents in deprived areas have access to dental care.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47008","47008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595815","2016-10-17","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to conduct a review of dentistry provision contracts.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47009","47009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595816","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to encourage clinical commissioning groups to abide in full by National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidelines on funding in vitro fertilisation.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47050","47050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595817","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the report of the Independent Cancer Taskforce, Achieving world-class cancer outcomes: A strategy for England 2015-2020, published in July 2015, what progress has been made on implementation of recommendation 47 on NHS England commissioning NICE to develop updated guidelines for adjuvant treatment for breast cancer.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46993","46993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595818","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made on reaching a decision on NHS England's commissioning responsibilities for drugs capable of preventing HIV infection in high-risk groups.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47039","47039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595819","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that medicines distributed within the UK on European Medicines Agency licence continue to be distributed once the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47020","47020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595820","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many drugs currently prescribed to NHS patients in England and Wales are distributed under a European Medicines Agency licence; what those drugs are; and what therapeutic areas they treat.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47021","47021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595821","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NICE to publish guidance on the use of bisphosphonates for the indication of preventing secondary breast cancer.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47026","47026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595822","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the number of (a) doctors and (b) nurses recruited by the NHS.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Mr Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46984","46984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595823","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much overtime was paid to NHS staff in (a) 2015-16, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2013-14.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46976","46976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595824","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to increase mental health support to UK students in the last 12 months.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47010","47010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595825","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of contested cases have been successfully defended by the NHS Litigation Authority.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47015","47015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595826","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to reply to the letter of 18 July 2016 from the hon. Member for Ashfield on the proposed closure of the children's heart surgery unit at Glenfield Hospital.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47138","47138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595827","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds in the number of people in a permanent vegetative state in the UK; and how many such people are cared for by the Brighton and Sussex University Hospitals NHS Trust.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47148","47148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595828","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that oncologists are able to routinely prescribe bisphosphonates for the indication of preventing secondary breast cancer before NICE guidelines on those drugs is published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47140","47140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595829","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to target the recruitment of new GPs to practices with high levels of clinical need and deprivation.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47147","47147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595830","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of mental health support available to British nationals affected by the terrorist attacks in (a) Tunis on 18 March 2015, (b) Sousse on 26 June 2015, (c) Paris on 13 November 2015 and (d) Nice on 14 July 2016; and what estimate he has made of the average waiting time to receive such services.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47095","47095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595831","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) capacity and (b) adequacy of neonatal units in Wirral.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47238","47238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595832","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of GP waiting times in (a) the North East and (b) County Durham.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47170","47170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595833","2016-10-12","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training and support the NHS provides to doctors who have returned from long-term career breaks.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47315","47315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595834","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government plans to negotiate to continue participation in the European Centre for Disease Control after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47173","47173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595835","2016-10-11","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Government plans to negotiate to continue participation in the European Medicines Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47174","47174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595836","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the changes outlined in the Reforming Healthcare Education Funding consultation on the take-up of Graduate Entry Midwifery Pre-Registration Programme courses.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47190","47190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595837","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the NHS Sustainability and Transformation Plans for West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47191","47191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595838","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many bariatric surgical procedures were carried out in (a) the UK and (b) each local health authority in 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47207","47207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595839","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions for paracetamol were issued in England and Wales in the 2014-15 financial year.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47203","47203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595840","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of support available for victims of sexual abuse under the age of 13.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47229","47229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595841","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance she has issued to police forces on initiatives to stop the illegal trading of ivory.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47201","47201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595842","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent changes have been implemented on internal UK flight security checks; and what plans he has to change those security checks in the future.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47197","47197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595843","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to (a) monitor the welfare of unaccompanied refugee children who arrive in the UK and are in the care of the relevant authorities and (b) locate those refugee children who have gone missing in the UK in the last five years.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47320","47320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595844","2016-10-12","Department for Education","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent progress her Department has made on the consultation into how the proceeds of the immigration skills charge should be spent.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47313","47313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595845","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what obligations the Government places on police and crime commissioners to commission local victims' services to meet the specific and ongoing needs of British (a) nationals and (b) residents who have been direct victims or witnesses of a terrorist attack in the UK or abroad.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47094","47094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595846","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are currently subject to immigration restrictions which require that they report to an immigration reporting centre.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47127","47127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595847","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have applied for asylum on the basis of sexual orientation; how many of these claims have been unsuccessful; on what grounds those unsuccessful applications were refused in the last 12 months; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47014","47014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595848","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases the Civil Penalty Compliance Team referred to HM Revenue and Customs in 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46962","46962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595849","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to address the issue of non-British citizens tricking British citizens into marriage to obtain a UK visa or citizenship.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47023","47023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595850","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what role her Department plays in Government plans to ensure a higher rate of prosecution for knife crimes.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46988","46988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595851","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have applied for spouse visas to marry a UK citizen from (a) India, (b) Pakistan, (c) Bangladesh, (d) Nigeria, (e) Australia, (f) New Zealand and (g) Jamaica in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47019","47019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595852","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK passports have been revoked in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47114","47114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595853","2016-10-13","HM Treasury","2016-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to make available funding at the same level as currently received from the Asylum, Immigration and Integration Fund after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47348","47348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595854","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU citizens resident in the UK are eligible to apply for permanent residency.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47091","47091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595855","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to locate missing refugee children in the UK.","Biography information for Amanda Solloway","Amanda Solloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47124","47124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595856","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many emergency travel documents were issued by HM Passport Office in each of the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47115","47115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595857","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what type of reception institution suspected people traffickers and illegal migrants who are intercepted by Border Force or other UK government bodies are taken to.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47103","47103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595858","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time is between application for asylum and transfer to the UK for unaccompanied children in Europe who are accepted for humanitarian protection under the Dublin regulation.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46819","46819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595859","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce knife crime.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46879","46879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595860","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assistance British police have provided to Bahrain in the last 12 months; what the (a) dates and (b) titles of those assistance projects were; which constabularies were involved; what type of assistance police forces plan to provide to Bahrain in the next 12 months; and if she will place copies of the relevant International Police Assistance Board referral forms in the Library.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46877","46877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595861","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions the e-gates at UK airports have broken down since 2015.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46799","46799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595862","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that unaccompanied refugee children in Europe with an existing family connection in the UK have their asylum under the Dublin Regulation processed without undue delay.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46739","46739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595863","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many investigations the International Corruption Unit (ICU) at the National Crime Agency (NCA) inherited from other agencies when it was first established; and how many new investigations the ICU at the NCA has started since it was established.","Biography information for Lord Davies of Gower","Byron Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46873","46873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595864","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions Ministers in her Department have delayed providing information to the Intelligence and Security Committee in order to make a determination as to whether to share that information as set out in Schedule 1 to the Justice and Security Act 2013.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46854","46854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595865","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support her Department offers to victims of labour exploitation; and what steps her Department is taking against individuals and businesses involved in such exploitation.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46875","46875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595866","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied asylum seeking children have been transferred under the national dispersal scheme in each month since that scheme was introduced.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46928","46928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595867","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions Ministers in her Department have declined to disclose information to the Intelligence and Security Committee under Schedule 1 to the Justice and Security Act 2013; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46857","46857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595868","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures are in place for her Department to monitor and deport former students of (a) the Cambridge College of Learning and (b) similar institutions which also closed before collection of sponsorship data of non-EU nationals began.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46953","46953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595869","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to ensure that all EU citizens living in the UK will receive proof of their right to remain in the UK before any restrictions on new EU citizens are introduced; and how it will ensure there is sufficient operational capacity for such plans.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46954","46954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595870","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases each presenting office referred to HM Revenue and Customs in 2015.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46960","46960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595871","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many churches from each denomination in each region have applied for funding under the Places of Worship Security Funding Scheme up to close of applications on 20 September 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46961","46961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595872","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what past roles her Department has had in (a) appointing superintendents of children's homes and (b) the inspection of such homes in the London Borough of Lambeth.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46938","46938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595873","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of changes to the funding of English for speakers of other languages services on the ability of local authorities to provide access to English language classes to resettled Syrian refugees.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46887","46887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595874","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department's policy is for individuals who were enrolled on courses at the Cambridge College of Learning that were found at an immigration tribunal to have been fraudulent is (a) deport those people and (b) allow those people to stay in the UK and apply for indefinite leave to remain.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46945","46945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595875","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on what date her Department began to record details of sponsorship of non-EU nationals entering the UK on student visas.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46946","46946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595876","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department is taking steps to promote cooperation on the resettlement of Syrian refugees between local authorities with experience of resettlement programmes and local authorities without such experience.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46888","46888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595877","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department plans to issue to local authorities on their responsibilities to resettle Syrian refugees in the second to fifth year of resettlement.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46889","46889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595878","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to provide additional financial assistance to local authorities to help support resettled Syrian refugees who have physical and mental health needs.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46890","46890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595879","2016-10-12","Cabinet Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many EU nationals were living in the Borough of Croydon in September 2016.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47427","47427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595880","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the implications for its policies of the conclusions and recommendations in the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales, submitted to the Minister of State for Crime and Prevention in March 2015.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47373","47373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595881","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been deported to (a) India, (b) Pakistan, (c) China, (d) Nigeria, (e) Uganda and (f) Iran in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47307","47307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595882","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many unaccompanied child refugees are in the process of seeking asylum to be reunited with family members who are already in the UK, under the terms of the Immigration Act 2016.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47390","47390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595883","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken to improve forensic pathology services in England and Wales other than those based on the Hutton review of forensic pathology since the General Election in 2015.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47371","47371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595884","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken as a result of the conclusions and recommendations in the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales, submitted to the Minister of State for Crime and Prevention in March 2015.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47372","47372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595885","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children who have applied in France for asylum in the UK have been successful in their application in the last three years.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47285","47285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595886","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people her Department removed to Vietnam in each year from 2013 to 2016 to date; and how many such people had been subject to positive grounds National Referral Mechanism decisions in each such year.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47284","47284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595887","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of employer enquiries to the Employer Checking Service resulted in a response confirming that the subject of the enquiry had the right to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47250","47250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595888","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how frequently her Department reviews engineering jobs on the occupational shortage list to prevent over supply.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47263","47263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595889","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure the accuracy of labour shortages reported by employers before adding professions to the occupational shortage list.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47264","47264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595890","2016-10-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will list the UK delegates who attended the UN General Assembly meetings on refugees and migrants that took place on 19 and 20 September 2016.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47355","47355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595891","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether special case funding to meet exceptional needs costs of resettled Syrian refugees beyond their first year of resettlement in the UK will be included as part of the UK's Official Development Assistance contributions.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47286","47286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595892","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were returned to Vietnam under the assisted voluntary return scheme in each year from 2013 to 2016 to date; and how many such people had been subject to positive grounds National Referral Mechanism decisions in each such year.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47283","47283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595893","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 September 2016 to Question 46253, what steps her Department has taken via (a) broadcast media, (b) UK Visas and Immigration, and (c) agencies of her Department to advise employers of their responsibilities under a points-based immigration system on employing non-EU nationals in the UK; and what the cost of that advice was to the public purse in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47246","47246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595894","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many calls have been made by employers to the Employer Checking Service in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47249","47249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595895","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of applications for Tier 1 entrepreneur visas have been unsuccessful in each of the last four quarters.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47272","47272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595896","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the main reasons for rejection of applications for Tier 1 entrepreneur visas have been in each of the last four quarters.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47271","47271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595897","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications her Department received for Tier 1 entrepreneur visas in each of the last four quarters.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47273","47273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595898","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who is responsible for deciding which heroin addicts are provided with heroin in line with his Department's policy set out on page 31 of the Modern Crime Prevention Strategy, published by his predecessor in March 2016.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47471","47471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595899","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with police forces and police and crime commissioners on heroin distributed in their areas in line with her Department's policy set out on page 31 of the Modern Crime Prevention Strategy, published by her predecessor in March 2016.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47472","47472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595900","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has spent on providing heroin to heroin addicts in line with his Department's policy set out on page 31 of the Modern Crime Prevention Strategy, published by his predecessor in March 2016.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47475","47475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595901","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what criteria are used when deciding to give heroin to heroin addicts in line with his Department's policy set out on page 31 of the Modern Crime Prevention Strategy, published by his predecessor in March 2016.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47473","47473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595902","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will publish a list of the areas in which heroin has been given to heroin addicts in line with his Department's policy set out on page 31 of the Modern Crime Prevention Strategy, published by his predecessor in March 2016.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47474","47474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595903","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much heroin has been given to heroin addicts in line with his Department's policy set out on page 31 of the Modern Crime Prevention Strategy, published by his predecessor in March 2016.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47476","47476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595904","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of the staff employed by her Department are non-UK nationals.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47417","47417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595905","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of spit hoods; and what assessment she has made of the extent of use of such hoods by police forces.","Biography information for Amanda Solloway","Amanda Solloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47542","47542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595906","2016-10-11","Department of Health","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when and by whom the decision was taken to give heroin to heroin addicts in line with his Department's policy set out on page 31 of Modern Crime Prevention Strategy, published by his predecessor in March 2016.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47544","47544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595907","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the correlation between people who commit crimes against animals and go on to commit crimes against the person.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47519","47519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595908","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to maintain the use of the Dublin System in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47506","47506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595909","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to require EU nationals to gain visas before entering the UK in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47507","47507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595910","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to maintain the Assisted Voluntary Returns schemes after 2020.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47505","47505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595911","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government has received any legal challenge regarding delayed acceptance of child refugees in Calais with a legal right to residence in the UK.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47554","47554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595912","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of staff on the payroll of her Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47587","47587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595913","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of her Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47565","47565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595914","2016-10-12","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many hate crimes were committed against disabled people in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47598","47598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595915","2016-10-11","House of Commons Commission","2016-10-07","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what proportion of people given security clearance and passes in 2015 to work for construction, maintenance and refurbishment purposes in the Palace of Westminster were not UK nationals.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47511","47511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595916","2016-10-11","House of Commons Commission","2016-10-07","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what proportion of people who have security clearance for catering and cleaning purposes in the Palace of Westminster are not UK nationals.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47510","47510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595917","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of the staff employed by her Department are non-UK nationals.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47418","47418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595918","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many companies her Department has excluded from public procurement for (a) a conviction for wrongdoing defined by the Public Contracts Regulations 2015 or (b) grave professional misconduct since January 2015.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47275","47275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595919","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she has made to her counterparts in (a) Haiti, (b) Jamaica, (c) Cuba and (d) the Bahamas on humanitarian aid to address the damage caused by hurricane Matthew.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47282","47282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595920","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to assist Medicins Sans Frontieres in offering medical assistance in Yemen.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47360","47360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595921","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in (a) Haiti, (b) Jamaica, (c) Cuba and (d) the Bahamas as a result of hurricane Matthew.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47280","47280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595922","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to address the humanitarian situation in (a) Haiti, (b) Jamaica, (c) Cuba and (d) the Bahamas caused by hurricane Matthew.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47281","47281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595923","2016-10-12","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what funding the Government has committed to the Global Fund Investment Case, Fifth Replenishment 2017-19 for fighting infections.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47346","47346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595924","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent representations she has made to the Israeli authorities on the effect on the Palestinians in the West Bank of restricting water supplies.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47293","47293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595925","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of her Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47566","47566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595926","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of staff on the payroll of her Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47588","47588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595927","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to section 6.5 of the Memorandum of Understanding between her Department and the Palestinian National Authority, whether her Department has been aware of any breach of the commitment of human rights and taken any action in response to a breach of that commitment.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47603","47603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595928","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to section 6.5 of the Memorandum of Understanding between her Department and the Palestinian National Authority, whether her Department has been aware of any breach of the commitment on the principle of non-violence and taken any action in response to a breach of that commitment.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47604","47604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595929","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to section 6.5 of the Memorandum of Understanding between her Department and the Palestinian National Authority, whether the implications of any breach of the commitment on human rights was discussed at the annual partnership talks between her Department and that Authority.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47605","47605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595930","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to section 6.5 of the Memorandum of Understanding between her Department and the Palestinian National Authority, whether the implications of any breach of the commitment on the principle of non-violence was discussed at the annual partnership talks between her Department and that Authority.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47606","47606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595931","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with regard to the amendment letter to the Memorandum of Understanding with the Palestinian Government for Financial Assistance, signed on 19 March 2015, whether her Department has a list of the eligible beneficiaries of the PEGASE support programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47607","47607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595932","2016-10-12","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 19 September 2016 to Question 45930, on the Palestinian Authority, if she will place a copy of her Department's formal assessment of the Palestinian Authority's commitment to the Partnership Principles in the Library.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46979","46979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595933","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the cost to the public purse is of the airport at St Helena.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46872","46872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595934","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with (a) her international counterparts, (b) non-governmental organisations and (c) toiletry companies on the provision of women's health and sanitary products to refugee women and girls.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46860","46860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595935","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of the Department's funding has been allocated to women's health initiatives, including education in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18 and (c) 2018-19.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46861","46861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595936","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to continue to fund (a) innovative projects on anti-corruption and transparency and (b) country-specific anti-corruption strategies.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46778","46778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595937","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she has taken to ensure that every government and organisation which her Department funds meets global transparency standards.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46779","46779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595938","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether official development assistance (ODA) spent by her Department on anti-corruption activities has reduced as a result of her Department's overall expenditure on ODA between 2014-15; and whether other government departments have taken over any spending on anti-corruption activities that were previously funded through her Department's expenditure on ODA.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46786","46786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595939","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with non-governmental organisations on tackling the taboo around women's periods and its effect on women in refugee camps.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46885","46885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595940","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when her Department plans to publish its Civil Society Review.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47088","47088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595941","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when her Department plans to publish its Multilateral Aid Review.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47089","47089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595942","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when her Department plans to publish its Bilateral Aid Review.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47090","47090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595943","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken to increase investment in decentralised renewable energy.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47022","47022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595944","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government has made plans to assist with additional funding or aid subsequent to the changes in refugee numbers entering into Mosul.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47028","47028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595945","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which EU commissioners she has met since taking office; and when and where such meetings took place.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47037","47037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595946","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 45678, on Ethiopia: security, what non-overseas development assistance elements were included in the executive masters programme in security sector management, which closed in June 2015.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47239","47239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595947","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department has made an assessment of the effect of changing levels of funding for non-conflicting affected states on the level of stability in those countries.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47243","47243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595948","2016-10-12","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many of her Department's country offices have direct bilateral expenditure that is coded under HIV prevention, treatment and care; and what the value of that expenditure is.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47335","47335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595949","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is giving to Palestinians displaced by Israeli settlement building and the demolition of Palestinian homes.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47225","47225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595950","2016-10-12","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policies of the recommendations in the UN High Level Panel on Access to Medicines report, published in September 2016, on stimulating research and development in underfunded areas and improving access to medicines; whether she has plans to take those recommendations forward; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47336","47336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595951","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to page 21 of her Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2015-16, what assessment she has made of progress against its target of doubling its funding on improving tax systems in developing countries by 2020.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47230","47230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595952","2016-10-11","Department for International Development","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many of the structures in the West Bank funded through aid provided by her Department have been demolished by Israeli forces in 2016 to date.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47227","47227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595953","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans she has to allow commercial companies access to sensitive information held by other government departments and agencies on the proposed enforcement purposes of those companies.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47208","47208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595954","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the contractual agreement between her Department and G4S Care and Justice Services (UK) Limited at HM Prison (a) Birmingham and (b) Oakwood, how many performance points have been incurred and for what reason those performance points have been incurred in each year from 2012-13 to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47220","47220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595955","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason her Department has invited private sector companies to tender for work currently carried out by its civilian enforcement officers.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47185","47185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595956","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason the Civil Service Code does not apply to those undertaking public sector work for her Department in the private sector.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47184","47184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595957","2016-10-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the contractual agreement between her Department and G4S Care and Justice Services (UK) Limited at HM Prison (a) Birmingham and (b) Oakwood for what reason financial remedies have been levied in (i) failure to comply with procedures, (ii) incidents and (iii) failure to comply with prison regime in each year from 2012-13 to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47319","47319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595958","2016-10-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of prisoners released on licence to a bail hostel have been subsequently recalled to prison in 2016 to date.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47323","47323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595959","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to increase capacity at the Asylum and Immigration Chamber.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47206","47206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595960","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of potential measures to make access to courts (a) easier and (b) substantially faster for a landowner seeking to get an order to evict travellers.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47244","47244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595961","2016-10-12","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether non-payment of the television licence for solely accessing the BBC iPlayer will be treated as a criminal or civil offence.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46995","46995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595962","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of child contact cases presided over by the family judiciary in each year since 2010, where there was an allegation of domestic abuse, either party were litigants in person.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47052","47052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595963","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information her Department holds on how many times provisions under Section 67 of the Serious Crime Act 2015 have been used to convict people in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) Scotland.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46895","46895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595964","2016-10-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of people released from each prison in England and Wales (i) reoffended and (ii) went into employment within six months of their release in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46986","46986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595965","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department has taken to ensure first-time offenders entering the prison system are (a) made aware of gang culture in prisons and (b) discouraged from becoming involved in that culture.","Biography information for Amanda Solloway","Amanda Solloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47120","47120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595966","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what safeguards are in place to protect the privacy of victims and witnesses in historic sex abuse cases.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47059","47059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595967","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many arrest warrants were issued for defendants who failed to attend court in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47082","47082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595968","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to make the punishment of people traffickers more severe to increase its deterrent effect.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47074","47074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595969","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many male offenders aged under 21 were sentenced to immediate custody in courts in each police force area in Wales in each year from 2010 to 2016; and what the custody rate for indictable offences was during that period.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47075","47075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595970","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many arrest warrants have been issued for people sentenced for a serious sexual offence who failed to appear in court for sentencing in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47076","47076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595971","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were prosecuted in their absence for (a) serious sexual offences, (b) class A drug use and (c) manslaughter in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47077","47077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595972","2016-10-11","Home Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people received pre-charge bail conditions that (a) withheld their travel documents and (b) restricted their movement in each year since 2010; and how many people breached those pre-charge bail conditions.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47078","47078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595973","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people prosecuted in their absence were on bail in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47079","47079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595974","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners are serving indefinite sentences in England.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46736","46736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595975","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to tackle illegitimate and fraudulent activity by claims handling companies.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46734","46734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595976","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners serving indefinite sentences in England are awaiting re-offending courses.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46737","46737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595977","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department plans to conduct a three and five year post-implementation review of the Taking Control of Goods Regulations 2013.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46871","46871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595978","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of domestic abuse victims in child contact cases in the family court have been in receipt of legal aid in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46936","46936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595979","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many civilian enforcement officers were employed by HM Courts and Tribunal Service in each year since 2010; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46842","46842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595980","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2016 to Question 44657, for what reasons the commencement of Section 67 of the Serious Crime Act 2015 has not yet taken place.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46894","46894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595981","2016-10-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether all European funding for schemes to improve the employability of prisoners has been protected for the duration of their funding period.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46967","46967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595982","2016-10-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drones have been intercepted operating over prisons in England and Wales (a) in 2015 and (b) from January 2016 to date.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46968","46968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595983","2016-10-12","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will make an assessment of the adequacy of the opportunities to present evidence in child custody cases; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46956","46956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595984","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps her Department is taking to protect victims of domestic abuse in family law courts.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46920","46920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595985","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of staff on the payroll of her Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47590","47590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595986","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of her Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47568","47568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595987","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2016 to Question 43488, what the reason is for the discrepancy between the figure provided in that answer and data in recent research published by Women's Aid on 13 September 2016 on the proportion of survivors of domestic abuse that had access to a separate waiting room in the family court.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47301","47301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595988","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the one-year post-implementation review of the Taking Control of Goods Regulations 2013 has been completed; and if she will make the outcome of that review available to hon. Members.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47401","47401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595989","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what preparatory work is currently underway in her Department on the consultation on increasing the small claims limit from 1,000 to 5,000.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47375","47375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595990","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 3.103 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015, when her Department plans to launch the consultation on increasing the small claims limit from 1,000 to 5,000.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47376","47376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595991","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether her Department has plans to bring forward proposals to amend the legislation requiring statutory declarations to be dated within six months of the date of the Gender Recognition Certificate application.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47439","47439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595992","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans her Department has for civilian enforcement officers within the context of its plans to outsource work to the private sector.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47362","47362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595993","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of the staff employed by her Department are non-UK nationals.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47420","47420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595994","2016-10-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to enable the prosecution of people who promote the use of miracle mineral solution as a cure for autism.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47521","47521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595995","2016-10-11","Leader of the House","2016-10-07","To ask the Leader of the House, how many (a) Peers and (b) civil servants have offices within the Palace of Westminster.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47459","47459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595996","2016-10-11","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of his Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47569","47569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595997","2016-10-11","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of staff on the payroll of his Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47591","47591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595998","2016-10-12","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions he has had with the Northern Ireland Executive on funding for inquests into the killings allegedly carried out by the British Army's Military Reaction Force.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46959","46959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/595999","2016-10-11","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what arrangements he plans to put in place for milk bank sharing between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47199","47199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596000","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with President Xi at the September 2016 G20 meeting on separating the building of the Hualong One reactor at Bradwell from the agreement on Hinkley Point C.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46701","46701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596001","2016-10-11","Cabinet Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will extend the proposed audit of public services to reveal racial disparities to all organisations and companies which provide (a) car insurance and (b) other consumer services required by law.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47432","47432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596002","2016-10-11","Scotland Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what recent discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the result of the EU referendum.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47274","47274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596003","2016-10-11","Scotland Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of staff on the payroll of his Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47592","47592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596004","2016-10-11","Scotland Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of his Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47570","47570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596005","2016-10-11","Scotland Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on the inclusion of Scottish universities in the post-study work visa pilot.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46838","46838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596006","2016-10-12","Scotland Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which EU Commissioners he has met since 23 June 2016; and when and where such meetings took place.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47143","47143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596007","2016-10-11","Scotland Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, when he plans to give effect to the provisions of the Scotland Act 2016 not yet in force.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47025","47025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596008","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the report by the British Red Cross, entitled Are pre-hospital deaths from trauma and accidental injury preventable?, published in September 2016, what steps he is taking to ensure that first aid education is included in the Government's road safety strategy.","Biography information for Dr Alasdair McDonnell","Dr Alasdair McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46989","46989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596009","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much road grit is available in the UK for the 2016-17 winter; and how much the (a) mining, (b) storage and (c) distribution of road grit costs per year.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47013","47013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596010","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to comments made by the former Chancellor of the Exchequer at a meeting in Birkenhead on 4 May 2015 and pursuant to the Answer of 14 September 2016 to Question 45786, whether he plans to directly intervene in the review of the Mersey tunnel tolls to reduce the cost of those tolls.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46998","46998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596011","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the cycling and walking investment strategy will include investment for the proposed cycling and pedestrian bridge linking Rotherhithe to Canary Wharf.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46996","46996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596012","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the rate of road traffic accidents.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47119","47119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596013","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with (a) Great Western Railway and (b) South West Trains on the provision of wifi services on those trains.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Mr Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47325","47325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596014","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to remove or reduce the fee incurred when paying vehicle excise duty via credit card.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre  Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47219","47219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596015","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 September 2016 to Question 906370, if he will publish the London and South Coast Rail Corridor Study; whether he plans to fund proposals for a Brighton Mainline 2 in order to remedy the significant capacity and performance constraints identified; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46898","46898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596016","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has for road investment in the north of England.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46897","46897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596017","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to introduce a limit to the number of Hackney carriage and private hire driver licences local authorities can issue.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46927","46927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596018","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department received applications from Govia Thameslink Railway (GTR) to activate the force majeure clause in the franchise agreement for Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern passenger rail services since July 2015.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46952","46952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596019","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department plans to put in place for an operator of last report for the Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern passenger rail franchise since September 2013.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46951","46951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596020","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the operator of last report provisions are for each franchise agreement for passenger rail services currently in operation.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46949","46949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596021","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when his Department plans to launch its consultation on biofuels; and whether that consultation will address the issues of indirect land use and level of the crop cap.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46965","46965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596022","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve the service on Southern Rail.","Biography information for Chris Philp","Chris Philp","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46974","46974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596023","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans that the Northern Chord at the Manchester junction will be retained in the route of HS2.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46942","46942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596024","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Network Rail on the rail electrification programme in the North West; and if he will publish a revised timetable for that work.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46947","46947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596025","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if the Northern Powerhouse Rail rolling stock will be permitted to operate on HS2 infrastructure.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46948","46948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596026","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of Network Rail's administrative performance in providing weekly operating and signalling notices to train drivers and other rail staff.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46725","46725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596027","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much compensation his Department is liable for in its contract with Agility Trains in the event that the Inter City Express (IEP) fleet cannot be introduced in line with the contracted schedule for (a) delivery and (b) operation of new IEP trains on the (i) Great Western and (ii) East Coast mainlines.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46726","46726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596028","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many government-owned goods vehicle test stations are based in (a) England, (b) Wales and (c) Scotland.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46711","46711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596029","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether British Transport Police officers based in Wales will continue to be accountable to his Department after the devolution of the rail franchise to the Welsh Assembly.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46712","46712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596030","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to reduce (a) dangerous driving and (b) driving under the influence of alcohol.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46714","46714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596031","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations his Department has received on the effectiveness of the laws against dangerous driving, speeding and driving while under the influence of alcohol in deterring those offences.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46715","46715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596032","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many volunteer coastguards were recruited by the Maritime and Coastguard Agency in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46716","46716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596033","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many coastguards were employed by the Maritime and Coastguard Agency in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46717","46717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596034","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department has undertaken on the effects on road safety of adopting harsher sentencing for those who break the law by dangerous driving, speeding or driving whilst under the influence of alcohol.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46718","46718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596035","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate has been made of the (a) coastguard and (b) lifeguard capacity on UK (i) beaches and (ii) coastal waters.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46719","46719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596036","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost to his Department was of each re-tendering exercise held for franchises for (a) long distance and (b) regional passenger rail services in each year since 2005-06.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46720","46720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596037","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether bidders for the next West Midlands regional rail franchise will be able to remove seats from rolling stock in order to increase passenger carrying capacity; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46721","46721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596038","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to increase passenger carrying capacity on Inter City West Coast services between cities in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46722","46722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596039","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with train operating companies on the New Stations Fund launched on 26 August 2016.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46723","46723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596040","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many platform train interface incidents that were reported on the national rail network in each year since 2010 involved driver-only operated passenger services.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46724","46724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596041","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether risk adjustments have been made to the rail passenger franchises currently out to tender for services on the (a) South Western, (b) West Midlands and (c) East Anglia lines since 23 June 2016; and if he will provide details of any such adjustments in each case.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46729","46729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596042","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has any plans to extend child discounts on public transport from 16 to 18 years to match the new compulsory school leaving age.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46732","46732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596043","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce the dates for the (a) planned commissioning, (b) delivery of contracted functionality and (c) installation of the first deployment traffic management system for the Rail Operating Centre at Cardiff.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46727","46727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596044","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the cost of the contract between Network Rail and Thales has been by heading for the supply of two first deployment traffic management systems for rail operating centres at (a) Cardiff and (b) Romford since the award of that contract.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46728","46728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596045","2016-10-11","Department for Education","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has any plans to extend her Department's policy of free school transport for children between eight and 16 years old living over three miles from their school to match the compulsory school leaving age of 18 years old.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46733","46733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596046","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all taxi and minicab drivers undergo disability equality training.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46880","46880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596047","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of noise from Heathrow Airport on people living in the Woking constituency; and if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of an increase in such noise as a result of the construction of a third runway.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46756","46756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596048","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many taxi licences have been issued in each local authority area in each of the past three years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46806","46806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596049","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many residential properties purchased ahead of the construction of High Speed 2 are being let; and what estimate his Department has made of the total amount it will receive in rent payments from those properties.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46878","46878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596050","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Civil Aviation Authority's review of impact of environmental landing charges published in 2013, if he will exercise his powers under the Civil Aviation Act 1982, Section 78, to direct airports to review their charges for night flights.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46787","46787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596051","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of his Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47571","47571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596052","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of staff on the payroll of his Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47593","47593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596053","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which organisations his Department has formally consulted on the location of the proposed High Speed 2 station in South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47257","47257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596054","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many crossings across traffic are planned to be closed on the A1 (a) southbound and (b) northbound.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47266","47266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596055","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 45695, on railways: fares, for what reason his Department uses the Retail Price Index as an index for inflation; and if he will consider using a different index for inflation.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47385","47385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596056","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 45695, what proportion of rail fares paid by passengers are reinvested in the railways by Network Rail.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47386","47386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596057","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much revenue the Office for Road and Rail and its predecessor raised through the Railway Safety Levy in each financial year between 2006-07 and 2015-16.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46950","46950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596058","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of the staff employed by his Department are non-UK nationals.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47421","47421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596059","2016-10-12","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what date his Department plans to open a consultation on biofuels; and if he will take steps to ensure that that consultation addresses indirect land use change and the level of the crop cap.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47492","47492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596060","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to amend the Cycle to Work scheme to incorporate a higher maximum allowance for disabled cyclists requiring specialist cycles.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47531","47531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596061","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when steps have been taken to enact the provisions within section 165 of the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47530","47530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596062","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations the Government has made to the US Department of Transportation on progress made on authorising Norwegian Air UK Ltd services from Gatwick and other British airports to the US, as permitted by the EU-US Air Transport Agreement in December 2015.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47550","47550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596063","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps have been taken to prevent taxi drivers charging extra to disabled people.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47527","47527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596064","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of over-staging by bus companies on journeys undertaken using a concessionary bus pass in England.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47508","47508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596065","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to (a) educate bus passengers about over-staging and (b) help them to report cases of over-staging.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47509","47509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596066","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will assess the potential merits of reforming the rail franchising system by reinstating sole ownership and maintenance of infrastructure and trains.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47518","47518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596067","2016-10-11","Department for Transport","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that Southeastern has access to sufficient rolling stock to enable it to alleviate capacity pressures across its London metro network.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47481","47481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596068","2016-10-12","Wales Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on Wales of the proposal to transfer responsibility for attendance allowance to local authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47503","47503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596069","2016-10-11","Wales Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of staff on the payroll of his Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47595","47595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596070","2016-10-11","Wales Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of his Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47573","47573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596071","2016-10-11","Wales Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of the net benefit to the Welsh economy of the steel to be used in the construction of the Hinkley C nuclear power plant.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46766","46766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596072","2016-10-11","Wales Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that GMB is able to negotiate on behalf of 200 workers at the Lidl warehouse in Bridgend.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46767","46767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596073","2016-10-11","HM Treasury","2016-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of funding the Welsh Government will lose in subsidies as a result of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46768","46768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596074","2016-10-11","HM Treasury","2016-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to match the level of funding for Wales that is provided by the EU.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46769","46769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596075","2016-10-11","HM Treasury","2016-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any increase in Welsh Government funding will come through the existing Barnett formula following the UK vote to leave the EU.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46770","46770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596076","2016-10-11","Wales Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of the net benefit to the Welsh economy of jobs created as a result of the construction of Hinkley Point C nuclear power plant.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46775","46775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596077","2016-10-11","Wales Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will estimate how many jobs will be created in Wales as a result of the construction of the Hinkley Point C nuclear power plant.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46774","46774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596078","2016-10-11","HM Treasury","2016-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect leaving the EU will have on the level of Welsh farming subsidies.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46771","46771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596079","2016-10-11","Wales Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what plans he has to devolve the Wales and Border Rail Franchise to the Welsh Government.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46772","46772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596080","2016-10-11","Wales Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much Welsh steel will be used in the construction of the Hinkley Point C nuclear power plant.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46773","46773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596081","2016-10-11","Wales Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues about proposals for a North Wales Growth Deal.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47038","47038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596082","2016-10-11","Wales Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, for what reasons he decided to give evidence on the Wales Bill to the National Assembly for Wales' Constitutional and Legislative Affairs Committee; and if he will give evidence to that committee.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47054","47054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596083","2016-10-11","Women and Equalities","2016-10-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent discussions she has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer about the level of VAT imposed on women's sanitary products; and what assessment she has made of the impact of that policy on equalities issues.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47060","47060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596084","2016-10-11","Women and Equalities","2016-10-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what assessment her Department has made of how transparently (a) insurance companies and (b) other providers of a public good (i) formulate the price of their products and (ii) ensure any pricing structure is not affected by the consumer's ethnicity.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47210","47210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596085","2016-10-11","Women and Equalities","2016-10-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the report entitled Ethnic Penalties in Motor Insurance Premiums by Webber Phillips, published in July 2016, what assessment her Department has made of concerns raised in that report that some car owners may be being charged higher premiums due to their ethnicity.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47209","47209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596086","2016-10-11","Women and Equalities","2016-10-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the Answer of 14 April 2016 to Question 904452, what assessment she has made of the merits of the Government's forthcoming legislation to tackle the disparity between the number of men and women in senior and higher paying management roles.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46803","46803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596087","2016-10-11","Women and Equalities","2016-10-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of the Government Equalities Office.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47563","47563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596088","2016-10-11","Women and Equalities","2016-10-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what proportion of staff on the payroll of the Government Equalities Office who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47585","47585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596089","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to publish its Work and Health Green Paper; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47529","47529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596090","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many respondents to the first consultation on reforming housing benefit for supported housing in 2011 responded that a localised pot would support the right of disabled people to live independently.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47528","47528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596091","2016-10-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with the Welsh Assembly Government on the transfer of attendance allowance to local authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47504","47504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596092","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of the staff employed by his Department are non-UK nationals.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47423","47423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596093","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many old-age pensioners in Ashfield constituency who live in social housing properties containing two or more bedrooms and who receive housing benefit will be affected by plans to limit housing benefit to the level of the local housing allowance.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47435","47435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596094","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress has been made on implementing the recommendations made by the Work and Pensions Committee in its report of 23 March 2016 on support for the bereaved.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47477","47477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596095","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2016 to Question 42446, how many people have (a) claimed and (b) received payment under the vaccine damages payment scheme where one of the vaccines cited in the claim was (i) whole cell vaccine for pertussis used up to 2003 and (ii) acellular vaccine used after 2003.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47443","47443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596096","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who will be affected by the proposed cap on housing benefit for people living in supported housing; and what estimate he has made of the average reduction in housing benefit for people so affected.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47465","47465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596097","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department has taken to monitor Universal Jobmatch for duplicate and fake advertisements.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47463","47463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596098","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Hemsworth constituency who have had benefit payments reinstated after a mandatory reconsideration decision are awaiting a fully back-dated entitlement payment.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47454","47454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596099","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance the Government makes available to people awaiting a fully back-dated benefits entitlement payment.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47453","47453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596100","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 September 2016 to Question 45590, what representations he has made to the Defined Benefit pension sector on pension deficits reported in September 2016; what steps his Department is taking to support that sector in decreasing their deficit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47381","47381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596101","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to change the calculation for child maintenance payments to take into account the outgoings of the non-resident parent.","Biography information for Gordon Henderson","Gordon Henderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47290","47290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596102","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the forthcoming change to limit housing benefit to the level of Local Housing Allowance on old age pensioners living in social housing properties with two or more bedrooms.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47430","47430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596103","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many qualified doctors are employed by Maximus in delivering work assessments.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47248","47248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596104","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish updated guidance for Work Programme providers on requests to review action plans by claimants.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47235","47235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596105","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Hemsworth constituency who have waited more than 42 days to receive a mandatory reconsideration decision since the introduction of that process.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47277","47277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596106","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of staff on the payroll of his Department who work in Westminster are (a) British nationals and (b) nationals of another country.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47596","47596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596107","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, approximately how many (a) British and (b) non-British nationals are employed cleaning the Westminster estate of his Department.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47574","47574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596108","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many adults in Cardiff Central constituency have received carer's allowance for caring for children under the age of 16 in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46809","46809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596109","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people aged under 16 in Cardiff Central constituency have received (a) personal independence payment and (b) disability living allowance in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46810","46810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596110","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people who are affected by funeral poverty.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46815","46815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596111","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce the cost of funerals.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46703","46703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596112","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations his Department has (a) received and (b) made to the Scottish Government on its approach to funeral expenses.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46704","46704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596113","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for the Social Fund Funeral Expenses Payment Scheme his Department has (a) received and (b) accepted in each of the last five years in (i) Birmingham, Northfield constituency, (ii) West Midlands and (iii) England.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46705","46705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596114","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the triple lock pension policy on the number of pensioners living in poverty in (a) Woking constituency, (b) the South East and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mr Jonathan Lord","Mr Jonathan Lord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46749","46749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596115","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44305, what estimate he has made of the number of people who are not in receipt of the expected level of guaranteed income because their defined benefit pension fund is in deficit.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46915","46915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596116","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward proposals to ensure that parents who are making child support payments to the Child Maintenance Service are not charged for the Collect and Pay service, where all reasonable attempts are made by the two parties to use the Direct Pay service.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47216","47216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596117","2016-10-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pregnant women in each constituency in Lancashire have been sanctioned for failing to attend back to work interviews for (a) universal credit and (b) employment and support allowance, in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47322","47322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596118","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 June 2016 to Question 38327, when his Department plans to publish its Work and Health Green Paper.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47240","47240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596119","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the prevalence of employer's using unpaid trial shifts, particularly in the hospitality sector.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47236","47236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596120","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what workplace protection is in place for young people under the age of 25 to protect them from exploitation by their employer.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47237","47237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596121","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many reports his Department has received on the number of letters on the Social Fund sent and lost in the in the post in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47128","47128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596122","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many reports his Department has received on the number of letters on the Fraud and Error Service sent and lost in the in the post in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47129","47129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596123","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many reports his Department has received on the number of letters on employment and support allowance sent and lost in the post in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47130","47130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596124","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many reports his Department has received on the number of letters to the Compensation Recovery Unit sent and lost in the post in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47131","47131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596125","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many reports his Department has received on the number of letters on the disability living allowance 65+ have been sent and lost in the post in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47132","47132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596126","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints his Department has received from hon. Members on the service of Ingeus as a Work Programme provider in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47092","47092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596127","2016-10-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what meetings he has had with Ministers of the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the British Steel Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47146","47146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596128","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many deduction from bank account orders the Child Maintenance Service has served on absent parents to recover payments due to parents with custody living in Bristol South constituency since May 2015.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47097","47097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596129","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many liability orders through magistrates courts the Child Maintenance Service has served on absent parents to recover payments due to parents with custody living in Bristol South constituency since May 2015.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47096","47096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596130","2016-10-12","HM Treasury","2016-10-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what protections his Department plans to put in place for rape victims who have more than two children and will be subject to the Government's proposal to limit child tax credits to two children per family.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47311","47311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596131","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many deduction from earnings or benefits orders the Child Maintenance Service has served on absent parents to recover payments due to parents with custody living in Bristol South constituency since May 2015.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47098","47098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596132","2016-10-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to make training materials for work coaches available.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47309","47309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596133","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any companies that participate in his Department's work trial programme for claimants who are in receipt of jobseeker's allowance are known to use unpaid trial shifts as part of their general recruitment process.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47057","47057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596134","2016-10-11","Cabinet Office","2016-10-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what statistics are held by the Government relating to incidences of unpaid trial shifts since May 2010 relating to (a) individuals not claiming benefits and (b) people under 25 years old.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47058","47058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596135","2016-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department plans to make changes to the eligibility criteria for the Sure Start maternity grant for families affected by changes to child tax credit from April 2017.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47005","47005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596136","2016-10-18","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to monitor the effect of the personal independence payments rollout for disabled people in work and using motability vehicles and ensuring employment is not lost as a result of differing thresholds between disability living allowance and the new benefit.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47350","47350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596137","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress he has made in reducing long-term youth unemployment.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47041","47041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596138","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if the Government will make it its policy to maintain existing levels of attendance allowance for new claimants if this benefit is devolved to local councils.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47032","47032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596139","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the Government plans to ensure that (a) award levels for attendance allowance and (b) award criteria will be the same across different local authorities if responsibility for administering this benefit is devolved to them.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47031","47031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596140","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the benefit to the Exchequer of devolving responsibility for administering attendance allowance to local authorities.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47030","47030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596141","2016-10-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether funding for attendance allowance will be ring-fenced if responsibility for administering this benefit is devolved to local authorities.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47029","47029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596142","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much (a) grant aid and (b) other financial support was provided to tech start-ups in the UK in the last five years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47011","47011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596143","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to prevent a brain-drain of UK young tech talent moving to find employment outside the UK.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47012","47012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596144","2016-10-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in Government investment in home energy efficiency on levels of fuel poverty.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46985","46985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596145","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which EU commissioners he has met since taking office; and when and where such meetings took place.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47036","47036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596146","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to reduce the level of business regulation.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47046","47046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596147","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of changes to the rules governing payment of embedded benefits on participation in the forthcoming capacity market auctions; and what assessment he has made of the effect of those changes in the cost to the consumer.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47006","47006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596148","2016-10-12","Department for Education","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships have been taken up in (a) Ashfield constituency and (b) the East Midlands in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47135","47135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596149","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with Ford on the long-term future of its plant in Bridgend.","Biography information for Lord Davies of Gower","Byron Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47056","47056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596150","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent progress his Department has made in negotiations on phase IV of the EU Emissions Trading Scheme.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47104","47104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596151","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the Government's position is on the negotiations on phase IV of the EU Emissions Trading Scheme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47105","47105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596152","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the amount of distribution-connected plants that might close in the event of a significant change to rules governing the payment of embedded benefits, including the triads benefit.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47003","47003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596153","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether it his policy to continue to take part in the EU negotiations on phase IV of the EU Emissions Trading Scheme while the UK remains a member of the EU.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47106","47106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596154","2016-10-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the value of distribution-connected generation to the (a) UK energy system as a whole and (b) security of supply.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47004","47004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596155","2016-10-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the Government will take into account the atmospheric carbon dioxide level of over 400ppm when deciding on the UK's energy policy.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47141","47141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596156","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make arrangements for companies in the register of persons with significant control to be identified by name.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47242","47242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596157","2016-10-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of support for the British Steel Pension Scheme in securing the future of the UK steel industry; and what steps he is taking to support that scheme.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47321","47321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596158","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many businesses have contacted the Business Support Helpline as a result of the Do More Online campaign in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47186","47186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596159","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has made an estimate of the Do More Online campaign's contribution to the British economy.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47187","47187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596160","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that smart meter software is secure by design.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47180","47180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596161","2016-10-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government plans to negotiate to continue participation in the European Chemicals Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47175","47175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596162","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what contribution the Do More Online campaign is making to protect British microbusinesses from cybercrime.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47188","47188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596163","2016-10-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to raise standards for energy efficiency in (a) new-build housing and (b) other new buildings.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47329","47329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596164","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on whether UK universities are being excluded from joint funding applications made with other EU universities for EU funding.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46893","46893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596165","2016-10-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 45332, for what reasons the use of wood which has not reached the end of its useful life attracts subsidies and not penalties for emissions of carbon dioxide; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46971","46971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596166","2016-10-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 45332, whether his Department plans to review the use of coal in the UK energy market; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46970","46970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596167","2016-10-12","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 45332, what assessment he has made of the use of biomass for electricity production and its contribution to supporting the decarbonisation of the UK economy.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46969","46969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596168","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department is taking steps to identify businesses that engage in labour exploitation.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46876","46876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596169","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Correction of 8 September 2016 to the Answer of 1 June 2016 to Question 38139, how much of the 10.3 million of minimum wage arrears recovered in 2015-16 was recovered from the 814 employers who were issued with both a Notice of Underpayment and a financial penalty; and how many workers were identified as having been underpaid by those 814 employers.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46899","46899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596170","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of trends in the level of inward investment in (a) Liverpool, (b) Merseyside and (c) the North West.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46862","46862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596171","2016-10-11","Department for International Trade","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what levels of investment have been received into the Liverpool City Region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46863","46863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596172","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect on investment in energy intensive industries of increased regulatory uncertainty around carbon emissions policy.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46864","46864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596173","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing an approach to carbon reduction other than emissions trading after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46865","46865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596174","2016-10-11","Department for Education","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how her Department plans to award teacher training contracts to universities; and what the selection criteria will be for such contracts.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46830","46830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596175","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to publish the next Carbon Plan.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46843","46843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596176","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Carbon Plan will outline policies that ensure that the UK meets the emissions limit in the fourth carbon budget of a 50 per cent reduction in annual emissions on 1990 levels.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46844","46844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596177","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Carbon Plan will outline policies that ensure that the UK meets the emissions limit in the fifth carbon budget of a 57 per cent reduction in annual emissions on 1990 levels.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46845","46845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596178","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions (a) he and (b) his officials have had with other government departments on the forthcoming Carbon Plan.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46846","46846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596179","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how his Department is (a) monitoring and (b) enforcing the requirement for companies to disclose information on persons with significant control in their company as part of their company register in Companies House.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46824","46824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596180","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking against companies which circumvent the requirement for businesses to disclose information to Companies House on persons with significant control in that company by registering another company rather than an individual as the person with significant control of that company.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46823","46823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596181","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if his Department will take steps to ensure that storage or disposal of nuclear waste is compliant with the obligations outlined in Article 29 of the UN Declaration on the Rights of Indigenous Peoples.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46886","46886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596182","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department takes when the register of persons with significant control reveals a criminal record.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46821","46821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596183","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the register of persons with significant control, how many companies have registered a shell company in an offshore tax haven as the persons with significant control of that company since 6 April 2016.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46822","46822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596184","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies have listed another company rather than an individual as the persons with significant control in that company as part of their company register since 6 April 2016.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46827","46827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596185","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many companies have disclosed information to Companies House on persons with significant control in their company as part of their company register since 6 April 2016.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46828","46828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596186","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the register of persons with significant control, what proportion of returns from companies have listed another company rather than an individual as the persons with significant control.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46826","46826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596187","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the register of persons with significant control, what proportion of returns from companies have listed a shell company in an offshore tax haven as the persons with significant control of that company since 6 April 2016.","Biography information for Dame Margaret Hodge","Margaret Hodge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46825","46825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596188","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will reform the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme to ensure that the surplus is used to benefit former mineworkers.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46740","46740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596189","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the security of the intellectual property of the European Pressurised Reactor technology to be used at Hinkley Point C.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46700","46700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596190","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the recommendations of the report, Lowest Cost Decarbonisation for the UK: the critical role of carbon capture and storage, published in September 2016.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46706","46706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596191","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what (a) national and (b) local arrangements are in place for issuing iodine tablets in the event of a radiation emergency involving an operational civil nuclear reactor or reprocessing facility; which localities have had a pre-distribution of iodine tablets to households and what the radii of those localities are; to which nuclear reactors those (a) national and (b) local arrangements are linked; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46883","46883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596192","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that consumers are adequately informed about the option to switch to gas and electricity tariffs with zero standing charge.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 46781","46781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596193","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of UK energy supply he plans to be produced by UK coal-fired power stations in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47262","47262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/596194","2016-10-11","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of staff employed by his Department  are non-UK nationals.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 47406","47406"
