"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418287","2015-09-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions she has had with her Chinese counterpart on areas of cooperation on green growth.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9838","9838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418288","2015-09-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Afghan counterpart on the treatment of the Hazara people in that country.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9842","9842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418289","2015-09-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what criteria he uses to determine the viability of strikes against terrorist targets in states against whom the UK is not at war; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9888","9888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418290","2015-09-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what rules of engagement his Department has developed for strikes using unmanned aerial vehicle systems against terrorist targets in states against which the UK is not at war other than Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9887","9887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418291","2015-09-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish the UN's response to the letter from the UK Permanent Representative to the UN sent on 7 September on recent action taken in Syria.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9944","9944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418292","2015-09-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on the relocation to the UK of interpreters who have worked for the British Army in Afghanistan.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9840","9840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418293","2015-09-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many interpreters who have worked for the British Army in Afghanistan have been relocated to the UK in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9841","9841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418294","2015-09-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what legal support is provided by his Department to members of the British Army in cases related to military combat operations within the UK.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9866","9866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418295","2015-09-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what statutory provisions provide for members of the British Army to conduct military combat operations in the UK.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9867","9867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418296","2015-09-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department has had discussions with Research Councils on the effect of pay freezes by that body on the research sector.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9917","9917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418297","2015-09-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the membership of the UKTI's Strategic Relations Team is; and which companies are involved with that team.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9886","9886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418298","2015-09-14","Home Office","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much compensation has been received by victims of trafficking identified by the Gangmasters' Licensing Authority in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9885","9885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418299","2015-09-14","Department for International Development","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 20 July 2015 to Question 7327, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policy of promoting religious tolerance and respect for diversity of the findings on pages 10 and 11 of the report of the US Commission on International Freedom entitled Connecting the dots: education and religious discrimination in Pakistan, published in 2011.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9945","9945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418300","2015-09-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make representations to the European Commission on overturning the ban on the herbicide Asulam.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9912","9912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418301","2015-09-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps are being taken to lower the level of air pollution in the area of Oxford Street in London.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9914","9914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418302","2015-09-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Single Intelligence Account is or will be incorporated into his Department's budget; and whether the Single Intelligence Account is included in calculations of the percentage of the UK's GDP being spent on defence.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9913","9913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418303","2015-09-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she is taking to ensure that cost overruns similar to those incurred in the building of the Flamanville nuclear power station do not occur in EDF's construction of Hinkley Point C.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9918","9918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418304","2015-09-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will take steps to ensure that the strike price per megawatt hour of production at the proposed Sizewell and Bradwell nuclear power stations (a) reflects the market rate and (b) is not subsidised from public funds.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9919","9919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418305","2015-09-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will take steps to ensure that the strike price per megawatt hour of production from Hinkley Point C nuclear power station (a) reflects the market rate and (b) is not subsidised from public funds.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9920","9920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418306","2015-09-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for which military vehicles components valued at £40 million were licensed for export to Egypt in March 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9941","9941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418307","2015-09-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) civilian staff of his Department based in the UK, (b) military personnel based in the UK, (c) civilian staff of his Department based in Saudi Arabia and (d) military personnel based in Saudi Arabia were employed by the Saudi Arabian National Guard Communications Project on 1 April 2015.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9894","9894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418308","2015-09-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which local planning authorities in 2014 (a) complied with their duty under section 69(2) of the Planning (Listed Buildings and Conservation Areas) Act 1990 and (b) designated conservation areas accordingly.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9923","9923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418309","2015-09-15","Department of Health","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to Section 10.4 of the Code of Practice on confidential personal information, published in December 2010, what plans the Care Quality Commission has to publish a review of that code.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9946","9946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418310","2015-09-15","Department of Health","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Care Quality Commission (CQC) requires CQC inspectors to identify themselves as such when visiting patients in a personal capacity in CQC inspected premises.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9922","9922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418311","2015-09-15","Department of Health","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that the Care Quality Commission (CQC) (a) publishes a code of conduct for its inspectors on its website and (b) places a duty on its inspectors and other staff involved in inspections to declare to CQC whether friends or family members are, to their knowledge, being looked after in CQC inspected premises.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9921","9921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418312","2015-09-15","Home Office","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which police forces in England ran campaigns in 2014 to tackle cyclists riding on footpaths other than a pavement; what the dates and locations was of each such campaign; and how many cyclists were given fixed penalties or prosecuted during those campaigns.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9931","9931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418313","2015-09-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance the Government is providing to armed forces veterans with post-traumatic stress syndrome and depression.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9865","9865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418314","2015-09-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many disputes on armed forces veterans' pensions entitlements Veterans UK and its predecessor organisations has dealt with in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9863","9863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418315","2015-09-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what pensions awards the Government has made to armed forces veterans in Inverclyde in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9864","9864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418316","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what statistics his Department holds on usage of (a) magistrates and (b) civil courts; and if he will place such statistics in the Library.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9884","9884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418317","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria he has used to determine a reasonable journey to court in considering proposals for court closures.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9890","9890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418318","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his definition is of a reasonable journey to court in proposing court closures.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9889","9889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418319","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to sell former court buildings; and to what purpose he plans to apply monies raised from such sales.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9860","9860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418320","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he plans to take to ensure the maintenance of good working relationships between magistrates, local solicitors, local authorities and the police in areas where it is proposed to close court buildings.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9856","9856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418321","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he plans to take to monitor links between local people and justice provision as part of the reform of court accommodation; and what assessment he has made of how that reform will effect the delivery of local justice.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9857","9857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418322","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what criteria he applies to determine which court buildings are (a) over- and (b) under-utilised.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9858","9858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418323","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how he plans to make greater use of video conferencing and other technology in reforming the court system; and what assessment he has made of the effect of greater use of such technology on the delivery of local justice.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9859","9859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418324","2015-09-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of (a) the level of imports of puppies to the UK from other EU countries under the pet travel scheme and (b) the adequacy of controls to avoid the use of that scheme to import puppies for sale.","Biography information for Christina Rees","Christina Rees","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9940","9940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418325","2015-09-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to support the installation of solar energy panels; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9937","9937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418326","2015-09-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September to Question 8243, what recent representations his Department has received from officials in the Kurdistan region of Northern Iraq on a strategy for tackling ISIL; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9911","9911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418327","2015-09-14","Department of Health","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2015 to Question 8027, what information his Department holds on the forecast amount to be spent on recruitment campaigns for GPs in each of the next two financial years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9910","9910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418328","2015-09-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations she has received from the solar energy industry on the feed-in tariff subsidy for solar panels; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9909","9909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418329","2015-09-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has conducted of the effectiveness of the feed-in tariff subsidy for solar panels in achieving its objectives; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9908","9908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418330","2015-09-15","Department for Transport","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the overall cost to his Department of increasing the cost of regulated national rail fares in line with the retail price index between 2014 and 2020.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9870","9870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418331","2015-09-15","Department for Transport","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received on the potential safety implications of reducing Network Rail's Control Period 5 maintenance and renewals delivery volumes.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9871","9871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418332","2015-09-15","Department for Transport","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, by what mechanisms he is permitted to reduce the Control Period 5 spending levels for the railway set by the Office of Rail and Road's Final Determination, published on 10 April 2014.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9872","9872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418333","2015-09-15","Department for Transport","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the withdrawal of Balfour Beatty from the North West electrification programme on the delivery timetable for that project.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9869","9869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418334","2015-09-15","Department for Transport","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 4 November 2014 to Question 212595, when he plans for his Department's review of the future activities of Directly Operated Railways to be concluded.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9868","9868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418335","2015-09-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support the Skills Funding Agency in prioritising adult basic skills training in English and mathematics.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9939","9939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417974","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2015 to the hon. Member for Moray to Question 222334, what the conclusions are of the Ministry of Defence Police Professional Standards investigation into disciplinary matters relating to police officers based at the Atomic Weapons Establishment, Burghfield; and if he will place a copy of that investigation report in the Library.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9672","9672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417975","2015-09-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department has taken to protect nuclear power stations from attacks carried out using unmanned drones.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9821","9821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417976","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the name, date and location is of each nuclear weapons accident response exercise which (a) has taken place or is planned in 2015 and (b) is scheduled for 2016.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9807","9807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417977","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he plans to publish the results of his review of the defence nuclear enterprise.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9808","9808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417978","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many reportable nuclear security incidents at defence sites he was notified of in the financial years (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15; and for each of these years, how many incidents were classified as (i) major, (ii) moderate, (iii) minor and (iv) of no significance according to the categorisation used by the Office for Nuclear Regulation.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9806","9806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417979","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which offices in his Department are responsible for maintaining and monitoring nuclear security at defence sites.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9805","9805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417980","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the Atomic Weapons Establishment review of how best to achieve the customer requirements for Project Pegasus was (a) started and (b) completed.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9803","9803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417981","2015-09-11","Prime Minister","2015-09-09","To ask the Prime Minister, pursuant to his statement of 7 September 2015, Official Report, column 26, on Syria: refugees and counter-terrorism, whether the meeting of the National Security Council to which he referred was provided with the full written advice to Government, a summary of that advice or a verbal statement by the Attorney General on the legal basis for the military action against Reyaad Khan.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9748","9748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417982","2015-09-11","Home Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Prime Minister's statement of 7 September 2015, Official Report, column 26, on Syria: refugees and counter-terrorism, how many terror suspects have been (a) arrested and (b) prosecuted in the UK in association with the six attempts to attack the UK.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9749","9749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417983","2015-09-11","Department for International Development","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the timetable is for the completion of programme reviews of UK aid funding for the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9698","9698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417984","2015-09-11","Department for International Development","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the likelihood and scale of food shortages in Yemen as a result of conflict in that country.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9699","9699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417985","2015-09-11","Department for International Development","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the prospects for re-establishing free and fair access for humanitarian aid to Yemen through Port Hodiedah.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9700","9700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417986","2015-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what action the Government is taking to secure free and fair access for humanitarian aid to Yemen via Port Hodiedah.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9701","9701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417987","2015-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to publish the Government response to the Industry Training Boards review, announced on 23 September 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9740","9740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417988","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the proposed closure of Hartlepool Magistrates' Court, what estimate he has made of additional costs arising from increased expenses of (a) staff of agencies using the court system and (b) members of the public.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9759","9759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417989","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the proposed closure of magistrates' courts, what estimate has been made of the (a) cost to the public purse and (b) effect on public safety of the increased travelling times of police officers attending magistrates' courts away from their designated beat patrol.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9760","9760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417990","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the savings from the proposed closure of Hartlepool Magistrates' Court.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9744","9744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417991","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost per case heard at (a) Hartlepool and (b) Teesside magistrates' court was in each of the last five years; and what the average cost per case heard in magistrates' courts in England and Wales was in each of those years.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9761","9761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417992","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases were heard at Hartlepool Magistrates' Court in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9763","9763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417993","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the utilisation rate of (a) Hartlepool and (b) Teesside magistrates' courts was in each of the last five years; and what the average utilisation rate in magistrates' courts in England and Wales was in each of those years.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9762","9762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417994","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England's high cost device steering group sought advice from clinicians and other healthcare professionals before recommending the removal of implantable cardiac defibrillators from the high cost device exclusion list.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9812","9812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417995","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ask NHS England to publish the minutes of meetings of the high cost device steering group at which the recommendation was made to remove subcutaneous implantable cardiac defibrillators from the high cost device exclusion list.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9813","9813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417996","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with NHS England and Monitor about the proposal to remove subcutaneous implantable cardiac defibrillators from the high cost device exclusion list as part of the 2016-17 national tariff proposals.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9804","9804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417997","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with NHS England about the criteria used to decide (a) when and (b) which high cost devices are removed from the high-cost drugs and devices list.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9695","9695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417998","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the NHS is an early adopter of innovation in regards to devices to prevent sudden cardiac death syndrome.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9711","9711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417999","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many implantations of (a) subcutaneous implantable cardiac defibrillators and (b) implantable cardiac defibrillators took place within the NHS in the last year for which data is available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9710","9710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418000","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure access for NHS patients to subcutaneous implantable cardiac defibrillators.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9712","9712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418001","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the removal of implantable cardiac defibrillators from the high cost drugs and devices list, as part of 2016-17 national tariff proposals.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9691","9691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418002","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who is responsible for the collection of data on families, their cases and the time in which they are within the justice system.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9814","9814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418003","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the recording of data within the family justice system.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9815","9815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418004","2015-09-11","Department for International Development","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what information her Department holds on (a) financial and (b) other support provided by the federal government of Iraq to internally displaced people in the Kurdistan region of that country; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9696","9696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418005","2015-09-11","Home Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of current regulations on spousal visas on low wage families in the UK; and if she will amend spousal visa application criteria to take into account potential employment opportunities that migrant spouses might have to bridge the minimum income threshold.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9697","9697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418006","2015-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the potential savings to the public purse from the reduction in the benefit cap over the course of this Parliament.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9738","9738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418007","2015-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects the targets for eradicating child poverty set out in the Child Poverty Act 2010 will be achieved.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9739","9739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418008","2015-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has had with the Highland Council on assessment of the roll-out of universal credit.","Biography information for Drew Hendry","Drew Hendry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9824","9824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418009","2015-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many tonnes of carbon dioxide were displaced by renewable (a) electricity and (b) heat generation in (i) the UK, (ii) England, (iii) Scotland and (iv) Wales in 2014.","Biography information for Callum McCaig","Callum McCaig","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9734","9734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418010","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect of changes to (a) tax relief to landlords and (b) regulations on buy to let mortgages on the number of homes (i) built and (ii) available to rent in the next five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9736","9736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418011","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2015 to Question 4115, how many (a) offences in West Yorkshire were committed by offenders on bail and (b) offenders in West Yorkshire committed offences whilst on bail in (i) 2008, (ii) 2009, (iii) 2011, (iv) 2012 and (v) 2013.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9809","9809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418012","2015-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his Answer of 9 September 2015 to Question 8714, for what reason the contract to provide PIP assessments stipulates that Capita is not permitted to provide recording equipment for use during assessments; and which Minister in his Department signed off this decision.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9725","9725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418013","2015-09-11","Department for International Development","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to make it compulsory for companies to comply with the 2013 Accord on Fire and Safety in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9671","9671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418014","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he expects the rollout of the new NOMS IT system to be completed; and what estimate he has made of the final cost of the contract.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9793","9793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418015","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what additional cost was incurred to the new NOMS IT system by the postponement of the rollout of the programme nationally in March 2015.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9792","9792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418016","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost is of the development and rollout of the new NOMS IT system.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9791","9791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418017","2015-09-14","Home Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish her Department's general policy advice on handling requests for revocations of a deportation by a person outside the UK; and for what reasons the website https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/revoking-a-deportation-order-requests-made-from-outside-the-uk-2 has been taken down.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9726","9726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418018","2015-09-14","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department has received to date from the sale of Plasma Resource UK Ltd.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9676","9676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418019","2015-09-14","Home Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugees have been accommodated in each local authority in England, Wales and Scotland under the Gateway scheme in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9675","9675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418020","2015-09-11","Cabinet Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to report on the performance of each Department against the five per cent target for the purchase of remanufactured office furniture in the Government Buying Standard.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9670","9670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418022","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2015 to Question 5351, what mechanisms are in place to assess whether the dietary and other standards set out in the service specifications for pancreatic cancer are being met.","Biography information for Richard Benyon","Richard Benyon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9714","9714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418023","2015-09-14","Department for Education","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secondary and primary school pupils in England are educated by a local authority other than the one in which they reside.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Mrs Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9719","9719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418024","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 6 of What's Important to me: A review of Choice in End of Life Care, whether he will invest £130 million in palliative and end of life care as recommended in the previous Government's review of end of life care.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9747","9747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418025","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to implement the recommendations of What's Important to me: A review of Choice in End of Life Care, published in February 2015.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9746","9746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418026","2015-09-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations she has made to the BBC on the potential implications of its decision no longer to use the Met Office's forecasts and expertise on resilience to flooding; and what response she has received to those representations.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9716","9716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418027","2015-09-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) Government and (b) emergency responders of those organisations receiving different information about the weather in an emergency to that provided by the BBC to the general public.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9819","9819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418028","2015-09-14","Cabinet Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for national security and resilience to extreme weather of the BBC broadcasting weather forecasts supplied by an overseas company.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9833","9833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418029","2015-09-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the (a) cost and (b) value for money implications to the Met Office of the BBC no longer using the Met Office for weather services.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9718","9718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418030","2015-09-14","Cabinet Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for (a) national security and (b) resilience to extreme weather of the BBC's decision no longer to use the Met Office's weather forecasts and expertise in its broadcasts.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9717","9717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418031","2015-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans the Government has to reduce the Feed-in-Tariff; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9789","9789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418032","2015-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to protect and promote the British solar power industry.","Biography information for Fabian Hamilton","Fabian Hamilton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9737","9737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418033","2015-09-14","Home Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers the Government plans to resettle in (a) Oldham, (b) Rochdale, (c) all 10 Greater Manchester metropolitan boroughs, (d) London and (e) the South East.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9666","9666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418034","2015-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many working age disability living allowance recipients notified his Department of a change of circumstance and sought a reassessment under special rules for people with terminal illness in each year from 2005 to 2010.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9720","9720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418035","2015-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many working age people applied for and received disability living allowance, claiming under special rules for people with terminal illness, in each year from 2005 to 2010.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9721","9721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418036","2015-09-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the effects of the proposal to reduce the feed-in tariff payments for solar energy on (a) the UK solar power industry, (b) employment in the sector and (c) the cost and accessibility of solar power.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9822","9822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418037","2015-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Turkish government on protecting (a) the democratic process and (b) minorities.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9708","9708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418038","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to use the NATO Incirlik Air Base in Turkey during operations against Daesh in Iraq.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9709","9709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418039","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Ministry of Defence staff were based in Iraq on (a) 1 January, (b) 1 April and (c) 1 September 2015.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9706","9706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418040","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Ministry of Defence staff were based in Bahrain on (a) 1 January, (b) 1 April and (c) 1 September 2015.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9707","9707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418041","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assistance his Department gave to the Pakistani Armed Forces during recent unmanned aerial vehicle operations in that country.","Biography information for Douglas Chapman","Douglas Chapman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9705","9705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418042","2015-09-11","Department for International Development","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the UK's support for the reconstruction effort in Nepal following the 2014 earthquake in that country.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9837","9837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418043","2015-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants are in receipt of universal credit; and of those claims how many have alternative payment arrangements in place.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9829","9829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418044","2015-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects the transition to universal credit to be complete.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9830","9830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418045","2015-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claims include an element for housing costs.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9828","9828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418046","2015-09-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans to exempt 18 to 21 year olds in supported accommodation who meet the specified accommodation definition under the Housing Benefit and Universal Credit (Supported Accommodation) (Amendment) Regulations 2014 from the withdrawal of housing support for this age group.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9834","9834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418047","2015-09-14","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the effect was of the tax and benefit changes announced in the Budget on median household income in each income quintile.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9827","9827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418048","2015-09-14","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the administrative cost was of the Cancer Drugs Fund re-evaluation process in 2014-15.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9754","9754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418049","2015-09-14","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England on how the survival rates for pancreatic cancer are reflected in assessments of new treatments for that disease.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9823","9823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418050","2015-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that Sudan begins a credible and inclusive peace process.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9733","9733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418051","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received from mental health charities on the potential effects of recent changes in welfare spending on mental health; and what assessment his Department has made of the content of those representations.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9685","9685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418052","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the devolved administrations on potential Barnett consequentials arising from the public expenditure on infrastructure and access associated with the proposed new runway in south east England.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9686","9686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418053","2015-09-11","Home Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her European counterparts on the possibility of closing country borders within the EU to refugees.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9810","9810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418054","2015-09-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress he has made on introduction of tax relief for local newspapers.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9731","9731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418055","2015-09-14","Department for Transport","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the £200 million made available to fix potholes in the 2014 Budget was allocated to councils in 2014-15.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9757","9757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418056","2015-09-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will prioritise town and city centres in the next wave of Enterprise Zones.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9758","9758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418057","2015-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much the Government has (a) allocated to promote growth in the English regions and (b) paid out to local projects since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9730","9730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418058","2015-09-14","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of estates where liable for inheritance tax in (a) Ellesmere Port and Neston constituency, (b) the North West and (c) England in the last financial year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9755","9755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418059","2015-09-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Government allocated to direct lending to UK businesses to promote exports in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9756","9756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418060","2015-09-11","House of Commons Commission","2015-09-09","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2015 to Question 3834, what disposal strategy there is for the Parliamentary Art Collection.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9732","9732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418061","2015-09-11","House of Commons Commission","2015-09-09","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, how many items in the Parliamentary Art Collection are (a) on and (b) not on public display.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9668","9668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418062","2015-09-11","House of Commons Commission","2015-09-09","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, how many items in the Parliamentary Art Collection are on loan outside the parliamentary estate.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9669","9669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418063","2015-09-11","Home Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of providing support to Syrian refugees relocated to the UK in each of the last four years; and what the number of such refugees resettled was in each of those years.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9680","9680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418064","2015-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate she has made of the number of abandoned or neglected horses.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9799","9799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418065","2015-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many prosecutions there have been for abandoning or neglecting horses in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9741","9741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418066","2015-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of horses not properly registered under passport and micro-chipping regulations in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9742","9742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418067","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effects of the proposed changes to the Tier 2 visas minimum income threshold on recruitment of NHS nursing staff in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9786","9786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418068","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ask NICE to revise the treatment criteria in NICE guidelines on eating disorders; and what recent discussions (a) he and (b) Ministers in his Department have had with NICE on eating disorder guidelines.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9782","9782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418069","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding under which categories of expenditure his Department has allocated to eating disorder support services in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9783","9783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418070","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses from outside the European Economic Area who were granted Tier 2 visas are working in the NHS in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9784","9784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418071","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the findings and recommendations of the Feel Happy (Eating) Fix on eating disorders, which took place in London on 16 June 2015.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9777","9777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418072","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time is for a NHS hernia operation for patients in (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) England.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9781","9781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418073","2015-09-11","Department for Education","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to introduce mandatory mental health training for education professionals.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9779","9779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418074","2015-09-11","Department for Education","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what training education professionals receive on identifying eating disorders and signposting support and treatment; and what guidance her Department issues to schools on eating disorders.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9780","9780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418075","2015-09-11","Home Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will include nursing on the Shortage Occupation List.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9785","9785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418076","2015-09-11","Department for Transport","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to alleviate passenger overcrowding on trains.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9778","9778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418077","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost of travel and subsistance has been to the National Offender Management Service for the operation of the nationally co-ordinated detached duty scheme since its introduction.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9816","9816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418078","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost was of (a) overtime payments, (b) required hours allowance, (c) Payment Plus, (d) constant watch, (e) bedwatch, (f) tornado, (g) dirty protest, (h) unsocial hours working payments and (i) additional committed hours within NOMS in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9817","9817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418079","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the value of Libyan assets frozen in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9796","9796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418080","2015-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Prime Minister will reverse the decision made by his predecessors not to seek compensation for all UK victims of IRA/Libyan-sponsored violence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9795","9795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418081","2015-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will establish an independent inquiry into the reasons why the Government has not sought compensation for UK victims of IRA/Libyan-sponsored terrorism; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9794","9794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418082","2015-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what criteria the Government applies to determine whether or not to seek compensation for UK victims of IRA/Libyan-sponsored violence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9788","9788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418083","2015-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions he has raised with representatives of the Libyan government compensation for UK victims of IRA/Libyan-sponsored violence since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9787","9787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418084","2015-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will meet UK victims of IRA/Libyan-sponsored violence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9713","9713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418085","2015-09-14","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to make lenalidomide available after the Patient Access Scheme for second line treatment is approved.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9753","9753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418086","2015-09-14","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NICE plans to approve the Patient Access Scheme for second line treatment with lenalidomide for patients with multiple myeloma.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9752","9752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418087","2015-09-14","Home Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions have been made under Section 13 of the Terrorism Act 2000 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9688","9688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418088","2015-09-14","Home Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Section 13 of the Terrorism Act 2000 in countering terrorism.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9689","9689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418089","2015-10-12","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the March 2015 Budget, what progress the Government has made on establishing a cross-government ministerial group to oversee future evolution of the anti-illicit tobacco strategy.","Biography information for Mark  Spencer","Mark Spencer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9677","9677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418090","2015-10-12","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 30 October 2012, Official Report, column 210W, on tobacco: smuggling, how many people were convicted in relation to seizures made by the Border Force and HM Revenue and Customs in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mark  Spencer","Mark Spencer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9679","9679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418091","2015-10-12","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Answer of 30 October 2012, Official Report, column 210W, on tobacco: smuggling, how many individual seizures were made by the Border Force and HM Revenue and Customs in each of the last five years; and what the total volume of the products seized in each year was.","Biography information for Mark  Spencer","Mark Spencer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9678","9678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418092","2015-10-12","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much (a) the UK Border Force and (b) HM Revenue and Customs spent on delivering the Government's tobacco smuggling strategy in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mark  Spencer","Mark Spencer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9684","9684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418093","2015-09-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of land is covered by a local plan.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9722","9722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418094","2015-09-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of land is covered by a neighbourhood plan.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9723","9723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418095","2015-09-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local councils have local plans in place.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9724","9724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418096","2015-09-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of air quality action plans in tackling local pockets of air pollution.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9729","9729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418097","2015-09-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the level of take-up of mathematics and science apprenticeships so far in 2015.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9687","9687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418098","2015-09-11","Cabinet Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on levels of self-employment in the (a) construction, (b) care, (c) cleaning, and (d) hospitality sectors.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9692","9692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418099","2015-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the need to (a) review or (b) increase Green Investment Bank (i) CEO or (ii) board salaries in the event of privatisation.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9667","9667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418100","2015-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when his Department plans to publish the post-2015 strategy for the prevention of torture.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9704","9704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418101","2015-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to her Department's announcement of 22 July 2015 on renewable energy subsidies, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on international investor confidence in the UK (a) solar and (b) renewable sectors of that announcement; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9694","9694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418102","2015-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of announcements on solar policy since May 2015 on (a) current and (b) future employment levels in that sector; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9693","9693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418103","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to his letter to the hon. Member for Brighton, Pavilion, dated 24 July 2015, what estimate he has made of the number of ISIL fighters killed as a result of UK strike activity; and what estimate the Global Coalition to Counter ISIL has made of civilian casualties arising from its activities.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9798","9798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418104","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to ensure that civil society and members of the public are able to contribute to a consultation on a British Bill of Rights.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9703","9703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418105","2015-09-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students studying at the University of Central Lancashire received hardship grants in the 2015-16 academic year.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9764","9764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418106","2015-09-14","Church Commissioners","2015-09-09","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, which Church of England dioceses have published regulations on monuments on burial plots and inscriptions on gravestones; which dioceses (a) allow and (b) do not allow nicknames on gravestones; which dioceses allow monuments; which dioceses (i) allow and (ii) do not allow pictorial etchings on gravestones; and which dioceses (A) allow and (B) do not allow free-standing containers on burial plots.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9765","9765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418107","2015-09-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 16 of Reducing the risks of flooding and coastal erosion: An investment plan, published by her Department in December 2014, what progress the Environment Agency has reported on the number and location of projects starting in development, construction and completing as well as the reasons for delay.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9766","9766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418108","2015-09-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effects of the proposed closure of Ormskirk Magistrates' Court on the (a) costs and (b) length of journeys to Preston Magistrates' Court for people from Skelmersdale, Halsall, Scarisbrick and other parts of West Lancashire who rely on public transport; and what assessment he has made of the effect on Preston Magistrates' Court of the length and complexity of journeys on public transport by defendants.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9767","9767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418109","2015-09-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many representations his Department has received from (a) councillors, (b) hon. Members and (c) members of the public expressing concerns over the working of local enterprise partnerships in the last three years.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9825","9825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418110","2015-09-14","Cabinet Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to extend freedom of information to local enterprise partnerships.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9826","9826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418111","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date the tender which led to the Money Advice Service finding 100 new debt advisers posts at Stepchange was published; how many and who the shortlisted bidders were for that tender; on what date the decision on the tender was made; and if he will publish in full information on to how that tendering process was undertaken.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Mr Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9818","9818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418112","2015-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what support the Government is providing for early stage innovation in the low carbon sector.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9797","9797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418113","2015-09-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department showed the Countryside Alliance the Hunting Act 2004 (Exempt Hunting) (Amendment) Order 2015 in draft prior to publication; and what representations she received from that organisation on the matters covered by that Order prior to its publication.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9715","9715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418114","2015-09-14","Home Office","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, where each of the (a) 68 clandestine migrants and (b) four lorry drivers are that were stopped in Harwich in June 2015; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9820","9820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418115","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to people diagnosed with hepatitis C acquired through NHS blood treatments where medical records have been lost.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9702","9702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418116","2015-09-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of biomass energy crops in delivering carbon reductions as set out in the UK Bioenergy Strategy.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9776","9776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418117","2015-09-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment her Department has made of the capacity of the UK to meet the 20 per cent renewable target for 2020 set out in the EU Renewable Energy Directive.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9681","9681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418118","2015-09-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the cost to the public purse of subsidies paid to the (a) solar and (b) wind power industries in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9682","9682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418119","2015-09-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the total subsidy paid for biomass production for the purposes of power generation in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9683","9683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418120","2015-09-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the value of biomass imported for the purposes of power generation in each of the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9775","9775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418121","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 5988, whether his Department operates a licensing system for trial hunting on its land.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9790","9790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418122","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 5988, whether his Department permits hunting exempt under Schedule 1 of the Hunting Act 2004 on its land.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9690","9690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418123","2015-09-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many complaints his Department has received from ex-service personnel about the Armed Forces Compensation Scheme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9727","9727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418124","2015-09-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 5988, whether any live quarry has been killed during a trail hunt on his Department's land.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9728","9728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418125","2015-09-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many awards of £570,000 his Department paid out under their Armed Forces Compensation Scheme since it was established.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9768","9768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418126","2015-09-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the amount paid out in awards from the the Armed Forces Compensation Scheme is since it was established in April 2005.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9769","9769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418127","2015-09-14","Department for Transport","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on the payment of salaries through (a) payroll companies and (b) personal service companies to staff who work on projects that are part-funded by his Department.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9663","9663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418128","2015-09-14","Department for Transport","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Dame Colette Bowe has submitted a draft of her report on the planning of major projects to his Department.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9673","9673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418129","2015-09-14","Department for Transport","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the publication by Network Rail of a CP5 Business Plan update in March 2015 was a regulated output of Control Period 5.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9674","9674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418130","2015-09-14","Department for Transport","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the four-tracking of the Midland Main Line from Bedford to Kettering and Corby is contingent upon the recommendations of the Hendy Review.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9751","9751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418131","2015-09-14","Department for Transport","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what support he has provided to rail freight operators as a result of the recent disruption to Channel Tunnel services.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9750","9750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418132","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress he has made on Action 36 of the UK Anti-Corruption Plan; and when he expects corporate criminal liability to be introduced.","Biography information for Lord Davies of Gower","Byron Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9735","9735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418133","2015-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the Trade in Services Agreement on the domestic oil and gas industry; and when her Department plans to update that assessment.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9800","9800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418134","2015-09-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken in negotiations of the Trade in Services Agreement to ensure that workers' rights are protected.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9831","9831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418135","2015-09-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he expects the Trade in Services Agreement to entail amendments to (a) employment law, (b) trade union law and (c) company law in the UK.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9832","9832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418136","2015-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the Trade in Services Agreement on employment levels in the UK (a) economy and (b) transport industry.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9802","9802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418137","2015-09-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on the inclusion of (a) employment law and (b) trades union rights in the Trade in Services Agreement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9664","9664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418138","2015-09-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment has been made of the potential effect that the Trade in Services Agreement will have on (a) employment law and (b) trade union rights; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9665","9665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418139","2015-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he made of the potential effect of the Trade in Services Agreement on the transport industry; and when his Department plans to update that assessment.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9801","9801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418140","2015-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the life sciences industry generated in trade surplus for (a) the UK and (b) Scotland in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9745","9745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418141","2015-09-14","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effects of the measures to restrict finance cost relief for landlords, announced in the Summer Budget 2015, on the level of housing demand in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9773","9773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418142","2015-09-14","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effects of the measures to restrict finance cost relief for landlords, announced in the Summer Budget 2015, on the supply of property in the private rented sector in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9770","9770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418143","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with Ministers in the Scottish Government on (a) Scottish Government borrowing by means of (i) the National Loans Fund, (ii) private financial institutions and (iii) the issuing of Scottish Government bonds and (b) Scotland's Fiscal Framework in general.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9743","9743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418144","2015-09-14","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effects of the measures to restrict finance cost relief for landlords, announced in the Summer Budget 2015, on the overall costs of Housing Benefit in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9774","9774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418145","2015-09-14","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effects of the measures to restrict finance cost relief for landlords, announced in the Summer Budget 2015, on levels of investment in the private rented sector in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9771","9771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418146","2015-09-14","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effects of the measures to restrict finance cost relief for landlords, announced in the Summer Budget 2015, on the average rent payable in the private rented sector in (a) Scotland and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9772","9772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418147","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of forestalling in relation to the land and building transaction tax; and what additional sums the Scottish Government has requested in transfer to the Scottish Budget for 2015-16 in relation to that tax.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9811","9811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418225","2015-09-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to mitigate the effect of recent changes in EU policy on the sugar industry.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901326","901326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418243","2015-09-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate the annual cost to businesses of inconsistent broadband coverage.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901327","901327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418286","2015-09-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will estimate the annual cost to businesses of inconsistent broadband coverage.","Biography information for Patricia Gibson","Patricia Gibson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901342","901342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418767","2015-09-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure employers fairly collect and distribute tips left by customers.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901340","901340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418768","2015-09-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to support people on low pay.","Biography information for Matt Warman","Matt Warman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901341","901341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418769","2015-09-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in funding for further education on young people.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901344","901344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/418770","2015-09-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with Ministers in the Welsh Government on economic development in the Deeside area.","Biography information for Mr David Jones","Mr David Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901324","901324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417510","2015-09-10","Attorney General","2015-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, in how many murder trials the issue of the loss of control of the defendant was raised in each year since 2010; and if he will estimate in how many such trials (a) female and (b) male defendants were not convicted of murder on those grounds.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9375","9375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417511","2015-09-11","Attorney General","2015-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, in how many cases of assisted suicide the Crown Prosecution Service has received files in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9398","9398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417512","2015-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the current number of intermediary qualification apprenticeships offering qualifications equivalent to five GCSE passes.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9449","9449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417513","2015-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of people currently enrolled on apprenticeships who were employed by the same organisation prior to the apprenticeship.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9450","9450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417514","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support students in part-time higher education.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9358","9358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417515","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to encourage employers to invest in part-time courses in higher education.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9359","9359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417516","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the reasons for changes in the number of students enrolling in part-time higher education courses in the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9360","9360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417517","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to support part-time higher education courses through Local Enterprise Partnerships.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9357","9357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417518","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of treating ethnic minority groups as a priority by the National Careers Service.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9368","9368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417519","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many officials in his Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9495","9495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417520","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9531","9531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417521","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which external organisations officials in his Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9513","9513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417522","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many export licences have been issued for export defence material to Saudi Arabia since April 2010; and for what purpose each such licence was so issued.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9577","9577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417523","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on UK exporters of recently imposed Russian restrictions on the sale of food and cleaning products; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9580","9580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417524","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the relationship is between the priorities of the Grand Challenges and the Eight Great Technologies programmes.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9583","9583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417525","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the comments made by a spokesperson for his Department as reported in The Guardian on 16 August 2015, when the final figure on the number of Growth Vouchers issued will be available.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9584","9584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417526","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what guidance he has issued to the Research Councils on deadlines for grant funding applications since May 2015; and what effect the forthcoming Spending Review has had on that guidance.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9581","9581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417527","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions Ministers and officials of his Department have had with the Research Councils on grant funding application deadlines.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9582","9582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417528","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish the report commissioned by his Department from McKinsey on the executive agencies and bodies funded by his Department; and what other external reports he has commissioned on such agencies and bodies since May 2010.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9587","9587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417529","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what external reviews or research he has commissioned on the future of the Research Councils.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9588","9588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417530","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Members for Ashfield and Streatham dated 15 June 2015 regarding women executives on company boards.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9619","9619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417531","2015-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that (a) a comprehensive set of shared e-infrastructure services and (b) funding for such services are provided for the higher education sector.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9643","9643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417532","2015-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of jobs in each Scottish parliamentary constituency have an hourly pay below the Living Wage as defined by the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9647","9647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417533","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, who was consulted in deciding on the personnel and terms of reference of a review into the secondary ticketing market; and how such consultees were selected.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9629","9629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417534","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many consortia (a) containing and (b) not containing UK businesses have (i) made bids for and (ii) been successful in securing funding under the Eureka Eurostars programme in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9625","9625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417535","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much public funding was spent by Innovate UK (a) in total and (b) under each of its programmes in each financial year since 2010-11; and what proportion of that spending was on research and development in each such year.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9626","9626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417536","2015-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Ashfield the Shadow Business Secretary on women executives on company boards dated 15 June 2015.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9636","9636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417537","2015-09-11","Cabinet Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what definition of social investment is used by his Department.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9607","9607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417538","2015-09-10","Cabinet Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which external organisations officials in (a) his Department and (b) Number 10 Downing Street have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9489","9489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417539","2015-09-10","Cabinet Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many officials within (a) his Department and (b) Number 10 Downing Street are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9488","9488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417540","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether public expenditure on infrastructure and access associated with a proposed new runway in South East England would be subject to the Barnett Formula.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9356","9356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417541","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many notices or demands for payment were posted to companies and individuals by HM Revenue and Customs for amounts less than £1 in each financial year since 2012-13.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9352","9352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417542","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, under what circumstances spending from the UK Conflict, Stability and Security Fund will be counted towards the Government targets of spending (a) 0.7 per cent of gross national income (GNI) on overseas development assistance, (b) 2 per cent of GNI on defence and (c) towards both of these targets.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9455","9455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417543","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, by what process his Department set the age limit for passing on a pension tax free.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9402","9402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417544","2015-09-14","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether Ministers in his Department met representatives of the Financial Conduct Authority (FCA) to discuss the FCA interest rate hedging products redress scheme in January 2013.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9410","9410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417545","2015-09-14","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Financial Conduct Authority made an estimate of the potential liability of (a) Lloyds and (b) RBS under the interest rate hedging products redress scheme during the development of that scheme.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9411","9411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417546","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect on (a) relative and (b) absolute child poverty of the four year freeze announced in the Summer Budget 2015 on the uprating of (i) tax credits and (ii) child benefit.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9470","9470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417547","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect on the average overall value of the pensions of people in Scotland over the course of their retirement of changes to (a) drawdown products and (b) switching retirement income products introduced in April 2015.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9473","9473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417548","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9547","9547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417549","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many officials in his Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9510","9510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417550","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which external organisations officials in his Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9528","9528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417551","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what definition of social investment is used by his Department.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9608","9608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417552","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with his Cabinet colleagues on the use of technology in (a) making savings to the public purse and (b) improving public services.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9611","9611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417553","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the effect on (a) relative and (b) absolute child poverty of (i) the two child limit for the child element of Tax Credit; and (ii) the removal of the family element of Child Tax Credit announced in the July Budget.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9627","9627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417554","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the savings that will accrue to the public purse from capping public sector pay increases at 1 per cent in each of (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19, (d) 2019-20 and (e) 2020-21.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9624","9624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417555","2015-09-11","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to publish an analysis of the distributional impact of changes alongside each Budget Statement in this Parliament.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9644","9644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417556","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department expects to be raised in VAT on Severn Bridge tolls in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017 and (d) 2018.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9658","9658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417557","2015-09-14","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he plans to publish the minutes and papers from the last two meetings of the Joint Exchequer Committee; and if he will place those documents in the Library.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9662","9662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417558","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assumptions his Department made about the likely percentage growth of public sector pay in (a) 2016-17, (b) 2017-18, (c) 2018-19, (d) 2019-20 and (e) 2020-21 before announcing the policy of a one per cent cap on public sector pay increases in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9659","9659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417559","2015-09-10","HM Treasury","2015-09-08","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the effect on revenue accruing to the Exchequer of restricting the additional nil-rate inheritance band (a) to residences only, (b) to direct descendants only and (c) by tapered withdrawal between £2,000,000 and £2,350,000.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9660","9660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417560","2015-09-10","Department for Transport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of debt that will remain outstanding after the current concession for operating the Severn Bridge expires; and between which bodies that debt will be distributed.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9661","9661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417561","2015-09-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which external organisations officials in his Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9514","9514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417562","2015-09-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to reduce the number of local government elected representatives.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9471","9471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417563","2015-09-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many officials in his Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9496","9496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417564","2015-09-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9532","9532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417565","2015-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy that local authorities each house 10 refugee families; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9493","9493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417566","2015-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of accessible homes for people with (a) muscular dystrophy, (b) neuromuscular conditions and (c) other progressive conditions.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9457","9457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417567","2015-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that the statutory maximum grant available for a Disabled Facilities Grant increases in line with inflation.","Biography information for Stuart Andrew","Stuart Andrew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9458","9458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417568","2015-09-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people (a) under 18 and (b) under 16 years of age have been allocated social housing since 2013; and what proportion of such people had children of their own.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9379","9379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417569","2015-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Homelessness Prevention Grant; and what his future plans are for this policy.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9390","9390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417570","2015-09-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which organisations owned the largest market share of (a) national radio, (b) local radio, (c) digital radio, (d) television other than pay-per-view, (e) pay-per-view television, (f) telecommunications and (g) newspapers in (i) 2000, (ii) 2005, (iii) 2010 and (iv) 2015; and what that market share was in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9376","9376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417571","2015-09-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the BBC's overall market share of (a) national, (b) local and (c) digital radio was in the most recent year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9377","9377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417572","2015-09-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9533","9533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417573","2015-09-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many officials in his Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9497","9497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417574","2015-09-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions Ministers in his Department have had with regional and devolved administrations on promoting sport and exercise in local communities.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9479","9479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417575","2015-09-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which external organisations officials in his Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9515","9515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417576","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) women and (b) men were found to be using a television without a licence by inspectors in the most recent year for which information is available; and what proportion of (i) women and (ii) men were subsequently prosecuted for a television licence offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9560","9560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417577","2015-09-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2015 to Question 6921, what the monetary values were of the successful applications in each year in the tables provided.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9556","9556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417578","2015-09-10","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the time taken by Openreach to provide for the connection of new housing developments to telephone and internet services in Sheffield, Heeley constituency.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9565","9565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417579","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what investigations were carried out by his Department prior to the statement that no UK submarines were within 150 miles of the incident involving the fishing vessel Karen.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9568","9568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417580","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what modifications will be needed at HMNB Clyde and RNAD Coulport to accept the successor submarine programme; what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of adapting the ship-lift facility at HMNB Clyde to accommodate the successor to the Vanguard class submarine; and how much of the money announced by the Chancellor of the Exchequer on 31 August 2015 will be used to undertake that work.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9569","9569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417581","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) service personnel and (b) civil servants have completed the (i) Nuclear Advanced Course, (ii) Nuclear Reactor Course, (iii) Nuclear Radiological Protection Course, (iv) Nuclear Dockyard Reactor Chemist Course and (v) Rolls Royce Nuclear Engineers Course in each financial year since 2001-02.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9572","9572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417582","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the Army Reserve's Order of Battle.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9578","9578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417583","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to recruit nuclear engineers from the civil sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9579","9579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417584","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the total value of defence-related contracts placed by his Department with suppliers based in Argyll and Bute constituency was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9570","9570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417585","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will make an estimate of Chinese defence expenditure on a Purchasing Power Parity basis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9573","9573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417586","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with (a) Ministerial colleagues and (b) the civil nuclear industry on the provision of nuclear engineers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9574","9574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417587","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on additional payments to retain nuclear engineers in service in each financial year between 2005-06 and 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9575","9575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417588","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list by rank and number of personnel in (a) the Surface Fleet, (b) the Royal Marines, (c) the Royal Fleet Auxiliary, (d) the Submarine Service and (e) the Fleet Air Arm.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9576","9576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417589","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which external organisations officials in his Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9516","9516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417590","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assets are monitoring the deployment of Severomorsk to the Arctic Ocean.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9425","9425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417591","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assets were involved in the Triplex Warrior exercise from (a) the UK, (b) NATO members and (c) non-NATO members in the (i) 2015 and (ii) 2014 exercise; what facilities in the North Sea were defended in the exercise; and if any maritime patrol aircraft took part.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9435","9435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417592","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the results of the Board of Inquiry into the incident involving a submarine and the fishing vessel Karen will be published.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9420","9420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417593","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the name was of the submarine involved in an incident with the fishing vessel Karen in April 2015; and which other Royal Navy vessels were in the area at that time.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9421","9421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417594","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason the submarine involved in the incident with the fishing vessel Karen did not surface immediately.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9422","9422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417595","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the incident involving a submarine and the fishing vessel Karen took place; and when his Department was first informed of the submarine's involvement.","Biography information for Brendan O'Hara","Brendan O'Hara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9423","9423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417596","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many officials in his Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9498","9498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417597","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9534","9534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417598","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what notice is given to emergency services in advance of visits by nuclear convoys.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9459","9459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417599","2015-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to improve the UK's aerial intelligence capacity.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9369","9369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417600","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 7 September 2015 on Royal Navy operations, if he will publish all information that the Royal Navy provided which indicated that a UK submarine was responsible for the snagging of the Karen's nets on 15 April 2015.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9641","9641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417601","2015-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Written Statement of 7 September 2015 on Royal Navy operations, when the Department was first made aware of the information that indicates that a UK submarine was responsible for snagging the Karen's nets.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9640","9640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417602","2015-09-11","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many secondary schools chose not to publish an overview of their GCSE results for the school year 2014-15.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9612","9612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417603","2015-09-11","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she plans to require secondary schools to publish an overview of their annual GCSE results.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9613","9613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417604","2015-09-11","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department's commitment to open 500 Free schools by 2020 as announced on 2 September 2015 will include those schools that open as (a) converter and (b) sponsored academies.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9642","9642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417605","2015-09-10","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools in England offer the International Baccalaureate.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9621","9621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417606","2015-09-11","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to increase the skills and qualification level of the early years workforce.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9454","9454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417607","2015-09-11","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans her Department has to ensure that there will be sufficient high quality early education places to meet the proposed target of 30 hours of free childcare a week for working parents of three and four year olds.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9444","9444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417608","2015-09-11","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to ensure there is adequate funding made available to childcare providers to provide sufficient high quality childcare places.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9451","9451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417609","2015-09-11","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people have (a) begun and (b) graduated from early years initial teacher training courses in each year since the introduction of the early years teacher status.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9452","9452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417610","2015-09-11","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to increase the supply of high quality childcare.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9453","9453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417611","2015-09-10","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many supply teachers are unable to pay into the Teacher's Pension Fund because their employers have not been granted Accepted Employer Status; and whether she has invited such employers to seek Accepted Employer Status.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9361","9361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417612","2015-09-11","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) capital and (b) revenue funding has been allocated by her Department to each local authority in the West Midlands in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9394","9394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417613","2015-09-10","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many officials in her Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9499","9499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417614","2015-09-10","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which external organisations she has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times she has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9535","9535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417615","2015-09-10","Department for Education","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which external organisations officials in her Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9517","9517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417616","2015-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which external organisations officials in her Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9518","9518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417617","2015-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many officials in her Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9500","9500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417618","2015-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what experience the consultants employed to produce the Feed-in-Tariff rates published in the current Feed-in-Tariff consultation have of working in the solar power industry.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9567","9567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417619","2015-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps she plans to take to protect people in Barnsley from potential harmful environmental effects of fracking.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9599","9599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417620","2015-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which external organisations she has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times she has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9536","9536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417621","2015-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment her Department has made of the need for financial support for those affected by fuel poverty following the end of the Green Deal Home Improvement Fund.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9443","9443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417622","2015-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what support is being made available for those affected by fuel poverty to make energy saving home improvements following the end of the Green Deal Home Improvement Fund.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9442","9442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417623","2015-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent steps she has taken to review the performance of (a) the cavity wall insulation industry and (b) the Cavity Insulation Guarantee Agency.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9388","9388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417624","2015-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people work in the solar industry in (a) London and (b) the UK; and what steps she is taking to support employment in that industry.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9362","9362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417625","2015-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether the feed-in tariff scheme will continue beyond January 2016.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9363","9363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417626","2015-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many mid-scale PV roofs were installed in (a) London and (b) the UK in 2014-15; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9364","9364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417627","2015-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when she next plans to update transparency data for ministerial expenses in her Department on the GOV.UK website.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9400","9400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417628","2015-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment she has made of the effect on investor confidence of the decision to consult on ending grandfathering under the Renewables Obligation.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9349","9349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417629","2015-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she has taken to reduce the financial penalties imposed by the European Commission on her Department relating to the Common Agricultural Policy; and what estimate she has made of the likely level of such penalties in 2016-17.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9378","9378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417630","2015-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which external organisations she has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times she has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9537","9537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417631","2015-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many officials in her Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9501","9501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417632","2015-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which external organisations officials in her Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9519","9519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417633","2015-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will have discussions with the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change on the merging of those departments.","Biography information for Mr Peter Bone","Mr Peter Bone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9592","9592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417634","2015-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons civil partnerships are not permitted in HM Embassy in South Korea.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9596","9596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417635","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Six-Monthly Report on Hong Kong, covering the period of 1 July to 31 December 2014 relating to the decision of the PRC Government to ban the Commons Foreign Affairs Committee from conducting an official inquiry by taking evidence within the Special Administrative Region of Hong Kong, whether he obtained legal advice on international law before its publication, and if he placed a record of all understandings and agreements reached by both countries under the Joint Declaration and subsequently through the Joint Liaison Group before the Foreign Affairs Committee before compiling the report; for what reasons universal suffrage was not incorporated in the Joint Declaration; and if the Government will take steps to encourage implementation of Article 45 of the Basic Law and immediately release all understandings and agreements reached by the Joint Liaison Group relating to Article 45 prior to 1990.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9618","9618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417636","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Members for Ashfield and Leeds Central dated 16 June 2015.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9634","9634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417637","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Members for Ashfield and Leeds Central and the Shadow Foreign Secretary dated 16 June 2015.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9635","9635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417638","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which external organisations officials in his Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9520","9520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417639","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials in his Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9502","9502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417640","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on the future status of Somaliland.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9564","9564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417641","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9538","9538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417642","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many British nationals have died in police custody in other countries in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9441","9441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417643","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with his counterparts in (a) Kenya, (b) Uganda, (c) South Africa, (d) Namibia and (e) other countries in Africa on measures to stop the killing of elephants and rhinos.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9438","9438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417644","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the implications for its policies of the US State Department report on Human Rights Practices in Afghanistan for 2014, published in June 2015.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9416","9416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417645","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received from the President of the European Commission on the proposed expansion of the European Resettlement Scheme for refugees.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9355","9355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417646","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Turkish counterpart on the political unrest in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9372","9372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417647","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his French counterpart on air strikes in Iraq.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9373","9373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417648","2015-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Russian counterpart on that country's escalating military intervention in Syria.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9374","9374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417649","2015-09-15","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish the expanded criteria for the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9412","9412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417650","2015-09-15","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Statement on Syrian Refugees and Counter-terrorism of 7 September 2015, Official Report, column 24, how many additional refugees the Government plans to take under the (a) Gateway programme and (b) Mandate programme over the duration of this Parliament.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9466","9466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417651","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from Heads of Government in other EU countries on the proposed European Resettlement Scheme for refugees.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9354","9354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417652","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England on recent guidance stating that NICE-recommended medicines will be funded from day 90 of publication.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9350","9350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417653","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals offer breast reconstruction to breast cancer patients.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9366","9366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417654","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent progress NHS England has made on developing new policies for in-year service developments and individual funding requests; and if NHS England will commit to a public consultation on these matters.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9346","9346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417655","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent progress NHS England has made in developing a scorecard to consider the relative ranking of specialised services in (a) clinical and (b) cost effectiveness; and if NHS England will commit to a public consultation on ranking specialised services.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9347","9347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417656","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England has had discussions with NICE on the assessment of medicines in specialised commissioning.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9348","9348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417657","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the level of provision of pancreatic cancer treatment on the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9405","9405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417658","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that expert clinicians are consulted when assessing new treatments for pancreatic cancer.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9406","9406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417659","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of training a UK citizen as a nurse; and what assessment he has made of how this figure compares with the costs of recruiting nurses from overseas.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9401","9401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417660","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of changes in cancer survival rates in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9393","9393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417661","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the current investigations being carried out by Monitor will continue following its move to single leadership with the Trust Development Authority; and whether those investigations will fall to be supervised by the new single leadership.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9415","9415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417662","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many hospitals offer breast reconstruction to breast cancer patients.","Biography information for Oliver Colvile","Oliver Colvile","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9365","9365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417663","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce the mortality rate from drug misuse in the North East.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9389","9389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417664","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the reasons are for the most recent NHS England review of the pancreatic cancer drug available on the national Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9391","9391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417665","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with which patient groups did NHS England consult before the decision was taken to remove 25 treatments from the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9395","9395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417666","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of patients who will be denied access to treatments no longer available on the national Cancer Drugs Fund list from 4 November 2015.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9396","9396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417667","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 June 2015 to Question 1281, when NHS England's Clinical Priorities Advisory Group will next hold a meeting on prioritisation.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9468","9468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417668","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of GP maternity cover posts have been left unfilled in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9490","9490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417669","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Innovative Medicines and MedTech Review plans to investigate how to reduce the period between NICE approval of a medicine and its funding by NHS trusts.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9467","9467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417670","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, under what criteria NHS England choose to fund a NICE-approved medicine before the three month period following the publication  of a positive NICE recommendation; and what steps NHS England is taking to encourage uptake of medicines after positive NICE recommendations as soon as possible.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9566","9566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417671","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what services NHS England commissions to support women and girls who have suffered female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9562","9562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417672","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many officials in his Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9503","9503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417673","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9539","9539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417674","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which external organisations officials in his Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9521","9521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417675","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the ease of access to Everolimus for Tuberous Sclerosis Complex sufferers.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9630","9630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417676","2015-09-10","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the ease of access to treatment and services for Tuberous Sclerosis Complex; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9631","9631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417677","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the budget made available for nurse recruitment by NHS trusts in England and Wales in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9652","9652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417678","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received from charities and patient groups on access to the drug Translarna for the treatment of Duchenne muscular dystrophy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9650","9650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417679","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place in the Library NHS England's terms of reference for the independent maternity review.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9606","9606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417680","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether postpartum contraception is being considered as part of NHS England's independent maternity review; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9604","9604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417681","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effects on maternal mental health of pregnancy and maternity discrimination at work; and what steps he plans to take to address this issue.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9594","9594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417682","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will take steps to reduce the time taken to approve for use drugs for the treatment of rare conditions and diseases; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9616","9616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417683","2015-09-15","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2015 to Question 6508, for what reasons his Department cannot report monthly on the litigation and Counsel's costs relating to the Freedom of Information request for the former Secretary of State for Health's diary of engagements referred to in Information Commissioner Decision Note No. FS50406024 and the subsequent appeals.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9617","9617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417684","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether availability of the drug Naloxone, under the new regulations to be introduced on 1 October 2015, will be restricted to those categorised in current Public Health England guidance.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9597","9597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417685","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of nurses that will be employed by NHS trusts in England and Wales in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9615","9615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417686","2015-09-11","Department of Health","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of patient access to innovative drugs approved under the MHRA's Early Access to Medicines Scheme ahead of NICE assessments and in the absence of any planned Cancer Drugs Fund meetings.","Biography information for Mrs Pauline Latham","Pauline Latham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9598","9598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417687","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect on funding for Greater Manchester Police of the replacement of the Police Allocation Formula.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9585","9585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417688","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of which Police Force in England and Wales will experience the highest percentage change in its funding as a result of the proposed replacement of the Police Allocation Formula.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9586","9586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417689","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the statement of 21 July 2015 on Police Funding: England and Wales, HCWS 164, what the effect on Greater Manchester Police will be of following the replacement of the Police Allocation Formula.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9622","9622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417690","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 17 July 2015 to Question 6880, what the circumstances and reasons were for the suspension of the licence of Bradford College of Management; and what the circumstances and reasons were for the suspension and revocation of the licences of (a) Bradford Metropolitan College and (b) Bradford Regional College.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9638","9638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417691","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which external organisations officials in her Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9522","9522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417692","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which external organisations she has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times she has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9540","9540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417693","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officials in her Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9504","9504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417694","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 July 2015 to Question 5239, from what countries of origin people were (a) who applied for or (b) were granted (i) asylum or (ii) another form of leave to remain.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9555","9555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417695","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to bring forward legislative proposals to tackle knife crime; and if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prohibit the carrying of a knife.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9440","9440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417696","2015-09-11","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's policy is on (a) receiving representations and (b) entering into correspondence with Members of the Scottish Parliament on behalf of constituents who are seeking asylum in the UK.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9409","9409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417697","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of pilot schemes undertaken by regional police forces to limit the resources available for the investigation of burglaries.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9417","9417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417698","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of refugees that the Government expects to receive under the expanded Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation Scheme before the end of this calendar year.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9418","9418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417699","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps her Department has taken to tackle female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9439","9439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417700","2015-09-11","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding her Department has allocated to each type of domestic and sexual violence support services in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9392","9392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417701","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce the level of illegal immigration from Calais into the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9371","9371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417702","2015-09-11","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have had their British citizenship revoked by her Department in each quarter since Q1 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9460","9460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417703","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures are in place to ensure that the police make prosecutors aware of the overseas criminal convictions of (a) foreign and (b) UK citizens appearing in court for the purposes of bail and sentencing.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9387","9387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417704","2015-09-15","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of asylum applications the Government expects to grant, not including the Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation Scheme, in (a) 2015 and (b) 2016.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9465","9465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417705","2015-09-15","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugees the Government expects to receive under the expanded Syrian Vulnerable Persons Relocation scheme in (a) 2016, (b) 2017, (c) 2018 and (d) 2019.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9413","9413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417706","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) refugees and (b) asylum seekers have been moved to the Tameside local authority area in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9351","9351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417707","2015-09-10","Home Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people in each nation and region of the UK receive support under her Department's asylum support regulations in each Government-defined period in each of the last three years.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9367","9367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417708","2015-09-11","House of Commons Commission","2015-09-08","To ask the hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what (a) overtime and (b) flexible working arrangements are in place for clerking, catering, security, Hansard and other ancillary or support staff and officers of the House during late sittings of the House.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9407","9407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417709","2015-09-11","Department for International Development","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the Prime Minister's statement of 7 September 2015, Official Report, column 23-25, when she plans to announce details of the reshaping of the aid budget referred to in that statement.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9408","9408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417710","2015-09-10","Department for International Development","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment her Department has made of the humanitarian situation in Aden.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9419","9419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417711","2015-09-10","Department for International Development","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment her Department has made of the humanitarian situation in Yemen.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9561","9561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417712","2015-09-10","Department for International Development","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with the World Health Organisation (WHO) over the structural reforms required to the WHO following the lessons learned from the organisation's response to the Ebola outbreak in West Africa.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9563","9563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417713","2015-09-10","Department for International Development","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many officials in her Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9505","9505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417714","2015-09-10","Department for International Development","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which external organisations she has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times she has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9541","9541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417715","2015-09-10","Department for International Development","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which external organisations officials in her Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9523","9523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417716","2015-09-10","Department for International Development","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's budget has been dedicated to the humanitarian crisis in Syria; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9370","9370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417717","2015-09-11","Department for International Development","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what guidelines her Department follows in regards to health data sharing in the countries in which it works.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9609","9609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417718","2015-09-11","Department for International Development","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what definition of social investment is used by her Department.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9610","9610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417719","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2015 to Question 4072, what proportion of appeals to the Tribunals Service from appellants in England relating to (a) personal independence payments, (b) employment and support allowance, (c) income support, (d) jobseeker's allowance and (e) tax credits were successful in (i) each quarter in 2014 and (ii) the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9593","9593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417720","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what impact assessment he has commissioned on the effects of court closures on access to justice in deprived areas.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9605","9605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417721","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the operating costs under each category of expenditure were of Bury Magistrates' Court in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9614","9614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417722","2015-09-10","Attorney General","2015-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of reimbursing self-employed witnesses for loss of earnings when they are obliged to attend court.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9623","9623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417723","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answers of 21 July 2015 to Questions 6745, 6746, 6747, 6748, 6749 and 6750, what the length was of each custodial sentence handed down; and which courts imposed the non-immediate custodial sentences referred to in those Answers.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9633","9633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417724","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) men and (b) women were committed to prison for the non-payment of a fine for a television licence offence in the most recent year for which information is available; and how many days each such offender spent in prison.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9632","9632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417725","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding his Department has allocated in 2015-16 for the provision of specialist legal advice and representation to new and expectant mothers who may have experienced unlawful discrimination at work.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9651","9651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417726","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2015 to Question 4115, what the reasons are for the reduction between 2010 and 2014 in the figures contained in the tables in that Answer.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9620","9620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417727","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2015 to Question 4115, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the reductions in those figures between 2010 and 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9657","9657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417728","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, for what reason contempt of court laws do not apply in the family court.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9404","9404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417729","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department (a) expected to receive and (b) received from employment tribunal fees in the year following the introduction of the scheme.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9462","9462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417730","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he will publish his Department's review of employment tribunal fees.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9463","9463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417731","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the annual cost of administering employment tribunal fee remission applications.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9464","9464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417732","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the total number of offenders convicted of cruelty to children were (a) men and (b) women in the last year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9381","9381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417733","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which (a) people and (b) organisations he has met in an official capacity since his appointment as Secretary of State for Justice.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9382","9382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417734","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which courts close routinely for a period of two consecutive weeks or more in each calendar year; and what the reason for the closure is in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9383","9383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417735","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders were given fixed-term recalls in the latest year for which information is available; and for which original offences those recalls were given.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9384","9384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417736","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of appeals heard in Crown Courts against (a) trial outcomes and (b) sentencing decisions in magistrates' courts were successful in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9385","9385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417737","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of times was that a person was received into prison in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9386","9386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417738","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which external organisations officials in his Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9524","9524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417739","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9542","9542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417740","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many officials in his Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9506","9506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417741","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners are held in open wings of closed prisons; and for which offences each such prisoner is serving their sentence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9558","9558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417742","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2015 to Question 4115, what offences were committed by the offenders on bail shown in table 1 in that Answer in (a) 2010 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9557","9557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417743","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 July 2015 to Question 6617, which offences each of the prisoners currently in open prisons who have previously absconded and were in open conditions in May 2014 had committed; and what length of sentence each such person was serving.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9553","9553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417744","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2015 to Question 4514, what the (a) sex of the offender and (b) offence type was of each person included in that Answer.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9559","9559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417745","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 July 2015 to Question 6617, which offences the prisoner currently in an open prison who had previously absconded but was allowed to move to open conditions since May 2014 had committed; and what length of sentence was being served in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9552","9552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417746","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2015 to Question 6753, what estimate he has made of the duration of the development period referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9554","9554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417747","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations he has received on his Department's review of employment tribunal fees.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9436","9436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417748","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether an internal review has been conducted of the case of Ross Underwood who absconded from HMP Springhill in May 2015; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9426","9426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417749","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his reasons are for reducing the legal aid budget.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9472","9472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417750","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will assess the effects on the (a) cost and (b) duration of journeys between prison and court of the closure of Bury Magistrates' Court.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9475","9475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417751","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much unused (a) physical courtroom capacity and (b) court time there is at Manchester and Salford Magistrates' Court in the last year; and what assessment he has made of the adequacy of unused capacity at Manchester and Salford Magistrates' Court to accommodate current levels of work at Bury Magistrates' Court.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9477","9477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417752","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much HM Courts and Tribunals Service has spent on maintenance of Bury Magistrates' Court in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9478","9478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417753","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will estimate the initial incidental cost to the public purse of transferring the work of Bury Magistrates' Court to Manchester and Salford Magistrates' Court.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9476","9476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417754","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether an internal review has been conducted of the case of Alexander Denny who absconded from HMP Ford; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9427","9427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417755","2015-09-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average length of time taken was by the Tribunals Service to administer a First-tier Tribunal Social Security and Child Support appeal in respect of (a) disability living allowance, (b) employment and support allowance, (c) income support, (d) jobseeker's allowance and (e) tax credits in (i) Coventry, (ii) the West Midlands and (iii) England in (A) each of the last six years and (B) the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9494","9494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417756","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, from which prisons prisoners have been released on temporary licence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9482","9482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417757","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners in closed prisons have been released on temporary licence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9483","9483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417758","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how long Lee Fudge had been at HMP Ford before he absconded; and whether an internal review has been conducted of the decision to move him to an open prison.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9428","9428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417759","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate HM Courts and Tribunals Service has made of the likely sale price of Bury Magistrates' Court.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9469","9469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417760","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how long Mark Chatfield had been at HMP Ford before he absconded; what proportion of his sentence he had served before being moved to HMP Ford; and whether an internal review has been conducted of the decision to move him to an open prison.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9429","9429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417761","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people who had previously been released from prison following a murder conviction were on life licence in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9430","9430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417762","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many copies of each newspaper were delivered to prisons in the most recent year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9431","9431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417763","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners currently in open prisons previously breached the conditions of their temporary licence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9432","9432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417764","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to publish responses to his Department's review of employment tribunal fees.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9433","9433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417765","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to implement all the powers set out in the Tribunals, Courts and Enforcement Act 2007.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9480","9480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417766","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for employment tribunal fee remission were (a) received and (b) awarded in each month since the introduction of tribunal fees.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9491","9491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417767","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2015 to Question 3603, how many offenders serving a sentence for murder (a) absconded and (b) escaped; and in what circumstances those offenders absconded or escaped in each case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9484","9484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417768","2015-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the annual administration costs of the employment tribunal fee scheme.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9492","9492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417769","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what proportion of (a) men's and (b) women's prisons are prisoners eligible for release on temporary licence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9485","9485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417770","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) prosecutions and (b) convictions there were for dog fighting in 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9486","9486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417771","2015-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many absconds from prison occurred in each month of the most recent year for which information is available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9487","9487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417772","2015-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many officials in her Department are engaged in research into the effects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9507","9507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417773","2015-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which external organisations she has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times she has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9543","9543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417774","2015-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which external organisations officials in her Department have met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many meetings such officials have had with each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9525","9525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417775","2015-09-10","Prime Minister","2015-09-08","To ask the Prime Minister, which external organisations he has met to discuss the consequences of the UK leaving the EU in each of the last three years; and how many times he has met each such organisation.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9544","9544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417776","2015-09-10","Prime Minister","2015-09-08","To ask the Prime Minister, whether the Government has carried out a cross-departmental assessment of the strategic implications of the targeted killing of British citizens outside declared war zones.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9571","9571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417777","2015-09-14","Prime Minister","2015-09-08","To ask the Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of whether the Caroline principles on the right to self-defence under Article 51 of the UN Charter have been strictly applied by the UK Government.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9656","9656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417778","2015-09-14","Prime Minister","2015-09-08","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will ensure that there is a debate in the House before further UK military intervention is taken in (a) Syria and (b) Libya.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9655","9655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417779","2015-09-10","Cabinet Office","2015-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if the Government will devise and disclose a distinct UK drones and targeted killing policy as part of the Strategic Defence and Security Review.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9637","9637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/417780","2015-09-14","Ministry of Defence","2015-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government has compiled a list of people for targeted killing outside Iraq.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 9654","9654"
