"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830587","2018-01-30","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department’s upcoming consultation on social care will include a review of prices charged by care homes to people funding their own care.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 125115","125115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830588","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-25","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance her Department has issued to jobcentres on processing claimants who have moved from one job centre catchment area to another, particularly when a claimant moves to or from a universal credit full service rollout area to one that does not yet offer universal credit.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 125116","125116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829783","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Government plans to respond to the Review of Survivor Benefits in Occupational Pension Schemes, published in June 2014.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124570","124570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829785","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 22 December 2017 to Question 120088, on Mental Health Services: Children and Young People, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in the level of local authority funding on the provision of child and adolescent mental health services in (a) Lewisham constituency, (b) Southwark, (c) London and (d) England; and how his Department plans to make good any shortfalls resulting from those changes.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124571","124571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829786","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the surface of the improved road connection between Sheffield and Manchester as proposed by Transport for the North will be constructed using all weather materials.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124572","124572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829787","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Secretary of State plans to reform the planning system to ensure that Jewish religious schools can develop barriers and other security infrastructure to ensure the safety of pupils and staff.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124573","124573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829789","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether the Secretary of State plans to reform the planning system to ensure that Muslim religious schools can develop barriers and other security infrastructure to ensure the safety of pupils and staff.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124574","124574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829790","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to reform the planning system to allow Christian religious schools to develop physical barriers and other security infrastructure to ensure the safety of pupils and staff.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124575","124575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829791","2018-01-29","House of Commons Commission","2018-01-24","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what criteria the Commission applies to people applying for press passes.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124576","124576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829793","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what measures are in place to ensure that professional athletes who suffer from hearing impairments and cannot register under the British Paralympic Association are not at a disadvantage when having to compete alongside other athletes who do not have hearing impairments.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124577","124577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829794","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to encourage employers as a result of the closure of the Employer Supported Childcare vouchers scheme to engage with and support employees who are parents.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124578","124578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829795","2018-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what information his Department holds on the rate of New Stores Rejects for his Department's contracts with Babcock International.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124579","124579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829797","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to strengthen the rights of freeholders against developers on newbuild estates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lucy Allan","Lucy Allan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124580","124580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829798","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether criminals make use of cyber-crime in the illegal wildlife trade.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124581","124581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829799","2018-01-29","Scotland Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether he plans to renew Keith Cochrane's membership of the Joint Management Board of the Scotland Office at the end of his three year term.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124582","124582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829801","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans the Government has to implement the EU Insolvency, Restructuring and Second Chance Directive.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124583","124583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829802","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the contribution was of (a) infrastructure improvements not being scheduled to be completed according to the franchise agreement and (b) revenue having fallen below what had been agreed under franchise agreement to the East Coast rail franchise being ended.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124584","124584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829804","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 122438 on Food: Waste, whether he has plans to apply a similar target for the incineration of food waste.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124585","124585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829805","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of Sate for the Home Department, what account her Department is taking of provisions relating to the alignment of basic living costs for victims of modern slavery and asylum seekers under the EU Directive and Convention on Action against Trafficking in Human Beings in developing its reforms of the National Referral Mechanism.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124586","124586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829806","2018-01-30","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish an assessment of the cumulative effect of policy measures on funding for supported housing from those measures set out in the Autumn Statement 2015 to date.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124587","124587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829808","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the ability of the General Medical Council to investigate concerns about doctors working in the NHS; and if he will make an assessment of the merits of lifting the GMC's 5-year rule on investigations.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124588","124588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829809","2018-01-29","Wales Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will list the attendees of the Severnside summit held on 22 January 2018.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124589","124589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829810","2018-01-29","Wales Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will list the invitees to the Severnside summit held on 22 January 2018 who did not attend.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124590","124590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829812","2018-01-29","Wales Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the total cost to the public purse of the Severnside summit held on 22 January 2018 was.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124591","124591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829813","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to increase voter registration among attainers; and if she will issue special guidance to electoral registration officers on working with schools to increase voter registration among school leavers.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124592","124592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829815","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to review the declaration of local connection to enable people without a fixed address to register to vote online.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124593","124593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829816","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government supports the continued existence of the edited electoral register.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124594","124594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829817","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on the health benefits of bike-share schemes.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124595","124595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829819","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will commission a distributional impact assessment of his Department’s policy to close childcare vouchers.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124596","124596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829820","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative estimate he has made of the number of families who will receive support under (a) tax-free childcare and (b) childcare vouchers.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124597","124597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829822","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the findings of KPMG's Autonomous Vehicles Readiness Index, published in January 2018, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that UK roads are ready for autonomous vehicles.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124598","124598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829823","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the level of freedom available for civil society groups operating in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124599","124599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829825","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the (a) level, (b) sources, and (c) effect of political violence in Bangladesh.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124600","124600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829826","2018-01-30","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the location of Vietnamese victims of modern slavery found in the UK in the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124601","124601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829827","2018-01-29","Wales Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department has spent on bottled water in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124602","124602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829829","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will conduct an assessment of the effect of RBS bank branch closures on free access to cash in Scotland; and what discussions he has had with the Payment Systems Regulator on potential intervention with respect to a reduction in the availability of free access to cash.","Biography information for Stewart Hosie","Stewart Hosie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124603","124603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829831","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions his Department has had with the Scottish Government on the home use of abortion medication in England.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124604","124604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829832","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his counterpart in the  Nigerian Government on recent violent clashes among tribes, herdsmen and farmers.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124605","124605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829834","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the (a) human rights and (b) security situation in Nigeria.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124606","124606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829835","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding has been allocated from the public purse to roads and highways in Hertfordshire since 2010.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124607","124607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829836","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of removing the rent cap for tenants of the Grenfell Walkways who have not yet been rehoused on the ability of those tenants to afford their interim accommodation.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124608","124608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829838","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's notice, entitled Expression of interest in providing legal services to victims of trafficking and modern slavery, published on 14 December 2017, what steps her Department plans to take to ensure that those who respond to the expression of interest have expertise on trafficking and modern slavery.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124609","124609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829839","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's notice, entitled Expression of interest in providing legal services to victims of trafficking and modern slavery, published on 14 December 2017, what funding will be made available for (a) legal advice and (b) other associated expenses such as interpreters and expert reports.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124610","124610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829841","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's notice, entitled Expression of interest in providing legal services to victims of trafficking and modern slavery, published on 14 December 2017, whether there will be any cost to victims of trafficking who access the services resulting from that expression of interest.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124611","124611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829842","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to her Department's notice, entitled Expression of interest in providing legal services to victims of trafficking and modern slavery, published on 14 December 2017, whether the providers of legal services in response to that expression of interest will be required to continue to advise their client up to a (a) National Referral Mechanism Conclusive Grounds decision and (b) any decision regarding a grant, discretionary leave to remain or appeal.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124612","124612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829843","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what guidance his Department provides to dental practices on the promotion of private tooth-whitening procedures in their surgeries.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124613","124613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829845","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to Answer Questions 121053 and 121054 tabled on 21 December 2017 by the hon. Member for Oxford West and Abingdon.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124614","124614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829846","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average journey time between Oxford and London Paddington station is (a) at present and (b) planned to be after the electrification of that route.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124615","124615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829848","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent online sales of illegal ivory.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124616","124616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829849","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress is being made on implementing the NHS England Cancer Strategy in Oxfordshire.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124617","124617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829851","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children's centres have not received an Ofsted inspection in the last five years.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124618","124618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829852","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has made an assessment of the suitability of (a) the Registration of Marriage Bill [Lords], (b) the Civil Partnerships, Marriages and Deaths (Registration Etc.) Bill and (c) the Registration of Marriage (No. 2) Bill to act as legislative vehicles to allow the Government to change the law in order to allow a mother's details to be recorded on marriage certificates; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124619","124619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829853","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reasons he has established a dedicated national security communications unit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124620","124620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829854","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which (a) Government department and (b) Minister will have responsibility for the new national security communications unit.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124621","124621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829855","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse will be of the new national security communications unit.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124622","124622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829857","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether any Ministers in his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educational Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124623","124623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829858","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any Ministers in her Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educational Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124624","124624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829860","2018-01-29","Scotland Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether any Ministers in his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educational Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124625","124625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829861","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether any Ministers in his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educatonal Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124626","124626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829862","2018-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any Ministers in his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educational Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124627","124627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829864","2018-01-29","Wales Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether any Ministers in his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educational Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124628","124628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829865","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any Ministers in her Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educatonal Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124629","124629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829866","2018-01-29","Northern Ireland Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether any Ministers in her Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educational Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124630","124630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829868","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any Ministers in his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educatonal Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124631","124631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829869","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether any Ministers from his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educatonal Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124632","124632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829871","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether any Ministers from his department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educatonal Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124633","124633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829872","2018-01-29","Department for International Development","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether any Ministers in her Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educatonal Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124634","124634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829873","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether any Ministers in his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educatonal Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124635","124635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829876","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether any Ministers in his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educational Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124636","124636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829877","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether any Ministers in his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educational Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124637","124637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829879","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether any Ministers from his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educatonal Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124638","124638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829880","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether any Ministers in his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educatonal Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124639","124639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829882","2018-01-29","Department for International Trade","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether any Ministers in his Department attended the Presidents Club Charity Dinner run by the Meller Educatonal Trust in an official capacity.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124640","124640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829883","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings he had with the Government Chief Scientific Adviser between 1 October and 31 December 2017.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124641","124641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829885","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Clean Growth Strategy, published on 12 October 2017, if his Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of reducing funding to biomass conversion and increase the resources available for wind and solar energy exploitation.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124642","124642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829886","2018-01-29","Department for International Trade","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, who has to date confirmed their attendance at the next meeting of the Board of Trade in the first quarter of 2018.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124643","124643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829887","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will write to RBS to ask whether it plans to provide ATMs and community banking services in respect of branch closures in Scotland.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124644","124644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829889","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations he has received from (a) the Payment Systems Regulator and (b) LINK on free to use ATMs in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124645","124645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829890","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of plastic waste which was (a) incinerated and (b) sent to landfill in the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124646","124646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829891","2018-01-31","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department is doing to improve the diagnosis of mothers suffering with post-natal mental health problems.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124647","124647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829893","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Government Minister will have responsibility for the fake news rapid response team.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124648","124648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829894","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what criteria the fake news rapid response team will use to decide whether news is fake or not.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124649","124649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829896","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what powers the Government plans to give to the fake news rapid response unit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124650","124650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829897","2018-01-31","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking in response to the finding by the Gambling Commission that 2 million people in the UK are addicted to gambling.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124651","124651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829898","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if the Government will take steps to fund the Transport for the North's Strategic Transport Plan for the North to at least the same level per head of population as is invested in transport in Greater London.","Biography information for Judith Cummins","Judith Cummins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124652","124652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829900","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 123454 on 22nd January 2018, which local authority areas have shown a decline in life expectancy of (a) males at birth, (b) females at birth, (c) males at 65 and (d) females at 65.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124653","124653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829901","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, the publication of the Law Commission‘s Thirteenth Programme of Law Reform, what further steps his Department plans to take to review legislation on offensive online communications; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124654","124654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829903","2018-01-31","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of refugees who will be resettled in the UK under the Gateway Protection Programme in 2018.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124655","124655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829904","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve pupil attainment in deprived areas of Greater London.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124656","124656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829906","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to close the attainment gap between boys and girls.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124657","124657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829907","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage more men to enter the teaching profession.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124658","124658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829908","2018-01-31","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of refugees who will be resettled in the UK under the asylum route in 2018.","Biography information for Meg Hillier","Meg Hillier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124659","124659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829910","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to devolve the adult education budget to local authorities which are not part of a mayoral combined authority.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124660","124660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829911","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the status is of the Health Protection (Ships and Aircraft) Regulations.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124661","124661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829913","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the budget was for non-apprenticeship adult education in each year since 2010; and what the budget is for adult education to 2020.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124662","124662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829914","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much Government and supplier obligation energy efficiency investment there was in each year between 2012-13 to 2016-17; and how many homes were insulated under Government programmes in each of those years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124663","124663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829916","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the average GCSE score was for pupils in (a) Barnsley and (b) England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124664","124664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829917","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many claimants of childcare vouchers there were in Barnsley East constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124665","124665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829918","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people in Barnsley East constituency who will take up the tax-free childcare service.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124666","124666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829920","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of young people leaving educational institutions after completing A-Level studies in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) East Hampshire constituency and (c) England enrolled in university courses in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124667","124667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829921","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children with autism as their primary educational special need received a permanent or fixed period exclusion in Barnsley in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124668","124668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829923","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Clean Growth Strategy, published in October 2017, what estimate his Department has made of the amount of investment required each year to meet the target for as many homes as possible to be brought up to EPC Band C by 2035.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124669","124669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829924","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children with an education, health and care plan or a statement of special educational needs received a permanent or fixed period exclusion in Barnsley in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124670","124670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829925","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the proportion of (a) primary and (b) secondary aged children in (i) Barnsley and (ii) South Yorkshire who are attending a school rated (A) outstanding and (B) good by Ofsted.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124671","124671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829926","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children in (a) Barnsley and (b) South Yorkshire who are (i) eligible and (ii) not eligible for free school meals reached the expected standard in (A) reading, (B) writing, (C) maths and (D) all of these subjects at the end of Key Stage 2 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124672","124672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829928","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many and what proportion of people his Department estimates to have lived in fuel poverty in each parliamentary constituency in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124673","124673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829929","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the UK Visas and Immigration to send a response to the email of 6 October 2017 sent on behalf of a constituent, subsequently chased on 22 November by email and on 21 December by telephone, reference B1275719; and what is the reason taken in responding to that correspondence.","Biography information for Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","Mr Tanmanjeet Singh Dhesi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124674","124674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829930","2018-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2018 to Question 123707, on Warships: Shipbuilding, if he will place a copy of his Department's internal research on the socio-economic effects of government-supported shipbuilding that was referred to in the Parker report and the National Shipbuilding Strategy in the Library.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124675","124675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829932","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of socio-economic background on the uptake of arts subjects at GCSE level.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124676","124676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829933","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to increase the uptake of arts subjects at GCSE level; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124677","124677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829935","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2018 to Question 123035, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of introducing an automated system for universal credit claimants to reset their login details.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124678","124678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829936","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many eligibility codes for 30 hours free childcare have been (a) generated and (b) validated in (i) Coventry South constituency and (b) Coventry.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124679","124679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829937","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when data on the number of badgers culled in 2017 in the Supplementary Badger Disease Control Areas of Gloucestershire and Somerset will be published.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124680","124680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829939","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to implement the recommendation of the Chief Coroner, set out in his Annual Report 2016 - 2017, that coroner areas should provide an out-of-hours service to meet the needs of those whose faiths require early burial.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124681","124681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829940","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many elective operations in the NHS have been cancelled in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124682","124682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829942","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings have taken place between Ministers of his Department or members of its Low Carbon Fuels team and counterparts in other countries on E10 fuel and overseas experiences of its implementation since 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124683","124683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829943","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had any discussions with his Canadian counterpart on securing the support of the Government of Canada for (a) a UN mandated global arms embargo on Burma and (b) a referral of the situation in Burma to the International Criminal Court.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124684","124684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829944","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many males who were resident in Wales at the time of their sentence are serving prison sentences in England.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124685","124685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829946","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) male and (b) female young offenders who were resident in Wales at the time of their sentence are serving sentences in England.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124686","124686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829947","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his policy is on the use of electronic training devices for dogs.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124687","124687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829949","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what meetings he has had with members of the UK Rohingya community to discuss the Government's response to the crisis in Burma and Bangladesh.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124688","124688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829950","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners in Wales were residents of England at the time of their sentencing.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124689","124689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829951","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the level of provision of Welsh language services in prisons in (a) Wales and (b) England.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124690","124690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829953","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the level of provision of Welsh language activities in prisons in (a) Wales and (b) England.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124691","124691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829954","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to regulate the sale of loot boxes to people aged under under 18.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124692","124692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829956","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to Ofgem's Biomass Sustainability dataset 2015-2016, published on 22 March 2017, what assessment he has made of the effect of UK biomass production on deforestation.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124693","124693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829957","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what records his Department holds on (a) how many patients have had operations postponed since 1 January 2018 and (b) what the average waiting time was to reschedule those operations.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124694","124694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829959","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made an assessment of the number of virgin forests that have been affected by biomass production in the past three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124695","124695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829960","2018-01-29","Department for International Development","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the planned allocation of funding from her Department in respect of the Syrian crisis is for (a) 2018 and (b) 2019; and what proportion of that funding will be spent (i) inside and (ii) outside Syria.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124696","124696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829962","2018-01-29","Department for International Development","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Department's funding in response to the Syrian crisis to date was delivered by means of (a) UK organisations, (b) UN agencies, (c) international NGOs and (d) Syrian NGOs.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124697","124697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829963","2018-01-29","Department for International Development","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Global Disability Summit in July 2018 has on its agenda the needs of disabled people in Syria and the support systems those people require in order to be able to access education and work.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124698","124698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829965","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much his Department has spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124699","124699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829966","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much his Department has spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124700","124700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829967","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much his Department has spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124701","124701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829969","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how much his Department has spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality since it was established.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124702","124702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829970","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been allocated Legal Aid funding to pursue (a) exceptional and complex cases and b) other cases, in the most recent three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124703","124703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829972","2018-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124704","124704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829973","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much her Department has spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124705","124705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829975","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department has spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124706","124706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829976","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse was of providing Legal Aid in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124707","124707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829977","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department has spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124708","124708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829979","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much his Department spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124709","124709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829980","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the effect of recent changes in welfare provision on the number of children living in poverty in Oldham West and Royton constituency.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124710","124710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829982","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much his Department spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124711","124711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829983","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list the most frequently given grounds for refusal of Legal Aid.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124712","124712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829985","2018-01-29","Department for International Trade","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how much his Department has spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each financial year since its establishment.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124713","124713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829986","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much his Department spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124714","124714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829987","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124715","124715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829990","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124716","124716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829991","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124717","124717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829993","2018-01-29","Scotland Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much his Department spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124718","124718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829994","2018-01-29","Wales Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much his Department spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124719","124719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829996","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department spent on (a) art, (b) wine and (c) hospitality in each of the last seven financial years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124720","124720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829997","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much has been spent from the public purse on the High Speed 2 project to date.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124721","124721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/829999","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 21 December 2017 to Question 118696 on Brexit and the oral contribution of the Secretary of State for Scotland of 24 January 2018, what steps his Department is taking to make available the non-redacted sectoral reports to Members of the Scottish Parliament.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124722","124722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830000","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many arrests have been made under the provisions of the Export Control Act 2002 in each year since that Act came into effect; how many charging decisions have been received on such breaches from the CPS; on what dates such decisions were received; and how many criminal convictions have resulted from each such charging decision.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124723","124723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830001","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for the Government to consult on, publish and introduce into Parliament its Domestic Violence and Abuse Bill.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124724","124724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830002","2018-01-29","Department for International Trade","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what vetting procedures the Export Control Joint Unit carries out on entities that apply to the Government for licenses to broker or deal arms.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124725","124725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830003","2018-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Saudi joint incidents assessment team which reports to the Government on allegations of its own violations of international humanitarian law employs the principles of the Law of Armed Conflict with respect to Saudi Arabia's air campaign in Yemen.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124726","124726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830005","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many impact assessments Government Departments have conducted since 2015.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124727","124727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830006","2018-02-01","Attorney General","2018-01-24","To ask the Attorney General, whether experience is a criterion for appointment to the role of Director of Public Prosecutions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124728","124728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830008","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the number and proportion of people who were unable to secure within a week an appointment with a GP since January 2017; and what assessment he has made of the effect of the level of access to GPs on attendance at accident and emergency departments since January 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124729","124729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830009","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 16 June 2015 to Question 2203, whether it remains his Department’s position that there will be no requirement to fit artificial sound devices on electric and hybrid-electric buses prior to July 2019.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124730","124730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830011","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of trends in the average time taken to process asylum applications.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124731","124731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830012","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 22 June 2015 to Question 2384, what proportion of young people in the custodial estate have had education, training and employment placements arranged as a result of (a) resettlement consortia and (b) the Turn Around to Work initiative since 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124732","124732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830013","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many Starter Homes (a) were built in 2017 and (b) are projected to be built in 2018.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124733","124733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830015","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 8 July 2015 to Question 4874, on general practitioners: Greater London, how many (a) general medical services, (b) personal medical services and (c) alternative provider medical services contracts were issued for GP surgeries in (i) Hampstead and Kilburn constituency and (ii) in London in (A) 2016 and (B) 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124734","124734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830016","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 8 July 2015 to Question 4879, on academies, how many academies whose funding arrangements were dependent on Qualified Teacher Status requested to amend their funding agreement in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017 and; how many of those requests were rejected.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124735","124735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830018","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Answer of 8 September 2015 to Question 8249, on mental health services: children and young people, how many Child and Adolescent Mental Services in-patient Tier 4 beds were available in each region since January 2017; and what the average waiting time was for such a bed in each such region in that same period.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124736","124736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830019","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask Secretary of State for Work and Pensions with reference to the Answer of 19 October 2015 to Question 10807, how many free guidance sessions with Pension Wise have been held for those with defined contribution pensions in each year since October 2015; and what estimate his Department has made of the number of such sessions which will be held in 2018.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124737","124737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830020","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 28 October 2015 to Question 13154, on shared ownership schemes, what steps his Department has taken to promote shared ownership in high value areas since 2015.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124738","124738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830022","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 7 January 2016 to Question 21042, what steps her Department has taken following the conclusion of the pilots in West Yorkshire and the South West of the recommendations of the National Referral Mechanism review.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124739","124739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830023","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 December 2015 to Question 19729, how many jobseekers were referred to English language skills educational providers by jobcentres in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124740","124740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830025","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 22 December 2015 to Question 19825, how many complaints were received by the Pay and Work Rights Helpline regarding employment issues in each of the last five years; and how many of those complaints were from (a) apprentices, (b) interns and (c) self-employed people in that same period.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124741","124741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830026","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of the recent murders of former FARC combatants, Vilmar Asprilla and Ansel de Jesus Montoya Ibarra, and the UN condemnation of those murders on the peace process in Colombia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124742","124742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830028","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to encourage the growth of housing co-operation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124743","124743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830029","2018-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what further steps he plans to take to promote access to the Armed Forces Credit Union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124744","124744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830031","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of tribunal appeals against (a) personal independence payments and (b) employment support allowance assessments were successful in the last 12 months in Leeds.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124745","124745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830032","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to help co-operatives and mutuals obtain access to capital for expansion and referencing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124746","124746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830034","2018-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to increase multinational interoperability.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124747","124747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830035","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what further incentives he will offer to encourage employee ownership of companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124748","124748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830036","2018-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the Order of Battle is of 77 Brigade.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124749","124749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830039","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to conclude the Sustainability and Transformation Partnerships process in Surrey and Sussex.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124750","124750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830040","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of lessons learned from areas which have already integrated health and social care services.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124751","124751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830042","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the timetable is for all the Sustainability and Transformation Partnerships to conclude their work.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124752","124752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830043","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what records his Department holds on whether Ministers or officials from Government Departments were invited to the Presidents Club Dinner on 18 January 2018.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124753","124753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830045","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will offer payroll deduction services for credit union membership to all employees of (a) HMRC and (b) hs Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124754","124754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830046","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she plans to offer payroll deduction services for credit union membership to all her Department's employees; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124755","124755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830047","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many homes that are in housing cooperatives were completed in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124756","124756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830049","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to recommend to the Oil and Gas Authority that final consent is not given for fracking in Ryedale while (a) Third Energy has not published its 2016 accounts due on 30 September 2017 and (b) the Chairman of Third Energy Onshore Ltd, Keith Cochrane, is under investigation for his Chief Executive Officer role in the failed construction firm Carillion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124757","124757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830050","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the total sum of revenue that it has generated from the gradual reductions in the rate of corporation tax since 2010.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124758","124758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830052","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the total sum of revenue that it has generated from increases in stamp duty since 2010.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124759","124759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830053","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps his Department has taken to work with other countries and multilateral institutions on ensuring global tax transparency.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124760","124760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830055","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to work with other countries and multilateral institutions on taxing global multinational digital businesses.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124761","124761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830056","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has spend on roads and highways in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124762","124762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830057","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many charging points there are for electric vehicles for staff at the offices of the Department for Transport and the Office for Low Emission Vehicles at Great Minster House.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124763","124763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830059","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of personal independence payment there are in North West Durham constituency.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124764","124764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830060","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people who had a lifetime award for disability living allowance have had a reduction in the amount they are entitled to as a result of transferring to personal independence payment.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124765","124765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830062","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of people have had their Motability car removed after being transferred from disability living allowance to personal independence payment.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124766","124766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830063","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the number of people claiming personal independence payment that have mental health conditions.","Biography information for Laura Pidcock","Laura Pidcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124767","124767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830064","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans his Department has to install charging points for electrical cars at its offices.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124768","124768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830067","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the oral contribution by the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Transport, on January 18 2018, Official Report, column 634, if his Department will publish details of meetings Ministers and officials of his Department have held with fuel suppliers in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124769","124769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830068","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what information his Department holds on the (a) quantity and (b) value of fireworks sold in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124770","124770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830071","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of complaints received on the use of fireworks in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124771","124771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830072","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department has made a recent assessment of trends in public opinion on the use of fireworks; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124772","124772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830074","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Turkish counterpart on Turkish military operations around Afrin in northern Syria and the loss of civilian lives.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124773","124773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830075","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the legality of Turkey's operations in the Afrin district of Northern Syria.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124774","124774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830077","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of introducing a compulsory eyesight test for all children aged under 5 on the number of diagnoses of (a) Amblyopia and (b) other serious eye conditions in childhood.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124775","124775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830078","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs what representations he has made to his counterpart in Turkey on the need for a negotiated peaceful and democratic solution to the Kurdish question in Syria and in Turkey.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124776","124776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830080","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124777","124777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830081","2018-01-29","Attorney General","2018-01-24","To ask the Attorney General, who the the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in the Law Officers' Departments.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124778","124778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830082","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124779","124779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830084","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124780","124780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830085","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, who the the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124781","124781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830087","2018-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124782","124782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830088","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who the lead non-executive director and non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124783","124783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830090","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124784","124784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830091","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124785","124785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830092","2018-01-29","Women and Equalities","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in the Government Equalities Office.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124786","124786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830094","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124787","124787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830095","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason there is a difference in the age of children for which families are eligible to receive support via the (a) childcare vouchers scheme and (b) tax-free childcare scheme.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124788","124788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830096","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in her Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124789","124789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830098","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Written Statement of 15 January 2018, Tax-Free Childcare rollout update, HCWS 401, what assessment he has made of the level of take-up of tax-free childcare accounts.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124790","124790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830099","2018-01-29","Department for International Development","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, who lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in her Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124791","124791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830101","2018-01-29","Department for International Trade","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124792","124792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830102","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Economic Secretary to the Treasury of 15 January 2018, Official Report, column 242WH, on Childcare Vouchers, what the evidential basis is for his statement that tax-free childcare has a greater reach than childcare vouchers.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124793","124793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830103","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124794","124794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830106","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of self-employed parents eligible to claim tax-free childcare (a) have registered for that scheme in England to date and (b) does the Government estimate will register for that scheme in England in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124795","124795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830107","2018-01-29","Scotland Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124796","124796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830109","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124797","124797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830111","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124798","124798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830112","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport whether he will ask (a) Southern and (b) Govia Thameslink Railway to fund a one-month rail refund to annual season ticket holders to compensate those ticket holders for rail disruption.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124799","124799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830114","2018-01-29","Wales Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124800","124800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830115","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, who the lead non-executive director and other non-executive director board members are in her Department.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124801","124801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830117","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he plans to respond to the letter of 8 December 2017 from the hon. Member for Birmingham Northfield on President Trump’s decision to recognise Jerusalem as the capital of Israel.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124802","124802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830118","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of the 18 January to Question 122811, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of treating food banks usage as an indicator for food insecurity.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124803","124803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830120","2018-01-29","Attorney General","2018-01-24","To ask the Attorney General, how many people have been prosecuted for setting off fireworks after curfew hours in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124804","124804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830121","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria the Government uses to distinguish between the political and military wings of Hezbollah.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124805","124805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830123","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will request from the Bank Of England an explanation of how tea with its Governor was permitted and advertised at the Presidents Club as an auction item; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124806","124806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830124","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will request from the Bank of England a list of the charitable or other organisations to which meetings or meals with its Governor, other of its officials or access to its premises have been gifted or auctioned since 2015.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124807","124807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830126","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all new build properties can access superfast broadband immediately from completion of the property.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124808","124808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830127","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the eligibility criteria is for people to qualify under the mandate resettlement scheme.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124809","124809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830130","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many refugees resettled under mandate resettlement  were (a) immediate family members of sponsors in the UK and (b) extended family members in the past three years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124810","124810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830131","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what his Department's policy is on ensuring that new build properties have superfast broadband installed upon completion.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124811","124811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830133","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, on how many occasions approval been granted for time with (a) the Foreign Secretary, (b) other Government Ministers and (c) public officials to be auctioned off; and how many of those approvals were for (i) charity and (ii) male-only auctions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124812","124812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830134","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will request and publish information from the Bank of England on whether its staff attended the Presidents Club dinner of 18 January 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124813","124813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830135","2018-01-29","Department for International Trade","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent assessment he has made of the level of business interest in the great.gov.uk digital platform.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124814","124814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830137","2018-01-29","Department for International Trade","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in Commonwealth countries on future trade and investment between the UK and Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124815","124815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830138","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will require from the Bank of England a list of all the meetings, meals with its Governor or its officials or other access to its premises which have been auctioned to charitable or other organisations since 2015.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124816","124816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830140","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to harness digital technology to deliver educational services.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124817","124817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830142","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Government has had discussion with the Legal Aid Agency on the funding of civil proceedings against John Downey; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124818","124818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830144","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how catapult networks will support the delivery of the Industrial Strategy.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124819","124819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830145","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps he has taken to promote tax simplification.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124820","124820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830146","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what role financial technology plays in promoting financial inclusion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124821","124821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830148","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will request and publish information from the Bank of England on whether that bank has offered meetings or meals to auction at the Presidents Club in years prior to 2018.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124822","124822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830149","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will request from the Bank of England and publish its policy on charitable donations.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124823","124823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830151","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many scientists and engineers have been refused a Tier 2 (General) Certificate of Sponsorship since November 2017 due to the annual cap having been reached; which Standard Occupational Classification codes have been affected by that cap; and how many applications have been refused for each such code.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124824","124824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830152","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Legal Aid Agency has provided funding for John Downey.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124825","124825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830154","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will respond to Early Day Motion 804, on Antarctic Ocean Sanctuary.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124826","124826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830155","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to support manufacturing in each of the countries and regions of the UK through the Industrial Strategy.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124827","124827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830157","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to encourage the Chinese authorities to respect freedom of religion and all religious faiths in Hong Kong.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124828","124828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830159","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to Question 121771, tabled by the hon. Member for Oxford East on 9 January 2018.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124829","124829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830160","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information he holds on the amount of trade originating in the Irish Republic which transited the UK en route to overseas destinations in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Nigel Dodds","Nigel Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124830","124830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830162","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to respond to Question 118845, tabled by the hon. Member for Oxford East on 12 December 2017.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124831","124831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830164","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has put in place to ensure that the reintroduction of otters does not lead to a serious deterioration in fish stocks.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124832","124832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830165","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2018 to Question 116503, whether the revised National Planning Policy Framework to include new developments will take account of culture, history and tradition where noise nuisance complaints are made about the continued ringing of church bells and chimes by residents living within existing developments.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124833","124833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830167","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2018 to  Question 116503, whether the revised National Planning Policy Framework to include new development will take account of culture, history and tradition where noise nuisance complaints are made about the continued ringing of church bells and chimes by residents living within developments that have changed in use such as where a house has been converted to a Bed and Breakfast.","Biography information for Craig Mackinlay","Craig Mackinlay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124834","124834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830169","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of removing the provision of allowing the sale of the edited electoral register.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124835","124835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830170","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans his Department has to increase the efficiency of customs clearance processes.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124836","124836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830172","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of registered voters are listed on the edited register.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124837","124837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830174","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, for what reasons the full-time social action review has been delayed.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124838","124838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830175","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were refused personal independence payment in 2016-17.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124839","124839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830177","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were refused personal independence payment had that decision changed at mandatory reconsideration in 2016-17.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124840","124840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830179","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who were refused personal independence payment had that decision changed at Tribunal in 2016-17.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124841","124841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830181","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to Drug shortages derail CCGs’ budgets, published by The BMJ on 24 January 2018, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for the ten-fold year on year increase in Clinical Commissioning Group's costs relating to drugs on no cheaper stock obtainable lists.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124842","124842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830182","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Government of Nigeria on the Zaria massacre and other human rights abuses; and whether the Government intends to make further representations to that Government on the protection of human rights and the right to peaceful protest.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124843","124843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830183","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2018 to Question 122980, what assessment his Department has made of the cost that is likely be incurred by energy companies in challenging Ofgem’s decision on the setting of the cap by way of judicial review in comparison with the cost that is incurred by energy companies in appealing to the Competition and Markets Authority.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124844","124844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830184","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2018 to Question 122977, which countries that regulate retail energy prices were considered by his Department prior to publishing the draft Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Bill.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124845","124845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830185","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Turkey, (b) the US, (c) Russia, (d) the EU, (e) the UN, (f) NATO and (g) the Arab League on (i) the Turkish assault on the city of Afrin and (ii) how a humanitarian crisis can be averted.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124846","124846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830186","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Turkish counterparts since President Erdogan’s statement of 20 January 2018 on an assault on the Syrian city of Manbij; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124847","124847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830187","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 6 December 2017 to Question 116245, when his Department plans to complete its consideration of the implications of the Walker v. Innospec Limited judgment for public service schemes.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124848","124848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830188","2018-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has plans to provide a 24/7 mental health care helpline for veterans and serving soldiers in the Armed Forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124849","124849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830189","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support aerospace supply chains.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124850","124850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830190","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the remit of the new National Security Communications Unit will be; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124851","124851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830191","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether the Government has made an assessment of the effect on Anguilla of the UK leaving the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124852","124852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830192","2018-01-29","Department for International Development","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to increase the flow of humanitarian aid into the north of Yemen.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124853","124853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830193","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the new National Security Communications Unit will be based in the (a) Government Communications Service, (b) National Security Secretariat or (c) elsewhere.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124854","124854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830194","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff and at what grades will be employed by the new National Security Communications Unit.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124855","124855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830195","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what resources he has allocated to the new National Security Communications Unit.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124856","124856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830196","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many mother and baby beds commissioned by NHS England Specialised Services in 2016/17 are (a) available and (b) in use.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124857","124857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830197","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to prevent future strikes on South Western Railway; and if will he make a statement.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124858","124858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830198","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to Being mindful of mental health - The role of local government in mental health and wellbeing, published by the Local Government Association in June 2017, how many local authorities have established peer networks.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124859","124859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830199","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in reference to the staying put initiative launched in 2013, whether his Department plans to raise the payment for HS236 foster carers who are looking after adults in their care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124860","124860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830200","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the mandatory binding arbitration clause in the UK’s new tax treaty with Lesotho will help the Lesotho Government to combat tax avoidance and evasion.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124861","124861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830201","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department plans to review the funding of sixth form colleges; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124862","124862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830202","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether Anguilla will be covered by the implementation period as part of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124863","124863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830203","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the liquidation of Carillion on apprenticeships in the rail supply chain; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124864","124864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830204","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to ensure police forces investigate household burglaries; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124865","124865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830205","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the liquidation of Carillion on the timetable for rail electrification works; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124866","124866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830206","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of Public Spaces Protection Orders.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124867","124867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830207","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the liquidation of Carillion on the (a)  timetables, (b) budgets and (c) other parts of the Road Investment Strategy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124868","124868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830208","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 5 December 2017 to Question 116945, on children: day care, whether that contract has been signed; and whether the composition of the working group remains the same.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124869","124869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830209","2018-01-29","Northern Ireland Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what support her Department provided to the joint bid by Belfast City Council and Derry and Strabane District Council to be named European Capital of Culture.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124870","124870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830210","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when the Government became aware that UK cities would not be able to bid to be named European Capital of Culture; and when this was communicated to those cities that were so bidding.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124871","124871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830211","2018-01-29","Northern Ireland Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many staff were employed by her Department in each year since 1996.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124872","124872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830212","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Conservative–DUP coordination committee last met to discuss future Government business; and whether she plans to publish details and minutes of such meetings.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124873","124873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830213","2018-01-29","Northern Ireland Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many peace walls there are in Northern Ireland; and how many there were in each year since 1997.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124874","124874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830214","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent estimate his Department has made of the total number of (a) paid and (b) unpaid internships in the UK.","Biography information for Alec Shelbrooke","Alec Shelbrooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124875","124875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830215","2018-01-29","Northern Ireland Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many special advisers were employed in her Department in each year from 1997 to 2018.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124876","124876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830216","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the lower rates of withholding tax for dividends and royalties in the UK’s new tax treaty with Lesotho will benefit Lesotho’s economy.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124877","124877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830217","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received on the decision of the Specialised Criminal Court in Sana'a to sentence Mr Hamed bin Haydara to death by public execution because of his religious beliefs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124878","124878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830218","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will publish the objectives that it is seeking to achieve before any future negotiations on bilateral tax treaties.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124879","124879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830219","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government's new tax treaty with Lesotho is the first UK tax treaty with (a) any country or (b) a low or middle-income country to include a mandatory binding arbitration clause.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124880","124880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830220","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information her Department holds on the number of incidents of shooting of (a) cats and (b) other animals with air weapons reported to the police in England in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124881","124881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830221","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an assessment of whether people on low incomes will receive less financial support with tax-free childcare than they would with childcare vouchers.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124882","124882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830222","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential implications for the Baha'i community and freedom of religion or belief in northern Yemen of the death sentence pronounced against the Yemeni Baha'i Mr bin Haydara.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124883","124883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830223","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2018 to Question 123704, on Randox Testing Services, which forensic guidelines Randox Testing Services were following during the period in which they were providing Section 5A drug analysis services to the criminal justice system; and if she will publish those guidelines.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124884","124884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830224","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the letter from the Financial Secretary to the Treasury to the hon. Member for St Helen's South and Whiston of 15 December 2017, whether a child in full-time education may claim disability benefit in their own right from the age of 16.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124885","124885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830225","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, further to the answer of the 23 January 2018 to Question 123692, on Randox Testing Services, how long FSR-C-133 has been in development; whether FSR-C-133 has been issued to any provider; and whether any provider has been following guidance under FSR-C-133.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124886","124886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830226","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to increase the age of eligibility for the childcare cost element of child tax credit from 16 to 20 years old for families with disabled children until adult social care provision becomes available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124887","124887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830227","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received on Iranian influence on the actions of the Houthi community against the Baha'i community in Sana'a, Yemen; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124888","124888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830228","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the speech made by the Secretary of State for International Trade to the American Enterprise Institute of 24 July 2017, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the increase in non-tariff barriers to trade between 2010 and 2015 on the UK services industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124889","124889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830229","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the speech made by the Secretary of State for International Trade to the American Enterprise Institute of 24 July 2017, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the increase in non-tariff barriers to trade between 2010 and 2015 on the UK dairy industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124890","124890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830230","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the speech made by the Secretary of State for International Trade to the American Enterprise Institute of 24 July 2017, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the increase in non-tariff barriers to trade between 2010 and 2015 on the UK car manufacturing industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124891","124891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830231","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the speech made by the Secretary of State for International Trade to the American Enterprise Institute of 24 July 2017, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the increase in non-tariff barriers to trade between 2010 and 2015 on the UK aerospace industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124892","124892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830232","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the speech made by the Secretary of State for International Trade to the American Enterprise Institute of 24 July 2017, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the increase in non-tariff barriers to trade between 2010 and 2015 on the UK chemicals industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124893","124893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830233","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the speech made by the Secretary of State for International Trade to the American Enterprise Institute of 24 July 2017, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the increase in non-tariff barriers to trade between 2010 and 2015 on the UK pharmaceutical industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124894","124894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830234","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the speech made by the Secretary of State for International Trade to the American Enterprise Institute of 24 July 2017, what assessment the Government has made of the effect of the increase in non-tariff barriers to trade between 2010 and 2015 on the UK data processing industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124895","124895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830235","2018-01-29","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the speech made by the Secretary of State for International Trade to the American Enterprise Institute of 24th July 2017, what assessment he has made of the effect of the increase in non-tariff barriers to trade between 2010 and 2015 on the UK’s future trade relationship with the EU in the event of the UK's reversion to WTO terms after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Antoinette Sandbach","Antoinette Sandbach","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124896","124896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830236","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to collate and publish data relating to employment support allowance similar to that which is made available on personal independence payments.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124897","124897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830237","2018-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he plans to support Albania’s application to join NATO.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124898","124898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830238","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Answer of 23 January 2018 to Question 903506, what steps the Government has taken to address unsafe conditions in youth custody following the Youth Custody Improvement Board report published in February 2017.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124899","124899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830239","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect on subcontractors in the construction industry of the liquidation of Carillion; and whether he plans to set up a taskforce to support those companies.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124900","124900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830240","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what (a) central government and (b) total spend was on the disabled facilities grants scheme in each year from 2009-10 to 2016-17, and what spend in each case is expected to be in each year to 2022-23.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124901","124901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830241","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of the 23 January 2018 to Question 123692, whether any guidance produced by (a) her Department and (b) FSR stipulate the requirement for providers to conduct duplicate blood analysis in relation to Section 5A drug driving analysis services.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124902","124902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830242","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the answer of 23 January 2018 to Question 123692, to what FSR guidelines are providers of Section 5A drug driving analysis services accredited.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124903","124903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830243","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to prevent the supply of ballistic missiles to Houthi rebels in Yemen.","Biography information for Leo Docherty","Leo Docherty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124904","124904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830244","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he plans to have discussions with the Charity Commission as result of the closure of the Presidents Club charitable club; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124905","124905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830245","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of establishing an inquiry into the events which led to the closure of the Presidents Club Charitable Trust.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124906","124906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830246","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, for what reasons the contract for Central and East London breast screening services has been awarded to Royal Free London NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124907","124907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830247","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate has been made of the cost of transferring the contract for Central and East London breast screening services from the current provider to the new provider; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124908","124908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830248","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to maintain the symptomatic breast service in Barts NHS Trust after the screening service has been transferred to the new provider.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124909","124909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830249","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to address robberies and assaults by gangs on scooters and mopeds.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124910","124910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830250","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many civil partnerships have been (a) established and (b) dissolved in each year since 2004.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124911","124911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830251","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of women suffering from Lipedema.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124912","124912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830252","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to remove the 50 per cent admissions cap on faith schools.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy  Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124913","124913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830253","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of civil partnerships have become marriages since the Marriage (Same Sex Couples) Act 2013.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124914","124914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830254","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what clinical commissioning groups offer treatment for Lipedema as standard.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124915","124915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830255","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many (a) same-sex  and (b) single-sex couples have (i) married and (ii) divorced in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124916","124916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830256","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what Lipedema treatments have been approved by NICE.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124917","124917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830257","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate the Government has made of the number of cohabiting opposite-sex couples (a) with and (b) without children, and what the number of children in such arrangements is.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124918","124918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830258","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has applied to the Chancellor of the Exchequer for any contingency funding relating to the UK leaving the EU for (a) 2018 and (b) 2019.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124919","124919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830259","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any sub-contractors carrying out work on the South Wales mainline electrification project are currently experiencing arrears in payment as a result of the collapse of Carillion.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124920","124920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830260","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to question 123102, which business organisations were represented at the Carillion taskforce meeting referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124921","124921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830261","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether Carillion was a Government strategic supplier.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124922","124922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830262","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 123102, on Carillion: Insolvency, what assurances were given by the major high street lenders referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124923","124923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830263","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of potential (a) delays and (b) rescheduling to the South Wales mainline electrification project as a result of the collapse of Carillion.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124924","124924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830264","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 122920, when he plans to announce the new list of Government strategic suppliers.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124925","124925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830265","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 123102, on Carillion: Insolvency, for how long the major high street lenders indicated they are prepared to put in place (a) overdraft extensions, (b) payment holidays and (c) fee waivers.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124926","124926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830266","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2018 to Question 123416, when he plans to respond to the Financial Conduct Authority's consultation on widening the remit of the Financial Ombudsman Service.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124927","124927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/830267","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 123102, on Carillion: Insolvency, what additional resources he is providing to the Local Growth Hubs referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124928","124928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828316","2018-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","What steps his Department is taking to improve support for prisoners with mental health conditions.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903499","903499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828317","2018-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","What steps he is taking to reduce the number of cases in which people are repeatedly compelled to appear in a family court due to action by a former partner.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903500","903500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828318","2018-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","What recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the number of victim support officers.","Biography information for Fiona Onasanya","Fiona Onasanya","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903501","903501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828319","2018-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","What steps his Department is taking to help treat prisoners with mental health problems.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903502","903502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828320","2018-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","What assessment he has made of the effect of reforms to the National Probation Service on the operation of the victim contact scheme.","Biography information for Matt Rodda","Matt Rodda","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903504","903504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828321","2018-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","What steps his Department is taking to modernise the courts system.","Biography information for Dr Caroline Johnson","Dr Caroline Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903505","903505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828322","2018-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","What recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of violence and self-harm in young offenders institutions.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903506","903506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828328","2018-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-23","What steps his Department is taking to reduce rates of fly-tipping.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903551","903551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828329","2018-01-25","Church Commissioners","2018-01-23","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what discussions the Church of England has had with the Department for Education on ensuring that religious studies remains a priority in schools.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 903525","903525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828570","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department has taken to support grassroots football organisations in tackling racism.","Biography information for Fiona Onasanya","Fiona Onasanya","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124243","124243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828571","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if his Department will take steps to introduce testing for all women over 30 years old for early signs of (a) ovarian and (b) breast cancer.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124244","124244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828573","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's report entitled Department for Environment Food and Rural Affairs Equality Objectives 2012-2016, published in April 2012, what steps his Department has taken to raise awareness of diversity by developing a communications plan to celebrate key  equality and culture events such as LGBT History Month and Black History Month.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124245","124245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828574","2018-01-29","Department for International Trade","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether exports of Turkey's TF-X fighter will be subject to UK Government approval on a case-by-case basis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124246","124246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828575","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what account his Department takes of the relatively high cost of delivering local services in London in determining the local government finance settlement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124247","124247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828576","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of EU Directives 2014/45/EU and 2014/47/EU in improving road safety.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124248","124248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828577","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to make an assessment of the potential merits of the review conducted by Stephen Shaw on the implementation of the recommendations on the welfare in detention of vulnerable persons, in advance of issuing updated guidance on her Department's adults at risk policy; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124249","124249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828578","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the core spending power of Wirral Council was in each financial year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124250","124250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828579","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to Answer of 19 January 2018 to Question 122912 on DHL, on what date the position of Crown Representative to DHL became vacant.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124251","124251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828580","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to Answer of 19 January 2018 to Question 122914 on ENGIE, on which date the position of Crown Representative to Engie (a) became vacant and (b) was filled.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124252","124252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828582","2018-01-29","Cabinet Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to Answer of 19 January 2018 to Question 122911 on British Telecom, on what date  position of Crown Representative to BT plc (a) became vacant and (b) was filled.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124253","124253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828583","2018-01-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many pregnant women with phenylketonuria have received Kuvan (sapropterin) treatment since that drug has been licenced for use in the UK; and what is the average duration of the course of that treatment.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124254","124254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828584","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals for an independent consumer advocate for the telecoms industry.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124255","124255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828585","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraph 4.5 of Brexit – the impact on British Orchestras, published by the Association of British Orchestras in December 2017, what discussions he has had with the EU Commission on maintaining access to the A1 system after the UK leaves the European Union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124256","124256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828586","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the EU Commission on the (a) introduction of carnets for transporting musical instruments and (b) application of the visa-national PPE system to EEA citizens after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124257","124257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828588","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the role of British orchestras in promoting UK cultural exchange.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124258","124258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828589","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to provide children with access to the arts after the EBacc becomes compulsory in schools.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124259","124259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828590","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of the use of flat-pack housing by local authorities to tackle housing shortages.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124260","124260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828591","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, whether Approved Document B allows for combustible material to be used in the cladding of a building with a storey of 18 metres or more above ground level.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124261","124261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828592","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many times which materials have failed the 8414 large-scale tests conducted by the Building Research Establishment in the last 5 years; and of those materials that failed such tests what information his Department holds on how many buildings there are that are clad in those materials.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124262","124262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828593","2018-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contingency plans his Department put in place to manage the Regional Prime and National Housing contracts run by (a) Carillon and (b) Amey in the event that those companies could no longer fulfil their contracts.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124263","124263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828595","2018-01-25","Department for International Development","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department has provided to the South Sudan Council of Churches in its reconciliation work in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124264","124264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828596","2018-01-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he will take steps to ensure that all pregnant women are provided with the joint Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists and Group B Strep Support patient information leaflet on Group B Streptococcal Disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124265","124265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828598","2018-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to support the viability of the domestic livestock market after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124266","124266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828599","2018-01-25","Women and Equalities","2018-01-23","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she plans to review the operation of the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124267","124267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828600","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has plans to increase the funding allocated to the Northern Forest.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124268","124268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828602","2018-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 19 January 2018, HCWS414, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of additional PIP benefits payable following the High Court's December 2017 judgement on the Social Security (Personal Independence Payment) (Amendment) Regulations 2017.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124269","124269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828603","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans the Government has to develop tax incentives and economic support to expand entrepreneurial opportunities for women in micro-businesses or who are self-employed.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124270","124270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828604","2018-01-25","HM Treasury","2018-01-23","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant the Answer of 6 November 2017 to Question 110943 on European Investment Bank: North East, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the extra due diligence on the timetable for the allocation of funds in the North East.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124271","124271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828605","2018-01-25","HM Treasury","2018-01-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 11 December 2017 to Question 118242, on Life Sciences: Capital Investment, what estimate he has made of the money that will be accrued to the public purse from the investment in the Life Sciences Sector deal.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124272","124272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828606","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of constructing a bridge between England and France.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124273","124273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828607","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs on constructing a bridge between England and France.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124274","124274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828608","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Parole Board stopped taking into account completion of the sex offender treatment programme in assessing the suitability of prisoners for release.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124275","124275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828609","2018-01-25","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people who are released from immigration detention on immigration bail as a result of the repeal of section 4(1) of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124276","124276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828610","2018-01-25","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the First Tier Tribunal on the (a) repeal of section 4(1) of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 and (b) provision of bail accommodation.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124277","124277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828611","2018-01-25","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the (a) the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government and (b) Ministers in the devolved administrations on the effect of releasing immigration detainees without bail accommodation on (a) local authorities, (b) street homelessness and (c) statutory homelessness applications.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124278","124278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828612","2018-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2018 to Question 122438, if he will estimate the amount of food waste that will be prevented as a result of the steps he proposes to take.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124279","124279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828613","2018-01-29","Scotland Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to his oral contribution of 6 December 2017, Official Report, column 1021, on what date officials were first instructed to prepare amendments to Clause 11 of the European Union (Withdrawal) Bill for its Report stage.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124280","124280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828615","2018-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2018 to Question 121390, what he and his Russian counterpart concluded were the best ways they could work together to tackle the global security issues in relation to North Korea.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124281","124281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828616","2018-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2018 to Question 121390 on North Korea: Nuclear Weapons, what steps he is taking to ensure the full implementation of UNSCR 2379 on North Korea.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124282","124282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828617","2018-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 12 January 2018 to Question 121391 on North Korea: Nuclear Weapons, what the evidential basis is for the statement that the impact of UNSC sanctions on North Korea are increasingly being felt by the Kim regime.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124283","124283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828619","2018-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2018 to Question 121389, what the latest date was on which he was briefed on the development of North Korean Ballistic Missile capability and the conduct of significant tests.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124284","124284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828620","2018-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2018 to Question 122320 on USA: Nuclear Weapons what views were sought by the US administration; and what response the UK Government provided.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124285","124285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828621","2018-01-29","Department for International Trade","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the number of exhibitors at the Consumer Electronics Show 2017 that came from (a) the UK, (b) France, (c) the Netherlands, and (d) Israel; and what support his Department provided to exhibitors from the UK.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124286","124286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828622","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps are being taken to put in place precautions to prevent the spread of the Schmallenberg virus.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124287","124287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828623","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department how much was spent on hire cars by each constabulary in the North West in 2016 and 2017; and what steps are being taken to reduce expenditure on such cars.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124288","124288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828624","2018-01-25","HM Treasury","2018-01-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 19 January 2018 to Question 122436, on Minimum Wage, how many of the 532 civil actions initiated since 2010 resulted in the recovery of unpaid minimum wage arrears.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124289","124289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828625","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which organisations his Department consulted on the introduction of a victims law; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124290","124290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828626","2018-01-25","Department for Education","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the 2018-19 local government pay offer on school finances.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124291","124291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828628","2018-01-25","Department for Education","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent meetings he has held with (a) schools, (b) the Local Government Association and (c) trade unions on school support staff pay.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124292","124292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828629","2018-01-25","Department for Education","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent discussions he has held with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the schools' wage costs.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124293","124293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828630","2018-01-25","Department for Education","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what research his Department has (a) undertaken and (b) commissioned on the adequacy of the level of school support staff pay.","Biography information for Ian Austin","Ian Austin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124294","124294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828631","2018-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his steps his Department is taking to support the rural economy in Hampshire.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124295","124295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828632","2018-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the performance of the Great British Food Unit in opening up new markets for food and drink from Hampshire.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124296","124296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828634","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of business insolvencies in the last two years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124297","124297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828635","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure the costs of making buildings safe are not passed on to tenants.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124298","124298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828636","2018-01-29","Wales Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the First Minister of Wales on legislative consent for the European Withdrawal Bill.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124299","124299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828637","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if the Government will make an assessment of the potential merits of temporarily displaying the Bayeux Tapestry in the National Museum of Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124300","124300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828638","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when the Government's consultation on the Shared Prosperity Fund will open; and when the Government plans to publish a response to that consultation.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124301","124301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828640","2018-01-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much funding has been allocated by his Department to the voluntary right to buy pilot process for each of the next five years; and how much of that funding has been spent.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124302","124302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828641","2018-01-25","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of houses that will be sold in each of the next five years as a result of the voluntary right to buy pilots.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124303","124303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828642","2018-01-25","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 10 January 2018 to Question 120539 on Immigrants: Employment, what steps her Department is taking to simplify the employer checking service  for (a) perspective employees and (b) employers.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124304","124304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828644","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Afrin district, northern Syria.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124305","124305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828645","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Turkish counterpart on Turkish military operations underway in Afrin district, northern Syria.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124306","124306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828646","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to Written Statement of 19 January 2018, HCWS414, whether applicants will be entitled to a reassessment if they were given the standard rate of the PIP mobility component after the February 2017 changes to PIP regulations, where the cause of the claim was psychological distress.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124307","124307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828647","2018-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Written Statement of 19 January 2018, HCWS414, what the timetable is for claimants to be informed if they are entitled to a back payment.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124308","124308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828648","2018-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department’s plans are for the Ministry of Defence Guard Service.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124309","124309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828650","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the human rights  situation of Kurdish communities in the Afrin district, northern Syria.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124310","124310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828651","2018-01-25","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to respond to Question 115815, tabled by the hon. Member for Halifax on 27 November 2017.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124311","124311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828652","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Turkish counterpart on the Turkish operation in the Afrin district of Syria.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124312","124312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828653","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police dogs and handlers there were in each force (a) in 2010 and (b) on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124313","124313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828654","2018-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department plans to involve people with Parkinson's disease in the process of improving the work capability assessment.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124314","124314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828656","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to provide (a) financial and (b) other support to West Midlands Fire Service.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124315","124315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828657","2018-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Egyptian counterpart on reports that Egyptian troops have been deployed in Asmara, Eritrea.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124316","124316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828658","2018-01-29","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse to date of the (a) Hinkley Point C and (b) Moorside nuclear projects.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124317","124317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828659","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department plans to run programmes to increase youth participation in football and other sports alongside the FIFA World Cup 2018.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124318","124318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828660","2018-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his UN Security Council counterparts on escalating tensions among Eritrea, Egypt, Ethiopia and Sudan.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124319","124319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828662","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many of his Department's officials are working on the monitoring and the delivery of the 25 Year Plan for the Environment.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124320","124320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828663","2018-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the funding his Department allocated to the Waste Resources Action Programme (WRAP) in each year from 2009-10 to 2017-18; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124321","124321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828664","2018-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his European counterparts on tensions between Eritrea, Egypt, Ethiopia and Sudan.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124322","124322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828665","2018-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the closure of the border between Sudan and Eritrea on the political and economic stability of the wider region.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124323","124323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828666","2018-01-25","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when his Department next plans to review the use of electronic shock collars for dogs.","Biography information for Kevin Foster","Kevin Foster","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124324","124324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828667","2018-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has discussed with the authorities of the Kingdom of Bahrain, the trial of relatives of UK-based human rights activist Sayed Ahmed al-Wadaei.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124325","124325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828668","2018-01-25","Ministry of Defence","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence if he will publish the Continuity of Education Allowance payments made to each Service, by rank, over each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124326","124326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828670","2018-01-25","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support is available to a child that receives a Conclusive Grounds decision in the National Referral Mechanism.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124327","124327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828671","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how often Carillion was stress-tested by his Department; when the last such stress test was carried out; and what the results of that stress test were.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124328","124328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828672","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how often Carillion was stress-tested by his Department; when the last such stress test was carried out; and what the results of that stress test were.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124329","124329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828673","2018-01-25","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether an impact assessment was completed before her Department's announcements on the alignment of basic living costs for victims of modern slavery and asylum seekers.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124330","124330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828674","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how often Carillion was stress-tested by his Department; when the last such stress test was carried out; and what the results of that stress test were.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124331","124331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828676","2018-01-25","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support the Government is providing to the Northern Ireland Assembly on the implementation of that administration's modern slavery strategy.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124332","124332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828677","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how often Carillion was stress-tested by his Department; when the last such stress test was carried out; and what the results of that stress test were.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124333","124333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828678","2018-01-29","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of supported housing (a) units and (b) residents living in short-term supported housing.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124334","124334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828679","2018-01-29","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he has taken to ensure that the UK retains its status as a European broadcasting hub after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124335","124335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828680","2018-01-29","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment has been made of the potential merits of using Eye Movement Desensitization and Reprocessing treatment to alleviate post-traumatic stress disorder.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124336","124336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828682","2018-01-25","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Governments of the UK Overseas Territories on creating fully enforced Marine Protected Areas in their waters.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124337","124337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828683","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department has taken to roll out 30 hours of free childcare in (a) Manchester, Withington constituency and (b) Manchester.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124338","124338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828684","2018-01-29","Department for Education","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education how many eligibility codes for 30 hours free childcare have been (a) generated and (b) validated in (i) Manchester Withington constituency and (b) Manchester.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124339","124339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828686","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will outline the itinerary of his visit to the London Borough of Redbridge that took place on 19 January 2018.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124340","124340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828687","2018-01-29","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what rail improvement contracts Carillion holds in (a) the North West and (b) Manchester.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124341","124341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828688","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he last met senior Metropolitan police officers from the London Borough of Redbridge.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124342","124342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828689","2018-01-25","Department for Education","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education how much per pupil funding was allocated to schools in (a) Manchester, Withington constituency, (b) Manchester and (c) the North West in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124343","124343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828691","2018-01-25","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of people who travelled to work by (a) car, (b) bus and (c) rail in Manchester in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124344","124344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828692","2018-01-29","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to appoint new members of the Advisory Council on the Misuse of Drugs.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124345","124345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828693","2018-01-25","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospital admissions caused by Fentanyl misuse there were in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124346","124346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828696","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to uphold the human rights of the Tamil people and to support the establishment of democratically accountable institutions in Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124348","124348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828697","2018-01-29","Department for International Trade","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that arms sold to the Government of Sri Lanka are not used to violate the human rights of the Sri Lankan people.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124349","124349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828698","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the Sri Lankan Government observes United Nations Human Rights Council Resolution 30/1.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124350","124350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828700","2018-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the Sri Lankan Government abides by the Oslo Declaration of 2002.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124351","124351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828701","2018-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he has received representations on the performance of the Inner North London Coroner's Office with reference to (a) ensuring appropriate burial arrangements for Jewish and Muslim people and (b) otherwise; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124352","124352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828702","2018-01-25","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the value of compensation payments to East Midlands Trains for the loss of revenue for trains stopping at Bedford.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124353","124353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828703","2018-01-25","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what information his Department holds on the number of people in Hartlepool who use a blue badge.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124354","124354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828705","2018-01-25","Home Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that firearms licensing medical procedures are being (a) complied with and (b) promoted.","Biography information for Mike Hill","Mike Hill","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124355","124355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828706","2018-01-25","Department for Education","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make it his policy to increase the minimum number of hours training in physical education required as part of teacher training.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124356","124356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828707","2018-01-25","Department for Education","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people took a GCSE or equivalent qualification in Food Technology in each of the past 15 years.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124357","124357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828708","2018-01-25","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that ticket machines at train stations always offer the lowest available fares.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124358","124358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828710","2018-01-25","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that ticket machines at train stations sell tickets at peak time for off-peak journeys.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124359","124359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828711","2018-01-25","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to increase the number of ticket machines available at train stations.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124360","124360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828712","2018-01-25","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the adequacy of the number of ticket machines available at train stations.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124361","124361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828713","2018-01-25","Department for Transport","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what support his Department is providing to bus companies to modernise their fleets.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124362","124362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828715","2018-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many additional child maintenance payments were made after investigations by HMRC in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124363","124363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828716","2018-01-25","Cabinet Office","2018-01-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people with disabilities who (a) are currently in work and (b) were in work in 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124364","124364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828718","2018-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have accessed the New Enterprise Allowance since its introduction.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124365","124365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828719","2018-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many businesses have signed up to the Disability Confident scheme.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124366","124366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828720","2018-01-25","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much her Department estimates it will save by co-locating Jobcentres in local authority premises.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124367","124367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828722","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the report of the Childcare Vouchers Providers Association, The future of childcare support for working parents, published on 20 February 2017, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the findings of that report.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124368","124368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828723","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when HMRC plans to publish its finalised guidance on the tax-free childcare scheme.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124369","124369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828724","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps are being taken to ensure the protection of data belonging to families registering for the tax-free childcare scheme online.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124370","124370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828725","2018-01-29","Department for International Trade","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will list the number of applications for export credit support and financing that UK Export Finance has received from Chemring and its subsidiaries in each of the past 10 years; and if he will list the value of the exports covered and the countries for which export support was provided.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124371","124371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828726","2018-01-29","HM Treasury","2018-01-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many parents of children with a disability currently claim (a) under the Employer Supported Childcare vouchers scheme and (b) under the tax-free-childcare scheme in England.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124372","124372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/828728","2018-01-29","Department for International Trade","2018-01-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, on how many occasions the Defence and Security Organisation has provided direct assistance to Chemring or its subsidiaries in the last 10 years.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124373","124373"
