"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483022","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has made an assessment of gaps in maritime capability.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31830","31830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483023","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the Fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment he has made of which of his Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31826","31826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483024","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children were permanently excluded from school during Key Stages 1 and 2 in (a) academies and (b) community schools in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31862","31862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483025","2016-03-24","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2016 to Question 30444, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of the Government's proposal for every school to become an academy on the responsibility of local authorities to provide sufficient school places.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31889","31889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483026","2016-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department plans to develop standard technical guidance and best practice guidelines for the energy storage market to ensure the safety and consistency of installations.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31859","31859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483027","2016-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential effect of replacing final consumption levies on energy storage devices with a net charging levy to ensure that energy storage devices are not charged twice.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31860","31860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483028","2016-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will ask her counterpart in the US administration for emissions data and costing information on the Petra Nova carbon capture and storage project; and if she will place a copy of that information in the Library.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31786","31786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483029","2016-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will ask her counterpart in the US administration for emissions data and costing information on the Kemper County energy facility, Mississippi; and if she will place a copy of that information in the Library.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31787","31787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483030","2016-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will ask her counterpart in the United Arab Emirates government for emissions data and costing information on the Abu Dhabi carbon capture and storage project; and if she will place a copy of that information in the Library.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31785","31785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483031","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to encourage households to donate unused food.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31864","31864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483032","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the average value of unused food thrown away by households in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31865","31865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483033","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the average amount of unused food thrown away by households in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31866","31866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483034","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what work has been carried out under the National Flood Resilience Review on the costs of protecting the UK from future flooding and extreme weather events.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31839","31839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483035","2016-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the EU's decision-making process is for (a) humanitarian and (b) military interventions; who is involved in those decision-making processes; and what the timetable for those processes is.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31841","31841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483036","2016-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the EU is taking to counter extremism and radicalisation in (a) the Middle East, (b) South Asia and (c) Africa; and in what way the Government is contributing to those steps.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31846","31846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483037","2016-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Indonesian counterpart on the imprisonment and shackling of people living with mental health conditions in that country.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31861","31861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483038","2016-03-23","Department for International Development","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the EU is taking to tackle poverty in (a) the Middle East, (b) South Asia and (c) Africa; and what the Government's contribution is to those steps.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31853","31853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483039","2016-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government provides to Kurdish authorities in (a) Iraq and (b) Syria to support refugees in those regions.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31797","31797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483040","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has made an estimate of the number of people in each of the next five years that would have received financial support as a result of the introduction of the cap on care costs proposed for April 2016 which has been postponed until April 2020.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31810","31810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483041","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons the Government plans to close Calderstones Partnership NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31800","31800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483042","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has for supporting low-security patients at Calderstones Partnership NHS Foundation Trust in reintegrating into the community if that facility is closed.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31801","31801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483043","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the proposed closure of Calderstones Partnership NHS Foundation Trust, what plans the Government has for relocating medium security patients under the care of that trust.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31802","31802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483044","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many outpatient (a) ophthalmology, (b) medical ophthalmology, (c) optometry and (d) orthoptic appointments for children under 19 years of age took place in 2014-15.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31784","31784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483045","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what involvement Ministers of his Department had in the decision by Public Health England to reduce the recommended amount of dairy in the Eatwell guide; for what reasons that change was made; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31890","31890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483046","2016-03-23","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the contribution of the UK's membership of the EU to the protection of the UK's borders.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31852","31852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483047","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which EU intelligence-sharing agreements the UK is part of; and which intelligence-sharing agreements the UK has with other EU countries.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31896","31896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483048","2016-03-24","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fixed penalty notices have been issued by police forces for driving on a motorway lane closed with a red X in each of the last 10 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31885","31885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483049","2016-03-23","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of planned future budget reductions on the capacity of Greater Manchester police service to tackle cyber-crime.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31857","31857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483050","2016-03-23","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the expected cost is of replacement of the Emergency Services Network in Greater Manchester; and how that project is to be funded.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31858","31858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483051","2016-03-23","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of planned future budget reductions on the capacity of Greater Manchester police service to tackle child exploitation and sexual offences.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31856","31856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483052","2016-03-23","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of planned future budget reductions on the capacity of Greater Manchester police service to tackle organised crime and terrorism.","Biography information for Mr Ivan Lewis","Mr Ivan Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31855","31855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483053","2016-03-24","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what contracts her Department has entered into with charter flight companies for the deportation of non-UK citizens to their country of origin.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31805","31805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483054","2016-03-23","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce the number of non-natural deaths (a) in police custody and (b) on the prison estate.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31782","31782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483055","2016-03-24","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost of online retail fraud was to retailers in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31815","31815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483056","2016-03-24","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect on unemployed people starting employment of the time taken by the Disclosure and Barring Service to process applications.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31817","31817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483057","2016-03-24","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications to the Disclosure and Barring Service from people in Clacton constituency have taken more than 60 days to process in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31818","31818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483058","2016-03-24","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of the time taken to process Disclosure and Barring Service checks.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31819","31819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483059","2016-03-23","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost of retail crime was to businesses in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31795","31795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483060","2016-03-23","Department for International Development","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, to what her Department allocated spending on malaria in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15; and how that spending was disbursed between multilateral and bilateral channels.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31854","31854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483061","2016-03-23","Department for International Development","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which humanitarian aid operations the Government has been involved in that (a) have involved other EU member states and (b) have been EU-led.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31843","31843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483062","2016-03-23","Department for International Development","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what international humanitarian aid exercises her Department has been involved in that have (a) involved EU member states and (b) been EU-led.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31847","31847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483063","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many claims for underpayment of the national minimum wage have been brought before employment tribunals in each of the last five years; how many such claims were successful; and how much was awarded to claimants in claims related to underpayment of the national minimum wage in that period.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31873","31873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483064","2016-04-11","Attorney General","2016-03-21","To ask the Attorney General, whether his Department plans to move any government legal services to the north of England.","Biography information for John Stevenson","John Stevenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31895","31895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483065","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many victims of trafficking have brought civil claims against their traffickers in each of the last five years; how many such claims have resulted in awards for damages; and what the value of such awards was in such cases.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31893","31893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483066","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will ensure the adequacy of provision of screens for use as a special protection measure for vulnerable and intimidated witnesses.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31820","31820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483067","2016-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of non-custodial sentences for knife crime offenders on the rate of reoffending.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31831","31831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483068","2016-03-24","Northern Ireland Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate her Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the Fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment she has made of which of her Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31825","31825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483069","2016-03-24","Northern Ireland Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of a Northern Ireland Bill of Rights.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31923","31923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483070","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to paragraph 4.49 of the National Security Strategy and Strategic Defence and Security Review 2015, what progress the Government has made on the proposal to adapt a Voyager aircraft for the secure transport of senior ministers and the Royal Family; what adaptations will be made to the aircraft for that purpose; what estimate the Government has made of costs of those adaptations; who is responsible for making those adaptations; and when those adaptations are planned to be completed.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31887","31887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483071","2016-03-24","Scotland Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate his Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the Fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment he has made of which of his Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31823","31823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483072","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which bus operators his Department has had discussions with on the Buses Bill; and how many meetings his Department has had with each of those bus operators.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31799","31799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483073","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to protect ancient woodland along the route of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31783","31783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483074","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much UK steel in (a) value and (b) weight his Department has used in projects it funds in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31877","31877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483075","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many statutory removals of vehicles have occurred on each section of motorway using an all-lane running configuration (a) since those configurations have been in use and (b) in each of the 10 years before those configurations were in use; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31894","31894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483076","2016-03-23","Wales Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate his Department has made of the number of its Senior Civil Servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the Fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31796","31796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483077","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance claimants with (a) Parkinson's disease, (b) rheumatoid arthritis, (c) motor neurone disease, (d) multiple sclerosis and (e) cystic fibrosis have been (i) placed in the support group, (ii) placed in the work-related activity group and (iii) found fit for work since 2008; and what statements have been made to current claimants of employment and support allowance to inform them that they will not be affected by changes.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31811","31811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483078","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many people in each (a) region and (b) constituent part of the UK will be affected by changes to personal independence payments: aids and appliances; and what support he plans to give to those affected.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31812","31812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483079","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people diagnosed with inflammatory bowel disease in (a) England and (b) Wales applied for disability living allowance in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31788","31788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483080","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who claim disability living allowance in (a) England and (b) Wales have been diagnosed with inflammatory bowel disease.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31789","31789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483081","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people diagnosed with inflammatory bowel disease in (a) England and (b) Wales applied for employment and support allowance in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31790","31790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483082","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many in work personal independence payment (PIP) claimants will be affected by his Department's proposed changes to aids and appliances points; and how many such claims will (a) no longer qualify for PIP and (b) receive a reduced PIP payment.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31806","31806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483083","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of in work personal independence payment (PIP) claimants who will no longer be able to work as a result of his Department's proposed changes to PIP aids and appliances points.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31807","31807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483084","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment (PIP) claimants in each (a) parliamentary constituency and (b) local authority area will be affected by his Department's proposed changes to aids and appliances points; and what the average reduction in PIP payment per person will be.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31808","31808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483085","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who claim employment and support allowance in (a) England and (b) Wales have been diagnosed with inflammatory bowel disease.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31791","31791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483086","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disability living allowance claimants he expects to transfer to personal independence payment in each year to 2020.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31891","31891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483087","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans the Government has for the allocation of the £70 million funding for relationship support announced by the Prime Minister on 11 January 2016; and what the timetable will be for the distribution of that funding over the Parliament.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31880","31880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483088","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Government plans to spend on relationship support in 2016-17; and on what programmes that funding will be spent.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31875","31875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483089","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much was spent by the Government on relationship support in 2015-16; and to what programmes that funding was allocated.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31876","31876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483090","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 February 2016 to Question 27438, on children: maintenance, on what basis those cases have been referred for arrears cleansing or validation.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31886","31886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483091","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2016 to Question 30693, on the Pubs Code Adjudicator, how many people were approached by (a) his Department and (b) Saxton Bampflyde Limited; and how many of those people (i) previously worked and (ii) work for pub companies.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31924","31924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483092","2016-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, on what date his Department plans to publish the final version of the Pubs Code.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31914","31914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483093","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2016 to Question 30126, what estimate his Department has made of the total cost of running sites operated by the (a) Skills Funding Agency and (b) Education Funding Agency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31935","31935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483094","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Freedom of Information Request release of 1 October 2014, reference BIS/FOI/2014/20352, what the data on referrals is for each financial year between 2009-10 and 2015-16.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31997","31997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483095","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2016 to Question 30732 and the oral contribution of the Minister for Small Business, Industry and Enterprise of 10 March 2016, Official Report, column 425, what the nature of Mr Newby's assistance to departmental officials was in the development and implementation of the Pubs Code.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31998","31998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483096","2016-03-23","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what average time was taken to hear non-domestic rates appeals in each local authority area in the latest year for which data is available.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31992","31992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483097","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate how much the apprenticeship levy is expected to raise in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31999","31999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483098","2016-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2016 to Question 30738 on employment: telephone services, what the equivalent data is for each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31993","31993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483099","2016-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2016 to Question 30688, if he will publish the interests submitted by Mr Paul Newby when he applied for the role of Pubs Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32012","32012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483100","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether learners studying on degree apprenticeship programmes are exempt from council tax.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32037","32037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483101","2016-03-23","Cabinet Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of deaths in (a) England, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales and (d) Northern Ireland resulted from (i) traffic offences and (ii) other offences in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31987","31987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483102","2016-03-24","Cabinet Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the mortality rate for people aged between 40 and 50 was in (a) England and Wales, (b) Newcastle, (c) Sheffield and (d) Newham in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31976","31976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483103","2016-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many badges of honour have been awarded by (a) Gibraltar, (b) the Falkland Islands, (c) the Cayman Islands and (d) Bermuda in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31901","31901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483104","2016-03-23","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of a reduction in VAT for small businesses in the tourism sector.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31959","31959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483105","2016-03-23","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many properties valued at or over £1 million were sold in October to December (a) 2014 and (b) 2015; and how much was raised in stamp duty land tax in each of those periods.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31919","31919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483106","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraphs 1.140 and 1.142 of the Budget 2016, whether it is his policy that apprentices over the age of 25 will be subject to the national living wage or the apprentice rate of the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31954","31954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483107","2016-03-23","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.205 of the Budget 2016, if he will publish the calculations referred to in footnote 143 on the potential costs to consumers of the rise in the standard rate of insurance premium tax.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31867","31867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483108","2016-03-23","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what training is provided to HM Revenue and Customs national minimum wage inspectors on identification and investigation of cases of human trafficking.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31872","31872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483109","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the budgetary implications of lower-than-predicted growth rates for government departments other than the Department for International Development.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31951","31951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483110","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department plans to include non-prescription incontinence pads, maternity pads and breast pads used by breastfeeding mothers in the definition of sanitary products for the purposes of zero rating under VAT.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32029","32029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483111","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of jobs that have been created by foreign direct investment from other EU countries in each region and constituent part of the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32043","32043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483112","2016-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2016 to Question 27887, what proportion of undecided and withdrawn appeals were (a) undecided and (b) withdrawn in each year since 2009-10; and for what reasons the number of undecided and withdrawn appeals is higher in 2015-16 than in any of the previous six years.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31996","31996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483113","2016-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of its spending on reducing homelessness in each of the next five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31943","31943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483114","2016-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on the salary levels of elected mayors of each of the combined authorities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31944","31944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483115","2016-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2016 to Question 31008, how many officials of his Department worked full-time on strategies to tackle homelessness in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31932","31932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483116","2016-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of the local government finance settlement announced in the 2015 Spending Review his Department plans to spend on homelessness prevention in each year up to 2019-20; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Berry","James Berry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31913","31913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483117","2016-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of underwriting a national rent deposit scheme to help more homeless people access the private rented sector.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31916","31916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483118","2016-03-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make it his policy to extend the protection granted to playing fields to any community leisure facilities, by ensuring that Sport England must be consulted before the sale of any such facility; and if he will ensure that Sport England is sufficiently resourced to carry out that role effectively.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31911","31911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483119","2016-03-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when he plans to publish further details of his Department's draft plans to change the way sports funding is allocated, with reference to pages 16 and 17 of Sporting Future: A New Strategy for an Active Nation.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31908","31908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483120","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the power systems upgrade for the Type 45 destroyer will commence fitting; and whether that work will be carried out by a contractor using facilities at HMNB Portsmouth for each ship in the class.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31871","31871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483121","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of fitting Mark 41 vertical launch capability to the Type 45 destroyer.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31870","31870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483122","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the role of the local authority in terms of (a) child protection, (b) safeguarding and (c) other duties for schools which become academies; and who will finance those roles.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31965","31965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483123","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that supply teachers are trained to an appropriate standard in the subjects they teach.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31964","31964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483124","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the maximum travelling time for a 16 to 18 year-old pupil to access sixth form education if it is not available in their local authority area; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31969","31969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483125","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has for the role of the local education authority in the provision of state education after the conversion of state-maintained schools to academies.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31961","31961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483126","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers have left the teaching profession in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31962","31962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483127","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers in each of the last five years have been foreign nationals.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31963","31963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483128","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to (a) assist and (b) encourage schools to make sport facilities available to the local community outside of school hours.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31907","31907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483129","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department provides to 16 to 18 year old pupils eligible for the pupil premium to ensure that they can access sixth form education if it is not available in their local authority area.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31968","31968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483130","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have been permanently excluded from school during Key stage 1 and 2 in the last three years.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31904","31904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483131","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children have been permanently excluded from school during Key stage 1 and 2 in each region in the last three years.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31905","31905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483132","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to make the Teenage Cancer Trust's education sessions available in every school.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31918","31918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483133","2016-03-24","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answers of 14 March 2016 to Question 30445 and 21 March 2016 to Question 31491, what estimate she has made of the final number of enterprise co-ordinators.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32000","32000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483134","2016-03-24","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence her Department holds on the effect of schools having no sixth form provision on (a) their ability to attract high-quality teaching staff, (b) their ability to attract pupils to fill available places and (c) the likelihood of them being good or outstanding schools.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31982","31982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483135","2016-03-24","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools participated in the Schools Direct programme in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31980","31980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483136","2016-03-24","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that there is high-quality sixth form provision within the Knowsley Borough Council area.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31983","31983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483137","2016-03-24","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on whether each local authority area should have at least one school with sixth form provision.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31984","31984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483138","2016-03-24","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and which local authority areas in England have no schools with sixth form provision.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31985","31985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483139","2016-03-24","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings she or officials of her Department have had on the future of (a) Halewood Academy and (b) sixth form provision in the Borough of Knowsley.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31986","31986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483140","2016-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate she has made of the proportion of the total annual cost of energy bills in the UK which results from EU legal requirements.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32027","32027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483141","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that schools take steps to promote the mental well-being of primary school students when they undertake Key Stage 1 and Key Stage 2 examinations.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32003","32003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483142","2016-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the UK meets its renewed target of zero carbon emissions by 2050.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32004","32004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483143","2016-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, reference to her speech of 18 November 2015, if she will take evidence from the CoalImP and the World Coal Association in her Department's forthcoming review of coal; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31910","31910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483144","2016-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will ask her Canadian counterpart for (a) emissions data and (b) the cost of the boundary dam power station in Saskatchewan, Canada; and if she will place that information in the Library.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31921","31921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483145","2016-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which measures originating in the EU have an effect on the level of energy bills.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31915","31915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483146","2016-03-23","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.159 of Budget 2016, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of the freeze in petrol and diesel duty on (a) carbon emissions by cars and (b) the environment.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32024","32024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483147","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support her Department provides to farmers who are waiting to receive a single farm payment.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31922","31922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483148","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to paragraph 1.301 of Budget 2016, how much funding will be made available to support delivery of the final phase of the Leeds Flood Alleviation Scheme; and what proportion of that funding is additional to the £2.3 billion capital programme previously announced.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31920","31920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483149","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to paragraph 1.242 of Budget 2016, how much of the additional £700 million for flood defence and resilience will be spent in Lancashire.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31906","31906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483150","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions her Department has had with the Treasury on the business case for delivery of the final phase of the Leeds Flood Alleviation Scheme.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31970","31970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483151","2016-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the press release by her Department of 17 March 2016, how much of the £33 million funding for flood defence schemes in Cumbria will be spent in Flimby.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31934","31934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483152","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of funding from the new measures announced in paragraph 1.205 of Budget 2016 she plans to allocate for flood defences on the River Medway and its tributaries.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32007","32007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483153","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to introduce a mandatory dog-breeding licence for any household planning to produce two or more litters per year; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32008","32008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483154","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward legislative proposals to ban the sale of puppies under eight weeks old; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32009","32009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483155","2016-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will ensure that a cost impact assessment, including the potential impact assessment on the mobile seed cleaning industry, is made for any future emergency order relating to the use of neonicotinoids.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31937","31937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483156","2016-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will ensure that any new Emergency Authorisations related to neonicotinoids or seed management will include a provision that both certified seed and farm-saved seed are acceptable for the distribution of the seeds that are in the order.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31938","31938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483157","2016-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will publish the stewardship documents for Emergency Authorisation No. 1949 and No. 1950 of 2015.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31939","31939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483158","2016-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which companies, organisations and other persons, in any capacity, were given sight of the stewardship documents either before, or after, the issuing of Emergency Authorisation No. 1949 and No. 1950 of 2015.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31940","31940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483159","2016-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent reports of Iran testing a new long-range ballistic missile.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31966","31966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483160","2016-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to the Palestinian Authority on allegations of its schools naming sports tournaments after terrorists.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32025","32025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483161","2016-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports his Department has received on the rebuilding by Hamas of its cross-border tunnel infrastructure into Israel.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32026","32026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483162","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps Public Health England has taken in conjunction with the National Public Health Workforce Advisory Group to implement the public mental health leadership and workforce development framework, published in March 2015.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32036","32036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483163","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that all applications to the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority (HFEA) for a licence to carry out research using human admixed embryos are published on the HFEA website with a description of the research proposed.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32041","32041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483164","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to Health Education England funding on training in (a) child psychotherapy, (b) clinical psychotherapy; and on the Improving Access to Psychological Therapies programme.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32035","32035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483165","2016-03-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of first stake free offers on (a) the incidence of gambling addiction amongst (i) children and young people and (ii) other people and (b) people who already have such an addiction.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32042","32042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483166","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support is provided to GPs to inform them of the research related to and treatments for people with mental health conditions.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31903","31903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483167","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the per capita funding for the Vale of York Clinical Commissioning Group (CCG) is in 2015-16; and what the equivalent funding is for each of that CCG's 10 most similar CCG's.","Biography information for Nigel Adams","Nigel Adams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31974","31974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483168","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to ensure that clinical commissioning groups implement the NICE guideline on diagnosis of food allergy in children and young people in a primary care setting.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31900","31900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483169","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department has provided for public information campaigns on brain tumours in children and young people in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31917","31917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483170","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has for the next National Clinical Audit of avoidable deaths in relation to epilepsy.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31958","31958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483171","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support people with (a) ocular melanoma and (b) other eye conditions with the financial cost of eye tests.","Biography information for Jo Cox","Jo Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31897","31897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483172","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to improve access to immunotherapy for the long-term management of allergic disease.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31898","31898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483173","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to improve GP training on the identification, diagnosis and management of allergic diseases.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31899","31899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483174","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his Department's policy to ensure that brain tumour symptom cards are distributed to child health clinics and health visitors.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31912","31912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483175","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to tackle premature mortality among people on the autism spectrum.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32015","32015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483176","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what data his Department collects on premature mortality in people on the autism spectrum.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32016","32016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483177","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on research into brain tumours in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31945","31945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483178","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure that NHS maternity units improve their safety records.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32013","32013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483179","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of representations that NHS England should conduct a national autism mortality review.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32014","32014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483180","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress Public Health England is making on its development of a wellbeing and mental health leadership support programme.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32034","32034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483181","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has for the successor body to Health Education England for the commissioning for non-medical education.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32033","32033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483182","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many delayed transfer days in England were recorded in the NHS in each year since 2010; and what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the number of delayed transfer days of the introduction of the cap on social care costs in each year between 2020 and 2026.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32040","32040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483183","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people in each year between 2015 and 2026 who will (a) enter the social care system, (b) be affected by the cap on care costs being delayed from April 2016 until April 2020, (c) be affected by the increase in the ceiling of the means test being delayed until April 2020 and (d) be affected by the delay until April 2020 of the full introduction of the duty on local authorities under Section 18(3) of the Care Act 2014 to meet the eligible needs of self-funders in care homes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32038","32038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483184","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to (a) introduce the appeals system set out in Section 72 of the Care Act 2014 and (b) revise the current care capital limits.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32039","32039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483185","2016-03-24","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representations she has received from the North Wales Police and Crime Commissioner on the removal of people convicted of child abuse and rape from the Sex Offenders Register.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32030","32030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483186","2016-03-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what powers the EU has to freeze the assets of suspected terrorist groups or individuals suspected of involvement in terrorism; and what assessment he has made of the benefits to the UK of those powers.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32019","32019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483187","2016-03-23","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the level of vulnerability of people on the autism spectrum to various aspects of cybercrime.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32018","32018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483188","2016-03-23","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the level of involvement of autistic people in cybercrime offences.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32017","32017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483189","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will provide an estimate of (a) the total level of immigration from other EU member states and (b) the annual number of people coming to settle in the UK from other EU member states which would trigger the activation of the proposed alert and safeguard emergency brake mechanism; and what discussions he has had with his counterparts in other EU member states and the European Commission on the appropriate thresholds for the emergency brake mechanism to be activated.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31955","31955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483190","2016-03-24","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken to strengthen its data collection strategy to help combat human trafficking.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31936","31936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483191","2016-03-23","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress her Department has made on plans for the future of the Cedars pre-departure accommodation site.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31868","31868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483192","2016-03-24","Home Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when those parts of the Psychoactive Substances Act 2016 which have not come into force are expected to come into force.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32044","32044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483193","2016-03-23","Department for International Development","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what plans the Government has to support efforts to achieve goal 6 of the 2030 Agenda for Sustainable Development on water and sanitation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31973","31973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483194","2016-03-24","Department for International Development","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the (a) effect of lower-than predicted growth rates on the Overseas Development Assistance budget and (b) implications of such rates on the budget for her Department.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31950","31950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483195","2016-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the number of times that lawyers have not been able to meet their clients in custody in England and Wales at less than 12 hours' notice due to staff shortages, staff disputes or other administrative reasons in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and how many Crown or magistrates' court hearings have been adjourned or delayed as a result in each of those years.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32011","32011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483196","2016-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on (a) support for independent monitoring boards and (b) consideration of the recommendations which those boards make in their annual reports to his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lord Garnier","Sir Edward Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32010","32010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483197","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Court of Appeal's decision on domestic violence evidential requirements for legal aid, what interim steps his Department plans to make to allow victims of domestic violence with evidence of financial abuse access to legal aid.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32031","32031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483198","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many claims for underpayment of the national minimum wage have been brought before employment tribunals since 1 July 2015; and how many such claims referred to underpayment of the national minimum wage for a period of more than (a) two and (b) six years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31952","31952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483199","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of child deaths (a) by people who have been found guilty of and (b) related to domestic violence.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31933","31933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483200","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many online sellers of knives have been (a) prosecuted and (b) convicted under section 141A of the Criminal Justice Act 1988 for selling knives to people under 18 since that section came into force; and what sentences were handed down to people so convicted.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31953","31953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483201","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent discussions he has held with his counterparts in the devolved administrations on proposals to repeal the Human Rights Act 1998.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31927","31927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483202","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to consult on proposals to repeal the Human Rights Act 1998.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31928","31928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483203","2016-03-23","Prime Minister","2016-03-21","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will create a group at ministerial level of representatives from the relevant government departments to ensure that progress is made on the Government's sport strategy with cross-departmental coordination.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31909","31909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483204","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which projects in the UK will receive funding from the Connecting Europe Facility transport 2015 Multi-Annual Work Programme.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31930","31930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483205","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many members of staff of HS2 Ltd have been provided with (a) mobile telephones, (b) tablet devices and (c) corporate credit cards in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31931","31931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483206","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to bring forward separate legislative proposals on the proposed extension of High Speed 2 from the West Midlands to Crewe.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31929","31929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483207","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2016 to Question 30285, whether the working assumption that benefits from the Bus Service Operators Grant are passed on to passengers 50 per cent through lower fares and 50 per cent through increased service levels was informed by discussions with bus operators.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31975","31975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483208","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Natura 20000 sites are located within 10 miles of the proposed route of phase two of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31956","31956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483209","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much EU funding has been provided for ground investigations related to High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31957","31957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483210","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the proposed Buses Bill, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on competition in the bus services market of bus operators retaining vehicle fleets, depots and other strategic assets when bus services are franchised.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31972","31972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483211","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2016 to Question 29611, in what specified format the Buses Bill will require data on routes, timetables, punctuality and fares to be published; and whether this format will differ from the format currently used by his Department to publish bus fares information.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31967","31967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483212","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to collect and publish data on bus fares by local authority; and if he will plan for that data to include fares information in prices rather than according to the retail prices index.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31971","31971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483213","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessments his Department has made of the potential economic benefit of (a) opening new stations on the Great Western Main line, (b) running later services on the Great Western Main line and (c) reducing rail fares on the Great Western Main line.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31988","31988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483214","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with (a) Network Rail and (b) train operating companies on minimising disruption from the planned closure of the Severn Tunnel for electrification.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31942","31942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483215","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 1.274 of Budget 2016, what plans the Government has made for the timetable of the review of the case for free-flow tolling on the Severn River Crossings.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32001","32001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483216","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 1.274 of Budget 2016, when the Government plans to consult on the tolls on the Severn River Crossings; and what (a) the aims and (b) the format of that consultation will be.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32002","32002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483217","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an estimate of the level of maintenance only toll on the Severn River Crossings.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31949","31949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483218","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans that the toll level for Vehicle Category 1 and Vehicle Category 2 will be equal when the Severn Bridges return to public ownership.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31948","31948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483219","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2016, to Question 31254, on road: accidents, which 31 local authorities have not yet received an agreement proposal.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31978","31978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483220","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many statutory removals of vehicles have taken place from the M1, M6, M62 and M25 in each of the last 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Mrs Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31981","31981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483221","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2016 to Question 30892, when his Department plans to set up the independent Road Safety Management Capacity Review, announced in his Department's Road Safety Statement, published on 21 December 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32028","32028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483222","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government's review of the Davies Commission on Aviation capacity in the South East includes an assessment of the costs and benefits of government investment in aviation biofuel.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32023","32023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483223","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans his Department has to extend the remit of the Child Maintenance Group to cover the investigation of cases in which a non-resident parent has failed to declare income to HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32021","32021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483224","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2016 to Question 30367, on vocational guidance, whether schools in Jobcentre Plus Districts in which Jobcentre Plus Support for Schools is being rolled out will be contacted by Jobcentre Plus or the Careers and Enterprise Company.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32032","32032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483225","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the criteria are for referral of a child maintenance case to the Child Maintenance Group's Financial Investigations Unit.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32020","32020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483226","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that rules relating to under-occupancy do not affect households in which couples have to sleep in separate rooms due to medical appliances.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32005","32005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483227","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that reforms of the welfare system are communicated clearly to recipients of welfare payments.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32006","32006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483228","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether Jobcentre Plus staff can provide support and advice to claimants who are intending to appeal against a benefit sanctions decision.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31979","31979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483229","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the mortality rate for claimants of incapacity benefit and employment and support allowance aged between 40 and 50 was in (a) England and Wales, (b) Newcastle, (c) Sheffield and (d) Newham in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31977","31977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483230","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 February 2016 to Question 27465, what the budget is for the Child Maintenance Group's Financial Investigations Unit for 2015-16.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31991","31991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483231","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment claimants there were in Inverclyde in 2015.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31989","31989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483232","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the level of household median net earnings after the deduction of income tax and national insurance contributions and before benefits was for (a) all working-age adults, (b) working-age adults without children and (c) working-age adults with children (i) including individuals in households without household earnings and (ii) excluding individuals in households without household earnings in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31994","31994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483233","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment claimants there were in Cardiff South and Penarth constituency in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31995","31995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483234","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 February 2016 to Question 27464, how many joint investigations by the Child Maintenance Group Financial Investigation Unit and HM Revenue Customs in connection with income fraud for child maintenance and tax purposes are underway; and how many such investigations have been completed.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31990","31990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483235","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average weekly personal independence payment was to people in Cardiff South and Penarth constituency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31941","31941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483236","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many recipients of disability living allowance between the ages of 16 and 64 qualifying for each rate of (a) care and (b) mobility component have a main disabling condition of cystic fibrosis.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31869","31869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483237","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what communications his Department had with people receiving personal independence payments to inform them of the potential changes to their benefits before announcing those changes.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31947","31947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483238","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2016 to Question 30986, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children who will be lifted out of poverty as a result of universal credit before any effect on employment.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31946","31946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483239","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to improve the assessment process for personal independence payments.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31925","31925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483240","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have had their initial assessments for personal independence payments assessments payments upheld on appeal in (a) the UK, (b) Wiltshire and (c) the Chippenham constituency in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31926","31926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483241","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what work his Department is undertaking to support people with mental health conditions who are subject to the personal independent payments assessment process.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31902","31902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483242","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects the findings of the review of industrial injuries disablement benefit to be published.","Biography information for Neil Gray","Neil Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31960","31960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483243","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 February 2016 to Question 27368, on what basis the Child Support Agency allows non-resident parents to self-categorise as self-employed for child maintenance purposes; whether the new Child Maintenance Service plans to adopt the HM Revenue and Customs definition of self-employed when considering the employment status of non-resident parents under the 2012 child maintenance scheme or to allow non-resident parents to self-categorise their own employment status; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32022","32022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484344","2016-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if she will ensure that the final determination on fracking applications is made by local authorities.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904308","904308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484409","2016-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department is taking to promote the development of small modular reactors.","Biography information for Dr Phillip Lee","Dr Phillip Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904297","904297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485336","2016-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of the UK's energy was generated from renewable sources in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Will Quince","Will Quince","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904295","904295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480609","2016-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which coal mining projects in Russia have been supported by UK Export Finance since 2011.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31747","31747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480610","2016-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which coal mining projects are being supported by UK Export Finance.","Biography information for Rebecca Pow","Rebecca Pow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31748","31748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480611","2016-03-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of UK firms was owed money for late payments in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31753","31753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480612","2016-03-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the level of funding for research and development on productivity.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31754","31754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480613","2016-03-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he  will make it his policy to create a single online platform for accessing government support for increasing exports for UK companies.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31755","31755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480614","2016-03-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department has invested in (a) large facilities and (b) other (i) national and (ii) international capital projects managed by the Research Councils in each of the last ten years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31756","31756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480615","2016-03-22","HM Treasury","2016-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average penalty awarded against employers who failed to pay the national minimum wage was in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31766","31766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480616","2016-03-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the total amount of student debt (a) repaid and (b) outstanding was in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31771","31771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480617","2016-03-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 3 March 2016 to Question 27866, what powers EEA states which are not EU members have to (a) terminate and (b) change the terms of the membership of the EEA of another EEA state which is not a member of the EU.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31775","31775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480618","2016-03-23","Cabinet Office","2016-03-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to page 5 of the publication, Socio-Economic Diversity in the Fast Stream, published in February 2016, what progress his Department has made on (a) targeting universities and academic departments, (b) evaluating the impact of campus activity and schools outreach, (c) the iterative use of live recruitment data to inform approaches to promoting SEB diversity and (d) introducing other enhanced data insights to direct resources more effectively through the attraction process.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31772","31772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480619","2016-03-22","Cabinet Office","2016-03-18","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of individual voter registration.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31752","31752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480620","2016-03-23","HM Treasury","2016-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.27 of Budget 2016, for what reason the full academisation of schools in England is not included in his Department's Budget 2016 policy costings report; and what costings his Department has related to that policy.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31722","31722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480621","2016-03-23","HM Treasury","2016-03-18","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many press officers are employed by his Department.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31750","31750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480622","2016-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will estimate how much revenue will be accrued from business rates in each local authority in each financial year to 2020.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31746","31746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480623","2016-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 1.160 of Budget 2016, what his policy is on providing compensation to local authorities for potential loss of income related to the planned reductions in business rates.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31745","31745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480624","2016-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of people who have purchased homes under the Help to Buy scheme were from BAME communities since the introduction of that scheme.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31731","31731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480625","2016-03-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Triennial Review of gambling machine stakes and prize limits plans to consider the (a) effect on mental health and (b) other social and non-economic effects of fixed-odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31749","31749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480626","2016-03-22","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he plans to take in response to the findings of the Clementi Review into Governance and Regulation of the BBC; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31727","31727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480627","2016-03-23","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the Fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment he has made of which of his Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31720","31720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480628","2016-03-23","Department for Education","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the Fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment she has made of which of her Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31718","31718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480629","2016-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions her Department has had with the EU institutions on the (a) level of VAT on energy saving materials and (b) European Commission's VAT Action Plan.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31734","31734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480630","2016-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what representations she has received on accusations of mis-selling by Home Energy and Lifestyle Management.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31735","31735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480631","2016-03-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent discussions her Department has had with HM Treasury on the level of VAT on energy saving materials.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31733","31733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480632","2016-03-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what criteria the Government is using to determine the sites of future small modular reactors.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31770","31770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480633","2016-03-24","Prime Minister","2016-03-18","To ask the Prime Minister, what plans he has to appoint a new envoy on climate change.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31764","31764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480634","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect on animal welfare of the use of glue traps.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31762","31762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480635","2016-03-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to the Countryside and Rights of Way Act 2000, what her policy is on the extension of the definition of mapped open countryside to caves.","Biography information for James Heappey","James Heappey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31768","31768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480636","2016-03-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26471, whether the UK cetacean Strandings Investigation Programme plans to assess the potential link between oil and gas activities and related seismic testing and the movement of sperm whales to North Sea waters.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31729","31729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480637","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department's estimate of the number of people who have been affected by HIV or hepatitis C through treatment with NHS-supplied blood or blood products has changed since the publication of Impact Assessment No. 3140 on 21 January 2015.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31744","31744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480638","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the reasons for the delay by NHS England on announcing a public consultation on pre-exposure prophylaxis for HIV; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31743","31743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480639","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to help pressures on local health care services resulting from an increasing population of elderly people.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31723","31723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480640","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what provision the Government has in place to provide extra funding for clinical commissioning groups to deal with increasing local pressures on social care resulting from limits on local authority resources and NHS trusts being placed on special measures.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31724","31724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480641","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the Fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment he has made of which of his Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31717","31717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480642","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will respond to the petition of Isabelle Garnett on the www.change.org website, entitled Help my son get the autism care he needs.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31751","31751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480643","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in each age group admitted to A&E for (a) psychiatric conditions and (b) intentional self-harm were re-admitted within 30 days in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31760","31760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480644","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many registered nurses aged between 60 and 67 are employed by (a) Lancashire Teaching Hospitals NHS Foundation Trust and (b) Lancashire Care NHS Foundation Trust respectively; and what proportion of registered nurses in each of those NHS trusts are 60 to 67 years of age.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31761","31761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480645","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of government NHS funding which primary care was allocated to in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31776","31776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480646","2016-03-23","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects NHS England to announce its public consultation on pre-exposure prophylaxis for HIV.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31765","31765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480647","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of changes in the level of administrative demands on GPs since 2014.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31778","31778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480648","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the change in capacity of GPs to conduct their NHS Health Check obligations resulting from changes in funding for those obligations in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31779","31779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480649","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on primary care delivery of changes in the level of administrative demands on those delivering that care.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31774","31774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480650","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of GP working hours available in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31781","31781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480651","2016-03-22","Home Office","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 25 February 2016 to Question 27389, what assessment her Department has made of the ability of failed asylum seekers to fund travel to their country of origin.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31773","31773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480652","2016-03-22","Home Office","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many fixed penalty notices police forces have issued related to smoking in vehicles with children in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31730","31730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480653","2016-03-22","Department for International Development","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what mechanisms are in place to ensure funding from her Department reaches the project for which it is intended.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31732","31732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480654","2016-03-23","Department for International Development","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what estimate her Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the Fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment she has made of which of her Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31721","31721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480655","2016-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what provisions are in place to ensure that provision of court time for non-molestation orders between parents is dealt with as a matter of urgency.","Biography information for Holly Lynch","Holly Lynch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31725","31725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480656","2016-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people aged 18 to 20 have received custodial sentences of under 12 months for knife crime offences in London since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31726","31726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480657","2016-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many compensation orders were made by HM Courts and Tribunals Service against people convicted of modern slavery offences in each of the last five years; and how much compensation was awarded to victims of modern slavery related to such compensation orders in each of those years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31757","31757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480658","2016-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many reparation orders have been made by HM Courts and Tribunals Service against people convicted of modern slavery offences under section 10 of the Modern Slavery Act 2015; and how much compensation has been awarded to victims of modern slavery related to such reparation orders.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31758","31758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480659","2016-03-23","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many reparation orders have been made by HM Courts and Tribunals Service against people convicted of modern slavery offences in each of the last six months.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31759","31759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480660","2016-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he has taken to ensure (a) the efficiency of the transition to new courts of cases from courts that are planned for closure and (b) minimal adverse effect on those remaining courts.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31767","31767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480661","2016-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his speech to the Inter-parliamentary Coalition for Combating Anti-Semitism on 15 March 2016, what legal changes he was referring to in that speech.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31769","31769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480662","2016-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what regulations govern parental consent for the recording of interviews with lone children in cases involving Cafcass.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31777","31777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480663","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 8.18 of the Airports Commission Final Report, July 2015, what the estimated cost is of the tunnelling work required for the M25; and whether that cost would be incurred by the public purse or Heathrow Airport Limited.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31763","31763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480664","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 18 January to Question 22232, when he plans to publish the findings of the London and South Coast Rail Corridor Study.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31738","31738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480665","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 1.236 of Budget 2016, how much additional funding will be provided for investment in roads; and to which schemes that funding will be disbursed.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31739","31739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480666","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what meetings he has had with Network Rail in the last 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain Stewart","Iain Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31740","31740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480667","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 5.13 of the Airports Commission: Final Report, published in July 2015, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the finding that 431 hectares of green belt designated land would be required for the proposed third runway at Heathrow.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31741","31741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480668","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many air pollution monitors there are in which location within Heathrow Airport's perimeter from which official data on air quality is collected.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31742","31742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480669","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his plans are for the trialling of driverless HGV platoons.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31728","31728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480670","2016-03-23","Department for Transport","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the Fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment he has made of which of his Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31719","31719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480671","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on levels of poverty of the proposed reforms to personal independence payment in the Budget 2016.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31737","31737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480672","2016-03-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if his Department will conduct a revised impact assessment for universal credit on the effect of reforms to its design since 2012.","Biography information for Nick Thomas-Symonds","Nick Thomas-Symonds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31736","31736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/480673","2016-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-18","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on jobseeker's allowance claimants taking up volunteer work of the requirement for them to spend 35 hours each week searching for work; and whether that assessment was conducted prior to implementation of that policy.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31780","31780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479477","2016-03-21","Attorney General","2016-03-17","To ask the Attorney General, how much his Department received from the European Social Fund between 2007 and 2014; and how much his Department further received from the European Social Investment Fund from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31679","31679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479478","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the running costs were for the 56 capital based science projects which his Department has funded for each year since 2007, referred to in the NAO Report entitled BIS's capital investment in science projects, HC 885, published on 10 March 2016; and what the projected running costs for those projects are for each year to 2020-21.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31687","31687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479480","2016-03-21","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many non-domestic rate arrears appeals were (a) lodged and (b) heard in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31686","31686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479481","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people were refused student loans as a result of their discretionary leave to remain immigration status in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31672","31672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479482","2016-03-21","Cabinet Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to develop a standardised methodology for measuring SME spending by government departments which can be used as a baseline over the next five years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31682","31682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479483","2016-03-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will withdraw the appointment of Paul Newby as the Pubs Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31660","31660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479484","2016-03-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many UK Trade and Industry (UKTI) staff have direct experience of working in private sector exporting companies before taking up their employment at UKTI.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31661","31661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479485","2016-03-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the proportion of global patents for graphene that is held in the UK.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31662","31662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479486","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average length was of apprenticeships in the construction, planning and the built environment sector in 2015.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31693","31693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479487","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average length of time was that an apprentice stayed on an apprenticeship in 2015.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31690","31690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479490","2016-03-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment he has made of which of his Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31524","31524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479491","2016-03-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 2 February 2016 to Question 23296, what estimate her Department has made of the amount of (a) public and (b) private sector investment for low-carbon infrastructure and supply chain investment which has been invested in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31530","31530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479492","2016-03-21","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 4February 2016 to Question 24536, what assessment he has made of the number of exit payments in the private sector above £1 million; and what assessment his Department has made of the effect of such exit payments on pay inequality within and between the public and private sectors.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31531","31531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479493","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to answer Written Questions 29167 and 29238, tabled on 1 March 2016 and Written Question 29372, tabled on 2 March 2016.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31537","31537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479494","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many companies have cited in their registration at Companies House their registered office, the address of another business or private individual which they are not authorised to use in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31546","31546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479495","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment has he made of the potential impact on innovation in the UK of his Department's change to government research and development funding from a grant-based to a loan-based system.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31572","31572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479496","2016-03-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which companies have failed to pay the national minimum wage since the introduction of the new naming and shaming regulations on 1 October 2013.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31589","31589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479497","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to help support research into the Zika virus.","Biography information for James Heappey","James Heappey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31598","31598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479498","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much funding his Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31633","31633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479500","2016-03-21","Cabinet Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he has taken to increase the level of voter registration in schools, colleges and universities.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31600","31600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479501","2016-03-21","Cabinet Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost was of producing single departmental plans for each central government department.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31591","31591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479502","2016-03-21","Cabinet Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps has he taken to monitor the conduct of charities when marketing commercial products.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31568","31568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479503","2016-03-21","Cabinet Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of diversity of membership of the Civil Service Board; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31570","31570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479504","2016-03-22","Cabinet Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what projection he has made of the number of civil service apprenticeships that will be created in each department in each year until 2020.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31555","31555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479506","2016-03-22","Cabinet Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what wage the Government plans to pay civil servant apprentices.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31554","31554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479508","2016-03-22","Cabinet Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department has made an assessment of the average cost of a working peer which includes expenses, salary, necessary equipment and office space.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31628","31628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479509","2016-03-22","Cabinet Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many permanent secretaries are from a lower socio-economic background.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31627","31627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479510","2016-03-21","Cabinet Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much funding his Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31634","31634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479511","2016-03-22","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish further information on the science and innovation audit for Edinburgh and the Lothians set out in paragraph 1.268 of Budget 2016.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31629","31629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479512","2016-03-22","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a geographical analysis of the distribution of properties by rateable value.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31630","31630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479513","2016-03-22","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.157 of Budget 2016, whether he plans for premixed alcoholic drinks to fall within the scope of the proposed sugar tax.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31631","31631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479515","2016-03-22","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many cheques have been drafted by government departments and executive agencies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31668","31668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479516","2016-03-22","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what independent inspectors were appointed to investigate the frauds at the Bank of Credit and Commerce International; when those inspectors reported; and when their reports were published.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31632","31632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479517","2016-03-21","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 3.63 of the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015 and paragraph 2.16 of the Budget 2016, for what reasons the funding to support women's charities equivalent to the annual VAT raised on sanitary products has changed from £15 million to £12 million.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31684","31684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479518","2016-03-22","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people he assumed would use the Lifetime ISA in order to estimate the cost to the Exchequer of that policy.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31698","31698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479519","2016-03-22","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to her financial statement of 16 March 2016, Official Report, column 963, how the £500 million funding will be used to speed up the introduction of a fair national school funding formula.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31704","31704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479521","2016-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which is the first year in which he expects welfare spending to be contained within the welfare cap.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31705","31705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479524","2016-03-22","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will arrange for HM Revenue and Customs to acknowledge or reply to the letter of 24 February 2016 from the hon. Member for Walsall North concerning a constituent.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31532","31532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479525","2016-03-21","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what planning his Department is undertaking to facilitate private sector investment in the scalability of the proofs-of-work aspects of blockchain technology; and what discussions he has had with the Bank of England on that topic.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31545","31545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479527","2016-03-21","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to simplify the declaration of gift aid payments.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31567","31567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479528","2016-03-22","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what planning his Department is undertaking in relation to the effect of crypto-currencies on traditional banking models.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31557","31557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479529","2016-03-22","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what planning his Department is undertaking on the collation of block chain data; and what discussions he has had with the Bank of England on that topic.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31559","31559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479530","2016-03-22","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to implement the University College London RSCoin proposal.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31558","31558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479531","2016-03-22","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Bank of England on utilising the University College London RSCoin proposal as an alternative to Western Union, CHAPS, BACS and the Faster Payment Service.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31556","31556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479532","2016-03-22","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the guidance note on public sector pay and terms published by his Department on 5 February 2016, whether he plans to place that guidance on a statutory footing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31588","31588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479533","2016-03-21","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether all documents released by his Department as a result of Freedom of Information requests are placed on his Department's website.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31610","31610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479535","2016-03-21","HM Treasury","2016-03-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the total amount that the UK will contribute to the EU budget in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31611","31611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479536","2016-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of domestic violence refuges which have closed as a result of lack of funding in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31623","31623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479537","2016-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to paragraph 1.149 of the Budget 2016, how much of the increased funding available to prevent and reduce homelessness is in addition to the funding allocated to his Department in the Spending Review and Autumn Statement 2015.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31560","31560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479538","2016-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment he has made of which of his Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31528","31528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479539","2016-03-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the publication Decentralisation: An account of progress, published in December 2012, what progress his Department has made on proposals to deliver on annual decentralisation statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31692","31692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479540","2016-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the oral contribution of Baroness Williams of Trafford, 1 March 2016, HL Deb column 809, if he will place in the Library a copy of the research referenced in that contribution on the affordability of starter homes.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31666","31666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479541","2016-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2016 to Question 30411, on grants, to which 45 bodies his Department has provided grant funding under the Charities Act 2011 during the financial year 2015-16.","Biography information for Colleen Fletcher","Colleen Fletcher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31665","31665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479543","2016-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what engagement his Department has conducted with EU officials on the application for assistance from the EU Solidarity Fund to help communities affected by recent floods since making that application.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31625","31625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479544","2016-03-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31635","31635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479545","2016-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding his Department has applied for from the EU Solidarity Fund to help communities affected by recent floods.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31624","31624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479546","2016-03-21","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding his Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31636","31636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479548","2016-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate his Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment he has made of which of his Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31527","31527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479550","2016-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to his Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 27079, on Victory 1744, how many such meetings, on which dates, have been held between his officials and those in the Department for Culture, Media and Sport.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31553","31553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479551","2016-03-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many applications for the Legion d'Honneur have been withdrawn since July 2015 due to the death of the applicant; and what further steps his Department is taking to ensure that people nominated to receive that medal receive it as quickly as possible.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31541","31541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479552","2016-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if his Department will reconsider its decision to withdraw Volunteer Gliding Squadrons provision for Air Cadets in Wales.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31578","31578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479553","2016-03-21","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much funding his Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31637","31637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479555","2016-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, by how much he plans that his Department's contribution to public sector pensions will increase in 2019-20 and future years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31664","31664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479556","2016-03-22","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what definition his Department uses for cyber warfare.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31663","31663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479557","2016-03-21","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to announce national minimum fostering allowances for 2016-17.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31681","31681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479558","2016-03-21","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to work with local authorities to ensure that the education provided to home educated children is effectively regulated and safeguarded.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31680","31680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479559","2016-03-21","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31638","31638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479560","2016-03-22","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage older professionals to enter the teaching profession for the first time.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31711","31711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479561","2016-03-22","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people started studying for a PGCE in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31712","31712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479562","2016-03-22","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy that new academies should not join under-performing multi-academy trusts.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31713","31713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479564","2016-03-21","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government has taken to assess whether the home education of children in consistent with Article 12 of the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31691","31691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479565","2016-03-22","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to paragraph 1.89 of the Budget 2016, whether nursery schools are included in the plans to convert all schools to academies; how she expects the changes announced in the Budget 2016 to affect nursery schools; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31594","31594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479566","2016-03-22","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will establish an awards scheme for schools that have excelled in supporting children with special educational needs and disability similar to the scheme for pupil premium awards.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31550","31550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479567","2016-03-22","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many non-UK children of each nationality are currently looked after in (a) foster care and (b) residential homes.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31551","31551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479568","2016-03-22","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what benefits and support services are not available to non-UK nationals leaving care that are available to UK citizens.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31552","31552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479569","2016-03-22","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether children who receive the higher rate of the mobility component of disability living allowance are considered to be eligible children for free school transport; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31573","31573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479570","2016-03-22","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether local authorities are obliged to provide free school transport to (a) all eligible children and (b) eligible children who receive the higher rate of the mobility component of disability living allowance.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31574","31574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479571","2016-03-22","Department for Education","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance and training Ofsted inspectors receive on applying the criteria for a good Ofsted grading in settings involving children with special education needs and disability.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31549","31549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479574","2016-03-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether Heysham and Hartlepool are being considered as sites for large nuclear or small modular reactors.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31538","31538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479575","2016-03-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when the techno-economic assessment of small modular reactors is expected to be completed and published.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31539","31539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479576","2016-03-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has made an assessment of the potential of small modular reactors as a heat source.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31540","31540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479577","2016-03-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate her Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment she has made of which of her Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31526","31526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479578","2016-03-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much funding her Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31639","31639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479579","2016-03-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, with reference to her speech of 18 November 2015, at the Institution of Civil Engineers, when her Department plans to publish the terms of reference and timescales for the consultation on closing all unabated coal-fired power stations.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31604","31604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479581","2016-03-22","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2016 to Question 30208, whether she plans to give Ministerial approval to relax the restrictions of the public sector exit cap on employees of the Nuclear Decommissioning Authority who leave work after 1 October 2016.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31669","31669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479582","2016-03-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding her Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31640","31640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479583","2016-03-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the total cost of damage caused by floods in winter 2015-16.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31626","31626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479584","2016-03-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment she has made of which of her Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31525","31525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479585","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the (a) establishment and (b) running costs of the Food Crime Unit have been to date; and what resources have been allocated to that Unit in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31533","31533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479586","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on establishing an investigative capability for the Food Crime Unit.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31534","31534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479588","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prosecutions have been made as a result of information supplied by the Food Crime Unit since its creation.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31535","31535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479589","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many reports of food fraud have been made to the Food Crime Unit through the official website since its creation.","Biography information for Nick Smith","Nick Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31536","31536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479590","2016-03-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will take steps to facilitate an application from Lancaster City Council and the Environment Agency for funding for flood defences along the River Lune.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31590","31590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479591","2016-03-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress her Department has made on the issues raised by the Sheep Dip Sufferers Support Group at the meeting of 19 November 2015 relating to (a) organophosphate sheep dip and (b) missing medical records from 1992; and if she will send the minutes of that meeting to the Sheep Dip Sufferers Support Group.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31579","31579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479592","2016-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26920, if he will offer the Iraqi government British forensic team support to investigate mass graves discovered in Sinjar.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31582","31582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479593","2016-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of whether Daesh has been responsible for (a) crimes against humanity and (b) ethnic cleansing.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31583","31583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479595","2016-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on the UN Security Council referring evidence of potential genocide by Daesh to the International Criminal Court.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31584","31584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479596","2016-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26922 and the statement with reference to genocide on 17 March 2016 by the US Secretary of State on Daesh atrocities, if he will reassess the Government's policy on judgements as to whether genocide has occurred.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31585","31585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479597","2016-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with US Secretary of State on the killing of Yazidis by Daesh.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31586","31586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479598","2016-03-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterparts on the demolition of the village of Umm el-Hiran.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31592","31592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479599","2016-03-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he intends to answer the letter to him dated 9 February from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Ms M Hamilton.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31607","31607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479600","2016-03-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the Indian government on the Seaman Guard Ohio since the Indian court ruling relating to that matter in January 2016.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31597","31597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479602","2016-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Angolan counterparts on the current outbreak of yellow fever in Angola.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31562","31562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479603","2016-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of people who have reported being tortured since the start of his Department's technical assistance programme in Bahrain.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31696","31696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479604","2016-03-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations his Department has made to the government of Bahrain on the imprisonment of Zainab Al Khawaja; and whether he plans to make representations to press for Zainab Al Khawaja's release.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31697","31697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479605","2016-03-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how much funding his Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31641","31641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479606","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding his Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31642","31642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479607","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission an independent assessment of the effect on children of legislation on smoking in cars.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31605","31605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479608","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate the Government has made of the likely savings to the public purse of implementing the changes to financial support for people affected by HIV or hepatitis C through treatment with NHS-supplied blood or blood products set out in the Government's consultation.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31671","31671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479609","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much financial support his Department has given to people affected by HIV or hepatitis C through treatment with NHS-supplied blood or blood products in each year since 1988.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31670","31670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479610","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people using cannabis in the UK for medicinal purposes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31606","31606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479612","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of Crown immunity on the ability to bring legal action on liability for the infection of patients with contaminated NHS blood.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31621","31621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479613","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much prescriptions for Sativex were issued in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31655","31655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479614","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the difference in cost to the public purse of people using medicinal cannabis rather than prescription drugs in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31656","31656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479615","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of medicinal cannabis use to the NHS in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31657","31657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479616","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures are being taken to ensure that (a) the outcomes of NHS England's proposals for a new Cancer Drugs Fund are aligned with the Accelerated Access Review (AAR), (b) the consultation outcomes are compatible with any forthcoming AAR recommendations relating to reform of NICE and (c) those programmes deliver consistent guidance on the medicines appraisal process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31678","31678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479617","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how the Government is monitoring the effects of the £1.25 billion funding for child and adolescent mental health services.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31689","31689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479619","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 1.233 of the March 2015 Budget, how much of the £1.25 billion funding for child and adolescent mental health services has been allocated.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31688","31688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479620","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will place copies of all responses received to NHS England's consultation on the new Cancer Drugs Fund in the Library.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31685","31685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479621","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consultation his Department conducted prior to the launch of its consultation on infected blood: reform of financial and other support.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31701","31701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479622","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of making the drug nabilone available on the NHS for people with multiple sclerosis.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31702","31702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479623","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many inflammatory bowel disease services have defined referral pathways in place to ensure that appropriate support is offered from a psychologist or counsellor with specialist knowledge of that condition.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31695","31695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479625","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which clinical speciality area had the highest drop-out rate for trainee doctors in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31706","31706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479626","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many agency mental health nurses have been employed by each clinical commissioning group in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31707","31707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479627","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many incidents of physical injury following restraint there have been in mental health services in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31708","31708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479628","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many incidents of face-down restraint there have been in mental health services in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31709","31709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479630","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the return on each pound invested in mental health research.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31710","31710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479631","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of how many inflammatory bowel disease services offer all people who are newly diagnosed a patient education session to help them understand their condition.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31694","31694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479632","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to introduce new initiatives to increase the uptake of new technologies on the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31566","31566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479633","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential change in the prevalence of genital warts following the award of the contract for supply of human papillomavirus vaccine to the bivalent vaccine.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31529","31529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479634","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many treatments for rare and infectious diseases have been approved for use on the NHS based on a foreign laboratory test analysis.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31521","31521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479635","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve the treatment on the NHS for people with Lyme disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31522","31522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479636","2016-03-22","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the International Lyme and Associated Diseases Society on use of results from the European Accredited Laboratory Assay related to Lyme disease to inform the provision of treatment on the NHS for that disease.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31523","31523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479638","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her French counterpart on French authorities' use of tear gas in the refugee camp in Calais.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31563","31563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479639","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to relax the Government's position on the settlement of refugees in Calais to allow the settlement of unaccompanied children in the UK.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31564","31564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479640","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many nationals from other EU member states have (a) applied and (b) been accepted for permanent residency in the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31612","31612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479641","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Albanian women (a) with (b) without children claimed asylum in the UK in each year since 2012; and how many of those women were subsequently removed from the UK.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31593","31593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479642","2016-03-22","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many women referred to the National Referral Mechanism for trafficking victims were subsequently removed from the UK in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31595","31595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479644","2016-03-22","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Albanian women were referred to the National Referral Mechanism in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31596","31596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479645","2016-03-22","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential merits of incorporating flood rescue into the statutory duties of the fire and rescue services.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31703","31703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479646","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether there is a limit on the number of Tier 2 (ICT) visas a company can apply for each year.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31676","31676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479647","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what examination of job roles her Department undertakes when issuing Tier 2 (ICT) visas.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31677","31677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479648","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which companies have been issued with more than 50 Tier 2 (ICT) visas in a calendar year for each of the last five years; and how many visas for each such company were issued.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31675","31675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479650","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2016 to Question 30235, in how many instances the Kingfisher Unit was used under rule (a) 40 and (b) 42 of the Detention Centre Rules in 2015.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31673","31673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479651","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her French counterpart on that country's current policy of dismantling the refugee camp in Calais.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31674","31674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479652","2016-03-22","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what advice her Department has received from the Migration Advisory Committee on whether nurses should remain in the occupation shortfall list; and when she next plans to issue a revised list.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31667","31667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479653","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many personal importation licences have been granted to EU citizens travelling to the UK with cannabis-based medication in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31653","31653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479654","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department provides to police forces on dealing with offenders who use cannabis to treat a serious medical condition.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31654","31654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479655","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of people using cannabis in the UK for medicinal purposes; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31651","31651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479656","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many personal importation licences have been granted to non-EU citizens travelling to the UK with cannabis-based medication in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31652","31652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479657","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with her French counterpart on steps to resettle people who have been displaced by the dismantling of sections of the refugee camp in Calais.","Biography information for Carol Monaghan","Carol Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31650","31650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479658","2016-03-21","Home Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much funding her Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31643","31643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479660","2016-03-21","Department for International Development","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much funding her Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31644","31644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479661","2016-03-21","Department for International Development","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2016 to Question 27367, in which countries her Department has integrated HIV and sexual reproductive health and rights programmes.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31659","31659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479662","2016-03-21","Department for International Development","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to encourage its bilateral partners to adopt a co-ordinated early childhood development approach to provide nutritional, medical and educational support for children.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31599","31599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479663","2016-03-22","Department for International Development","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the current outbreak of yellow fever in Angola and its regional implications; and whether the Government will assist the World Health Organisation supported vaccination campaign led by the Angolan government.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31561","31561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479664","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prosecutions for smoking in vehicles with children present have been carried out under the Smoke-free (Private Vehicles) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31571","31571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479665","2016-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he will publish further information on his plans for increasing the autonomy of prison governors.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31547","31547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479667","2016-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which prisons have been selected to take part in the pilot scheme on increasing the autonomy of prison governors; and how long that pilot scheme is expected to last.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31548","31548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479668","2016-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what research his Department is undertaking on the use and effects of psychoactive substances on the prison estate.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31543","31543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479669","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what training is available for prison officers in dealing with inmates who are under the influence of psychoactive substances on the prison estate.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31544","31544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479670","2016-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 1.287 of Budget 2016, what estimate he has made of how many civil servants will be relocated in his Department as a result of the programme to create centres of expertise outside the capital.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31608","31608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479671","2016-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people have been prosecuted for cultivation of cannabis in each of the last five years for which records are available; in how many of those prosecutions a serious medical condition was cited in mitigation; and what the cost to the public purse was of those prosecutions.","Biography information for Mr Nick Clegg","Mr Nick Clegg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31658","31658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479673","2016-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much funding his Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31645","31645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479674","2016-03-21","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how his Department defines a vulnerable and intimidated witness; and what processes are in place to support such witnesses when giving evidence.","Biography information for Mims Davies","Mims Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31609","31609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479675","2016-03-22","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many suppliers of knives have been convicted and prosecuted under section 141A of the Criminal Justice Act 1998 since that Act's implementation; and what average length of custodial sentence was received for such convictions.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31622","31622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479677","2016-03-21","Northern Ireland Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how much funding her Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31646","31646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479678","2016-03-21","Department of Health","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the Prime Minister's policy is on moving to an insurance or user-funded NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31565","31565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479679","2016-03-21","Scotland Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how much funding his Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31647","31647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479680","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of constructing a river crossing at Ipswich; and whether he plans that that cost will be wholly funded by his Department.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31618","31618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479681","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Government plans to halve the level of the Severn Bridge tolls inclusive or exclusive of VAT following the return of the Severn Bridge to public ownership.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31619","31619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479682","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the level of the Severn Bridge tolls for each vehicle category in January (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31620","31620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479683","2016-03-21","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding his Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31648","31648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479684","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it is the Government's policy that the EU Ports Services Regulation should be subject to the 12-month review procedure to assess its conformity with the principles of subsidiarity and proportionality agreed between the Prime Minister and the EU and that no further action should be taken to progress that regulation until that review has taken place.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31715","31715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479685","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on the proposed EU Ports Services Regulation; and what proposals he plans to make to other EU member states on that regulation.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31716","31716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479686","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether it is the Government's policy to oppose the proposals of the EU Competition Directorate to introduce a block exemption from state aid regulations for EU ports.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31714","31714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479687","2016-03-21","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential economic impact of building a third runway at Heathrow on the North and Yorkshire.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31542","31542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479689","2016-03-21","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the fixed cost to local authorities for submitting bids to the New Station Fund on the number of bids being made.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31569","31569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479690","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much funding has been received from the EU to meet expenditure arising from or in connection with High Speed 2 since 2009.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31575","31575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479691","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many lorry movements there have been to remove spoil excavated in Greater London related to the construction of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31576","31576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479692","2016-03-21","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which road projects his Department plans to finance from the (a) £49 million previously announced to repair roads following Storms Desmond and Eva and (b) £130 million set out in paragraph 1.239 of the Budget 2016; and how much he plans to allocate to each such project.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31603","31603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479693","2016-03-21","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what improvements will be introduced on the West Coast Main Line after High Speed 2 comes into operation.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31601","31601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479694","2016-03-21","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 1.292 of the Budget 2016, what road schemes he plans will receive funding from the £24 million from the Local Growth Fund.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31602","31602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479695","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many schools are located under the current Heathrow Airport final approach flight paths; and what projection he has made of the number of schools that would be located under proposed flight paths in the event of the construction of a third runway at Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31613","31613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479697","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what timetable he has set for a consultation on the night flight operations perimeters at Heathrow Airport to replace the existing agreement after October 2017.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31614","31614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479698","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many reports of lasers being shone into the cockpits of passenger aircraft landing or taking off from Heathrow Airport there have been in the last three years.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31615","31615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479699","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department's work on assessing the three airport options proposed by the Airport's Commission includes a review of the safety and security risks associated with an (a) additional or extended runway at Heathrow and (b) additional runway at Gatwick Airport.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31616","31616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479700","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost of constructing a river crossing at Lowestoft; and whether he plans that that cost will be wholly funded by his Department.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31617","31617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479701","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made on the effect of a potential third runway at Heathrow on insurance premiums for (a) business and (b) residential properties under the proposed new flightpath.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31587","31587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479702","2016-03-22","Department for Transport","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the schedule is for road works to establish a connected corridor from London to Dover; and what the projected end date is for establishing that corridor.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31581","31581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479704","2016-03-21","Wales Office","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how much funding his Department received from the European Social Fund (a) between 2007 and 2014 and (b) from 2014 to the last month for which data is available.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31649","31649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479706","2016-03-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to ensure that Community Work Placement providers are held to the standards required in their contract.","Biography information for Chris Heaton-Harris","Chris Heaton-Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31683","31683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479707","2016-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, further to the Government response to the consultation on aids and appliances and the daily living component of personal independence payment, Cm 9194, what modelling his Department undertook to assess how the changes proposed in that consultation will affect existing claimants.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31699","31699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479708","2016-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of care leavers in receipt of jobseeker's allowance or employment and support allowance had a sanction applied in each year from 2010 to 2015.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31700","31700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479710","2016-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have had their motability cars withdrawn due to changes in disability benefits in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31580","31580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479711","2016-03-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much has been paid in personal independence payments to (a) UK and (b) non-UK citizens in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31577","31577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479031","2016-03-21","Attorney General","2016-03-16","To ask the Attorney General, how many unduly lenient sentences were given out to (a) British nationals, (b) non-British EU nationals and (c) nationals from outside the EU in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Pursglove","Tom Pursglove","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31332","31332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479032","2016-03-21","Attorney General","2016-03-16","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2016 to Question 30579, which outsourced providers the Law Offices use for security services; and if he will request information from those providers on the rate of pay for security guards providing services to his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31326","31326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479033","2016-03-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment she has made of the availability of bank loans for oil exploration companies which operate in the North Sea.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31340","31340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479034","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much public funding was spent on research and development in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31341","31341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479035","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received from pub tenants and pub tenant groups on the appointment of the new Pubs Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Karl McCartney","Karl McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31376","31376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479036","2016-03-21","Cabinet Office","2016-03-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps is he is taking to support the youth work sector; and if he will take steps to support that sector through sustainable funding, investment in research and incentives to encourage volunteering.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31381","31381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479037","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value was of Official Development Assistance spent by his Department in each of the last six years; and what proportion of that assistance was subject to the International Development Act 2002.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31275","31275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479038","2016-03-21","Department for Transport","2016-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with motor vehicle insurance companies on reducing the level of insurance premiums.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31297","31297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479039","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to Best in Class, published by the CBI in December 2015, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of Swedish four box grid approach to analysing the attractiveness of international markets.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31385","31385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479040","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of the devolution of skills policy to local authorities on the development of British Sign Language and sign language interpreting skills.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31401","31401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479041","2016-03-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the percentage change in high street footfall figures was in each UK region in the last two years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31405","31405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479042","2016-03-21","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many jobs were lost in the North Sea oil industry in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31406","31406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479043","2016-03-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the value was of direct investment from China in each (a) sector and (b) industry sector in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31408","31408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/479044","2016-03-21","HM Treasury","2016-03-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to require large companies to publish a country-by-country report in their annual financial report.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31412","31412"
