"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136721","2019-07-08","Department for International Trade","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272754","272754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136722","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272755","272755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136723","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the total amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in her Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272756","272756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136724","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272757","272757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136725","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the total amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272758","272758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136726","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-03","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the total amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272759","272759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136727","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272760","272760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136728","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate she has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in her Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272761","272761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136729","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the total amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272762","272762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136730","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272763","272763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136731","2019-07-08","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what estimate she has made of the total amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in her Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272764","272764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136732","2019-07-08","Leader of the House","2019-07-03","To ask the Leader of the House, what estimate he has made of the total amount of unpaid overtime worked by staff in his Department in the last 24 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272765","272765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136733","2019-07-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to promote women's football in (a) Liverpool and (b) England.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272721","272721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136734","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government,  when he intends to provide an answer to Question 268565 tabled on 24 June 2019 for answer on 27 June 2019; and for what reason there has been a delay in answering that Question.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272848","272848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136735","2019-07-08","Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority","2019-07-03","To ask the hon. Member for Broxbourne, representing the Speaker's Committee for the Independent Parliamentary Standards Authority, how much the new system for reimbursing hon. Members' expenses cost to implement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272731","272731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136736","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will review the way that facial palsy treatment is (a) assessed and (b) funded.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272915","272915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136737","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what procedures the Food Standards Agency has in place to monitor and ensure compliance with Schedule 1, Part 5, paragraph 28 (f) of the Welfare of Animals at the Time of Killing (England) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272808","272808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136738","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what procedures the Food Standards Agency has in place to monitor and ensure compliance with Schedule 3, Part 3, paragraph 8 of the Welfare of Animals at the Time of Killing (England) Regulations 2015.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272809","272809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136739","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many recorded instances or reports from official veterinarians there have been of birds entering the next stage of production while still showing signs of consciousness in slaughterhouses in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272810","272810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136740","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many orders to stop or suspend the operation of a production or shackle line because birds were showing signs of consciousness before entering the next stage of production were issued by official veterinarians to slaughterhouses in England and Wales in each of the last five years.","Biography information for George Eustice","George Eustice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272811","272811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136741","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the report entitled, The state of the nation: The UK Family Business Sector 2018-19 by Oxford Economics, published in July 2019, what steps his Department is taking to make it easier for family businesses to access external finance.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272777","272777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136742","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what records his Department holds on the number of child contact services contracts entered into by local authorities in England and Wales on an annual basis; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Mr Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272766","272766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136743","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on the (a) market value of courts sold as part of HM Courts and Tribunal reform programme and (b) the resale value of those courts after they entered private ownership.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272804","272804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1137110","2019-07-10","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-03","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to facilitate cross-governmental co-operation on tackling climate change.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911856","911856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135832","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent steps he has taken to protect workers rights in the gig economy.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271367","271367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135911","2019-07-03","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were extradited from the UK to the United States for non-violent crimes in each year from 2013 to 2019.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271379","271379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136089","2019-07-02","Treasury","2019-07-02","What estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the proposals announced by the Prime Minister since 23 May 2019.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911689","911689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136090","2019-07-02","Treasury","2019-07-02","What recent assessment his Department has made of the short-term economic effect of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911690","911690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136091","2019-07-02","Treasury","2019-07-02","What fiscal steps he is taking to increase (a) jobs and (b) economic growth.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911691","911691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136092","2019-07-02","Treasury","2019-07-02","What steps he is taking to increase incentives for people to save.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911692","911692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136093","2019-07-02","Treasury","2019-07-02","What fiscal steps he is taking to grow the digital economy.","Biography information for Eddie Hughes","Eddie Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911693","911693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136100","2019-07-04","Attorney General","2019-07-02","To ask the Attorney General, what recent discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the application of the rule of law to cyber activities.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 911731","911731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136185","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Consumer Protection Partnership in protecting the public from unsafe electrical products.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272229","272229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136186","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the European Union’s embargo on sales of arms and military equipment to the Venezuelan Government.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272165","272165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136187","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Iranian counterpart on (a) allowing a UK Government representative to meet Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe in prison in Iran to assess her health and well-being and (b) the implications of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe's diplomatic status for the terms of her detention.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272166","272166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136188","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the  increase in impartial pensions guidance usage following the introduction of the Financial Guidance and Claims Act’s provisions for ensuring savers first receive impartial pensions guidance before accessing their pension savings.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272167","272167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136189","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the oral contribution of the Prime Minister of 6 June 2018, Official Report col 306, where the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence has allocated the £800,000 in research funding to help identify existing services and gaps in provision for young adults with ADHD.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272230","272230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136190","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the oral contribution of the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State for Justice of 5 September 2017, Official Report, Column 19, whether protocols his Department were developing with the Department of Health in 2017 on mental health and prisoner access to healthcare have been implemented; and what those protocols are.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272231","272231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136191","2019-07-08","Department for International Trade","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what representations he is making to the European Commission on quotas for UK steel exports into the EU in the event of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272168","272168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136192","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2019 to Question 264459 on the Clean Growth Ministerial Group, whether the Environment and Clean Growth Inter-Ministerial Group met between 16 April 2018 and 21 May 2019.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272309","272309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136193","2019-07-04","House of Commons Commission","2019-07-02","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, what plans the Commission has to increase the level of (a) recycling and (b) reuse to reduce the use of single-use plastic.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272117","272117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136194","2019-07-04","Attorney General","2019-07-02","To ask the Attorney General, how he will ensure that the Criminal Justice Board review of how rape and sexual violence cases are handled across the criminal justice system provides independent scrutiny of CPS case handling.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272118","272118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136195","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his timescale is for bringing forward legislative proposals to reform the taxi and private hire industry.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272232","272232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136196","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to tackle the import to the UK of products from illegal settlements in the Palestinian Occupied Territories.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272169","272169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136197","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans she has to ensure that the Social Fund Funeral Payments meet the costs of cremation.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272119","272119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136198","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sitting days in courts were presided over by a recorder in (a) England, (b) Greater London and (c) Greater Manchester in (i) each of the last three financial years and (ii) the 2019-20 financial year.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272170","272170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136199","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether specialised employees with training on how to support people with disabilities are available in each court.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272171","272171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136200","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 25 June to Question 266066 on boilers, for what reasons Building Research Establishment has changed its assessment set out in its paper of 7 February 2018 that there is an increased risk that boilers will in fact be non-compliant.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272120","272120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136201","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he plans to publish the Green Paper on social care.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272233","272233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136202","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make it his policy to ensure that police officers receive training on understanding autism.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272234","272234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136203","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when Rail Gourmet’s contract with LNER on the East Coast Mainline is planned to expire.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272172","272172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136204","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions officials in his Department have had with representatives of LNER on Rail Gourmet not paying the living wage on the East Coast Mainline.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272173","272173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136205","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether there are any provisions in LNER's franchise agreement that would prevent that compnay from ensuring that its sub-contractors pay the living wage.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272174","272174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136206","2019-07-04","Department for Transport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential value for money merits of bringing outsourced catering staff on the East Coast Mainline back in-house.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272175","272175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136207","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect on the community pharmacy sector of excluding pharmacists from the shortage occupation list.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272176","272176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136208","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for the Home Department on the exclusion of pharmacists from the shortage occupation list and the effect of that exclusion on the community pharmacy sector.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272177","272177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136209","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for British National (Overseas) Passport applications were received by his Department in (a) 2018 and (b) 2019.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272178","272178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136210","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance his Department has issued to police forces in England and Wales on the use of algorithms in decision-making for (a) bail and (b) release from custody.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272179","272179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136211","2019-07-08","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on the sharing of information between (a) police forces, (b) probation services and (c) community rehabilitation companies on the decision-making process for (a) bail and (b) release from custody.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272180","272180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136212","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department has issued to (a) probation services and (b) community rehabilitation companies on the use of algorithms in relation to recall decisions following a breach of licence conditions.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272181","272181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136213","2019-07-08","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to improve the quality of Sites of Special Scientific Interest in National Parks.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272121","272121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136214","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on the sharing of information between the two Departments to inform decisions on recall following breach of licence conditions.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272182","272182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136215","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what process is used by his Department to monitor the use of algorithms by community rehabilitation companies.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272183","272183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136216","2019-07-04","Treasury","2019-07-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the value was of (a) R&D expenditure and (b) R&D tax credits as (i) payable credits and (ii) deductions to Corporation Tax for UK life science SMEs SIC codes (A) 21100, (B) 72110, (C) 72190 and (D) 86900 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272184","272184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136217","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the imprisonment of the main opposition leader in Bangladesh, Khaleda Zia, on political stability in that country; and what representations he has made to his Bangladeshi counterpart on that matter.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272185","272185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136218","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to inform people entering the UK of the dangers of bringing in meat from areas affected by African swine fever.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272186","272186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136219","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what additional resource has been allocated to UK border force to (a) provide communications to the public on and (b) increase surveillance of imported meat products from areas affected by African swine fever.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272187","272187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136220","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has made an economic assessment of the potential effect of African Swine Fever being identified in the UK on (a) the public purse and (b) pig producers’ incomes.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272188","272188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136221","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the Government has plans to strengthen biosecurity arrangements on imported meat products after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Martin Vickers","Martin Vickers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272189","272189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136222","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Intergovernmental Conference on an international legally binding instrument under the United Nations on the Law of the Sea on the conservation and sustainable use of marine biological diversity of areas beyond national jurisdiction, what steps the Government is taking to ensure benefits from areas of the ocean beyond national jurisdiction are shared fairly and equitably; if he will make it his policy to promote the international law principle of common heritage of mankind in future sessions of that Conference; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272190","272190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136223","2019-07-09","Treasury","2019-07-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to UK Government spending on the 2022 Commonwealth Games, what comparability percentage will be applied for the purpose of the Barnett formula.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272191","272191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136224","2019-07-04","Department for Transport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to support electric vehicles in (a) becoming competitive without financial incentives or subsidies for their purchase and (b) reaching price parity with non-electric vehicles.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272192","272192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136225","2019-07-04","Department for Transport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to provide support for the purchase of electric vehicles to meet the targets set out in the Government's Net Zero Road Strategy.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272193","272193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136226","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average sentence length was for an offender convicted for domestic burglary for offenders for which this was their (a) first, (b) second, (c) third, (d) fourth, (e) fifth, (f) sixth, (g) seventh or (h) eighth or more conviction for that offence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272235","272235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136227","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many families are in receipt of Healthy Start vouchers in (a) Lewisham Deptford constituency, (b) London borough of Lewisham and (c) London.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272236","272236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136228","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272103","272103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136229","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272104","272104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136230","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272105","272105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136231","2019-07-04","Cabinet Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272106","272106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136232","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272107","272107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136233","2019-07-04","Treasury","2019-07-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272108","272108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136234","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to (a) end subsidies to the fossil fuel-based energy industry, (b) phase out fossil fuel-based energy infrastructure and (c) accelerate the transition to a clean energy economy within the 11-year timeframe set out in the IPCC report to limit temperature rise this century to 1.5 degrees Celsius published on 8 October 2018.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272194","272194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136235","2019-07-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272109","272109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136236","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy, and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of pursuing the target of net zero emissions by 2050 on historically economically marginalised communities;  and what steps his Department has taken to ensure that policies to achieve the net zero target account for the needs of (a) workers in carbon-intensive industries and (b) historically economically marginalised communities.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272195","272195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136237","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of people sentenced for domestic burglary for (a) the third time, (b) more than three times received (i) an immediate custodial sentence of up to three years, (ii) an immediate a custodial sentence of more than three years and (iii) a non-custodial sentence in each year since 1993.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272237","272237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136238","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what comparative assessment his Department has made between the annual cancer mortality rate in (a) the London borough of Hounslow and (b) London in each of the last five years; and what steps his Department is taking to tackle cancer mortality in (i) the London borough of Hounslow and (ii) London.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272196","272196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136239","2019-07-04","Department for International Development","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of processes to prevent the misuse of reconstruction material in Gaza.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272238","272238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136240","2019-07-04","Women and Equalities","2019-07-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, with reference to the Equality Act 2010, what steps the Government is taking to inform businesses and the service sector of the rights of assistance dogs.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272197","272197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136241","2019-07-04","Women and Equalities","2019-07-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the Equality Act 2010 in relation to assistance dogs.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272198","272198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136242","2019-07-04","Women and Equalities","2019-07-02","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will take steps to amend the definition for assistance dog to ensure that it  applies to the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272199","272199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136243","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with representatives of suppliers of medical radioisotopes on the feasibility of using air freight to import their products in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272239","272239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136244","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what representations he has received from the suppliers of medical radioisotopes on the potential risk to the import of those instruments in the event that the UK leaves the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272240","272240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136245","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with the Civil Aviation Authority on the potential risk to the import of medical radioisotopes in the event that the UK leaves the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272241","272241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136246","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with his EU counterparts on the supply of medicines from other EU member states in the event that the UK leaves the EU without an agreement.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272242","272242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136247","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the ability of suppliers of medicines based in the EU to maintain medical supplies to the UK in the event that the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272243","272243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136248","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what discussions he has had with his European Union counterparts on the maintenance of supply of medicines from the EU to the UK in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272244","272244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136249","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect on the finances of medicine suppliers in the UK of stockpiling an additional six weeks supply of medicines in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272245","272245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136250","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much his Department spent from the public purse on additional warehouse space to stockpile medicines in advance of (a) the 29 March 2019 and (b) the 31 October 2019 deadline to prepare for the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272246","272246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136251","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to ensure the maintenance or improvement of animal welfare standards for pets after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272133","272133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136252","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions he has had with the Director of Public Prosecutions on ensuring more effective prosecutions of cases involving repeat offenders.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272134","272134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136253","2019-07-04","Department for Education","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage more school leavers to pursue a career in the fishing industry.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272135","272135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136254","2019-07-04","Department for Education","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to encourage more school leavers to pursue a career in the video games industry.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272136","272136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136255","2019-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether she has plans to increase defence spending in the next three years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272137","272137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136256","2019-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when her Department plans to complete its order for all 50 AH-64E Apache attack helicopters.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272138","272138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136257","2019-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the timetable is for the conclusion of Exercise Dynamic Mongoose 19.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272139","272139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136258","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272110","272110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136259","2019-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272111","272111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136260","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272112","272112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136261","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2018 to Question 186245 on Right of Abode: Veterans, what progress his Department has made on making a decision on whether to grant right of abode to former British-Hong Kong servicemen.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272140","272140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136262","2019-07-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272113","272113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136263","2019-07-04","Department for International Trade","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272114","272114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136264","2019-07-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what preparations his Department is making for the UK leaving the EU without an agreement; and how much funding has been allocated to those preparations.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272115","272115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136265","2019-07-04","Department for International Development","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what country-specific direct support his Department is providing to Kenya to (a) support economic development and (b) strengthen democratic institutions in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272141","272141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136266","2019-07-04","Department for International Development","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what country-specific direct support his Department is providing to Zambia to (a) support economic development and (b) strengthen democratic institutions in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272200","272200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136267","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had recent discussions with his Argentinian counterpart on the sovereignty of the Falkland Islands; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272201","272201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136268","2019-07-04","Department for International Development","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what country-specific direct support his Department is providing to the Seychelles to support economic development in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272202","272202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136269","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to improve diplomatic relations with Trinidad and Tobago.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272203","272203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136270","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to improve diplomatic relations with Malawi.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272204","272204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136271","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his Brazilian counterpart on protecting the Amazon rainforest.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272247","272247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136272","2019-07-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has targets for the number of (a) organisations and (b) people registered for the cyber security information sharing partnership.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272248","272248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136273","2019-07-08","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of pieces of information that were shared on the cyber security information sharing partnership in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272249","272249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136274","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Litigant in Person portal will be expanded to include minor personal injury claims by April 2020.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272142","272142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136275","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many meetings (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have held with representatives of claimant bodies on the operation of the Litigant in Person portal in the last three months.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272143","272143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136276","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to publish his Department's response to Part 2 of the consultation paper, Reforming the Soft Tissue Injury (whiplash) Claims Process.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272144","272144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136277","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that customers' experience of the litigant in person portal can be (a) monitored and (b) evaluated.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272145","272145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136278","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that insurance companies do not submit incorrect Not Admitted responses through the Litigant in Person portal.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272146","272146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136279","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the Litigant in Person portal will include the ability for the litigant to present all losses in relation to an accident.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272147","272147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136280","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Litigant in Person portal will provide adequate protection to (a) minors and (b) vulnerable people.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272148","272148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136281","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department plans to take to support a Litigant in Person to manage a claim through the portal if the litigant does not have access to the internet.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272149","272149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136282","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost to the public purse is of the (a) design, (b) construction and (c) annual operation of the Litigant in Person portal.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272150","272150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136283","2019-07-04","Department for Education","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of state schools in England are classified as (a) rural town and fringe, (b) in a sparse setting, (c) rural village and hamlet, (d) urban, (f) urban major conurbation, (g) urban minor conurbation and (h) urban city and town.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272250","272250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136284","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Saudi Arabia counterpart on the release of senior political detainees held without charge in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272251","272251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136285","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what information his Department holds on the health and welfare of political detainees in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272252","272252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136286","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to review the strategic relationship with Saudi Arabia as a result of the murder of Jamal Khashoggi.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272253","272253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136287","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what plans he has to coordinate with his P5+1 partners a response to reports Iran has exceeded its permitted stockpile of low-enriched uranium.","Biography information for Mary Robinson","Mary Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272205","272205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136288","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of the offence of coercive control under section 76 of the Serious Crime Act 2015 in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272254","272254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136289","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of clinical trials of Maraviroc in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272206","272206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136290","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the (a) adequacy of NHS procurement options for and (b) the affordability of Maraviroc.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272207","272207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136291","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment NHS England has made of the availability of Maraviroc to patients with progressive multifocal leukoencephalopathy.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272208","272208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136292","2019-07-08","Department for International Development","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 15 February 2019 to Question 220733, whether the independent review of Palestinian Authority textbooks will be published by September 2019.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272116","272116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136293","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information he holds on the reasons why demolitions have recently been carried out at the new Royal Liverpool University Hospital; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dame Louise Ellman","Dame Louise Ellman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272122","272122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136294","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many inquests have been undertaken following a person taking their own life while in the care of (a) the NHS and (b) private mental health facilities in each of the last 10 years; how many of those inquests resulted in a change of leadership at the facility in question; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272209","272209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136295","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page five of the Public Health England position statement on The Impact on Health of Emissions to Air from Municipal Waste Incinerators, what information he holds on the development of work in that area.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272123","272123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136296","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people have taken their own lives while being detained under the Mental Health Act 1983 in an (a) NHS and (b) private hospital in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272210","272210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136297","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of encouraging manufacturers to reduce levels of nicotine in all cigarettes to reduce dependency.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272151","272151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136298","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many bonuses have been paid by the Army/Capita to recruits who agree to enlist earlier than originally intended; what the average size is of those bonus payments; what the total sum spent is on those bonuses as of 2 July 2019; and what the qualifying criteria are for those bonus payments.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272152","272152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136299","2019-07-08","Treasury","2019-07-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Written Statement of 21 March 2019 on Decommissioning Relief Deeds, HCWS1435, what the name is of the oil company that defaulted on its decommissioning obligations causing the Government to make two payments totaling £45.4 million in 2017-18; what the circumstances were of that default; and if he will place in the Library a copy of the evidential basis for calculating the provision of £357.1 million for future defaults.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272255","272255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136300","2019-07-04","Treasury","2019-07-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of social care funding for people living with dementia.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272256","272256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136301","2019-07-04","Department for Transport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on taking steps to adopt the International Maritime Organization’s interim goal of reducing shipping’s greenhouse gas emissions by at least 50 per cent by 2050.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272124","272124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136302","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 269123, the total amount of civil penalties her Department has issued in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272257","272257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136303","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 269122, what sums her Department has spent on the use of enforcement agencies to collect (a) civil penalties and (b) benefit overpayments in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth George","Ruth George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272258","272258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136304","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if she will publish the seven Astute class submarines by (a) name, (b) actual or estimated in-service date and (c) estimated out-of-service date.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272153","272153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136305","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if she will publish the (a) problems with the (i) engines and (ii) gearbox of the A400M aircraft and (b) extent of the work required to address those problems.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272154","272154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136306","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what decisions were taken at the recent NATO Ministerial meeting on the Airbus A400m aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272155","272155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136307","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the circumstances were of any crashes involving A400M aircraft.","Biography information for Mr Mark Francois","Mr Mark Francois","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272156","272156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136308","2019-07-08","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when HMS Audacious will enter service.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272211","272211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136309","2019-07-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many homes have been purchased through the Help to Buy scheme in (a) Lewisham, Deptford, (b) Lewisham borough and (c) London in each year since the scheme's inception.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272259","272259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136312","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent representations the Government has made to the Government of Japan against its decision to resume commercial whaling.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272212","272212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136316","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps the Government is taking with women who are transitioning to men to (a) inform them about and (b) screen them for the risk of contracting breast cancer.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272260","272260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136319","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of provision of social workers in schools with a high volume of cases requiring social worker support.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272261","272261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136323","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations the Government has made to the Government of the People's Republic of China on the treatment of (a) Christian and (b) Muslim minority communities in that country.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272262","272262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136326","2019-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when HMS Talent and HMS Triumph will be based at HMNB Clyde; and when and where those vessels will be decommissioned.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272213","272213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136329","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he is planning to hold the meeting with GKN Aerospace and the hon. Member for Birmingham Northfield on the future of GKN Aerospace in Kings Norton.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272125","272125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136331","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to support deaf children’s education in the upcoming Spending Review.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272214","272214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136332","2019-07-08","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who the six law firms are that are approved to provide legal services to Post Office Limited.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272157","272157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136333","2019-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Answer of 1 July 2013 to Question 162999 on Trafalgar Class Submarines, whether those planned end of service dates remain the same for each boat.","Biography information for Deidre Brock","Deidre Brock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272215","272215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136334","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how he plans to (a) monitor and (b) evaluate the support for newly recognised refugees under the new asylum advice and accommodation contracts.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272263","272263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136335","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has had recent discussions with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the effect of that Department's policies on resettled refugees; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272264","272264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136336","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he takes to ensure that recommendations made by the Independent Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration are implemented by his Department.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272265","272265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136337","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to announce additional details of the integrated programme to resettle an additional 5,000 refugees from 2020-2021.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272266","272266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136338","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that children who make an asylum application in the UK are not incorrectly identified as adults.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272267","272267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136339","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment she has made of uprating Local Housing Allowance rates from April 2020; and if she will bring forward proposals to extend the exemption from the shared accommodation rate for people who have lived in a homeless hostel to include people aged 18 to 25.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272268","272268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136340","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of the provision of healthcare services to prisoners in private prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272269","272269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136341","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what data his Department holds on the working hours of judges in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272270","272270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136342","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of CCGs and NHS trusts setting higher thresholds for NHS treatment of tonsillitis than for private treatment.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272271","272271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136343","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the cost to the public purse of an increase in the level of self-representation in courts.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272272","272272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136344","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent steps he has taken to reduce the level of the use of restraint on children in custody.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272273","272273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136345","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect on children of the removal of parts of education law from the scope of legal aid under Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272274","272274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136346","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost was to the public purse on legal aid for education law in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272275","272275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136347","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of children in custody have special education needs.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272276","272276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136348","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2019 to Question 263187 on Prisons: Contracts, what estimate he has made of the cost of the (a) staffing and (b) external advice required to (i) develop and (ii) run the prison operator competition.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272277","272277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136349","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of exposure to prison violence on re-offending rates.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272278","272278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136350","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) value and (b) proportion of employment tribunal fees have been refunded since those fees were abolished.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272279","272279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136351","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been spent from the public purse on notifying people that paid employment tribunal fees of their right to a refund.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272280","272280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136352","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the longest waiting time was between an application for an employment tribunal and the date of first hearing in (a) 2012, (b) 2015 and (c) 2018 by employment tribunal office.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272281","272281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136353","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for employment tribunal fee refunds have been refused by reason for refusal.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272282","272282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136354","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of prison officers in post was in each of the prisons in the 10 Prisons Project in (a) the last six months of 2017 and (b) the last six months of 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272283","272283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136355","2019-07-08","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average level of prison population above Certified Normal Accommodation capacity was in each of the prisons in the 10 Prisons Project in (a) the last six months of 2017 and (b) the last six months of 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272284","272284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136356","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total additional capital spend was on physical security in each of the prisons in the 10 Prisons Project in (a) the last six months of 2017 and (b) the last six months of 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272285","272285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136357","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2019 to Question 264329 on universal credit, of the 749,000 claimants with deductions from universal credit for non-universal credit debits, how many of those tax credit overpayments were repaid by each year to which those overpayments were made to those claimants.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272126","272126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136358","2019-07-08","Department for International Development","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the independent evaluation of the Palestinian Authority curriculum commissioned by the Palestinian Authority in 2018 and due in March 2019 has been completed.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272127","272127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136359","2019-07-08","Department for International Trade","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what export licences relating to defence are in place with Hong Kong.","Biography information for Jonathan Edwards","Jonathan Edwards","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272216","272216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136360","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 13 June 2019 to Question 262315 and to the Answer on 1 July 2019 to Question 269696 on Wakefield City Academies Trust: Deloitte and Touche, how much Wakefield City Academies Trust spent on services provided by Deloitte from 1 June 2019 to 30 June 2019.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272217","272217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136361","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to support scientific human-relevant research methods.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272218","272218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136362","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to support human-relevant science.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272219","272219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136363","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the National Genomic Healthcare Strategy will include all types of cancer.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272220","272220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136364","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to minimise negative ecological effects on carbon-rich, biodiversity-rich ecosystems throughout the world of UK imports of (a) soft commodities including (i) palm oil, (ii) soy, (iii) cocoa, (iv) rubber, (v) beef, and (vi) timber and (b) hard commodities including (A) minerals, (B) oil and gas, and (C) other products of mining; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272221","272221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136365","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, who (a) Companies House and (b) HMRC share information on business owners with when a limited company is set up.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272286","272286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136366","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what personal information of a business owner is placed in the public domain when a limited company is set up.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272287","272287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136367","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will (a) review and (b) increase the 6GW capacity cap in the Contracts for Difference auctions to support the target of net zero carbon emissions by 2050.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272288","272288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136368","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the finding of the Committee on Climate Change that the UK will require up to 75GW by 2050, if he will review the 30GW by 2030 target for offshore wind.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272289","272289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136369","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to accelerate the electrification of (a) heat and (b) transport.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272290","272290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136370","2019-07-04","Department for International Trade","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to encourage green investment in the UK to ensure that the UK reaches Net Zero by 2050.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272291","272291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136371","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons the Environment Agency does not have a Chief Scientific Advisor.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272222","272222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136372","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which scientific advisory committees the Environment Agency manages; and how advice from those committees has been used by the Environment Agency in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272223","272223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136373","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent trends in real term funding for education on the ability of schools to provide high quality SEND support.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272292","272292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136374","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the effect of the academisation of schools on the ability of schools to deliver high-quality SEND provision.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272293","272293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136375","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which NHS trusts offer immunotherapy; and for which (a) indications and (b) ages of patient.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272294","272294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136376","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to increase the availability of immunotherapy.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272295","272295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136377","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of whether the level of availability of immunotherapy is consistent with the objectives of the NHS Cancer Plan.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272296","272296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136378","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking with the UN Security Council to ensure that de-escalation zones in Idlib, Syria are recognised by all states.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Sir Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272128","272128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136379","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June to Question 266291 on Transport: Exhaust Emissions, what methodology his Department used to provide real term changes in percentages in cost of transport in the Answer of 16 January 2018 to Question 121761 on Travel.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272224","272224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136380","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2019 to Question 257458 on Universal Credit: Overpayments, how many overpayments were waived in (a) full and (b) part as a result of applications made by (i) claimants and (ii) their representatives in 2014-15.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272129","272129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136381","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Israeli counterpart on recognition of the plight of Jewish refugees from the Middle East and North Africa.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272225","272225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136382","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what cancer types will be offered whole genome sequencing through the Genomic Medicine Service as part of routine care in the next five years.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272297","272297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136383","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to consult with charities and patient organisations on whole genome sequencing.","Biography information for Eleanor Smith","Eleanor Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272298","272298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136384","2019-07-08","Department for Transport","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 269094 on Driving: Qualifications, when the EU contingency Regulation (Regulation 2019/501) expires.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272299","272299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136385","2019-07-04","Treasury","2019-07-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the tax duty revenue was from (a) aviation gasoline, (b) aviation turbine fuel, (c) unleaded petrol and (d) diesel in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272300","272300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136386","2019-07-04","Department for International Development","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to the recent State of the World Food Security and Nutrition report findings that global hunger has increased for the fourth year running, what steps the Government is taking to (a) help end this trend and (b) help ensure that sustainable development goal two is achieved.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272301","272301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136387","2019-07-08","Cabinet Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2019 to Question 270401, whether the number of operators who use Huawei Cyber Security Evaluation Centre advice is collated and monitored centrally.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272302","272302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136388","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Independent Monitoring Board annual report on HMP Northumberland, what the timeframe for prisoners accessing inpatient psychiatric treatment will be; and what improvements that prison is working towards.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272303","272303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136389","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of prisoners released from (a) HMP Northumberland and (b) prisons nationally have had permanent accommodation on their release in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272304","272304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136390","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of prisoners released from (a) prison and (b) HMP Northumberland have had temporary accommodation to go to on their release in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272305","272305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136391","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of prisoners released from (a) HMP Northumberland and (b) prisons nationally have had no accommodation to go to on their release in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272306","272306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136392","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the maintenance of NICE standards on antenatal services in prisons.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272158","272158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136393","2019-07-04","Treasury","2019-07-02","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Finance Bill, what steps his Department is taking to require a review of the public health effects of fixed odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272307","272307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136394","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent discussions officials in his Department have held with the officials from the Ministry of Justice on ensuring the maintenance of his Department's nutritional standards for pregnant women in prisons.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272159","272159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136395","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many and what proportion of (a) pregnant women and (b) new mothers in prison have reported symptoms of depression.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272160","272160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136396","2019-07-08","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to bring forward legislative proposals to require public buildings to provide changing facilities for people with a disability.","Biography information for Stephen Morgan","Stephen Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272308","272308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136397","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of primary school aged children had swimming lessons provided through school in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272226","272226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136398","2019-07-08","Department for Education","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been spent from the public purse on swimming lessons for primary school students in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272227","272227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136399","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether welfare advisers have the discretion not to impose job seeking conditions on a claimant in their (a) customer agreement and (b) claimant commitment when that claimant is no longer entitled to employment and support allowance and is advised to claim universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272130","272130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136400","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on studies carried out by the (a) National Institute for Health Research and (b) NHS Health Protection Research Unit into the effects on human health of (i) PM1 and (ii) PM0.1.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272131","272131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136401","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to have eye clinic liaison officers deployed at (a) Royal Stoke University Hospital and (b) all hospitals in England with ophthalmology departments.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272161","272161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136402","2019-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps her Department is taking to support the development of metal 3D printing in the shipbuilding industry.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272162","272162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136403","2019-07-08","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing a national screening programme for structural heart diseases.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272163","272163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136404","2019-07-08","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Nigerian Government on progress towards cleaning up oil pollution in the Niger Delta.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272132","272132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136406","2019-07-08","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much funding the Government has allocated under section 22 of the Family Law Act 1996 to (a) the provision of marriage support services and (b) research into (i) the causes of and (ii) preventing marital breakdown in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272228","272228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1142669","2019-09-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-02","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will take steps to ensure that the payment of housing benefit or the housing element of universal credit to foster carers does not adversely affect any other benefits they receive.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 284142","284142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1134983","2019-07-01","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference the June 2019 report of the Children’s Commissioner, We need to talk: access to speech and language therapy, if he will meet with the Local Government Association to discuss the implications for his Department's policies of the findings of that report.","Biography information for Geraint Davies","Geraint Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269599","269599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135766","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to reduce the effect of house building on (a) air and (b) soil pollution.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271448","271448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135767","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to support people who self-harm.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271449","271449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135768","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to support the construction of specialist housing for elderly people.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271450","271450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135769","2019-07-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support his Department provides for young people who want to set up an online retail business.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271451","271451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135770","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made the effect on the environment of disposable barbecues.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271452","271452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135771","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department plans to ban disposable barbecues.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271453","271453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135772","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to ensure that local authorities fulfil their statutory duties under section 63 of the Care Act 2014 to provide transition assessments for young carers.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271454","271454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135773","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking in response to the recent allegations of institutional and sexual  abuse of young people in the International Planned Parenthood Federation.","Biography information for Sir William Cash","Sir William Cash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271337","271337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135774","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps is he taking to improve retention of NHS staff.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271455","271455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135775","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will reinstate the student nurse bursary.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271456","271456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135776","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations his Department has received on (a) certification and (b) packaging of food items imported from the Far East.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271457","271457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135777","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support his Department is providing to landowners to encourage tree planting.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271458","271458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135778","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support large scale food processing.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271459","271459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135779","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of culling badgers on TB rates in cattle.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271460","271460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135780","2019-07-03","Church Commissioners","2019-07-01","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England has taken to promote tourism to its churches and cathedrals.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271461","271461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135781","2019-07-03","Church Commissioners","2019-07-01","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what steps the Church of England is taking to encourage parishioners to support the local economy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271462","271462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135782","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of increasing co-operation between medical R&D facilities in the UK and Israel.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271463","271463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135783","2019-07-03","Department for International Trade","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what recent discussions the Government has had with the US administration on a potential trade deal after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271464","271464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135784","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to help ensure the supply of skilled workers in the tech sector.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271465","271465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135785","2019-07-03","Department for International Trade","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the role of the UK's tech sector in attracting foreign direct investment.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271466","271466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135786","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that its policies and funding support equal pay for female and male farmers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271467","271467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135787","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to strengthen global civil society throughout the world.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271468","271468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135788","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps his Department is taking to increase coordination of its work with charities operating in rural Africa.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271469","271469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135789","2019-07-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Devolved Administrations on the promotion of cycle to work schemes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271470","271470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135790","2019-07-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to improve road user awareness of safe (a) speeds and (b) distances when overtaking horses.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271471","271471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135791","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to (a) support and (b) incentivise small food and catering businesses to reduce plastic waste.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271472","271472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135792","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the level of oil exports from (a) Sudan and (b) South Sudan in the last two years; how much oil has been produced by each of those countries in the last two years; and how much revenue each Government has received in respect of oil production.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271338","271338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135793","2019-07-03","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the implications for his Department’s policies in relation to the definition of applicable crime in Part 3 of the Investigatory Powers Act 2016 of the finding of the Court of Justice of the European Union in Secretary of State for the Home Department v Watson & Others that surveillance data retained for the purposes of fighting crime should be restricted solely to serious crime.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271353","271353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135794","2019-07-03","Treasury","2019-07-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether officials in his Department have had discussions with officials in the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the UK Steel charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271384","271384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135795","2019-07-03","Wales Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether officials in his Department have had discussions with officials in the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the UK Steel Charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271385","271385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135796","2019-07-03","Wales Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will make it his Department's policy to sign up to the UK Steel Charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271386","271386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135797","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether officials in her Department have had discussions with officials in the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the UK Steel Charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271387","271387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135798","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make it her Department's policy to sign up to the UK Steel Charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271388","271388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135799","2019-07-03","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will make it her Department's policy to sign up to the UK Steel Charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271389","271389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135800","2019-07-03","Northern Ireland Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether officials in her Department have had discussions with officials in the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the UK Steel Charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271390","271390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135801","2019-07-03","Scotland Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will make it his Department's policy to sign up to the UK Steel Charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271391","271391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135802","2019-07-03","Scotland Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether officials in his Department have had discussions with officials in the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the UK Steel Charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271392","271392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135803","2019-07-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make it his Department's policy to sign up to the UK Steel Charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271393","271393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135804","2019-07-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether officials in his Department have had discussions with officials in  the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the UK Steel Charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271473","271473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135805","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if he will make it his Department's policy to sign up to the UK Steel Charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271474","271474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135806","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether officials in his Department have had discussions with officials in the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on the UK Steel Charter.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271475","271475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135807","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the publication of the master trust and GPP defaults report by Corporate Adviser magazine, whether her Department plans to reduce the protection on charges for members of occupational pension schemes used for automatic enrolment.","Biography information for Ms Angela Eagle","Ms Angela Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271354","271354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135808","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make an estimate of the volume of recyclable waste that has been sent to be incinerated in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271476","271476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135809","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has informed any EU nationals that they have no recourse to public funds since June 2018.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271477","271477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135810","2019-07-03","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the number of families whose visa applications have been rejected due to the minimum income requirement.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271394","271394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135811","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps he is taking to support (a) the removal of plastic waste and (b) increase plastic recycling internationally.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271395","271395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135812","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to (a) increase the amount of plastic that is recycled, and (b) improve the UK’s recycling infrastructure.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271396","271396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135813","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what projects his Department supports in Bangladesh that remove plastic waste from (a) rivers and (b) the sea.","Biography information for Mrs Anne Main","Mrs Anne Main","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271397","271397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135814","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has taken steps to install the Official Representative of interim President Juan Guaidó in the Venezuelan embassy in London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271355","271355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135815","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international partners on migrant boats capsizing off the coast of Venezuela.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271356","271356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135816","2019-07-03","Treasury","2019-07-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has taken steps to release assets held by the Bank of England to the Official Representative to the UK of interim Venezuelan President Juan Guaidó; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271357","271357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135817","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his international counterparts on the shortage of food and medicine in Venezuela.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271358","271358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135818","2019-07-04","Treasury","2019-07-01","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of introducing (a) a minimum dwell time and (b) prompts that require active demonstrations of consumer understanding on consumer credit application pages.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271398","271398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135819","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the effect of poor air quality on the level of demand on the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271359","271359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135820","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs,  what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the economic crisis in Venezuela on the (a) political and (b) economic situation in that country.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271360","271360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135821","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care on the effect on the NHS of rising temperatures as a result of climate change.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271361","271361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135822","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps he has taken to improve careers information and guidance for secondary school leavers.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271399","271399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135823","2019-07-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate he has made of the unemployment rate among former male inmates compared with the rate among the general male population.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271362","271362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135824","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the level of availability of (a) places on UK Foundation Programme F1 and F2 courses and (b)  work within the NHS for course graduates.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271363","271363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135825","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the proportion of people working in the gig economy that are in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271364","271364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135826","2019-07-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to support people leaving prison to move directly to employment on their release.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271365","271365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135827","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the total payments made by NHS England to private providers in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271400","271400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135828","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the effect of right to rent on the ability of BAME tenants to access the rental market.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271637","271637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135829","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps he is taking to tackle the transport needs of the global south to enable marginalised groups to engage in (a) education, (b) work, (c) healthcare, (d) leisure and (e) other life-supporting activities.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271401","271401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135830","2019-07-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases have been prosecuted under the Assaults on Emergency Workers (Offences) Act 2018.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271366","271366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135831","2019-07-04","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will bring forward plans to improve access to intermediary services for adopted children seeking to contact their biological relatives.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271478","271478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135833","2019-07-04","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the process by which adoptees access intermediary services for contact with biological relatives.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271479","271479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135834","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of ensuring universities publish potential earnings returns for all degree courses.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271402","271402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135835","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to reduce the cost of university accommodation for students.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271368","271368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135836","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to extend Government guidance on the tethering of owls and vultures in zoos to all birds of prey.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271369","271369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135837","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support research on alternatives to plastics.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271370","271370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135838","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made a recent assessment of the effect on the environment of the use of disposable barbecues; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271480","271480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135839","2019-07-03","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made in establishing a joint bridging unit in Germany.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271371","271371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135840","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 2 May 2019 to Question 248721, whether he has had meetings with the Turkish Government since 2 May 2019 to raise the issue of Abdullah Öcalan's access to lawyers and family visits; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271481","271481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135841","2019-07-03","Cabinet Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps his Department is taking to help ensure that procurement processes reduce the use of single-use plastics.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271372","271372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135842","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the current plastic recycling system.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271373","271373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135843","2019-07-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of enabling investors to realise returns while solar power plants, onshore and offshore wind farms and hydroelectric power plants are being built to ensure that projects go ahead.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271403","271403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135844","2019-07-04","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the June 2019 Sutton Trust and Social Mobility Commission report Elitist Britain 2019: the educational backgrounds of Britain's leading people, what steps he is taking to tackle social segregation in schools; and whether he plans to introduce contextual recruitment and admissions practices for entry to the UK's top universities.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271404","271404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135845","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the effectiveness of the penalties incurred for knife crime.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271405","271405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135846","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to improve the (a) rates of diagnosis and (b) management of genetic haemochromatosis.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271374","271374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135847","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the March 2019 report by the National Audit Office and current inquiry by the Public Accounts Committee into apprenticeships, if he will launch a public consultation on the future of the apprenticeships programme.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271482","271482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135848","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether apprenticeship levy-paying employers will continue to be able to use half of the funds that they contribute to the apprenticeship levy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271483","271483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135849","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to help apprenticeship levy-paying employers to use more of the levy funding available to them than the 15 per cent that they used between 2017 and 2019; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271484","271484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135850","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the reasons for the reduction in retail sector apprenticeship starts between 2012 and 2017.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271485","271485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135851","2019-07-03","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to implement the recommendations in the report of Her Majesty’s Inspectorate of Constabulary and Fire and Rescue Services on Fire and Rescue Service Inspections 2018/19.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271576","271576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135852","2019-07-03","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of the conclusion in the report of Her Majesty’s Inspectorate of Constabulary and Fire and Rescue Services on Fire and Rescue Service Inspections that there are too few firefighters to meet the foreseeable fire risk.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271577","271577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135853","2019-07-03","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the findings in the report of Her Majesty’s Inspectorate of Constabulary and Fire and Rescue Services’ on Fire and Rescue Service Inspections 2018/19, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of the resources available to fire service inspection programmes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271578","271578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135854","2019-07-03","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has made a recent assessment of the adequacy of Suffolk Fire Service’s (a) fire engine crewing levels, (b) emergency response times, (c) delivery of training and (d) firefighter numbers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271579","271579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135855","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to help mitigate the effect of pension taxation on the NHS.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271375","271375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135856","2019-07-03","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has made a recent assessment of the adequacy of the day crewing plus duty system in place at Leicestershire Fire and Rescue Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271580","271580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135857","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to help protect children from the consequences of the bombing in Idlib, Syria.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271376","271376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135858","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 June 2019 to Question 267319 on Apprentices: Taxation, how frequently his Department plans to publish expiry of funds information for the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271486","271486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135859","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to respond to the letter of 19 June 2018 from the hon. Member for Sheffield Central in respect of Written Parliamentary Questions on Tier 2 Visas, CTS Reference number M8354/18.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271487","271487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135860","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to help prevent homeless people becoming victims of modern slavery.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271406","271406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135861","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the cost to businesses producing calendars of the alteration of the date of the 2020 early May bank holiday.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271407","271407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135862","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he plans to compensate businesses producing printed calendars for the costs that they have incurred as a result of the alteration of the date of the 2020 early May bank holiday.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271408","271408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135863","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he undertook a consultation with businesses before deciding to alter the date of the 2020 early May bank holiday; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271409","271409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135864","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which Minister in his Department is responsible for alterations to the dates of bank holidays.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271410","271410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135865","2019-07-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will meet representatives of businesses that make printed calendars to discuss the decision to change the date of the 2020 early May bank holiday.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271411","271411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135866","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children with special educational needs receive free home to school transport in England.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271488","271488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135867","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children with an education health and care plan receive free home to school transport in England.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271489","271489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135868","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children with special educational needs that are unable to access education as a result of inadequate provision of free home to school transport.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271490","271490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135869","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of children with with an education health and care plan that are unable to access education as a result of inadequate provision of free home to school transport.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271491","271491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135870","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of young people with special educational needs in post-16 education that receive local authority funded home to school transport in (a) England and (b) each local authority.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271492","271492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135871","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the number of young people with an education, health and care plan in post-16 education who receive local authority funded home to school transport in (a) England and (b) each local authority.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271493","271493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135872","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, many young people with special educational needs in post-16 education have been unsuccessful in an application for local authority funded home to school transport in (a) England and (b) each local authority for the latest school year.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271581","271581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135873","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, many young people with an education health and care plan in post-16 education have been unsuccessful in an application for local authority funded home to school transport in (a) England and (b) each local authority for the latest school year.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271582","271582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135874","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the amount spent in England by local authorities on home to school transport for children with special educational needs in (a) pre-16 and (b) post-16 education.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271583","271583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135875","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the amount spent in by local authorities in England on home to school transport for children with education, health and care plans in (a) pre-16 and (b) post-16 education.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271584","271584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135876","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money has been spent from the public purse on free home to school transport for children and young people with special educational needs in (a) pre-16 and (b) post-16 education in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271585","271585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135877","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money has been spent from the public purse on free home to school transport on children and young people with an Education, Health and Care Plan in (a) pre-16 and (b) post-16 education in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271586","271586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135878","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much money has been spent from the public purse on chaperones to support children with special educational needs travel from home to school in (a) pre-16 education and (b) post-16 education every year since 2014.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271587","271587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135879","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much has been spent from the public purse by local authorities on contracts for specialist providers of transport to support children with special educational needs travel from home to school in (a) pre-16 and (b) post-16 education every year since 2014.","Biography information for Emma Hardy","Emma Hardy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271588","271588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135880","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps his Department has taken to increase the level of numeracy in Nottinghamshire.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271589","271589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135881","2019-07-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidences there were of the use of synthetic cannabinoids in prisons in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ben Bradley","Ben Bradley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271590","271590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135882","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the strength of Sudan’s rapid support forces.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271494","271494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135883","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support his Department provides to the Ugandan Government to help with refugees in that country.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271495","271495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135884","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment he has made the accuracy of reports of Kenyan authorities teargassing and attacking peaceful demonstrators in Nairobi on 19 June.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271496","271496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135885","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the restrictions on the independent media in Burundi.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271497","271497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135886","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of (a) China’s influence in sub-Saharan Africa and (b) the extent of Chinese investment in ports in sub-Saharan Africa.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271498","271498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135887","2019-07-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made a recent assessment of the effect of usage-based telematics products on levels of (a) road safety and (b) environmental sustainability.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271499","271499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135888","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how long on average it takes to (a) agree and (b) allocate the Social Fund funerals expense payment.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271339","271339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135889","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether she has plans to increase awareness among the relatives of deceased people of (a) direct funerals and (b) other funeral options; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271340","271340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135890","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many pauper funerals were held in England in each of the last five years for which figures are available; and whether local authorities are in all cases able to claim back the costs of those funerals through the Social Fund funeral expenses fund.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271341","271341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135891","2019-07-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has (a) plans and (a) a budget allocated to eliminate paper rail tickets from the network; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271412","271412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135892","2019-07-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish his response to the consultation on pay-as-you-go on rail.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271413","271413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135893","2019-07-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to incentivise the take-up of electric vehicles in areas with high levels of pollution.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271500","271500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135894","2019-07-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of vehicles that are electric in each (i) region and (ii) nation of the UK.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271501","271501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135895","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what (a) financial and (b) other support the Government (i) is providing in 2019 and (ii) has provided in each of the last five years to schools for summer school programmes.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271502","271502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135896","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of people released on Home Detention Curfew in each year since 2010 were serving sentences relating to (a) criminal damage and arson, (b) drug offences, (c) fraud, (d) miscellaneous crimes against society, (e) possession of weapons, (f) public order, (g) robbery, (h) sexual offences, (i) summary motoring, (j) summary non-motoring, (k) theft and (l) violence against the person.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271591","271591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135897","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding (a) academies and (b) non-academy schools have received from the soft drinks industry levy.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271503","271503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135898","2019-07-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number was of previous community orders issued to an offender sentenced to immediate custody in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271592","271592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135899","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to regulate the cannabidiol market; and whether he plans to create a new medical model for the (a) tetrahydrocannabinol and (b) cannabidiol sectors.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271414","271414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135900","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many visas have been (a) applied for, (b) granted and (c) refused for footballers where the sponsoring organisation was in Scotland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271504","271504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135901","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average number of previous (a) cautions and (b) convictions offenders had in each year since 2007 before being sentenced to an immediate custodial sentence for (i) possession of a blade or point, (ii) possession of an offensive weapon, (iii) common assault, (iv) assaulting a police officer, (v) sexual assault, (vi) public order, (vii) theft, (viii) robbery, (ix) burglary, (x) drugs, (xi) criminal damage, (xii) breach of anti social behaviour order, (xiii) fraud and (xiv) vehicle taking.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271593","271593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135902","2019-07-03","Cabinet Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has plans to commission and investigation into the the potential disenfranchisement of EU citizens resident in the UK in the 2019 European Parliament elections.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271505","271505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135903","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of the value for money of prescribing Liothyronine (T3) on the NHS.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271506","271506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135904","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to ensure access to Liothyronine on the NHS as an alternative to Levothyroxine.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271507","271507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135905","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people sentenced to an immediate custodial sentence for (a) possession of a blade or point, (b) possession of an offensive weapon, (c) common assault, (d) assaulting a police officer, (e) sexual assault, (f) public order, (g) theft, (h) robbery, (i) burglary, (j) drugs, (k) criminal damage, (l) breach of and anti-social behaviour order, (m) fraud, (n) vehicle taking in each year since 2007 had (i) no, (ii) between one and four, (iii) between five and nine, (iv) between 10 and 15, (v) between 16 and 25, (vi) between 26 and 50, (vii) between 51 and 75, (viii) between 76 and 100 and (ix) 101 or more convictions and cautions for an offence.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271594","271594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135906","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent steps he has taken to ensure access to Liothyronine on the NHS for people with hypothyroidism.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271508","271508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135907","2019-07-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps his Department has taken to reduce the duration of delays at the Dartford Crossing.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271377","271377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135908","2019-07-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department has taken to reduce delays on (a) the A2, (b) Bob Dunn Way and (c) other roads approaching the M25 to cross the Dartford Crossing.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271415","271415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135909","2019-07-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the level of air pollution caused by traffic congestion on (a) the A2, (b) Bob Dunn Way and (c) other roads approaching the M25 to cross the Dartford Crossing.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271416","271416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135910","2019-07-03","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people were extradited from the UK to the United States in each year from 2013 to 2019.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271378","271378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135912","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were given an immediate custodial sentence for possession of an offensive weapon in each year since 2007; and of those people how many had (a) no, (b) one to four, (c) five to 10 and (d) 11 or more previous cautions or sentences for carrying an offensive weapon.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271595","271595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135913","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to (a) identify and (b) mitigate against any conflict of interest by NHS consultants referring patients to private hospitals in which those consultants have an interest.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271509","271509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135914","2019-07-04","Cabinet Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2019 to Question 268457 on European Parliament: elections, whether the Government received such legal advice after 23 May 2019.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271417","271417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135915","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants submitted a DS1500 form during that application process in each year from 2016 to 2018.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271418","271418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135916","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants received universal credit payments through the special rules for terminal illness route in each year from 2016 to 2018.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271419","271419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135917","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants who submitted a DS1500 form met with a work coach during that application process.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271420","271420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135918","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants who applied for universal credit died within six months of having their application rejected in each year from 2016 to 2018.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271421","271421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135919","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit claimants using the standard application route have been rejected and subsequently applied under the special rules for terminal illness route.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271422","271422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135920","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of universal credit payments and administration in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271423","271423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135921","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of employment support allowance in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271424","271424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135922","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the cost to the public purse was of revising her Department's guidance notes for the DS1500 form.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271425","271425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135923","2019-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, by what methods (a) HM Paymaster, (b) the Defence Council and (c) an authorised officer determine the amount payable by a member of the armed forces in child maintenance.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271510","271510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135924","2019-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what criteria (a) HM Paymaster, (b) Defence Council and (c) an authorised officer use to determine when child maintenance should be paid.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271511","271511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135925","2019-07-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to identify (a) privately owned and (b) social housing high-rise blocks of flats with high pressure laminate cladding and combustible insulation.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271512","271512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135926","2019-07-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the number of  (a) privately owned housing blocks and (b) social housing blocks with high pressure laminate cladding and combustible insulation that have been remediated.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271513","271513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135927","2019-07-04","Attorney General","2019-07-01","To ask the Attorney General, what the status is of the Serious Fraud Office investigation into British American Tobacco that was opened in 2017.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271596","271596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135928","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of patients with ADHD that access NHS Mental Health services.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271597","271597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135929","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 21 June 2019 to Question 263894 on Israel: Hebron, if he will make representations to the Israeli Government on reports of tear gas canisters being fired at schools in Hebron by Israeli armed forces.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271514","271514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135930","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of non-advised pension savers used a face-to-face or telephone appointment with the Pension Wise guidance service when accessing their pension benefits in each of the last four years since its introduction.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271426","271426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135931","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timetable is for pension savers to start benefiting from the provisions of the Financial Guidance and Claims Act 2018 for ensuring that those savers receive impartial pensions guidance before accessing their pension savings.","Biography information for Jack Dromey","Jack Dromey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271427","271427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135932","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his department plans to publish the pathway for people with ADHD.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271598","271598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135933","2019-07-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department plans to take to ensure that high pressure laminate cladding and combustible insulation is removed from (a) privately owned and (b) social housing blocks in the event that the building owners do not remove that material.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271515","271515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135934","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent estimate he has made of (a) the value of eligible Healthy Start vouchers that have not been used in (i) England, (ii) London and (ii) Ealing; and (b) the cost to the public purse on promoting Healthy Start vouchers in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271516","271516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135935","2019-07-03","Attorney General","2019-07-01","To ask the Attorney General, what steps his Department is taking with the legal profession to raise awareness of ADHD in the decision-making process on prosecutions.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271599","271599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135936","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the flats in Barandon Walk are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and of those flats how many are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271600","271600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135937","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the flats in Testerton Walk are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and of those flats how many are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271601","271601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135938","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the flats in Hurstway Walk are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and of those flats how many are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271602","271602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135939","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the flats in Treadgold House are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and of those flats how many are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271603","271603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135940","2019-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2019 to Question 264428, what assessment his Department has made of the environmental effect of the use of weapons that have been manufactured and sold by the UK.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271517","271517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135941","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the flats in Bramley House are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and of those flats how many are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271604","271604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135942","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the flats in Camborne Mews are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and of those flats how many are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271605","271605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135943","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the flats in Camelford Court are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and of those flats how many are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271606","271606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135944","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the flats in Camelford Walk are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and of those flats how many are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271607","271607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135945","2019-07-04","Cabinet Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2017 to Question 268970, whether his Department received proposals from the Electoral Commission on the implementation of section 10 of the Political Parties and Elections Act 2009.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271380","271380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135946","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many of the flats in Upper Camelford Walk are waiting to be deep-cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and how many of those flats are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271608","271608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135947","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will make it her Department's policy to process mandatory reconsiderations for personal independence payment claims within 15 working days.","Biography information for Faisal Rashid","Faisal Rashid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271609","271609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135948","2019-07-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the timeframe for bringing forward secondary legislation to enable the launch of small satellites will ensure that the target date of achieving a first launch by 2021 can be met.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271518","271518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135949","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the flats in Clarendon Walk are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and of those flats how many are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271610","271610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135950","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the flats in Lower Clarendon Walk are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and of those flats how many are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271611","271611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135951","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the flats in Morland House are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and of those flats how many are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271612","271612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135952","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many and what proportion of the flats in Talbot Grove House are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and of those flats how many are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271613","271613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135953","2019-07-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure a greater number of northbound East Midlands Railway trains stop at (a) Luton and (b) Luton Airport Parkway stations under the new franchise.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271428","271428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135954","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many of the flats in Talbot Walk are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and how many of those flats are (i) occupied and (ii) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271614","271614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135955","2019-07-04","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with East Midlands Trains on northbound services that fail to stop at (a) Luton and (b) Luton Airport Parkway under the existing timetable.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Mr Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271429","271429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135956","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many of the flats in Upper Talbot Walk are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and how many of those flats are (i) occupied and (ii) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271615","271615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135957","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 30 April to Written Question 245704, whether the UK Government plans to send experts to (a) to determine whether the Chunnakam power plant in Northern Sri Lanka was responsible for pollution in that area and (b) assist in the cleanup process in that area.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271323","271323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135958","2019-07-03","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many of the flats in Verity Close are waiting to be deep cleaned after the Grenfell Tower fire; and how many of those flats are (a) occupied and (b) empty.","Biography information for Emma Dent Coad","Emma Dent Coad","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271616","271616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135959","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what comparative data and analysis his Department holds on (a) operational practice and (b) waste content in municipal waste incineration sites in (i) England and (ii) Italy (iii) Scandinavia and (iv) other Member States of the EU.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271342","271342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135960","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the Scotch beef sector of the (a) European Commission and (b) Irish Government's emergency support for the Irish beef sector.","Biography information for David Duguid","David Duguid","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271519","271519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135961","2019-07-04","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans to direct the £10 million funding allocated to the  South West announced in the 2018 Budget to (a) the fishing industry and (b) the redevelopment of Brixham harbour.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271520","271520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135962","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether an EU national granted settled status in the UK is classified as having a right to be habitually resident for the purposes of applying for (a) universal credit and (b) other benefits.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271381","271381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135963","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many EU nationals have been refused universal credit in the last 12 months on the grounds that they have not demonstrated a right to be habitually resident.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271382","271382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135964","2019-07-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has to extend funding for the Community Housing Fund beyond 2020.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271343","271343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135965","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Justice on the provision of capacity building programmes for the domestic legal system in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271521","271521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135966","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he plans to review the trade relationship with Saudi Arabia as a result of the detention of political detainees and female activists in that country.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271522","271522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135967","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assurances he has received from his Saudi Arabian counterpart on the health and well-being of political detainees in that country.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271523","271523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135968","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations to his Saudi Arabian counterpart on the publication of proof of life evidence on political detainees being in custody in that country.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271524","271524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135969","2019-07-04","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to oral Answer of 27 June 2019 on the EU Settlement Scheme, if he will place a copy in the Library of his correspondence with the Department for Education and the Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government on the matter of applying for settled status for children in care of local authorities.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271617","271617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135970","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the (a) number of court cases rescheduled due to problems with interpreting or translating services and (b) additional cost incurred from that rescheduling in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271430","271430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135971","2019-07-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sitting days in courts in England were presided over by a recorder in each of the last 18 months.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271431","271431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135972","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people received a (a) custodial and (b) non-custodial sentence for assault of a (i) police officer and (ii) prison officer in each year since 2007, and what the average custodial sentence was for those offences.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271618","271618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135973","2019-07-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous offences was that a convicted person committed for that same offence before receiving a sentence other than an immediate non-custodial sentence in each of the last three years for offences relating to (a) possession of a blade or point, (b) possession of an offensive weapon, (c) common assault, (d) assaulting a police officer, (e) sexual assault, (f) public order, (g) theft, (h) robbery, (i) burglary, (j) drugs, (k) criminal damage, (l) breach of anti social behaviour order, (m) fraud and (n) vehicle taking.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271619","271619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135974","2019-07-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to his counterpart in the Guatemalan Government in response to reports of threats against human rights defender Domingo Vasquez and other members of the Nuevo Dia Ch'orti Indigenous Association in Guatemala.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271432","271432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135975","2019-07-04","Department for International Trade","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what representations he is making to the European Commission on quotas for UK steel exports into the EU, in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271525","271525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135976","2019-07-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 May 2019 to Question 253599 on Glen Pava Prison and Wellingborough Prison: Contracts, on what date his Department plans to award the Prison Operator Framework; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271526","271526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135977","2019-07-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 May 2019 to Question 253599 on Glen Pava Prison and Wellingborough Prison: Contracts, on what date his Department plans to announce the result of the mini-competition for the operation of the prison at Wellingborough.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271527","271527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135978","2019-07-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how he plans to use the Northern Powerhouse strategy refresh to improve productivity in the North of England.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271528","271528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135979","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 June 2019 to Question 264474 on Prisons: Private Sector, how many of the funded posts for Prison Custody Officers at each privately managed prison were filled as of the dates those figures relate to.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271529","271529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135980","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how he plans to use the Northern Powerhouse strategy refresh to improve health outcomes for people in the North of England.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271530","271530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135981","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure that vulnerable families can access children’s hospice services in the long-term.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271620","271620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135982","2019-07-03","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what plans he has to ensure future public health funding allocations prioritise areas with the poorest health outcomes.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271531","271531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135983","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total number of assaults on (a) prison officers, (b) prison educators, (c) prison instructors, (d) prison health-care staff and (e) other prison staff was across the prison estate in (i) 2012 (ii) 2018.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271532","271532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135984","2019-07-03","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps his Department is taking to help reduce the number of electrical fires in the home.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271533","271533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135985","2019-07-03","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what number and proportion of those who were given a suspended sentence in each of the last three years were required as part of that sentence to (a) do unpaid work, (b) be subject to a curfew, (c) undertake a treatment programme for alcohol or drug and (d) be subject to a rehabilitation activity requirement.","Biography information for Neil O'Brien","Neil O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271621","271621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135986","2019-07-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 20 June 2019 to Question 265525 on Buildings: Insulation, which materials referred to in the Written Statement of 1 May 2019, Official Report HCWS1533, have now been tested; and whether those tests have uncovered an immediate public safety concern.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271534","271534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135987","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to ensure (b) specialist roles and (b) Parkinson’s nurses are included in the NHS workforce plan.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271535","271535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135988","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what succession planning arrangements the NHS is making to minimise the vacancy rates for (a) Parkinson’s nurses and (b) other specialist roles.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271536","271536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135989","2019-07-04","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on large scale fire safety tests of timber cladding in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271537","271537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135990","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate he has made of the number of applications that have been (a) received, (b) concluded and (c) turned down for the EU Settlement Scheme at 31 May 2019.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271538","271538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135991","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people prosecuted under the Animal Welfare Act 2006 in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Farrelly","Paul Farrelly","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271433","271433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135992","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many locations in Wales provided UK Visas and Immigration biometric services in (a) 2016 and (b) 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271539","271539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135993","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of trends in the availability of appointments at UK Visa and Immigration biometric services in each year from 2016 to 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271540","271540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135994","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions he had with the university sector on the demand for UK Visa and Immigration biometric services by international students before the contract for those services was awarded to Sopra Steria.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271541","271541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135995","2019-07-04","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment his Department has made of the potential for local spikes in applications for UK Visa and Immigration biometric services by international students.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271542","271542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135996","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations he has received from (a) the US Administration and (b) lobbyists from the US pork production sector on the import of pork products from pigs fed with the additive ractopamine.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271344","271344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135997","2019-07-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the kit for the Team GB Olympic squad is produced sustainably.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271434","271434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135998","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 5 March 2019, Official Report column WS1376, what the implementation dates are for the new stipulations on personal independence payment.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271435","271435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1135999","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her Written Statement of 5 March 2019, HCWS1376,what assessment she has made of the effect of new provisions for reviews of personal independence payments on the review timescale for claimants who are state pension age and over.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271436","271436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136000","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to her Written Statement of 5 March 2019, WS1376, whether there will be regular reviews of personal independence payment awards to people (a) at and (b) above state pension age.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271437","271437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136001","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Government’s commitment to reach net zero carbon emissions by 2050, whether the Government plans to increase the 6GW capacity cap in the Contracts for Difference auctions.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271543","271543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136002","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant of his Answer of 16 May 2019 to Question 252526 on the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists, what steps his Department takes to ensure that no conflict of interest occurs in the drafting of clinical guidelines on abortion procedures by the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271438","271438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136003","2019-07-04","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, which Ministers are permanent members of the Environment and Clean Growth Inter-Ministerial Group.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271544","271544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136004","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 14 February 2019 to Question 217544 on Spina Bifida: Surgery, what estimate he has made of the average cost of pain relief that will be administered an unborn baby prior to undergoing that fetal surgery.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271439","271439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136005","2019-07-04","Department of Health and Social Care","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department has taken to ensure the (a) thorough and (b) objective scrutiny of the recommendations submitted by abortion providers to the NICE consultation on its guidance on the termination of pregnancy.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271440","271440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136006","2019-07-03","Home Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the potential implications the proposed cuts to Devon and Somerset Fire and Rescue Service will have on the safety of the area that service covers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karen Lee","Karen Lee","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271622","271622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136007","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will reconsider the Government’s opposition to listing in the UN business and human rights database of companies involved in settlement-related activities in the Palestinian Territories.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271545","271545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136008","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the suitability of the application process for personal independence payments for applicants with agoraphobia.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271546","271546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136009","2019-07-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the suitability of the application process for personal independence payements for people with a learning disability.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271547","271547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136010","2019-07-04","Ministry of Justice","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the susceptibility of the lasting power of attorney process to fraud.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271548","271548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136011","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the suitability of the application process for personal independent payments for people with post-traumatic stress disorder.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271549","271549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136012","2019-07-04","Department for Work and Pensions","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the application process for personal independent payments for applicants that are homeless and do not have access to (a) a telephone and (b) IT facilities .","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271550","271550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136013","2019-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, under what circumstances (a) the MoD Defence Council, (b) an Authorised Officer, and (c) HM Paymaster is able to reject a deduction of earning request from the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271551","271551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136014","2019-07-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Israeli settlements in the Palestinian Territories will be included in the future free trade agreement between the UK and Israel.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271552","271552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136015","2019-07-04","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the withdrawal of free TV licences for over-75s on the (a) well-being and (b) isolation of elderly people.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271553","271553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136016","2019-07-03","Department for International Trade","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, if he will seek the inclusion of a binding human rights clause in a future free trade agreement with Israel to establish that the (a) relations between the parties and (b) provisions of the agreement shall be based on respect for human rights and democratic principles as is provided for in article 2 of the EU-Israel Association Agreement.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271554","271554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136017","2019-07-04","Cabinet Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 269128 on GovTech Fund, how many of the 11 challenges have been fulfilled; and what the cost-benefit ratio was for each of those challenges.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271623","271623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136018","2019-07-03","Cabinet Office","2019-07-01","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department offers employees a payroll deduction service to enable them to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271324","271324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136019","2019-07-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department offers employees a payroll deduction service to enable them to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271325","271325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136020","2019-07-04","Ministry of Defence","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2019 to Question 269662 on Armed Forces: Heart Diseases, what criteria clinicians follow when seeking to detect significant structural and electrophysiological abnormalities in recruits.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271441","271441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136021","2019-07-03","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport,  whether his Department offers employees a payroll deduction service to enable staff to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271326","271326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136022","2019-07-03","Department for Education","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether his Department offers employees a payroll deduction service to enable staff to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271327","271327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136023","2019-07-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs,  whether his Department offers employees a payroll deduction service to enable staff to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271328","271328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136024","2019-07-03","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union,  whether his Department offers employees a payroll deduction service to enable staff to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271329","271329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136025","2019-07-03","Department for International Development","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether his Department offers employees a payroll deduction service to enable staff to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271330","271330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136026","2019-07-03","Department for International Trade","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, whether his Department offers employees a payroll deduction service to enable staff to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271331","271331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1136027","2019-07-03","Department for Transport","2019-07-01","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department offers employees a payroll deduction service to enable them to join a credit union; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271332","271332"
