"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35882","2014-02-04","Department for Transport","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the current estimated end date is of the Severn River Crossings concession.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185728","185728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35883","2014-02-03","Department for Transport","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of accidents on the national trunk road network that led to the death or serious injury of a cyclist involved a heavy goods vehicle in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185741","185741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35884","2014-02-03","Department for Transport","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) gross and (b) net revenue from each tolled crossing in the UK was in 2013.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185605","185605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35885","2014-02-03","Department for Transport","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) gross and (b) net revenue from the Severn Bridge and the Second Severn Crossing was in 2013.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185606","185606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35886","2014-02-03","Department for Transport","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the number of vehicles that used the (a) Severn Bridge and (b) Second Severn Crossing in 2013.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185607","185607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35887","2014-02-03","Wales Office","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what estimate he has made of the number of young adults in Wales living with their parents.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185789","185789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35888","2014-02-03","Wales Office","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer about publication of a Welsh taxes forecast.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185787","185787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35889","2014-02-03","Wales Office","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what changes have been made to the Welsh block grant in each year of the current Parliament in (a) real and (b) absolute terms.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185788","185788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35890","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the financial effect that charging a premium rate for the (a) personal independence payment helpline and (b) Capita helpline is having on the household income of claimants; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185764","185764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35891","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment claims have exceeded the three-month qualifying period; and what the (a) average and (b) longest time it has taken for a claimant to receive a decision from when the claim was first made in (i) the UK, (ii) Wales and (iii) Aberconwy constituency.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185765","185765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35892","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many homeless people have been referred to the Work Programme since June 2011; and how many of those people have secured a job outcome.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185846","185846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35893","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Warrington North constituency have been living in the same property since 1996 and in receipt of council tax benefit or a successor benefit during that time; and what estimate he has made of the number of such people who have (a) received transitional support, (b) erroneously had their benefit cancelled and (c) moved home following erroneous deductions from their benefit.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185736","185736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35894","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of regional variations in the cumulative impact of the Government's welfare reform programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185737","185737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35895","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he has taken to ensure there is sufficient capacity in Jobcentre Plus to process individuals returning after completion of the Work Programme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185735","185735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35896","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the total DEL budget allocated to the development, implementation and running of the Universal Credit programme was in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15, (f) 2015-16, (g) 2016-17, (h) 2017-18 and (i) total.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185692","185692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35897","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints have been received by (a) Jobcentre Plus and (b) his Department over Universal Jobmatch; and what the reasons were for each complaint.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185694","185694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35898","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 23 January 2014, what advance notice he will give pension providers of changes to auto enrolment provisions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185684","185684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35899","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the efficiency of the personal independence payment helpline; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Guto Bebb","Guto Bebb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185763","185763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35900","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will uprate the income threshold for carers allowance in line with increases in the minimum wage.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185757","185757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35901","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what provisions his Department has put in place to monitor the maintenance of Universal Jobmatch by Monster.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185705","185705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35902","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on public relations and communications consultants in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185707","185707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35903","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on communications and media training for (a) Ministers and (b) senior civil servants in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185708","185708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35904","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what budget his Department has allocated to spend on advertising (a) the under-occupancy penalty and (b) universal credit in the current financial year.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185709","185709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35905","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on advertising in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185710","185710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35906","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on advertising the introduction of the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185711","185711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35907","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether any provision has been made to transfer funds between the DEL and AME allocations for universal credit within his Department's overall allocation.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185611","185611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35908","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employers in Kingston-upon-Hull have applied for wage subsidies under the Youth Contract scheme to date.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185580","185580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35909","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseekerts in Kingston-upon-Hull have been supported by wage subsidies under the Youth Contract scheme to date.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185581","185581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35910","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employers (a) in the adult entertainment industry and (b) possessing a sexual entertainment venue licence have applied for wage subsidies under the Youth Contract scheme to date.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185583","185583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35911","2014-02-03","Cabinet Office","2014-01-29","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the effect of the exclusion of universal credit claimants on the overall claimant count in (a) April, (b) May, (c) June, (d) July, (e) August, (f) September, (g) October, (h) November and (i) December 2013.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185690","185690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35912","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants referred to Universal Jobmatch have entered employment for (a) less than one month, (b) between one and three months, (c) between three and six months and (d) more than six months to date.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185733","185733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35913","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what plans he has to extend to industrial premises the exemption for Sikhs from requirements to wear safety helmets on construction sites.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185731","185731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35914","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants have been sanctioned at any one time in the (a) last month, (b) three months, (c) six months and (d) year; and if he will publish the unemployment figures for the (i) last month, (ii) three months, (iii) six months and (iv) year if people on sanctions were included in the figures.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185691","185691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35915","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effects of (a) the reassessment of people in receipt of the higher rate of disability living allowance and (b) the personal independent payment appeals process on people currently participating in the Motability Scheme.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185619","185619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35916","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will have discussions with the Recruitment and Employment Confederation on ways of ensuring that the recruitment process for temporary workers is as transparent and efficient as possible.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185616","185616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35917","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants appealing against the removal of employment and support allowance were not able to claim jobseeker's allowance during the period of appeal in the latest year for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185615","185615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35918","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people claim (a) £20,000, (b) £30,000, (c) £40,000, (d) £50,000, (e) £60,000, (f) £70,000 and (g) £80,000 and above in housing benefit per annum.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185835","185835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35919","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of pensioners who receive pension credit in (a) Scottish parliamentary constituencies, (b) Fife region, (c) Scotland and (d) the UK; and what the cost to the public purse is of that provision for each category.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185867","185867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35920","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of providing pension credit in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185868","185868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35921","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the likely cost to the public purse of providing pension credit in (a) Scotland, (b) Northern Ireland, (c) England and (d) Wales in the current financial year.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185869","185869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35922","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of pension credit since it was introduced.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185870","185870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36326","2014-02-04","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-29","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to reduce re-offending among young offenders.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902394","902394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35345","2014-01-30","Attorney General","2014-01-28","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions there were following (a) kerb crawling, (b) brothel keeping and (c) controlling prostitution in each of the last six years; and how many such cases were reported to the Crown Prosecution Service by the Police for a charging decision.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185442","185442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35346","2014-01-30","Attorney General","2014-01-28","To ask the Attorney General, what recent surveys or studies the Crown Prosecution Service has carried out on (a) the level of victim and witness satisfaction with the quality of service provided by its witness care units and (b) the morale of staff at its witness care units.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185443","185443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35347","2014-01-30","Attorney General","2014-01-28","To ask the Attorney General, what data the Crown Prosecution Service records on the call response time of charging lawyers at CPS Direct.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185444","185444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35348","2014-01-30","Attorney General","2014-01-28","To ask the Attorney General, how many and what proportion of decisions to take no further action referred to the Crown Prosecution Service by the police concerned (a) indictable-only offences, (b) serious sexual offences excluding child abuse, (c) child abuse and (d) domestic violence in each year since 2006.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185446","185446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35349","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish an evaluation of the Small Business Research Initiative.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185367","185367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35350","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) home and (b) international students there are at West Midlands universities.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185368","185368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35351","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the degree to which the Small Business Research Initiative has met its targets.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185369","185369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35352","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what training initiatives his Department has launched to increase the skills needed by young people in new high technology enterprises.","Biography information for Mr Lee Scott","Mr Lee Scott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185449","185449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35353","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff in UKTI West Midlands have been tasked with supporting inward investment into the region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185432","185432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35354","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of his Department's spending on science.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185416","185416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35355","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to promote UK business at the Winter Olympic Games in Sochi.","Biography information for Mr Lee Scott","Mr Lee Scott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185433","185433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35356","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received (a) in favour and (b) against the provisions in the draft Deregulation Bill on the licensing of insolvency practitioners.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185385","185385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35357","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect of partial licensing of insolvency practitioners on small businesses seeking financial advice.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185386","185386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35358","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make a statement on the implication of the UK aerospace industry of the $8.7 billion subsidy package awarded to Boeing by Washington State in November 2013.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185347","185347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35359","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will raise with the World Trade Organization the $8.7 billion subsidy package awarded to Boeing by Washington State in November 2013.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185348","185348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35360","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from his Department have subsequently been re-employed by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185557","185557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35361","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to tackle the abuse of trusts for money laundering.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185555","185555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35362","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress his Department has made on creating a public register of companies' beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185556","185556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35363","2014-01-30","Cabinet Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from his Department have subsequently been re-employed by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185558","185558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35364","2014-01-30","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-28","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what (a) grants and (b) other external activity have been issued under the Democratic Engagement Programme to date.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185383","185383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35365","2014-01-30","Cabinet Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for each of the last three financial years how much and what proportion of his Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools; and what the value of such contracts was.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185401","185401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35366","2014-01-30","Cabinet Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of his Department's overall procurement spend for each of the last three financial years was spent (a) in joint procurement exercises with other departments and (b) shared between different organisations within the same Department group.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185395","185395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35367","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much HM Revenue and Customs has spent on advertising on Facebook for the purposes of preventing tax evasion in the current financial year.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185440","185440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35368","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has received on a VAT reduction for the tourism sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185379","185379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35369","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from his Department have subsequently been re-employed by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185570","185570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35370","2014-02-03","HM Treasury","2014-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) higher rate taxpayers and (b) individuals who earn over £1 million there are in Wales in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185536","185536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35371","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many new loans have been made to small businesses in north east England through the Funding for Lending scheme; and which participating building society or bank provided each such loan.","Biography information for Pat Glass","Pat Glass","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185474","185474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35372","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for each of the last three financial years how much and what proportion of his Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools; and what the value of such contracts was.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185405","185405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35373","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of his Department's overall procurement spend for each of the last three financial years was spent (a) in joint procurement exercises with other departments and (b) shared between different organisations within the same Department group.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185400","185400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35374","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he intends to answer question number 183496 tabled on 15 January 2014.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185517","185517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35375","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he intends to answer question number 183499 tabled on 15 January 2014 for Named Day Answer on 20 January 2014.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185518","185518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35376","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he intends to answer question number 184121 tabled on 20 January 2014 for Named Day Answer on 23 January 2014.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185519","185519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35377","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many homes have been completed under the Get Britain Building scheme.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185480","185480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35378","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many jobs the Get Britain Building scheme has created.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185481","185481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35379","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many affordable homes have been completed under the Get Britain Building scheme.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185482","185482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35380","2014-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from his Department have subsequently been re-employed by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185559","185559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35381","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what requirements there are under building regulations for fire sprinklers in timber-framed residential and nursing care homes.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185356","185356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35382","2014-02-03","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what requirements there are for (a) frequency and (b) certification of fire inspections of residential and nursing care homes.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185354","185354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35383","2014-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what advice and assistance his Department has made available to communities seeking to retain their local pubs.","Biography information for Mr Lee Scott","Mr Lee Scott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185450","185450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35384","2014-02-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the projected cost under each cost heading is of the commemoration of the First World War.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185363","185363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35385","2014-02-03","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what amount of funding her Department gave to each youth choir in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185364","185364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35386","2014-01-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to promote the rights of LGBT people during the Sochi Olympic Games.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185349","185349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35388","2014-01-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to help small and medium-sized arts organisations increase their business and marketing skills.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185359","185359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35389","2014-01-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from her Department have subsequently been re-employed by her Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185561","185561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35390","2014-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many systems (a) have been delivered and (b) are operational under the Aircrew Moving Map Alerting System contract since that contract was awarded in October 2013.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Howarth","Sir Gerald Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185475","185475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35391","2014-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had on the possible disposal of surplus Ministry of Defence land and property for housing development in London and the South East.","Biography information for Mr Lee Scott","Mr Lee Scott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185469","185469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35392","2014-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for each of the last three financial years how much and what proportion of his Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools; and what the value of such contracts was.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185402","185402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35393","2014-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of his Department's overall procurement spend for each of the last three financial years was spent (a) in joint procurement exercises with other departments and (b) shared between different organisations within the same Department group.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185396","185396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35394","2014-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the recently declassified study on stress suffered by UK RPAS pilots carried out by Dr Wayne Cappelle.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185372","185372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35395","2014-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2014, Official Report, column 696W, when he or officials of his Department last discussed with Iranian officials or their legal representatives the Court of Arbitration's ruling in the case of International Military Services Ltd v Iran.","Biography information for Mr Ben Wallace","Mr Ben Wallace","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185362","185362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35396","2014-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 15 January 2014, Official Report, columns 578-9W, on unmanned aerial vehicles, what the role of the UK is in each of the three activities of the Unmanned Aerial Systems Programme identified in the Answer.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185412","185412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35397","2014-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the (a) name and (b) regiment was of the Royal Engineer whose repatriation parade was scheduled for 31 December 2013 but which was cancelled soon after; and for what reason the repatriation was not carried out in public.","Biography information for Patrick Mercer","Patrick Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185447","185447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35398","2014-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 709W, on unmanned Air Vehicles, whether the RAF officer responsible for liaison with US visiting forces at RAF Croughton has authority to stop a command by the USAF Commander for release of a lethal weapon.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185430","185430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35399","2014-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2014, Official Report, column 664W, on Asia, what projects are currently being carried out to help his Department assess the implications of sharing military assets, including unmanned systems, with the US in Asia.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185420","185420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35400","2014-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to sell the former Coastguard building in Greenock; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185414","185414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35401","2014-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2014, Official Report, column 695W, on Djibouti, how many UK personnel are based at Camp Lemonnier; what the purpose is of their deployment; and under whose line of command those personnel fall.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185455","185455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35402","2014-01-30","Department for Education","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many times Edapt UK Ltd has been referred to in his Department's emails and written correspondence in each of the last 12 months; and how many items of email and written correspondence there have been between his Department and Edapt UK Ltd over the same period.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185448","185448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35403","2014-02-03","Department for Education","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 November 2013, Official Report, column 63W, on school meals, what support his Department will give to primary schools in providing universal free school meals to all children up to the age of seven; and what additional support his Department will give those primary schools without kitchen facilities.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185453","185453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35404","2014-02-03","Department for Education","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions he (a) has had and (b) plans to have with the School Teachers' Review Body about extending the terms and conditions for teachers to allow them to buy cars through salary sacrifice schemes.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185515","185515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35405","2014-02-03","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what funding his Department will make available for students from a disadvantaged background in higher education after 2015-16.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185533","185533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35406","2014-01-30","Department for Education","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will categorise the Reception class in primary schools as part of Key Stage 1.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185500","185500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35407","2014-02-03","Department for Education","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what mechanisms are in place to support maintained schools which do not have a Special Educational Needs co-ordinator.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185390","185390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35408","2014-02-03","Department for Education","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reason the definition of progress in Chapter six of the draft Special Education Needs Code of Practice no longer includes improvements in self help, social and personal skills.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185392","185392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35409","2014-02-03","Department for Education","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what measures are in place to ensure that all maintained schools receive the required level of support from a Special Educational Needs Coordinator.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185393","185393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35410","2014-02-03","Department for Education","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to discuss the draft Special Education Needs Code of Practice with disability charities and other stakeholders before publication of the final version.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185391","185391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35411","2014-01-30","Department for Education","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from his Department have subsequently been re-employed by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185562","185562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35412","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from his Department have subsequently been re-employed by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185563","185563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35413","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what criteria his Department uses for allocating green subsidies to power plants.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185539","185539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35414","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which power plants in the UK applied for the most recent round of green subidies.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185540","185540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35415","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, for what reasons his Department did not allocate a green subsidy to Eggborough power plant in the most recent round of subsidies.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185541","185541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35416","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which power plants that were awarded a green subsidy will be able to commence biomass production as a result of that subsidy.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185542","185542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35417","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the potential effects on the (a) local and (b) national economy of Eggborough power plant not converting to a biomass energy plant.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185543","185543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35418","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will estimate the number of jobs dependent on the operation of Eggborough power plant.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185544","185544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35419","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many onshore wind farms were granted planning permission in each year from 2004 to 2009.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185537","185537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35420","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the proportion of UK electricity needs that will be supplied by Eggborough power plant in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185538","185538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35421","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will make an assessment of the financial sustainability of power plants that did not receive green subsidies in the most recent round.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185545","185545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35422","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will draw up a contingency plan for regeneration of the area around Eggborough power plant in the event that that plant closes.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185546","185546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35423","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will bring forward proposals to ring-fence funding as part of the boiler replacement scheme for rural pensioners who use oil boilers.","Biography information for Mark Garnier","Mark Garnier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185479","185479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35424","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the total number of fuel poor households (a) benefiting from and (b) taken out of fuel poverty as a result of energy efficiency measures installed under supplier-funded energy efficiency programmes in each year since 2008-09 in (i) Great Britain and (ii) each constituent part of the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185476","185476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35425","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the number of fuel poor households benefiting from energy efficiency measures installed under the (a) Affordable Warmth Obligation, (b) Carbon Saving Communities Obligation and (c) Carbon Obligation elements of the supplier-funded Energy Company Obligation in (i) Great Britain and (ii) each constituent part of the UK since the scheme went live in January 2013.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185477","185477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35426","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on household bills of the closure of Eggborough power station.","Biography information for Mrs Linda Riordan","Mrs Linda Riordan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185493","185493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35427","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether all direct employees of Eggborough Power Station are paid above the living wage.","Biography information for Mrs Linda Riordan","Mrs Linda Riordan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185494","185494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35428","2014-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what support he plans to provide to (a) families, (b) businesses and (c) individuals who are struggling to pay their heating bills this winter; and what financial support he is providing to each local authority in England and Wales for this purpose.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185487","185487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35429","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the United States Department of Energy on the effect of hydraulic fracturing on gas prices in the United States.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185436","185436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35430","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the level of total shale gas reserves in the United Kingdom.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185437","185437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35431","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the potential of hydraulic fracturing to reduce energy bills in the United Kingdom.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185438","185438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35432","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of energy bills were made up of green levies in 2004.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185439","185439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35433","2014-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent investment the Government has made into the UK energy infrastructure; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185413","185413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35434","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what progress he has made on ensuring that off-grid households have access to affordable heating fuels in winter.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185473","185473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35435","2014-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, when he will reply substantively to the letter from the hon. Member for Mid Worcestershire of 25 July 2013, acknowledged by his Department on 2 October 2013, about Hartlebury parish council and the proposed mass burn incinerator.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185358","185358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35436","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Energy Company Obligation on the introduction of minimum energy efficiency standards for poorest households living in the coldest homes in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185417","185417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35437","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate his Department has made of the total number of fuel poor households who will receive energy efficiency measures installed (a) under the supplier funded Energy Company Obligation, (b) the Carbon Saving Communities Obligation and (c) the Carbon Obligation elements up to (i) 2015 and (ii) 2017 in each constituent part of Great Britain.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185418","185418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35438","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the total amount per year spent on households in fuel poverty for supplier-funded energy efficiency polices in (a) Great Britain, (b) England and (c) each of the other constituent parts of the UK from 2008-209 to date.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185410","185410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35439","2014-02-03","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the amount of payments made by domestic customers to energy companies via their energy bills as at 31 December 2013 as a result of the introduction of the Energy Company Obligation.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185365","185365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35440","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment his Department has made of the number of fuel poor households in the private rented sector qualifying for installations under (a) the Affordable Warmth Obligation, (b) the Carbon Saving Communities Obligation and (c) the Carbon Obligation elements of the supplier-funded Energy Company Obligation since the scheme went live in January 2013 in (i) Great Britain, (ii) England and (iii) each of the other constituent parts of the UK.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185409","185409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35441","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what percentage of the UK's natural gas consumption was imported in (a) 2000, (b) 2005 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185344","185344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35442","2014-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the feasibility of dredging the River Ribble in order to minimise flood risk to homes, businesses and agricultural land.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185408","185408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35443","2014-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will have discussions with the Royal College of Veterinary Surgeons on the introduction of mandatory oral and written English tests for veterinary surgeons from the EU.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185411","185411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35444","2014-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of recent trends in the number of eels in the UK; and what steps he is taking to improve eel habitats.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185467","185467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35445","2014-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of owls in the UK; and what steps he is taking to increase that number.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185461","185461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35446","2014-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many wildlife incidents were reported in the UK in each of the last three years; how many such incidents were prosecuted; and how many such prosecutions resulted in a conviction.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185462","185462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35447","2014-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made on implementation of the recommendations of the Climate Change Risk Assessment for the Energy Sector on mitigation of the identified in the Tier 1 assessment for each of the 11 sectors collectively; how much has it cost to date to (a) mitigate and (b) adapt to the impacts; and if he will make a statement on how he plans to take forward work on this report.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185509","185509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35448","2014-02-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assistance the Government is giving to farmers whose land has been flooded.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185485","185485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35449","2014-02-04","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cats and dogs were used in experiments in the UK (a) in the last 12 months and (b) in the year ended January 2009; and what steps her Department is taking to ensure that the use of cats and dogs in experiments is phased out.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185490","185490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35450","2014-02-04","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to release more information pertaining to the conducting of animal experiments in the UK; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185572","185572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35451","2014-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from his Department have subsequently been re-employed by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185564","185564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35452","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from his Department have subsequently been re-employed by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185565","185565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35453","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the government of Pakistan regarding the constitutional Federal Shariah Court in Pakistan's call for the implementation of the death penalty against those found guilty of breaking blasphemy laws; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185468","185468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35454","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for each of the last three financial years how much and what proportion of his Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools; and what the value of such contracts was.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185403","185403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35455","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of his Department's overall procurement spend for each of the last three financial years was spent (a) in joint procurement exercises with other departments and (b) shared between different organisations within the same Department group.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185397","185397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35456","2014-02-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of measures in place to protect children on the Pitcairn Islands from convicted sex offenders.","Biography information for Meg Munn","Meg Munn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185457","185457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35457","2014-02-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the situation of LGBT people in Uganda; and what recent representations he has made to his Ugandan counterpart on this issue.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185394","185394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35458","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether officials in his Department have participated in any EC Working Group considering policy or law applying to use of unmanned aerial vehicles.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185350","185350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35459","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the South Sudanese government about persecuted religious groups.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185343","185343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35460","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on security in Yemen of drone strikes in that country.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185407","185407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35461","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment the Government has made of the political stability of South Sudan.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185346","185346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35462","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the division of responsibility for health services policy is between his Department and NHS England.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185374","185374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35463","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2014, Official Report, columns 405-6W, on cancer drugs, what communications he has received from NHS England on the effect of NICE decisions on the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185387","185387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35464","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2014, Official Report, columns 405-6W, on cancer drugs, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes in the cancer drugs approved by NICE on the Cancer Drugs Fund.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185388","185388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35465","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2014, Official Report, columns 405-6W, on cancer drugs, what assurance he has received from NHS England that a potential overspend in the Cancer Drugs Fund will not affect patients who need access to medicines through the Fund; and if he will place in the Library a copy of any such assurance received.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185389","185389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35466","2014-02-03","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects the next review of the adult autism strategy to take place, after the publication of the revised strategy in March 2014.","Biography information for Annette Brooke","Annette Brooke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185351","185351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35467","2014-02-03","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January, Official Report, column 178W, on Manor Hospital, Walsall, if the Department has now received notification arising from the report of the Mid Staffordshire Special Administrators and Monitor for additional investment at the Manor Hospital, Walsall, in view of the need for additional capacity to take in patients arising from external situations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185357","185357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35468","2014-02-03","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) black, (b) red, (c) amber and (d) green alerts there has been at (i) central Manchester University Hospitals Foundation NHS Trust and (ii) University Hospitals South Manchester Trust in each month of the last five years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185361","185361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35469","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to prevent under-age smoking.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185466","185466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35470","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many infants were diagnosed with botulism in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185465","185465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35471","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the British Medical Association on the potential health risks associated with mouthwashes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185464","185464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35472","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Cardiff University on the drug developed by that university that may control the spread of breast cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185463","185463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35473","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many meetings of the Health Care Strategy Forum officials from his Department have attended.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185434","185434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35474","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations on public policy his Department has received from the Health Care Strategy Forum.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185435","185435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35475","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will include stroke patients in the list of those exempted from prescription charges.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185431","185431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35476","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the benefits to treatment and care quality of making health records available for medical research.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185506","185506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35477","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Scottish Government on the effect of drug driving legislation on patients taking long-term medication for chronic pain and similar conditions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185505","185505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35478","2014-02-03","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government plans to take to address risks to public health caused by a rise in the incidence of risky sexual behaviour related to drug use.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185530","185530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35479","2014-02-03","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether any medical data will be extracted by care.data from GP-held records of patients who have objected to the use of their confidential information by others than those providing them with care.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185516","185516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35480","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure that greater transparency and accountability in the delivery of services for adults with autism are incorporated into the forthcoming review of the adult autism strategy.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185495","185495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35481","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to develop greater autism awareness in local communities.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185496","185496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35482","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he has given to local authorities on (a) assessment of the effect of musculoskeletal conditions on their local population and (b) inclusion of musculoskeletal conditions in Joint Strategic Need Assessments.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185497","185497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35483","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government has taken to promote comprehensive fracture liaison services.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185491","185491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35484","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people with (a) long-term conditions and (b) osteoarthritis currently have a personalised care plan.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185492","185492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35485","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from his Department have subsequently been re-employed by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185566","185566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35486","2014-02-03","Department of Health","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish its response to Next Steps for Nursery Milk consultation, which closed in October 2012.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185529","185529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35487","2014-02-03","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 647, on psychoactive substances, if she will list the 250 new psychoactive substances banned since May 2010.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185528","185528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35488","2014-01-30","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from her Department have subsequently been re-employed by her Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185567","185567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35489","2014-01-30","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for each of the last three financial years how much and what proportion of her Department's procurement was conducted using e-procurement tools; and what the value of such contracts was.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185404","185404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35490","2014-02-03","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, on how many occasions she has used powers under the Royal Prerogative to prevent people suspected of terrorism from travelling abroad in the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185520","185520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35491","2014-02-03","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to provide additional funding to the police and security services to cover the cost of surveillance of individuals previously subject to Terrorism Prevention and Investigative Measures Orders.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185526","185526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35492","2014-02-03","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 26W, on drugs: misuse, if she will list the members of the expert advisory panel on new psychoactive substances who have been appointed to date.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185531","185531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35493","2014-02-03","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 647, on psychoactive substances, what public awareness campaigns her Department has undertaken to alert young people to the dangers of new psychoactive substances.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185532","185532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35494","2014-02-03","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many former unaccompanied asylum-seeking children who were in the UK under discretionary leave had (i) applications heard, (ii) applications accepted and (iii) applications refused to extend their leave in each of the last five years for which records are available.","Biography information for Sarah Teather","Sarah Teather","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185486","185486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35495","2014-01-30","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of her Department's overall procurement spend for each of the last three financial years was spent (a) in joint procurement exercises with other departments and (b) shared between different organisations within the same Department group.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185398","185398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35496","2014-02-03","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many known persons of interest have been processed by the Semaphore system in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185456","185456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35497","2014-01-30","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will introduce a code or other guidance to regulate the collection, storage and use of data obtained by departments using unmanned aerial systems.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185419","185419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35498","2014-02-03","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of retail crime on businesses in West Mercia.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185366","185366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35499","2014-02-03","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the introduction of gender non-specific passports; and what discussions she has had with international counterparts on this matter.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185451","185451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35501","2014-01-30","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the extent to which recommendation 14 in the Fourth Report of the Home Affairs Committee of Session 2001-02, The Conduct of Investigations into Past Cases of Abuse in Children's Homes, HC 836-I, that the use of similar allegations as evidence to corroborate a child sex abuse charge be tightened to include only allegations that bear a striking similarity, has been implemented.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185345","185345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35502","2014-01-30","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Metropolitan Police Service has ever trialled or used any unmanned aerial surveillance system.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185406","185406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35503","2014-01-30","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-28","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what the cost of preparing, publishing and monitoring Early Day Motions has been in each year of this Parliament.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185380","185380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35504","2014-01-30","Department for International Development","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from her Department have subsequently been re-employed by her Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185568","185568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35505","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps she is taking to maintain the recent ceasefire in South Sudan.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185553","185553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35506","2014-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from his Department have subsequently been re-employed by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185569","185569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35507","2014-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders have been reconvicted within 12 months of breaching a Suspended Sentence Order in each year since the introduction of Suspended Sentence Orders.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185507","185507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35508","2014-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the cost of running the Office of the Public Guardian Investigations Unit was in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185488","185488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35509","2014-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders have been sent to prison after breaching a Suspended Sentence Order in each year since the introduction of Suspended Sentence Orders.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185508","185508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35510","2014-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how staff were recruited to the Office of the Public Guardian Investigations Unit in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185489","185489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35511","2014-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total amount is of fines (a) issued by the courts and (b) uncollected was in (i) 2010, (ii) 2011, (iii) 2012 and (iv) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185484","185484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35512","2014-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total amount is of fines issued by the courts between 2010 and 2013 which remain uncollected.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185483","185483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35513","2014-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether community rehabilitation companies will continue to be badged as the Probation Service.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185352","185352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35514","2014-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff worked on the collection of confiscation orders in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185452","185452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35515","2014-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will publish a quarterly summary of the number of convictions for a primary offence of rape over the last three years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185445","185445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35516","2014-02-03","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff were employed by his Department on the enforcement of payment of fines in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185415","185415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35517","2014-02-03","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to scrutinise the performance of Geo Group UK Ltd following the HM Inspectorate of Prisons' Report.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185460","185460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35518","2014-02-03","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Geo Group UK Ltd, contractors for HM Prison Harmondsworth, will be allowed to bid in the re-tendering process following HM Inspectorate of Prisons' Report.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185458","185458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35519","2014-02-03","Home Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to change the terms of the contract for HM Prison Harmondsworth in light of the HM Inspectorate of Prisons' Report.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185459","185459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35520","2014-01-30","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-01-28","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what information the Electoral Commission holds on the registration rates of attainers in (a) Great Britain and (b) each region of Great Britain.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185478","185478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35521","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish his Department's business case score for the Crown Point East bypass scheme in Denton, Greater Manchester submitted under the Pinch Point initiative.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185498","185498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35522","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to include information on the new drug driving offence in the driving theory test; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185501","185501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35523","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish his Department's business case scores for the projects awarded funding in the latest round of the Pinch Point initiative.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185499","185499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35524","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on the pharmaceutical industry of the changes required to Patient Information Leaflets following the introduction of the new drug driving offence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185502","185502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35525","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that patients taking long-term medication for chronic pain and similar conditions understand the medical defence under in the drug driving legislation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185503","185503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35526","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with (a) the Secretary of State for Health and (b) the Scottish Government on the effect of drug driving legislation on patients taking long-term medication for chronic pain and similar conditions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185504","185504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35527","2014-02-03","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research his Department is undertaking on the potential (a) social and economic effects of Graduating Driver Licensing, (b) the effect of reforms to young driver training and testing on road safety and (c) road safety benefits of telematics.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185527","185527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35528","2014-02-03","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to his Answer of 24 January 2014, Official Report, column 362W on Re-employment, what the total cost was of those redundancy payments.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185360","185360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35529","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure long term investment in train services to the far South West.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185341","185341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35530","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the impact on rail resilience of the Environment Agency's proposals for flood defences at Cowley Bridge, Exeter.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185342","185342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35531","2014-02-04","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure the continued availability of zero or low content biofuel at five per cent or below for use by owners of older motor vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185399","185399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35532","2014-02-03","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will introduce legislative proposals to reduce road congestion around primary schools.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185353","185353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35533","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the budget for rail resilience works to the Devon stretch of the London Paddington to Plymouth rail link is for the current and next four financial years.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185378","185378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35534","2014-02-03","Department for Transport","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of Northern Rail on passenger satisfaction in Cumbria.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185355","185355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35535","2014-01-30","Women and Equalities","2014-01-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what the average salary was of employees of the Government Equalities Office who were (a) male, (b) female, (c) of white ethnic origin, (d) of Black and minority ethnic origin, (e) disabled and (f) not disabled in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185375","185375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35536","2014-01-30","Women and Equalities","2014-01-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many staff currently working at the Government Equalities Office have not received diversity training.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185376","185376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35537","2014-01-30","Women and Equalities","2014-01-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many grievances have been raised by staff at the Government Equalities Office on the grounds of any kind of discrimination in each of the last five years; and what the outcome was in each case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185377","185377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35538","2014-01-30","Women and Equalities","2014-01-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what proportion of staff of the Government Equalities Department has not declared their status in answer to any or all of the questions in diversity declaration forms in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185339","185339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35539","2014-01-30","Women and Equalities","2014-01-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many employees of the Government Equalities Office are currently (a) male, (b) female, (c) of white ethnic origin, (d) of Black and minority ethnic origin, (e) disabled and (f) not disabled.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185340","185340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35540","2014-02-03","Women and Equalities","2014-01-28","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, when she expects conversion of civil partnerships to marriages under Section 9 of the Marriage (Same Sex Couples) Act 2013 to begin; and what the reasons are for the delay in starting this process.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185534","185534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35541","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential effects of the under-occupancy penalty on the level of child poverty in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185522","185522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35542","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his most recent assessment is of the effectiveness of the Youth Contract.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185523","185523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35543","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much income the Health and Safety Executive earned from commercial sources in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185524","185524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35544","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what future plans he has for reducing spending on working-age benefits.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185525","185525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35545","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the effects on (a) Exchequer receipts and (b) individual incomes of eligibility for universal credit being established using gross rather than net income with disregards and the taper rate maintained at the levels currently proposes.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185521","185521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35546","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in receipt of personal independence payment are not receiving their benefit payments.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185470","185470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35547","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of direct payments to sub-contractors of prime providers made by his Department under the Work Programme related to delivery of the Work Programme in Clackmannanshire.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185510","185510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35548","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of direct payments to individual prime providers made by his Department under the Work Programme related to delivery of the Work Programme in Clackmannanshire.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185511","185511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35549","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints have been submitted to prime providers of the Work Programme in Clackmannanshire.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185512","185512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35550","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what oversight his Department has of contracts between prime and sub contractors delivering the Work Programme in Clackmannanshire.","Biography information for Gordon Banks","Gordon Banks","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185513","185513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35551","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on the number of people claiming carers' allowance of a rise in the minimum wage; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185514","185514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35552","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children are living in poverty in Birmingham to the smallest area for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185371","185371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35553","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the written statement of 23 January 2014, on Pensions, whether the delay announced to the introduction of a charge cap on workplace pension scheme also extends to his Department's planned changes regarding the governance of pension schemes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185547","185547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35554","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the written statement of 23 January 2014, on Pensions, when he expects to bring forward proposals for a pensions charge cap before Parliament; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185548","185548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35555","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has held with officials from HM Treasury in the last four months.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185549","185549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35556","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the written statement of 23 January 2014, on Pensions, if he will publish the responses to the Government consultation on charging in workplace pensions.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185550","185550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35557","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to introduce a pension scheme for those beginning employment for the first time which would commence at a nominal monthly sum, increase automatically each year on a compound basis but have an opt out basis.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185551","185551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35558","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that pension providers that send out default annuity offers do so on a more competitive basis.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185552","185552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35559","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment (PIP) claims (a) have been made, (b) received assessments and (c) been awarded to date; and what the (i) average and (ii) longest time it has taken for a claimant to receive a decision from when the claim was first made in (A) Wales and (B) Newport East constituency.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185535","185535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35560","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many staff who have been made redundant or retired from his Department have subsequently been re-employed by his Department since May 2010.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185571","185571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35561","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the average waiting time for claimants of the personal independence payment who require a home consultation in each (a) country, (b) region and (v) parliamentary constituency of the UK.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185381","185381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35562","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of personal independence payment who require a home consultation have waited longer than (a) one month, (b) two months, (c) three months, (d) four months, (e) five months and (f) six months or more for such a consultation to date.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185382","185382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35563","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his Answer of 23 January 2014, Official Report, column 263W, on children's maintenance, which particular Project Change Lifecycle Framework criteria will govern his Department's assessment of its operational readiness to start the process of Child Support Agency case closure.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185384","185384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35564","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) working and (b) non-working single parents are in receipt of benefits in Birmingham to the smallest area for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185370","185370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35565","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish a code of conduct on the disclosure of pension charges to employers; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185428","185428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35566","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of the consultation announced by his Department on pension charge cap published on 30 October 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185429","185429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35567","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the number of pension pots in pension schemes with an annual management charge in excess of 1 per cent; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185427","185427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35568","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Written Statement of 23 January 2014, on pensions, whether he will introduce a pensions charge cap inclusive of transaction costs; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185426","185426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35569","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on advertising (a) tackling benefit fraud and (b) unclaimed benefits on Facebook in the current financial year.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185441","185441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35570","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have met (i) Prudential, (ii) Fidelity Investments, (iii) the Association of British Insurers and (iv) the Investment Management Association in the last four months; and for what purpose.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185421","185421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35571","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects the Office of Fair Trading to complete its review of legacy pension schemes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185422","185422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35572","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussion he has had with the Office of Fair Trading on the review of legacy pension schemes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185423","185423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35573","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the take up of pensions credit among those who are eligible.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185424","185424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35574","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he plans to take to increase the take up of pensions credit among those who are eligible.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185425","185425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35575","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims for personal independence payments are outstanding for each of the last three years.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185472","185472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35576","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when (a) Ministers and (b) officials his Department have met (i) Axa, (ii) Aviva, (iii) Friends Life, (iv) Scottish Life, (v) Scottish Widows, (vi) Legal and General, (vii) Aegon and (vii) Standard Life in the last four months; and for what purpose.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185454","185454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35577","2014-02-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the causes of delays in the delivery of personal independence payments.","Biography information for Lindsay Roy","Lindsay Roy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185471","185471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36022","2014-02-03","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on ensuring that the disposal of the military estate results in maximum benefit to local communities.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902332","902332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/36912","2014-02-05","Scotland Office","2014-01-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Scotland currently employed on zero-hours contracts.","Biography information for Ann McKechin","Ann McKechin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902342","902342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35135","2014-01-30","Attorney General","2014-01-27","To ask the Attorney General, if he will set out the Law Officers' Departments' priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185302","185302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35136","2014-02-05","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will instigate an inquiry into the use of the Enterprise Finance Guarantee and Royal Bank of Scotland handling in relation to C. May Brickwork Ltd of Mold, Flintshire.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185252","185252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35137","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185301","185301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35138","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effects on the universal postal service of the extension of end-to-end delivery services by companies other than the universal service provider.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185263","185263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35139","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who have chosen to use (a) Royal Mail's opt-out scheme and (b) the mailing preference service.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185118","185118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35140","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will release the Business is Great campaign posters and related materials under a creative commons licence.","Biography information for Mr Steve Baker","Steve Baker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185124","185124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35141","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the effect of the carbon price floor of industrial competitiveness of UK businesses.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185163","185163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35142","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the financial effects of the removal of Climate Change Levy Levy Exemption Certificates for combined heat and power stations on industrial sites which use combined heat and power.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185164","185164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35143","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to reduce industrial energy costs for sites which have invested in combined heat and power for the purposes of reducing emissions and improving their industrial competitiveness; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Iain Wright","Mr Iain Wright","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185166","185166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35144","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he has taken to implement the recommendations of the Tomlinson Report into Banks' lending practices.","Biography information for Natascha Engel","Natascha Engel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185180","185180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35145","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he or Ministers in his Department have had with ministers in the Scottish Government on the blacklisting of Scottish workers.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185128","185128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35146","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent meetings his Department has had where the blacklisting of Scottish workers has been discussed.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185129","185129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35147","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will place a copy of the model used to forecast revenue from student loan payments in the Library.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185133","185133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35148","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his forecast outturn for science spending is in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185184","185184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35149","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with TNT on extending end-to-end postal services in (a) Liverpool, (b) Manchester, (c) Glasgow, (d) Birmingham, (e) Edinburgh and (f) other areas of the UK.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185185","185185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35150","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what publicly-funded research budgets are ongoing at universities in the West Midlands.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185186","185186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35151","2014-01-30","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with (a) Ofcom and (b) Consumer Futures on the effect of end-to-end competition in the postal market on the universal postal service.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185187","185187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35152","2014-01-29","Cabinet Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the average cost per download was for each campaign in each of the electoral registration campaigns since 2004.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185198","185198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35153","2014-01-29","Cabinet Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what effect changes in pensions contributions have had on the take-home pay of civil servants compared with May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185222","185222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35154","2014-01-29","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect the Government's policies have had on the take-home pay of officials across the Civil Service compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185223","185223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35155","2014-01-30","Cabinet Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185303","185303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35156","2014-01-29","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-27","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, pursuant to the Answer of 17 January 2014, Official Report, column 181W, on the electoral register, and columns 189-90W, on the electoral register: Northern Ireland, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland on the registration of attainers in (a) Northern Ireland and (b) Great Britain.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185325","185325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35157","2014-01-29","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185321","185321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35158","2014-02-03","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to chart 2.H of his Department's publication Impact on households: distributional analysis to accompany Autumn Statement 2013, if he will publish the data on which that chart is based; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185250","185250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35159","2014-02-03","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to chart 2.H of his Department's publication Impact on households: distributional analysis to accompany Autumn Statement 2013, what the 10 items are that make up the change in public service spending for the top quintile; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Swales","Ian Swales","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185251","185251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35160","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to require banks not to prevent customers taking out large sums of money in cash without proof of reason for withdrawal.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185245","185245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35161","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will estimate the cost to the Exchequer of exempting the state pension from income tax.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185136","185136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35162","2014-01-29","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of changes in the revenue accrued to the Exchequer (a) to date, (b) by 31 March 2014 and (c) by 31 March 2015 as a result of changes to the top rate of income tax from 50 pence to 45 pence in the pound.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185127","185127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35163","2014-01-29","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect changes in pensions contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at HEO and equivalent grades in his Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185221","185221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35164","2014-01-29","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect the change in pension contributions has had on the take-home pay of officials at Grade 7 and equivalent grades in his Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185225","185225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35165","2014-01-29","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at AO, LO2 and equivalent grades in his Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185226","185226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35166","2014-01-29","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at AA and equivalent grades in his Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185230","185230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35167","2014-01-29","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at EO, LO1 and equivalent grades in his Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185234","185234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35168","2014-01-29","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at SEO and equivalent grades in his Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185237","185237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35169","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will investigate the potential effect on business of HSBC's policy of limiting the amount customers can withdraw in cash.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185246","185246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35170","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many businesses have been compensated for being missold interest rate hedging agreements to date.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185158","185158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35171","2014-01-30","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the speech delivered to the Mile End Group by the Permanent Secretary to the Treasury on 15 January 2014 represents the policy of the Government.","Biography information for Sir Bernard Jenkin","Mr Bernard Jenkin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185190","185190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35172","2014-01-29","HM Treasury","2014-01-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect changes in pensions contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at senior civil service grades in his Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185219","185219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35173","2014-01-29","Church Commissioners","2014-01-27","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, for what reasons the Church Commissioners found the previous Bishop's accommodation at the Bishop's Palace at Wells to be unsuitable for the new Bishop and his wife.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185267","185267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35174","2014-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has, other than monetary provision, to empower local authorities to further tackle unscrupulous landlords.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185266","185266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35175","2014-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received on the decision to withdraw the local welfare provision grant in 2015-16; and what consultation he undertook prior to making that decision.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185294","185294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35176","2014-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, by what date he expects to have made full payments to local authorities in respect of small business rate relief for the 2013-14 financial year.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185295","185295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35177","2014-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the successful bidder in the competition to purchase the lease for the site of his Department's Sea Mounting Centre at Marchwood, in New Forest East, will be required to make a full planning application for any change of use; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185299","185299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35178","2014-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185304","185304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35179","2014-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each such contract following the contract award.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185217","185217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35180","2014-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that grants paid under section 31 of the Local Government Act 2003 can be paid to local authorities promptly during the 2014-15 financial year.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185273","185273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35181","2014-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the overall fairness of both the level of charge and the enforcement procedure of penalty charge notices issued on behalf of local authorities.","Biography information for Mr Lee Scott","Mr Lee Scott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185214","185214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35182","2014-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that the deadline to complete works at a quarry and restore it to nature is strictly adhered to without extensions.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185125","185125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35183","2014-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that electrical installation work undertaken by tradespeople in homes meets minimum safety standards.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185115","185115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35184","2014-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what evidence his Department is collecting on the effect of changes to Part P of building regulations covering domestic electrical work adopted in April 2013.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185119","185119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35185","2014-01-29","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will assess the effect on overall awareness of electrical safety due to changes to Part P of the building regulations covering domestic electrical work made in April 2013.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185120","185120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35186","2014-01-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much money the Arts Council spent per head of population in the District of Walsall in (a) 2013 and (b) 2012.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185123","185123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35187","2014-01-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the £250 million additional funding for superfast broadband rollout to achieve 95 per cent coverage will be delivered.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185239","185239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35188","2014-01-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps to ensure that superfast broadband is made available to the village of Braybrooke in Kettering constituency.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185205","185205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35189","2014-01-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she has agreed any voluntary scheme for improved player protection with betting companies; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185156","185156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35190","2014-01-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will set out her Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185305","185305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35191","2014-01-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Arts Council spent per head of the population in the district of Birmingham in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185259","185259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35192","2014-01-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Arts Council spent per head of the population in the district of Dudley in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185260","185260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35193","2014-01-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Arts Council spent per head of the population in the district of Wolverhampton in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185261","185261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35194","2014-01-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much the Arts Council spent per head of the population in the district of South Staffordshire in (a) 2012 and (b) 2013.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185262","185262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35195","2014-01-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent assessment she has made of the level of promotion of food and drink products to (a) child and (b) adult users of online computer games.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185285","185285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35196","2014-01-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the number of (a) children under the age of 16, (b) adults over the age of 60 and (c) people in total who have taken part in a swimming session in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185286","185286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35197","2014-01-29","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, who the recipients were of match funding provided by her Department and administered by the Creative Skillsets Creative Industry Fund since May 2010.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185265","185265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35198","2014-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many applicants to the Army were aged (a) 17, (b) 16 and (c) under 16 years of age at the time of submitting their application in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185255","185255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35199","2014-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether self-harming or suicidal ideation among disaffected armed forces personnel are grounds for medical discharge; and whether he has received legal advice on this matter.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185253","185253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35200","2014-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trainee soldiers who enlisted in financial year 2012-13 at (a) Army Foundation College (Harrogate) and (b) Infantry Training Centre (Catterick) subsequently dropped out before the completion of phase two training.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185254","185254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35201","2014-02-04","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the funding streams his Department has to the Afghan government; what the purposes are for the funding in each case; what steps he is taking to ensure that such funds are used by the Afghans for the intended purposes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185296","185296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35202","2014-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185306","185306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35203","2014-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date his Department allocated funding to permit the contract process to begin for the North Uist air defence radar upgrade.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185276","185276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35204","2014-01-30","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date his Department decided that money would need to be allocated to fund the upgrade of the air defence radar on North Uist.","Biography information for Angus Brendan MacNeil","Mr Angus Brendan MacNeil","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185277","185277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35205","2014-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to (a) help (i) Army families not eligible for final tour of duty allowance and (ii) other Army families cover the cost of moving out of service families accommodation and into civilian homes and (b) reduce the time between the end of service date and pension and resettlement payments.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185213","185213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35206","2014-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to (a) provide access to training and funding for training for returning service personnel and (b) help spouses of returning service personnel return to work or access training.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185212","185212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35207","2014-01-29","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure service children returning from Germany are not disadvantaged in applications for school places.","Biography information for Lord Campbell of Pittenweem","Sir Menzies Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185211","185211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35208","2014-01-30","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-27","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, which individuals and organisations will accompany him on his forthcoming visit to Colombia.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185191","185191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35209","2014-01-29","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-27","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, if he will set out his Office's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185307","185307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35210","2014-01-29","Department for Education","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185308","185308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35211","2014-01-30","Department for Education","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much capital funding has been allocated to each local authority for basic need for the 2011-17 period.","Biography information for Dr Thérèse  Coffey","Dr Thérèse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185159","185159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35212","2014-01-30","Department for Education","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the proportion of children of foreign nationals who are enrolled for school but do not attend; and what assessment he has made of the (a) quality and (b) reliability of information received by (i) his Department and (ii) schools from the Immigration Service and other agencies on the whereabouts and wellbeing of such children.","Biography information for Andy McDonald","Andy McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185197","185197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35213","2014-01-29","Department for Education","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to reduce funding gaps between schools (a) in the County of Staffordshire and (b) in the local authority areas of Wolverhampton, Dudley, Walsall and Birmingham.","Biography information for Gavin Williamson","Gavin Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185122","185122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35214","2014-01-29","Department for Education","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of poor behaviour and absenteeism on pupil attainment.","Biography information for Mary Macleod","Mary Macleod","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185114","185114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35215","2014-01-29","Department for Education","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of how schools can best support pupils to pursue further education and careers in STEM subjects.","Biography information for Mary Macleod","Mary Macleod","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185179","185179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35216","2014-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he is taking ahead of the anticipated cold weather.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185165","185165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35217","2014-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each such contract following the contract award.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185218","185218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35218","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many buildings owned by (a) central government departments or agencies and (b) local government have received finance under the Green Deal to date.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185274","185274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35219","2014-01-29","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their the 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185309","185309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35220","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what meetings (a) he and (b) officials in his Department have held in which the requirement that energy companies carrying out fracking need the permission of homeowners to drill beneath their houses was discussed.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185249","185249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35221","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if the Government will take steps to ensure that energy companies carrying out fracking cannot drill beneath homes without the homeowners' consent.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185248","185248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35222","2014-01-30","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the Government's policy is towards permitting fracking operators to drill under land belonging to homeowners.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185247","185247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35223","2014-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185310","185310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35224","2014-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of onshore wind farms on (a) the tourism industry and (b) house prices in rural areas.","Biography information for Glyn Davies","Glyn Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185300","185300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35225","2014-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when his Department plans to publish the findings of its review entitled Household Food Security - a Literature review of Food Aid.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185324","185324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35226","2014-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will list all staff seconded to his Department from private water companies since May 2010; and what the (a) period, (b) terms and (c) duties of those secondments were.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185334","185334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35227","2014-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether any staff have been seconded to his Department from Thames Water since 31 May 2010.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185335","185335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35228","2014-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether any staff seconded to his Department from a private water company since 31 May 2010 worked on (a) water reform policy and (b) the Water Bill currently before Parliament.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185336","185336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35229","2014-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what level of vetting and security clearance is applied to staff seconded to his Department from the private sector.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185331","185331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35230","2014-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department takes to guard against any potential commercial or other conflicts of interest involving staff seconded to his Department from the private sector.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185337","185337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35231","2014-01-30","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether staff seconded to his Department from a private water company have contributed to submissions to Ministers.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185338","185338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35232","2014-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether any staff seconded to his Department from private water companies since 31 May 2010 have advised or worked on issues relating to the Thames Tideway Tunnel.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185332","185332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35233","2014-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will list all staff seconded to his Department from a private water company since 31 May 2010; what the level of pay and remuneration of such staff was; and whether they were funded from the public purse or by their private sector employer.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185333","185333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35234","2014-01-29","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether the National Farmers' Union is underwriting any part of the costs of the badger cull.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185202","185202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35235","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the political unrest in Ukraine.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185160","185160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35236","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Thailand on the recent violence and state of emergency in that country; and what assessment he has made of the effect of this situation on the general election due to be held on 2 February 2014.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185192","185192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35237","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on establishing more marine reserves in UK Overseas Territories.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185193","185193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35238","2014-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at EO, LO1 and equivalent grades in his Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185232","185232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35239","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will list the hon. Members who have stayed at the Residence in (a) Paris, (b) Berlin, (c) Rome and (d) Madrid since May 2010; on what date each such visit took place; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185244","185244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35240","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the safety and whereabouts of Abbas Yazdi; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185279","185279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35241","2014-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2014, Official Report, column 340W, on EU High Representative for Foreign Affairs and Security Policy, on what date he used the aeroplane charted by the European External Action Service; and for what purpose.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185210","185210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35242","2014-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at AO, LO2 and equivalent grades in his Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185227","185227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35243","2014-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at AA and equivalent grades in his Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185231","185231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35244","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received of continuing sexual violence by the Burmese Army against women in Burma; and what assessment he has made of the report by the Women's League of Burma contained in Same Impunity, Same Patterns, that over 100 women have been raped by the Burmese Army since the election of 2010.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185328","185328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35245","2014-02-04","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will list the funding streams his Department has to the Afghan government; what the purposes are for the funding in each case; what steps he is taking to ensure that such funds are used by the Afghans for the intended purposes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185297","185297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35246","2014-01-29","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185311","185311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35247","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the (a) Home Office, (b) the Law Officers' Departments and (c) the Serious Fraud Office on the disappearance of Abbas Yazdi.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185280","185280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35248","2014-01-30","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the UK, through the Preventing Sexual Violence Initiative, has had with the Women's League of Burma.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185283","185283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35249","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 January 2014, Official Report, column 347W, on fast food, which Ministers attended the meetings on (a) 7 March 2013 and (b) 5 July 2013; and what was discussed at each such meeting.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185287","185287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35250","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 January 2014, Official Report, column 83W, on radiotherapy, what the tarriff paid for stereotactic radiosurgery treatment is by local commissioners in each English region.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185256","185256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35251","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 March 2013, Official Report, column 248W and 21 January 2014, Official Report, column 148W, on radiotherapy, whether the stereotactic ablative radiotherapy (SABR) consortium will be part of the review team examining the clinical and cost effectiveness of SABR.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185258","185258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35252","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 21 January 2014, Official Report, column 148W, on radiotherapy, from where the clinical reference group will gather its evidence to examine the clinical and cost effectiveness of stereotactic ablative radiotherapy.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185257","185257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35253","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185313","185313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35254","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions patients from other areas were admitted to in-patient psychiatric facilities run by NHS Cumbria due to a shortage of beds elsewhere in the last 12 months for which figures are available; and from which trust areas these patients were transferred.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185293","185293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35255","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will take steps to enable local authorities to exempt patients on home dialysis from the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185242","185242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35256","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average time waiting to be seen is for GP appointments in (a) Birmingham South Central clinical commissioning group and (b) clinical commissioning groups in England.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185240","185240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35257","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the effects of trans fats on public health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185284","185284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35258","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to (a) improve awareness of stem cell transplants for treating cancers and (b) increase registration of stem cell donors.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185215","185215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35259","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether households which do not receive a Better information means better care leaflet will be able to seek legal redress against GPs who have acted as data controllers for their practice and uploaded patient information to care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185199","185199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35260","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many dialysis units in England provide the full range of treatments for end stage renal failure.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185188","185188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35261","2014-01-30","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what measures are in place to monitor the performance of renal units in managing kidney transplant recipients.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185189","185189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35262","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had about the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence's appraisal of ipilimumab for use as a first line treatment for advanced melanoma in the light of the high incidence of melanoma amongst young people.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185209","185209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35263","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had on the availability and development of innovative treatments for melanoma with (a) the Christie NHS Foundation Trust, (b) other specialist cancer centres, (c) NHS England and (d) the National Institute for Health and Care Excellence.","Biography information for Mr John Leech","Mr John Leech","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185208","185208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35264","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with whom is data held by the Health and Social Care Information shared; and for what purpose.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185201","185201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35265","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether individuals whose medical confidentiality has been breached by the caredata programme will be notified of their eligibility for compensation.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185117","185117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35266","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2014, Official Report, column 227W, on abortion, how many doctors have been challenged to defend their judgment that grounds for an abortion were met; and how many such doctors had their decision overturned in each of the last 30 years.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185162","185162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35267","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people with (a) long term conditions and (b) osteoarthritis currently have a personalised care plan.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185168","185168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35268","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to promote comprehensive fracture liaison services.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185169","185169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35269","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has given to local authorities on assessing the effect of musculoskeletal conditions on their local population, including the effect of musculoskeletal conditions in joint strategic needs assessments.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185170","185170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35270","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding the Action on Smoking and Health charity received from his Department in 2013-14; and what assessment he has made of how these funds have been spent.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185126","185126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35271","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether households which have opted out of receiving bulk, junk or unaddressed mail will receive a Better information means better care leaflet.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185177","185177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35272","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that all individuals living in (a) shared accommodation, (b) care homes, (c) residential homes, (d) blocks of flats or apartments (e) university halls of residence and (f) prisons will receive an individual copy of the Better information means better care leaflet.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185181","185181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35273","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when NHS England's review into Stereotactic Radiosurgery (SRS) will be published; whether the SRS Clinical Reference Group assisted in writing this review; and which other stakeholders were consulted by NHS England during this review's production.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185130","185130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35274","2014-01-29","Department of Health","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether individuals will be notified if their personal data has been provided to researchers with identifying details provided under care.data.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185131","185131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35275","2014-01-29","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will review the fee for a firearms certificate.","Biography information for Harriett Baldwin","Harriett Baldwin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185175","185175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35276","2014-01-29","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions have been secured for wildlife crimes and trafficking offences at UK airports in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185172","185172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35277","2014-01-29","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what effect the changes in pensions contributions have had on take-home pay of officials at HEO and equivalent grades in her Department compared with May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185220","185220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35278","2014-01-30","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the oral Answer of 27 January 2014, Official Report, column 638, on police recruitment, if she will place the letter to HM Inspector of Constabulary on an all-force inspection on the welfare of vulnerable people in custody with particular reference to people with mental health conditions and people from Black and minority ethnic backgrounds in the Library.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185207","185207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35279","2014-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when she intends to implement a ban on pornography depicting rape.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185275","185275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35280","2014-01-29","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at SEO and equivalent grades in her Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185236","185236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35281","2014-01-29","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at SEO and equivalent grades in her Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185235","185235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35282","2014-01-29","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at Grade 7 and equivalent grades in her Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185224","185224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35283","2014-01-29","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at AO, LO2 and equivalent grades in her Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185228","185228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35284","2014-01-29","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at EO, LO1 and equivalent grades in her Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185233","185233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35285","2014-01-29","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at AA and equivalent grades in her Department compared to May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185229","185229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35286","2014-01-29","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what effect changes in pension contributions have had on the take-home pay of officials at senior Civil Service grade in her Department compared with May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Michael McCann","Mr Michael McCann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185238","185238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35287","2014-01-29","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will set out her Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185314","185314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35288","2014-01-30","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish her Department's strategy to reduce the number of animals used in medical experimentation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185282","185282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35289","2014-01-30","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she intends to include a target for the number of scientific experiments conducted on animals in her Department's strategy for reducing the number of animals used in medical experimentation.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185281","185281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35290","2014-01-30","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) standard and (b) enhanced disclosure Criminal Record Bureau checks were requested in 2013.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185278","185278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35291","2014-01-29","Department for International Development","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will set out her Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185315","185315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35292","2014-02-04","Department for International Development","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will list the funding streams her Department has to the Afghan government; what the purposes are for the funding in each case; what steps she is taking to ensure that such funds are used by the Afghans for the intended purposes; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185298","185298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35293","2014-01-29","Department for International Development","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to tackle trachoma in the developing world.","Biography information for Susan Elan Jones","Susan Elan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185176","185176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35294","2014-01-29","Department for International Development","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department are taking to ensure that people with disabilities are able to benefit equally from UK aid programmes and have a voice in international development.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185171","185171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35295","2014-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many staff in the Prison Service have been on deferred duty in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185135","185135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35296","2014-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what effect the delay in Probation Trust termination orders to 1 June 2014 will have on the tax liabilities of Trusts and Community Rehabilitation companies.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185154","185154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35297","2014-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidance his Department has issued to the judiciary relating to road traffic fatality cases; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185121","185121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35298","2014-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what targets community rehabilitation companies will be set under the Transforming Rehabilitation programme.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185203","185203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35299","2014-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much was spent on (a) travel, (b) accommodation and (c) subsistence costs for deferred duty cover for staff in the Prison Service each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185161","185161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35300","2014-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many students in receipt of legal aid had their payments (a) reduced or (b) halted as a result of also receiving childcare grants since changes made under the Legal Aid, Sentencing and Punishment of Offenders Act 2012.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185268","185268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35301","2014-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185316","185316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35302","2014-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many years Lin Mu Yong served in prison in the UK for his part in the Morecambe Bay cockle pickers disaster; and when he was deported to China.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185327","185327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35303","2014-01-29","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what information his Department holds on whether Lin Liang Ren, who served part of his sentence in the UK after being convicted for his part in the Morecambe Bay cockle pickers disaster, is currently incarcerated in China.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185326","185326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35304","2014-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what year Lin Liang Ren was deported to China following his conviction relating to the Morecambe Bay cockle pickers disaster; and how many years of his sentence he had served in the UK before that deportation.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185329","185329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35305","2014-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many years Zhao Xiao Qing served in prison in the UK for his part in the Morecambe Bay cockle pickers disaster; and when he was deported to China.","Biography information for David Morris","David Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185330","185330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35306","2014-01-29","Northern Ireland Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, if she will set out her Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185317","185317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35307","2014-01-29","Prime Minister","2014-01-27","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will set out No. 10 Downing Street's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185318","185318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35308","2014-01-29","Scotland Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185319","185319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35309","2014-01-29","Department for Transport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185320","185320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35310","2014-01-29","Department for Transport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Public Service Vehicles (Carrying Capacity) Regulations 1984 are meaningfully upheld; and what steps he is taking to ensure that infringements of overcrowding regulations are prosecuted.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185264","185264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35311","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the funding allocation is for Highways Agency route based strategies in Oxfordshire.","Biography information for Baroness Blackwood of North Oxford","Nicola Blackwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185194","185194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35312","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what total funding is allocated to Highways Agency route based strategies.","Biography information for Baroness Blackwood of North Oxford","Nicola Blackwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185195","185195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35313","2014-01-30","Department for Transport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the funding allocation is for Highways Agency route based strategies in the South East.","Biography information for Baroness Blackwood of North Oxford","Nicola Blackwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185196","185196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35314","2014-01-29","Department for Transport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had about the effect of High Speed 2 on tourism and waterways in (a) the UK and (b) Eddisbury and Cheshire West.","Biography information for Mr Stephen O'Brien","Mr Stephen O'Brien","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185216","185216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35315","2014-01-29","Department for Transport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much his Department has provided to each local authority for the repair of potholes in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185173","185173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35316","2014-01-30","Wales Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will place in the Library all assessments of new policy and legislation from his Department since January 2013 which give due consideration to the UN Convention on the Rights of the Child.","Biography information for Mr Elfyn Llwyd","Mr Elfyn Llwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185204","185204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35317","2014-01-29","Wales Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185322","185322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35318","2014-01-29","Women and Equalities","2014-01-27","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if she will set out the Government Equalities Office's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185312","185312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35319","2014-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect on the Government's equality policies of information from the 2011 census relating to the employment, education and health prospects of Gypsies and Travellers.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185206","185206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35320","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department has issued to Job Centre Plus staff on targets for the number of sanctions placed on jobseekers; and if he will place in the Library a copy of any such guidance.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185182","185182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35321","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what target or limit is set on the maximum distance a new claimant of personal independence payment must travel to an assessment centre.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185183","185183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35322","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department takes to ensure that people who stop claiming employment and support allowance are removed from the system to prevent the public purse being charged for fraudulent appointments.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185200","185200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35323","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of the Workchoice programme in getting disabled people into work.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185157","185157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35324","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent progress he has made on My Benefits Online; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185243","185243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35325","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects My Benefits Online to be completed; how much it will cost in total; and what proportion of the budget has been spent to date.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185241","185241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35326","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what target or limit is set as the maximum time a new claimant for personal independence payment must wait to receive an assessment date.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185174","185174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35327","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 23 January 2014, Official Report, column 264W, on employment and support allowance (ESA), if he will confirm whether it is correct that his Department does not keep precise records of assessments carried out by companies such as Atos but instead relies on a representative sample; whether the sample of ESA cases is provided by Atos or selected by his Department; and what steps he takes to ensure that this sample is accurate and representative.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185178","185178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35328","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints about (a) staff behaviour, (b) contested sanction decisions and (c) telephone line waiting times have been made by residents of Heywood and Middleton constituency about local Jobcentre Plus offices in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185167","185167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35329","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will mark the 40th anniversary of the Health and Safety at Work etc. Act 1974.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185155","185155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35330","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of (a) the cost to the Exchequer of the Government's contribution to an auto-enrolment pension scheme, (b) the number of people enrolled and (c) the average contribution by employees and employers in each year to 2018-19.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185134","185134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35331","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will assess whether jobseeker's allowance claimants who are sanctioned are more likely to find employment afterwards.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185132","185132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35332","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, under what conditions new personal independence payment claimants are granted a home assessment.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185112","185112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35333","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new personal independence payment (PIP) claims have been made since the inception of PIP; and how many such claims were (a) assessed at an assessment centre, (b) assessed at home and (c) have not yet been assessed following a claim made more than six months ago.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185113","185113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35334","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time personal independence payment claimants (a) able to travel to an assessment centre and (b) awaiting a home assessment have to wait to be given an assessment date is.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185116","185116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35335","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of social housing tenants in wheelchair-standard properties affected by the implementation of the under occupancy penalty also qualify for and receive disability living allowance.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185291","185291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35336","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have been affected by his Department's decision to time-limit contributory employment and support allowance (ESA) to one year; how many claimants are entitled to means tested ESA after their entitlement to contributory ESA has expired; and how much his Department expects to save by time-limiting contributory ESA to one year.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185288","185288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35337","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the cumulative effects of its policies on disabled people in (a) Birkenhead constituency, (b) the Metropolitan Borough of Wirral and (c) the UK since May 2010.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185289","185289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35338","2014-01-30","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of social housing tenants affected by the implementation of the under occupancy penalty live in wheelchair-standard properties.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185290","185290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35339","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of social housing tenants affected by the implementation of the under occupancy penalty in wheelchair standard properties have been given exempt status.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185269","185269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35340","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has allocated in discretionary housing payments to cover the effects of the implementation of the under occupancy penalty on social housing tenants.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185272","185272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35341","2014-01-30","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many households will lose eligibility for the reimbursement for costs of servicing essential home adaptations under universal credit.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185292","185292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35342","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of disabled social housing tenants affected by the implementation of the under occupancy penalty have downsized to a smaller property.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185271","185271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35343","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of social housing tenants affected by the implementation of the under occupancy penalty have downsized to a smaller property.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185270","185270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35344","2014-01-29","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will set out his Department's priorities for discussions with the European Commission over their 2014 Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185323","185323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35387","2014-01-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with the BBC Trust on political impartiality.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902301","902301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35500","2014-01-30","Home Office","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent progress the Government has made in eradicating forced marriage.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902282","902282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35690","2014-01-30","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the contribution of tourism to the British economy.","Biography information for Mr Tobias Ellwood","Mr Tobias Ellwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902288","902288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/35862","2014-01-30","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate she has made of the number of women in prison.","Biography information for Valerie  Vaz","Valerie Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902276","902276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34951","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what forecast his Department has made of (a) the amount spent on student loans for students at private colleges in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15 and (b) the RAB charge for such loans.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185071","185071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34952","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's forecast underspend of DEL was for the years 2013-14 and 2014-15 at the time of the Autumn Statement.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185072","185072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34953","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects to issue the Skills Funding Agency funding letter.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185073","185073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34954","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he expects to issue the Higher Education Funding Council for England funding letter.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185074","185074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34955","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps (a) Royal Mail and (b) Post Office Limited are taking to tackle scam mail in its mail deliveries.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185075","185075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34956","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what action Post Office Limited has taken with regard to the customer with prepaid account number HQ 50456 regarding concerns over scam mail fraud.","Biography information for Nick Gibb","Mr Nick Gibb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185076","185076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34957","2014-01-29","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have had with (i) the World Sugar Research Organisation, (ii) Sugar Nutrition UK and (iii) British Sugar since May 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185056","185056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34958","2014-01-28","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on an EU-level non-financial reporting law that would require all large companies to report on the effect of their supply chains on people and the environment.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185093","185093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34959","2014-01-28","HM Treasury","2014-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people were in receipt of child benefit in (a) Jarrow constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) the North East and (d) the UK in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185146","185146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34960","2014-01-28","Cabinet Office","2014-01-24","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what number of leasehold properties was revealed in the 2011 Census.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185033","185033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34961","2014-01-28","HM Treasury","2014-01-24","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total amount of stamp duty accruing from leasehold property transactions has been in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 185034","185034"
