"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786975","2017-11-15","Department for Education","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what support her Department has provided to local authorities to aid recruitment of teachers and temporary supply teachers.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112288","112288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786976","2017-11-15","Department for Education","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the White Paper, Educational Excellence Everywhere, published in March 2016, what the timetable is for the launch of the national teacher vacancy website; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112377","112377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786977","2017-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what travel and health advice his Department is providing to British citizens visiting Madagascar since the outbreak of plague on that island.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112270","112270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786978","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the NHS is planning to take any steps in response to the outbreak of plague in Madagascar; and what assessment his Department has made of potential risks to public health in the UK related to that outbreak.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112271","112271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786979","2017-11-14","Home Office","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps are being taken at UK borders to prevent any dangers to public health relating to the outbreak of plague in Madagascar.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112269","112269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786980","2017-11-14","Department for International Development","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department has offered to the Government of Madagascar since the outbreak of plague on that island.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112272","112272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786981","2017-11-14","Department for Transport","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to release the business case which has been put to Transport for London on the future of Crossrail 2.","Biography information for Sir Edward Davey","Sir Edward Davey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112273","112273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786982","2017-11-14","Department for International Development","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the cost to the public purse was of the visit to Kenya by the Secretary of State for International Development on 7 to 8 November 2017.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112422","112422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786983","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assistance his Department plans to give to users of the GP at Hand service who need to visit a GP face-to-face.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112427","112427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786984","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of whether there is greater potential for misdiagnosis of patients using the GP at Hand service than there is in a face-to-face appointment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112426","112426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786985","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the cost to the public purse of the GP at Hand service.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112428","112428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786986","2017-11-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to protect social media users' privacy from social networks while using video and microphone equipped devices.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112388","112388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786987","2017-11-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the cost of retrofitting sprinkler systems to residential tower blocks.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112339","112339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786988","2017-11-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support home ownership among people with poor or no credit history.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112340","112340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786989","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will undertake an evidence-based review into the association with and effect of abortion on the psychological and mental health of women that draws on (a) UK and (b) international research; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112337","112337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786990","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to ensure that studies on abortion that are (a) funded and (b) supported by his Department do not omit women who are at higher risk of complications from abortion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112338","112338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786991","2017-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to end personal independence payment reassessments for people with incurable conditions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112203","112203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786992","2017-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the criteria are for successful applications by local authorities for funding from the Government's Clean Air Fund.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112328","112328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786993","2017-11-14","HM Treasury","2017-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Transport on introducing a targeted diesel scrappage scheme.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112326","112326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786994","2017-11-14","HM Treasury","2017-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with (a) local authorities and (b) Cabinet colleagues on increasing the level of funding available for the maintenance and installation of electric vehicle infrastructure.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112325","112325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786995","2017-11-14","HM Treasury","2017-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on reforming vehicle excise duty banding to include harmful nitrogen dioxide emissions.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112327","112327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786996","2017-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made an assessment of the potential benefits to waterways management of the proposals by the Inland Waterways Association to transfer management of the waterways from the Environment Agency to the Canal and River Trust.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112204","112204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786997","2017-11-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what representations his Department has received on electricity and gas suppliers increasing standing charges to customers who have reduced their consumption of electricity or gas.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112241","112241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786998","2017-11-14","Home Office","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications have been received by her Department for the discretionary 12 months leave to remain visa for survivors of the Grenfell Tower fire.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112395","112395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786999","2017-11-14","Home Office","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many of the total number of applications for a 12 months leave to remain visa made under her Department's discretionary policy for survivors of the Grenfell Tower fire have been received from people who (a) already had an outstanding asylum claim, (b) were already known either to her Department or the local authority and (c) had spouses who have immigration status within the UK.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112391","112391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787000","2017-11-14","Home Office","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if the Government will carry out a comprehensive national audit of local authorities that are volunteering to take in unaccompanied refugee children; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112316","112316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787001","2017-11-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department plans to implement a policy to encourage or mandate the retro-fitting of sprinklers into high-rise buildings; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112315","112315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787002","2017-11-14","Home Office","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the potential merits of (a) amending or (b) extending the discretionary immigration policy for Grenfell Tower fire immigration cases beyond the end of November 2017.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112314","112314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787003","2017-11-14","Home Office","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government plans to provide additional financial assistance for successful applicants under the discretionary 12 months leave to remain visa for survivors of the Grenfell Tower fire to make any further immigration applications.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112313","112313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787004","2017-11-14","Home Office","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will lift the requirement that applicants to participate in the Dubs scheme be under 18-years olds at 20 March 2016.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112311","112311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787005","2017-11-14","Home Office","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many meetings have been held between Ministers and civil servants of her Department and representatives from the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea on the introduction of the discretionary 12 months leave to remain visa for survivors of the Grenfell Tower fire; when such meetings took place; who attended such meetings; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112312","112312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787006","2017-11-14","Home Office","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether legal assistance will be provided to unaccompanied children who are seeking to apply to live in the UK under the Dubs scheme.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112317","112317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787007","2017-11-14","Home Office","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many children the Government plans to accept into the UK under the Dubs scheme by the end of 2017; and how many of those children will be children with disabilities.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112318","112318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787008","2017-11-15","Department of Health","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that patients are able to receive treatment in (a) hospitals and (b) primary care settings in the event of a cyber attack.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112221","112221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787009","2017-11-15","Department of Health","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps have been taken (a) since the WannaCry cyberattack in May 2017 to improve IT security in NHS organisations and (b) to ensure that NHS organisations update their IT systems.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112222","112222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787010","2017-11-15","Department of Health","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps have been taken to educate NHS staff on how to minimise vulnerability to cyberattacks.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112223","112223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787011","2017-11-14","Department for Transport","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many instances of number plate fraud have been recorded in England and Wales in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112341","112341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787012","2017-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, where each University Service Unit is in the UK.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112450","112450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787013","2017-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the budget was for each University Service Unit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112448","112448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787014","2017-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many University Service Units there are in the UK by service.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112449","112449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787015","2017-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many naval assets have visited Northern Ireland in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112447","112447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787016","2017-11-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to support 16 to 21-year olds leaving social care who are not eligible for housing benefit and become homeless.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112279","112279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787017","2017-11-14","Department for Transport","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to update regulations relating to taxi and private hire vehicles; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112195","112195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787018","2017-11-14","Department for Transport","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of establishing a central UK-wide register of taxi and private hire vehicle drivers.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112196","112196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787019","2017-11-14","Department for Transport","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the safety of people using taxi and private hire vehicles as a result of the 2015 changes to the rules on cross-border taxi and private hire vehicle use.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112197","112197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787020","2017-11-14","Department for Transport","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of taxi and private hire vehicles which are working cross-border despite having their licences revoked by a local licensing authority.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112198","112198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787021","2017-11-14","Department for Transport","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to put in place additional measures to empower local licensing authorities to ensure public safety in taxi and private hire vehicles.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112199","112199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787022","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) total and (b) average value of properties escheated to the Crown Estate has been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112372","112372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787023","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average length of time is for properties to remain subject to escheat under the Crown Estate.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112373","112373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787024","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many properties have been subject to escheat under the Crown Estate in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112369","112369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787025","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount of land covered by properties escheating to the Crown Estate.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112370","112370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787026","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many properties escheating to the Crown Estate were disposed of in each year since 2000.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112371","112371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787027","2017-11-14","Scotland Office","2017-11-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with Scottish Enterprise on plans to boost productivity in the Scottish Borders.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112434","112434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786159","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2017 to Question 108244, on Prosperity Fund, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of Prosperity Fund projects on gender equality in developing countries.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111886","111886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786160","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 23 October 2017 to Question 108244, on Prosperity Fund, what strategy he has for Prosperity Fund programmes explicitly to tackle issues of gender inequality in developing countries as required by the International Development Act 2002.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111887","111887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786161","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether he plans to consolidate responsibility for criminal records disclosure into a single department as recommended by the Justice Select Committee report on the disclosure of youth criminal records, published on 17 October 2017, HC 416.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111893","111893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786162","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the proposed Borderlands Growth Deal on the economies of (a) the Borderlands area, including Berwickshire, Roxburgh and Selkirk constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111866","111866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786163","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average length of time for valuations appeals was in each of the valuation offices marked for closure by 2023 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111905","111905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786164","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with Howard Quayle, Chief Minister of the Isle of Man, on tax refunds to private jet owners.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111906","111906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786165","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with Appleby since the release of the Paradise Papers.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111908","111908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786166","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with Howard Quayle, Chief Minister of the Isle of Man, on the implementation of the EU Savings Directive.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111909","111909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786167","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has made an estimate of the scale of tax avoidance in the (a) overseas territories and (b) Crown Dependencies.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111910","111910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786168","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to launch a public inquiry into tax (a) avoidance, (b) evasion and (c) transparency in the Crown Dependencies and UK overseas territories.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111911","111911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786169","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in East Renfrewshire constituency paid the (a) top, (b) higher and (c) basic rate of income tax in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111960","111960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786170","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in East Renfrewshire constituency earn over £24,000 per annum before tax.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111961","111961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786171","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 110432, on tax evasion, how many staff were employed in the (a) High Net Worth Unit and (b) Affluent Unit in the month proceeding the merger.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112013","112013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786172","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to provide supportive housing for adults with learning disabilities whose parents have died or who are unable to care for their children on account of age or infirmity.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111933","111933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786173","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to identify the number of private renters who are evicted for rent arrears and in receipt of local housing allowance; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111938","111938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786174","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2017 to Question 109732, for what reasons there is a disparity between reference to discussions occurring with recognised trade unions throughout the year in the text of that Answer and the lack of recorded meetings in the documents provided in links to that Answer.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111999","111999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786175","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of directly employed staff of (a) his Department, (b) its executive agencies and (c) its non-departmental public bodies are paid at least the real living wage.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112000","112000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786176","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with counterparts in the Scottish Government on improving digital connectivity in the Scottish Borders.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111864","111864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786177","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Military and Security Cooperation Agreement signed with Saudi Arabia in September 2017 covers the (a) transfer of any equipment to the Saudi Armed Forces or National Guard and (b) stationing of any additional UK civil servants or military personnel in Saudi Arabia; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111860","111860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786178","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many British (a) personnel and (b) amphibious bridging vehicles are planned to take part in Exercise Full Throttle; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111861","111861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786179","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what changes have been made to the Defence Medical Information Capability Programme in relation to (a) regular and (b) reserve personnel since 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111862","111862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786180","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 8059, on Yemen: military intervention, of the 293 incidents logged as alleged international humanitarian law violations reportedly conducted by the Saudi-led coalition in Yemen since March 2015, what proportion involved dynamic targeting.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111884","111884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786181","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 4 July 2017 to Question 2038, on armoured fighting vehicles, when he plans to make an investment decision on the number of vehicles to be upgraded under the Warrior Capability Sustainment programme and the timetable for the agreement of a manufacturing contract.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111956","111956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786182","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of square miles of territory freed from Daesh control as a result of military activity by ground forces supported by International Coalition airstrikes in (a) Iraq and (b) Syria.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111929","111929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786183","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of people freed from Daesh control as a result of military activity by ground forces supported by International Coalition airstrikes in (a) Syria and (b) Iraq.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111931","111931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786184","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 24 July 2017 to Question HL863, what the reasons were for the delays to the Warrior Capability Sustainment Programme; and when that programme will be completed.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111962","111962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786185","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people work at NSA/NRO Menwith Hill; and how many of those people are (a) US Army, Navy, Air Force and Marines, (b) US contractors, (c) US civilians, (d) NSA, (e) NRO, personnel, (f) US CIA, (g) British military, (h) RAF personnel, including the RAF Liaison Officer, (i) his Department's personnel, (j) GCHQ personnel, (k) British contractors and (l) British civilians.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112002","112002"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786186","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the cost of development and upgrading of USAF Fairford will be; and who will bear that cost.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112003","112003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786187","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many requests for direct admission to an academy of a looked-after child  she received in the academic year 2016-17.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112004","112004"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786188","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that all schools have a policy for the care of pupils with Type 1 diabetes.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111939","111939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786189","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109743, how much of the £26 million of funding to expand breakfast club provision will be spent in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111964","111964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786190","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109743, how many pupils will benefit from the plans to expand breakfast club provision in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111965","111965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786191","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109401, how many of the schools formerly within the Wakefield City Academies Trust have been placed with new trusts.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111966","111966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786192","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109401, what evidence she has to suggest that the publication of the ESFA report into Wakefield City Academies Trust would be obstructive to the process of ensuring all the schools are placed with new trusts; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111967","111967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786193","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many children attending schools in the London Borough of Southwark have been taken out of school (a) to undergo female genital mutilation abroad or (b) for a forced marriage abroad in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111920","111920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786194","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, on what day she plans to respond to the Fourth Report of the Education Committee, Evidence check: Grammar Schools, Session 2016-17, HC 780.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111925","111925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786195","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of people not being offered jobs after the completion of apprenticeship; and what assessment she has made of the most common reasons for those people not being offered jobs.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111912","111912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786196","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Children and Families of 6 November 2017, on free childcare, Official Report, column 1183, which journalists that Minister was referring to.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111897","111897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786197","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 24 April 2017 to Question 71222, on children's centres: closures, what criteria her Department uses to measure the planned increase in efficiency of local council services as a result of the closure of Sure Start centres.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111899","111899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786198","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Children and Families of 6 November 2017, on free childcare, Official Report, column 1182, what plans her Department has to introduce a mechanism to allow early years settings to provide detailed information on the reasons underlying the costs of nursery provision.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111898","111898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786199","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the 2,730 fully agreed commitments for apprenticeships for under 19 year olds for May to July 2017 as reported by her Department at 31 July 2017 registered through the National Apprenticeship Service will receive an additional payment due to the fact they are taking on apprentices that have been in the care of the local authority.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111900","111900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786200","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the 5,820 fully agreed commitments for apprenticeships for under 19 to 24 year olds for May to July 2017 as reported at 31 July 2017 registered through the National Apprenticeship Service will receive an additional payment due to the fact they are taking on apprentices that have been in the care of the local authority.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111901","111901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786201","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many achievements were recorded for care leavers aged under 25 for (a) intermediate, (b) advanced and (c) higher level apprenticeships in the academic years (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111903","111903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786202","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeship programme starts awarded to care leavers at (a) intermediate, (b) advanced and (c) higher level apprenticeships there were in (i) 2014-15 and (ii) 2015-16 and (iii) 2016-17.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111904","111904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786203","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to (a) publish and (b) implement the eligibility criteria for free schools meals under universal credit; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112008","112008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786204","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the criteria will be for eligibility for the pupil premium after the roll-out of universal credit has been completed.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112009","112009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786205","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions officials of her Department have had with (a) families and (b) staff affected by the collapse of Wakefield City Academies Trust on the new trusts with which the schools will be placed; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112010","112010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786206","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to identify environmental protections which may require additional legislation when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111937","111937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786207","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with UK beet sugar farmers on the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the UK beet sugar industry.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112011","112011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786208","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the UK beet sugar industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112012","112012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786209","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to support the interests of British food producers in the negotiations on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111953","111953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786210","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to reduce indoor air pollution and the associated public health effects of household pollutants.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111954","111954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786211","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the economic contribution of the British sugar beet industry to the East of England.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111955","111955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786212","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Answer of 21 November 2017 to Question 53422, on Islamic State: war crimes, what evidence has been gathered and preserved by the UN.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111930","111930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786213","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the outcome was of discussions he had with his Iranian counterpart after charges were brought against Nazanin Zaghari Ratcliffe by the Iranian Revolutionary Court on 4 November 2017.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111896","111896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786214","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assistance his Department gave to the Secretary of State for International Development during his visit to Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112029","112029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786215","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he or Ministers of his Department became aware of the visit of the Secretary of State for International Development to Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112026","112026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786216","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Cabinet colleagues routinely inform him about any meetings they might have with foreign government ministers and officials.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112054","112054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786217","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether Government Ministers are routinely accompanied by Government officials when they meet foreign government ministers and officials.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112055","112055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786218","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he first became aware that the Secretary of State for International Development was meeting Israeli Government Ministers and officials.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112056","112056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786219","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he became aware of the Secretary of State for International Development's discussions with Israeli Government Ministers and officials on potential Government aid to the Israeli Defence Force.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111984","111984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786220","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to prohibit smoking on the grounds of hospitals, health centres and other NHS buildings in England.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112062","112062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786221","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to implement the recommendation in the Independent Mental Health Taskforce's Five Year Forward View for Mental Health on the need for more thorough capturing of data.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112063","112063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786222","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on the development of medical indemnity insurance for GPs.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111940","111940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786223","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 110827, if his Department will commit to monitor the average duration of transfers of care.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111963","111963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786224","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve the identification and management of Lynch syndrome.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111889","111889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786225","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to promote awareness and early diagnosis of bowel cancer.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111891","111891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786226","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted via accident and emergency with a primary diagnosis of dislocation, fracture, joint injury or amputation in each month of the financial years (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15, (f) 2015-16 and (g) 2016-17.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111881","111881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786227","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients were admitted via accident and emergency with a primary diagnosis of a muscle or tendon injury in each month of the financial years (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14, (e) 2014-15, (f) 2015-16 and (g) 2016-17.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111882","111882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786228","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on whether clinical commissioning groups have made deductions from NHS Continuing Healthcare payments for patients in receipt of a personal health budget.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112014","112014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786229","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received on clinical commissioning groups placing a cap on NHS Continuing Healthcare packages.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112015","112015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786230","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has received reports of clinical commissioning groups refusing to pay for NHS Continuing Healthcare home care packages if they exceed the cost of a care home place by more than 10 per cent.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112017","112017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786231","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people who have been returned to their homes on condition of receiving medication after having been detained under the Mental Health Act 1983 do proceed to take that medication.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111935","111935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786232","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many more NHS endoscopies will be performed annually by 2020 by the clinical endoscopists being trained through the accelerated training programme.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111915","111915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786233","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical endoscopists have been trained as part of the accelerated training programme.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111916","111916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786234","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of any risks to the health of 16 to 18-year olds that may be caused by voting.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111907","111907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786235","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical endoscopy cohorts have completed training in 2017 as part of the accelerated training programme.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111917","111917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786236","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of children under the age of 18 living in the London Borough of Southwark who have (a) undergone female genital mutilation in the UK, (b) undergone female genital mutilation abroad and (c) been subjected to a forced marriage in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111921","111921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786237","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many UK citizens returning to the UK after joining Daesh in (a) Syria and (b) Iraq have been (i) interviewed under caution and (ii) charged with criminal offences.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111928","111928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786238","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any non-human primates that were previously housed at the Max Planck Institute in Tübingen, Germany, which was the subject of an investigation and forced to end its research on non-human primates earlier in 2017, have been received in the UK between December 2016 and present.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112016","112016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786239","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, by what date she expects that the Government will have fulfilled its commitment to transfer 480 children under the Dubs scheme.","Biography information for Alex Burghart","Alex Burghart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111895","111895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786240","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with the National Police Chiefs Council on additional funding requirements for counter-terror policing; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111941","111941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786241","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she discussed with Israeli Government Ministers or officials on her visit between 13 and 25 August 2017 any issues that are not her Departmental responsibility.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112053","112053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786242","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she discussed any of her Department's business in her meetings in Israel in August 2017; and whether Lord Polak attended any of those meetings.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111979","111979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786243","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if any of the meetings she held in Israel between 13 and 25 August 2017 were organised using email accounts or stationary provided by Parliament or her Department.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111978","111978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786244","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she informed colleagues of her discussions with Israeli Government Ministers and officials on potential Government aid to the Israeli Defence Force.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111985","111985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786245","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether Lord Polak accompanied her to all or any of her  meetings in Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111980","111980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786246","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she had any meetings or communications with any official from the British Embassy in Israel between 13 and 25 August 2017.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111981","111981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786247","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what advice she has received on whether use of official development assistance for the Israeli Defence Force would meet the terms of the International Development Acts.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111987","111987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786248","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the context was of her discussions with Israeli Government Ministers and officials on potential Government aid to the Israeli Defence Force; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111986","111986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786249","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her meetings in Israel between 13 and 25 August 2017, what follow-up actions have been commissioned by her Department as a result of those meetings.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112031","112031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786250","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she informed the Permanent Secretary at her Department before her visit to Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112030","112030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786251","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what meetings, conversations, telephone calls or email exchanges she had with the Israeli Embassy in the UK prior to her visit to Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112027","112027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786252","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she had with Ministers of her Department about Middle East policy prior to her visit to Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112028","112028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786253","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she made the decision to visit Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112019","112019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786254","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she used her official departmental email account to arrange her visit to Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112020","112020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786255","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she used her parliamentary email account to arrange her visit to Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112021","112021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786256","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she used her office telephone to discuss arrangements for her visit to Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112022","112022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786257","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with officials of her Department before her August 2017 visit to Israel.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112023","112023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786258","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what advice she received from officials of her Department before her visit to Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112024","112024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786259","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will list all her meetings with representatives of the Government of Israel since June 2017 and the dates of each such meeting.","Biography information for Mike Gapes","Mike Gapes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112025","112025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786260","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to Question 7534, on legal aid scheme, whether he has looked more widely at the impact of recent policy changes on access to legal aid; and whether his Department will be taking steps to ensure that people in all regions can access legal aid providers.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111932","111932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786261","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2017 to Question 109713, on staff: probation, what the minimum level of staffing required by each community rehabilitation company is to meet its obligations of a sufficient level of staff.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112018","112018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786262","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to reduce the prevalence of the resale of tickets at inflated prices for theatrical, musical and other artistic performances.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111936","111936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786263","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of risk assessments for cell-sharing in prisons.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111952","111952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786264","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to answer the named day written question 107525 tabled on 12 October 2017.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111883","111883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786265","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in prison in England and Wales (a) requested and (b) received drug and alcohol treatment in each quarter for the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111869","111869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786266","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were litigants in person in England and Wales in each of the last five years in (a) civil and (b) criminal cases.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111870","111870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786267","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate the Government has made of the cost of the Client and Cost Management System in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111871","111871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786268","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much the Government has spent on the Client and Cost Management System in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111872","111872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786269","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of the calls received by the Mandatory Civil Legal Advice Gateway in each year since 2013 have been referred for face-to-face advice, for each category of advice.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111873","111873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786270","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many calls have been received by the Mandatory Civil Legal Advice Gateway in each year since 2013, for each category of advice.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111874","111874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786271","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of the Government funding for legal aid is spent on court fees.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111875","111875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786272","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people who lost their home after being recalled to prison in each quarter of the last five years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111876","111876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786273","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners aged (a) 60 to 69, (b) 70 to 79, (c) 80 to 89 and (d) over 90 have been sentenced to sentences of (i) six months or less, (ii) 12 months or less, (iii) two years or less and (iv) five years or less in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111877","111877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786274","2017-11-13","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the development of the Northern Irish ex-gratia support scheme for people affected by the contaminated blood scandal.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111923","111923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786275","2017-11-13","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what representations he has received from the (a) Regional Business Services Organisation, (b) former North Irish Executive and (c) Northern Irish political, parties on the (i) inquiry into the contaminated blood scandal and (ii) ex-gratia support for people so affected by that scandal.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111924","111924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786276","2017-11-13","Prime Minister","2017-11-07","To ask the Prime Minister, if she will ask the Cabinet Secretary to investigate the circumstances surrounding meetings held by the Secretary of State for International Development in Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111894","111894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786277","2017-11-13","Prime Minister","2017-11-07","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she has instructed the Cabinet Secretary to review the ministerial code.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112068","112068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786278","2017-11-13","Prime Minister","2017-11-07","To ask the Prime Minister, when she became aware of the Secretary of State for International Development's discussions with Israeli Government Ministers and Officials on potential Government aid to the Israeli Defence Force.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111983","111983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786279","2017-11-13","Prime Minister","2017-11-07","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she plans to strengthen the ministerial code as a result of the conduct of the Secretary of State for International Development in Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112066","112066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786280","2017-11-13","Prime Minister","2017-11-07","To ask the Prime Minister, when she first became aware of the visit to Israel and meetings with Israeli Ministers and officials by the Secretary of State for International Development","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112065","112065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786281","2017-11-13","Prime Minister","2017-11-07","To ask the Prime Minister, why she concluded that the Secretary of State for International Development had not broken the ministerial code following her meetings with members of the Government of Israel.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112067","112067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786282","2017-11-13","Prime Minister","2017-11-07","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she has received any advice about any potential breach of the ministerial code by the Secretary of State for International Development when she visited Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112064","112064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786283","2017-11-13","Prime Minister","2017-11-07","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she discussed the Secretary of State for International Development's meetings with Israeli Government Ministers and officials at her meeting with the Israeli Prime Minister on 2 November 2017.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112057","112057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786284","2017-11-13","Scotland Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with Ministers from the Scottish Government on ensuring that the UK and Scottish Governments work together to deliver the Borderlands growth deal.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111867","111867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786285","2017-11-13","Scotland Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with local authorities on the borderlands growth deal.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111863","111863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786286","2017-11-13","Scotland Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what the next steps are for the Borderlands Growth Deal.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111865","111865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786287","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on opening Carlisle airport to domestic flights as part of the proposed Borderlands Growth Deal.","Biography information for John Lamont","John Lamont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111868","111868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786288","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the Maritime and Coastguard Agency on the administration of the Certificate of Competency process for seafarers.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111885","111885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786289","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the average waiting time was for an oral examination required to obtain a seafarers' Certificate of Competency in the last 12 months; and what the average waiting time was for that exam in each of the previous 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111888","111888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786290","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent progress he has made on the Quality Bus Contract Scheme in West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112001","112001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786291","2017-11-13","Wales Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what bilateral meetings he has had with (a) Welsh and (b) UK Government Ministers to discuss valuation office closures in Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111902","111902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786292","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people living in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Southwark have been in receipt of guaranteed income payment in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111918","111918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786293","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people living in Camberwell and Peckham constituency have experienced a delay in receiving their universal credit payment in each of the last 12 years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111919","111919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786294","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 20174 to Question 110900, whether the information passed to local authorities and housing associations relates specifically to new universal credit claims.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111913","111913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786295","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that adults with schizophrenia and other permanent mental health conditions are made aware of their entitlement to claim the benefits to which they are entitled and assisted in making that claim.","Biography information for Sandy Martin","Sandy Martin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111934","111934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786296","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease have been transferred from disability living allowance to personal independence payment to date.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111958","111958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786297","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease have been placed in the personal independence payment no review required category.","Biography information for Stephen Lloyd","Stephen Lloyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111959","111959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786298","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 71 of the report by Demos entitled, Shopping for Good, if he will implement the recommendation to set up clear communication channels with local charity shop managers on the voluntary nature of placements.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111892","111892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786299","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Jobcentre Plus offices signpost clients to volunteer opportunities in charity retail from which they could gain employability skills.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111878","111878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786300","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking at (a) national and (b) regional level to support effective working relationships between jobcentres and charity retailers in the placement of volunteers in charity shops.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111879","111879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786301","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2017 to Question 110019, on universal credit, how many and what proportion of claimants transferring to other benefits took up their entitlement for an advance without a needs assessment.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111880","111880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786302","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, by what date his Department plans to complete its longitudinal study into former employees of Sahaviriya Steel Industries UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112061","112061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786303","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to facilitate the creation of more jobs in Leeds for young people.","Biography information for Alex Sobel","Alex Sobel","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111998","111998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786304","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to track the employment status of former employees of Sahaviriya Steel Industries UK to complete its study into the former employees of that organisation.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112060","112060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786305","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Camberwell and Peckham constituency are in receipt of universal credit.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112058","112058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786306","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that unspent funds allocated to the SSI taskforce remain available to that taskforce.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112059","112059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786307","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Intellectual Property Office report, Share and share alike, published on 20 July 2017, what steps are being taken to address intellectual priority infringement through social media.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111957","111957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786308","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to protect British companies who are planning to use their EU emissions trading system allowance provided in 2018 to meet their 2017 obligations.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111914","111914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786309","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the readiness of UK businesses to adopt fourth industrial revolution technologies, in particular (a) machine learning and (b) the Internet of Things.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111926","111926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786310","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to increase the adoption of digital technologies by UK businesses.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111927","111927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786311","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what progress has been made on allowing zero subsidy contract for difference on-shore wind farms in Scotland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111922","111922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786312","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect on non-UK citizens wishing to bring non-EU spouses into the UK of plans to make them subject to the same income requirements as British citizens once the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Ben Lake","Ben Lake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111890","111890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786313","2017-11-13","Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster","2017-11-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, what discussions he has had with the Duchy Council on the Queen's private estate being invested in a fund based in the Cayman Islands.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111857","111857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786314","2017-11-13","Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster","2017-11-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, what discussions he has had with the (a) Prime Minister and (b) Chancellor of the Exchequer on the Queen's private estate being invested in a fund based in the Cayman Islands.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111858","111858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786315","2017-11-13","Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster","2017-11-07","To ask the Chancellor of the Duchy of Lancaster, what information his Department holds on funds from the Queen's private estate being invested in a fund based in the Cayman Islands.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111859","111859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786316","2017-11-13","Attorney General","2017-11-07","To ask the Attorney General, how many times the Serious Fraud Office has requested beneficial ownership information from registers of beneficial ownership from the UK's Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies since 1 July 2017.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112101","112101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786317","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of Kuwaiti Bidoons resident in the UK.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112005","112005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786318","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure that 33 per cent of government contracts are given to small and medium-sized businesses by the end of the 2017 Parliament.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111993","111993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786319","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to ensure the accuracy of charity numbers data published by the Government Grant Information Service.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112172","112172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786320","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government Grant Information Service will standardise its use of the 360Giving format across all Government departments.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112173","112173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786321","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will set a deadline for the UK Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies to make public their central registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112180","112180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786322","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to bring into force Schedule 19 of the Finance Act 2016.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112181","112181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786323","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will bring forward legislative proposals so that a person engaged in tax avoidance is prohibited from preparing the skilled persons report under section 166 of the Financial Services and Markets Authority Act.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112081","112081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786324","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times HM Revenue and Customs has requested beneficial ownership information from registers of beneficial ownership from the UK's Overseas Territories and Crown Dependencies since 1 July 2017.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112100","112100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786325","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the level of (a) income tax and (b) National Insurance contributions paid to the public purse  by people under the age of 18 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112092","112092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786326","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a list of the number of successful and unsuccessful prosecutions mounted by HM Revenue and Customs for offshore tax evasion.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112079","112079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786327","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether any of the skilled persons reports submitted under section 166 of Financial Services and Markets Authority Act were prepared by a party engaged in tax avoidance schemes rejected by tax courts and tribunals.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112080","112080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786328","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a table showing the total value of tax relief given to companies for interest payments on borrowing from third parties, intragroup entities and related parties.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112076","112076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786329","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the tax relief given to companies and limited liability partnerships for insurance premiums in which they exercise significant control.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112077","112077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786330","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will appoint an independent commission to examine the tax avoidance schemes designed by PricewaterhouseCoopers.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112078","112078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786331","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish correspondence between his Department and the Government of Bermuda on its policy on beneficial ownership of companies.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112082","112082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786332","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many requests his Department has made to the Government of Bermuda for assistance in its investigation of offshore tax avoidance and evasion.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112083","112083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786333","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a list of the reports commissioned, and the costs of those reports, under section 166 of the Financial Services and Markets Authority Act for each of the last five years.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112084","112084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786334","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the amount accrued to the public purse in landfill tax in each of the last five years by region.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112140","112140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786335","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Oral Statement of 6 November 2017, Official Report, column 1222, to which universities the 26 student residential buildings that have been tested through the building safety programme and failed those tests belong; and what those buildings are.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112132","112132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786336","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Oral Statement of 6 November 2017, Official Report, column 1212, how many of the 26 student residential buildings that have failed tests through the building safety programme are owned by (a) universities and (b) others in the private sector.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112131","112131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786337","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take to ensure that people are not placed in temporary accommodation for more than the legal six weeks limit.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112099","112099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786338","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much funding from the public purse his Department has allocated to each coastal town from the Coastal Communities Fund in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112088","112088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786339","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department holds any responsibility for ensuring that all schools in England are aware of and compliant with the statutory guidance entitled, Supporting pupils with medical conditions at school.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111949","111949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786340","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she has taken to ensure that third sector organisations operating projects currently funded by the EU are able to bid for funding from the proposed UK Shared Prosperity Fund.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112175","112175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786341","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Digital Economy Act 2017, what guidance her Department has issued to providers of online social media platforms on their obligations to (a) report and (b) cooperate with the police on instances of serious digital abuse.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111945","111945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786342","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, when her Department plans to respond to the House of Lords Select Committee on Charities report of 2016-17 on Stronger charities for a stronger society, HL Paper 133.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112108","112108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786343","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure that the proposed UK shared prosperity fund will be open to bids from charity and voluntary organisations with a focus on social and community development.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112138","112138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786344","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what representations she has received from charities and social enterprises on improving procurement rules after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112139","112139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786345","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure that charity staff are paid at least the living wage.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112137","112137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786346","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-07","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential financial effect on charities of his Department's Making Tax Digital scheme; and if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of exempting charities from liability for VAT.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112174","112174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786347","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of using dormant assets, as identified by the Dormant Assets Commission, to help put charities on a more sustainable financial footing.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112171","112171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786348","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much funding her Department has provided to the Rugby Football League in each of the last 10 years; and on what projects that funding has been spent.","Biography information for Ms Marie Rimmer","Ms Marie Rimmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112142","112142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786349","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what support her Department is providing for small and medium-sized enterprises to prepare for the implementation of the (a) Data Protection Bill and (b) General Data Protection  Regulation.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112162","112162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786350","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with his NATO counterparts on locating NATO's North Atlantic command in the UK.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112047","112047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786351","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether officials of his Department in discussions with Saudi officials are critical of the actions and policies of the Saudi Government; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111947","111947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786352","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the apprenticeship training programmes which the Education and Skills Funding Agency quality approved six months ago are still (a) operational and (b) quality-approved.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111950","111950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786353","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many non-UK EU nationals employed as teachers in state schools have left that employment since 23 June 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111994","111994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786354","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question 109339, if she will take into account information from the independent published evaluation of early implementation on the income of families benefiting from the 30 free hours of childcare policy when assessing the effectiveness of that policy.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112074","112074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786355","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 September 2017 to question 9014, on sign language: GCSE, for what reason it is not Government policy to include British Sign Language as a GCSE; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112129","112129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786356","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the criteria is for a free school to be (a) closed and (b) merged with another school.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112151","112151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786357","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional financial support will be made available to schools that are rebrokered as a result of the collapse of Wakefield City Academies Trust.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112104","112104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786358","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in what circumstances her Department will intervene in the (a) financial management and (b) governance of multi-academy trusts in which concerns have been brought to her attention by reports of the Education and Skills Agency.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112103","112103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786359","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the enforcement of the welfare code on purpose-breeding of pheasants and partridges.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112149","112149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786360","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with other Departments on continued funding for EU structural and investment projects that provide strong value for money and are in line with domestic strategic priorities signed since the Autumn Statement 2016.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112141","112141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786361","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the  implications for his policies of the finding of the World Health Organisation's report, Preventing Noncomunicable Diseases by Reducing Environmental Risk Factors, published on 12 September 2017, (a) in general and (b) on the adverse health effects and premature mortality risks associated with indoor air pollution; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112118","112118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786362","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in the Irish Government on tackling the smuggling of puppies from the Republic of Ireland into the UK.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112121","112121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786363","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the supply of labour to the agriculture sector.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112036","112036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786364","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on a new migration system which will allow farmers to employ seasonal workers from other countries.","Biography information for Mr Alister Jack","Mr Alister Jack","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112039","112039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786365","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Iranian counterparts on the release of Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe since his Select Committee appearance on 1 November 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112044","112044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786366","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse was of translating and promoting the Prime Minister's speech in Florence on 22 September 2017 in (a) English, (b) German, (c) French, (d) Italian, (e) Spanish, (f) Polish, (g) Dutch and (h) any other languages.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112045","112045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786367","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the cost to the public purse was of his Department's advertising of the Prime Minister's speech in Florence on 22 September 2017 on (a) Facebook, (b) Twitter and (c) all other social media platforms.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112046","112046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786368","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Iranian counterpart on the case Nazanin Zahari-Ratcliffe since 4 November 2017; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112087","112087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786369","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when and how the British Embassy in Israel became aware of the meeting involving the Secretary of State for International Development and Israeli Government Ministers and officials and in Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111976","111976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786370","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when and how his Department first became aware of Secretary of State for International Development's meetings with Israeli Government Ministers and officials between 13 and 25 August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111977","111977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786371","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which of the Overseas Territories currently have (a) non-public and (b) public registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112102","112102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786372","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Government of the British Virgin Isles on (a) automatic exchange of beneficial ownership information with HM Revenue and Customs and UK law enforcement agencies and (b) a public central register of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112097","112097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786373","2017-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the rise of IS-affiliated groups in Yemen, Libya and North Africa.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112133","112133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786374","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what date the e-healthcare service procured as part of the London Sexual Health Transformation Programme is planned to go live; whether that date has been amended since the establishment of that programme's procurement process; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112168","112168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786375","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the contract value is of the e-healthcare service procured as part of the London Sexual Health Transformation Programme.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112169","112169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786376","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether an assessment has been made of the effectiveness of the implementation of the London Sexual Health Transformation Programme.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112170","112170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786377","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many births per full time equivalent NHS midwife there were in each region of England in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112134","112134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786378","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse was of training (a) one midwife and (b) all student midwives in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112135","112135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786379","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with (a) HM Prison Service, (b) the Secretary of State for Justice and (c) NHS England on funding for research into the provision of mental health services in prisons.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112089","112089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786380","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to allocate funding to the NHS to finance the lifting of the NHS pay cap.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112094","112094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786381","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 20 April 2017 to Question 71524, on NHS staff, what estimate he has made of the average cost to the NHS of employing one (a) nurse, (b) midwife, (c) doctor and (d) GP in 2016-17.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112112","112112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786382","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the funding per patient is awarded to Babylon Health as part of its GP appointment trial.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112146","112146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786383","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union on future immigration policy for nurses, midwives and other essential health workers.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112107","112107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786384","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many midwifery graduates there were in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Ellie Reeves","Ellie Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112136","112136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786385","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has he made of the adequacy of access to mental health services for children and young people in (a) Barnsley East constituency and (b) Barnsley; and will he make a statement.","Biography information for Stephanie Peacock","Stephanie Peacock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112128","112128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786386","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many training places for midwifery were (a) commissioned and (b) filled in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112152","112152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786387","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical endoscopists have been trained as part of the accelerated training programme.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111942","111942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786388","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of additional NHS endoscopies that will be performed annually by 2020 as a result of the additional number of clinical endoscopists in training under the accelerated training programme.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111943","111943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786389","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 111111, when he plans to respond to the resolution of the House of 13 September 2017, on NHS pay; and whether he plans to do so by means of an Oral Statement to the House.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112075","112075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786390","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were referred to mental health therapies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111968","111968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786391","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people entered mental health therapies in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111969","111969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786392","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of people in England entering talking therapies waited more than 18 weeks for their treatment to start in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111970","111970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786393","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many tests for sexually transmitted infections have been provided by the NHS in London in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112071","112071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786394","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of (a) research and (b) data on incidents of mental health issues in prisons.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112090","112090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786395","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how may prisoners were diagnosed with a mental health condition in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112086","112086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786396","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many online-ordered tests for sexually transmitted infections he estimates will be provided by the NHS in London in (a) 2017 and (b) each of the next five years.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112176","112176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786397","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to prohibit the promotion, sale and use of MMS chlorine dioxide bleach as a cure for autism.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112048","112048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786398","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to prohibit the promotion, sale and use of  Turpentine, GcMAF and Rerum as treatments for autism.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112049","112049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786399","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with Babylon Health on the criteria for that company to refuse to accept patients for the GP appointment trial.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112050","112050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786400","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Southwark have been diagnosed with autism in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112041","112041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786401","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children and young people aged under 19-years olds with autism spectrum disorder in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Southwark have waited longer than three months after referral to be diagnosed in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112042","112042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786402","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect of the non-availability of Lithyronine on the NHS on patients who have previously being prescribed that drug.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112033","112033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786403","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Education on guidance to (a) primary and (b) secondary schools on ensuring that they understand the difference between Type 1 and Type 2 diabetes and their responsibilities to children with medical conditions.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111948","111948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786404","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure Lithyronine sold by third parties meets legal requirements and its safe sale for patients to use.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112034","112034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786405","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the price of medication sold online by third parties.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112035","112035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786406","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many successful applications have been made in Crown Courts in England and Wales under section 41(2) of the Youth Justice and Criminal Evidence Act 1999 enabling defence lawyers to cross-examine rape complainants about their sexual history in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111944","111944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786407","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what tasks each strategic migration partnership are funded to undertake.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112032","112032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786408","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the contribution of police community support officers to crime prevention and neighbourhood policing.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112037","112037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786409","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether police and crime commissioners are required to consult the public on changes to their Police and Crime Plan within the plan's timeframe.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112038","112038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786410","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that immigration caseworkers fully comply with guidance on handling medical evidence for asylum seeker applications.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111951","111951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786411","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what evidence EU citizens not yet able to establish the five years' continuous residence necessary to obtain settled status but who were resident before the specified date will have to provide to ensure that they will be given temporary status.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112179","112179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786412","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people who already have indefinite leave to remain have had to apply to have their biometric resident permit card corrected due to an error on their documentation in England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111971","111971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786413","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the number of (a) stateless people resident in the UK and (b) applications her Department has received for leave to remain from a stateless person in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112006","112006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786414","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure UK residents are not being charged £1.37 a minute rate applied to non-UK residents over and above network charges to access her Department's spousal visa helpline.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111996","111996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786415","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average waiting time for people in England with indefinite leave to remain was to receive their returned corrected biometric documentation in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111972","111972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786416","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for (a) leave to remain and (b) further leave to remain were not decided within the target six month processing time in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112154","112154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786417","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what information she has received from the National Police Chiefs' Council on the total cost to Greater Manchester Police of the terrorist incident in May 2017; and what proportion of that cost was accrued by that force's budget.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112147","112147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786418","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2017 to Question 9634, on asylum, (a) when and (b) where the information on the number of people claiming asylum on the basis of sexuality or gender identity in each year since 2011 will be published.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112122","112122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786419","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-UK citizens in Glasgow South constituency will be required to apply for (a) settled and (b) temporary status as outlined in the Government's November 2017 technical note, citizens' rights, administrative procedures in the UK.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112120","112120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786420","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people living in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Southwark who have been detained for immigration purposes have successfully appealed her Department's asylum claim decision in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112119","112119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786421","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many decisions on applications for leave to remain and further leave to remain were made outside of her Department's six month processing target.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112085","112085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786422","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what funding her Department allocated to the strategic migration partnerships in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112093","112093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786423","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the number of 999 calls reaching the two-minute point and remaining unanswered in September (a) 2015, (b) 2016 and (c) 2017.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112161","112161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786424","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she used an email account other than that of an official parliamentary or departmental email account to organise meetings in Israel between 13 to 25 August 2017.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112158","112158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786425","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, who in her office organising her meetings in Israel between 13 to 25 August 2017; and if she will publish all communications related to the organisation of those meetings.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112157","112157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786426","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what projects her Department sponsors in Tunisia.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112115","112115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786427","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether an impact assessment has been conducted of the effect on projects sponsored by her Department in Yemen of the closure of ports and airports by the Saudi-led coalition.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112116","112116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786428","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to tackle the cholera outbreak in Yemen.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112117","112117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786429","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will publish all correspondence between her, Lord Polak, the Israeli authorities, her Permanent Secretary and her private office related to the meetings and events she conducted in Israel between 13 to 25 August 2017.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112155","112155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786430","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she used her parliamentary email address when organising meetings in Israel between 13 to 25 August 2017.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112156","112156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786431","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she plans to publish the details of her meetings with members of the Israeli Government and business people during her visit to Israel.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112150","112150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786432","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, who (a) organised and (b) paid for her travel to her meetings in Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111989","111989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786433","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she received any gifts at her meetings in Israel between 13 and 25 August 2017.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111990","111990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786434","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when she first informed her Department and the Foreign and Commonwealth Office about her meetings in Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111991","111991"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786435","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what declarations she made to her Department on the hospitality and services provided during her meetings and visits in Israel between 13 and 25 August 2017.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111973","111973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786436","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she informed her Department and the Foreign and Commonwealth Office of her visit to Israel between 13 and 25 August 2017 before she travelled to Israel.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111974","111974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786437","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, with reference to her meetings in Israel between 13 and 25 August 2017, what follow-up actions have been commissioned by her Department as a result of those meetings.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111992","111992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786438","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what meetings she has had since being appointed Secretary of State for International Development with Lord Polak; and whether Lord Polak has visited her Department in Whitehall.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111975","111975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786439","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues about providing aid to the Israeli Defence Force in the Golan Heights.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112007","112007"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786440","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, who made the arrangements for her visit and meetings in Israel between 13 and 25 August 2017.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111988","111988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786441","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the list of meetings that she published on 6 November 2017 was a complete list of the meetings and topics that took place during her visit to Israel in August 2017.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111982","111982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786442","2017-11-13","Department for International Development","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, at how many meetings during her visit to Israel she was accompanied by Lord Polak; and who was present at each meeting on that visit.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112177","112177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786443","2017-11-13","Home Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how a many domestic violence orders have been issued by courts to people in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Southwark in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112043","112043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786444","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of people living in (a) Camberwell and Peckham constituency and (b) the London Borough of Southwark who were in receipt of legal aid in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112040","112040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786445","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2017 to Question 108880, how many of the 10,000 planned new prison places will be (a) additional places that increase the total number of prison places or (b) replacement places for older cells no longer deemed fit for use.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112069","112069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786446","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many buildings sold by HM Courts and Tribunals Service since 2010 have been (a) listed with Historic England, (b) located in a conservation area and (c) classified as being of historic significance.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112070","112070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786447","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to respond to the consultation on reforming the advocates' graduated fee scheme which closed on 2 March 2017.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112130","112130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786448","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent estimate he has made of the number of prison officers required to maintain safe staffing levels in prisons.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112123","112123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786449","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Government's paper, Deaths of offenders in the community, published on 26 October 2017, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the incidents of deaths classified as self-inflicted of people under the supervision of community rehabilitation companies.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112148","112148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786450","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what is the average time taken to complete vetting processes for a prison officer recruit.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112124","112124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786451","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress his Department has made on plans to outsource the work of civilian enforcement officers employed by HM Courts and Tribunals.","Biography information for Jared O'Mara","Jared O'Mara","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112052","112052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786452","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the economic viability of criminal defence firms of proposed changes to the Litigators' Graduated Fee Scheme.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112144","112144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786453","2017-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on the recruitment and retention of criminal law practitioners as a result of the proposed changes to the Litigators' Graduated Fee Scheme.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112145","112145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786454","2017-11-13","Prime Minister","2017-11-07","To ask the Prime Minister, when she was shown the summaries of the sectoral analyses collated by the Department for Exiting the European Union; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112153","112153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786455","2017-11-13","Scotland Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what his Department's policy is on siting a possible NATO North Atlantic Command in Scotland.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112072","112072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786456","2017-11-13","Scotland Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with (a) the Prime Minister, (b) the Secretary of State for Defence and (c) other Cabinet colleagues on the siting of a possible NATO North Atlantic Command in Scotland.","Biography information for Martin Docherty-Hughes","Martin Docherty-Hughes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112178","112178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786457","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what criteria his Department has given to Transport for the North for the location of the (a) line and (b) stations on the Northern Powerhouse Rail.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112096","112096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786458","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many and what proportion of stations on the rail network do not have staff available to assist disabled passengers who arrive at a station without having made an advance booking.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111946","111946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786459","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the economic value of the East Coast Main Line to the UK economy.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112125","112125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786460","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what enhancement projects are planned for the East Coast Main Line in Control Period 6 in order to accommodate the forecast growth in passengers using that line.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112127","112127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786461","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the expected increase in passengers using the East Coast Main Line over the next 10 years.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112126","112126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786462","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Statement of Funds Available for Control Period 6, published on 12 October 2017, how much of the £47.9 billion of Network Rail expenditure will be allocated to investment in the upgrade of the East Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112091","112091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786463","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the planned £300 million infrastructure spending to connect Northern towns and cities with High Speed 2 will be allocated for strategic planning purposes in addition to certification purposes.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112095","112095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786464","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 110675, whether the announced £300 million of infrastructure spending related to Northern Powerhouse Rail will be devolved directly to Transport for the North.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112109","112109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786465","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 110675, whether the announced £300 million of infrastructure spending related to Northern Powerhouse Rail will be allocated including spending on connectivity to that project.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112110","112110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786466","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2017 to Question 110552, what discussions his Department has had with Transport for the North on connecting Leigh to the planned Northern Powerhouse Rail.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112111","112111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786467","2017-11-13","Department for Transport","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions his Department has had with Transport for the North on the route of the proposed Liverpool to Manchester line of the Northern Powerhouse Rail project.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112143","112143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786468","2017-11-13","Women and Equalities","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Written Statement of 23 October 2017, on equalities, HCWS192, whether her Department consulted with (a) Members of the Northern Ireland Assembly and (b) hon. Members on extending the Northern Ireland abortion scheme to include provision for free travel to an abortion provider in England for Northern Ireland residents from low income backgrounds before making that statement.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112163","112163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786469","2017-11-13","Women and Equalities","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Written Statement of 23 October 2017, on equalities, HCWS192, with which organisations she consulted on extending the Northern Ireland abortion scheme to include provision for free travel to an abortion provider in England for Northern Ireland residents from low income backgrounds before making that statement.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112164","112164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786470","2017-11-13","Women and Equalities","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Written Statement of 23 October 2017, on equalities, HCWS192, how many women her Department estimates will travel from Northern Ireland to England for an abortion in the (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20 and (d) 2020-21 financial years.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112165","112165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786471","2017-11-13","Women and Equalities","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Written Statement of 23 October 2017, on Equalities, HCWS 192, what the estimated annual cost is of providing a central booking service for the provisions of free travel to an abortion provider in England for Northern Ireland residents in the (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20 and (d) 2020-21 financial years.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112166","112166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786472","2017-11-13","Women and Equalities","2017-11-07","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what discussions has she had with the Equalities and Human Rights Commission on the number of (a) redundancies, (b) planned redundancies, (c) vacancies and (d) agency workers employed at the Commission; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111995","111995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786473","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish information on the geographical area covered by each Jobcentre Plus office.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112051","112051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786474","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 30 October 2017 to Question HL2020, on universal credit, whether an assessment has been made on the effect of the roll-out of universal credit on the number of jobs available for people in each parliamentary constituency; and if he will make an assessment of the effect of the roll-out of universal credit on the number of jobs available for people in Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland constituency.","Biography information for Mr Simon Clarke","Mr Simon Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112167","112167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786475","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 7 November 2017, Official Report, on the Royal Bank of Scotland: small business customers, to which practices of the Global Restructuring Group that Answer refers to.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112159","112159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786476","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Oral Answer of 7 November 2017, Official Report, on the Royal Bank of Scotland: small business customers, to which inquiry that Answer refers to.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112160","112160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786477","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department will be running a competition for carbon capture, utilisation and storage projects in the (a) oil, (b) gas and (c) coal sectors as well as the industrial sector; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111997","111997"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786478","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2017 to Question 110674, what the deadline is for making a decision on whether EU Structural and Investment projects that have been signed since the Autumn Statement 2016 meet the criteria for providing strong value for money and are in line with domestic strategic priorities.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112113","112113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786479","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many and which of the EU Structural and Investment projects that have been signed since the Autumn Statement 2016 will be guaranteed by the Government on the grounds that they provide strong value for money and are in line with domestic strategic priorities.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112114","112114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786480","2017-11-13","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps the Government is taking to ensure sustainable, long-term funding for the Police Intellectual Property Crime Unit.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112106","112106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786481","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, which countries he has visited on official business in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112098","112098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786482","2017-11-13","Department for International Trade","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what the dates of appointment and end of appointment are of the Prime Minister's special trade envoys.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112073","112073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/786483","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to ensure that adequate numbers of essential healthcare staff will continue to be recruited after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112105","112105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/787028","2017-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Government has received in charges levied by the Child Maintenance Service in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901854","901854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788749","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to provide additional funding to the NHS to finance the lifting of the NHS pay cap.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901825","901825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788750","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with NHS England on ensuring that the Northern Devon Healthcare Trust has adequate resources to deliver acute services at North Devon District Hospital.","Biography information for Peter Heaton-Jones","Peter Heaton-Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901824","901824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788751","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if his Department will end the policy of imposing financial penalties on local authorities which do not meet targets on transfers of care.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901823","901823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788752","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of NHS funding to meet patient need.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901822","901822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788753","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the use of hyper-acute stroke units on patient outcomes.","Biography information for James Duddridge","James Duddridge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901829","901829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788754","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made on the development of a state-backed indemnity scheme for GPs.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901831","901831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/788755","2017-11-14","Department of Health","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to community pharmacy budgets on the number of pharmacies.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901821","901821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789383","2017-11-15","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what steps the Government is taking to tackle paramilitary activity in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Craig Tracey","Craig Tracey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901700","901700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789384","2017-11-15","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what recent discussions he has had with political parties in Northern Ireland on equal marriage for same-sex couples.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901701","901701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/789385","2017-11-15","Northern Ireland Office","2017-11-07","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what progress has been made on restoring devolved government in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Alan Mak","Alan Mak","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 901702","901702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784760","2017-11-13","Attorney General","2017-11-06","To ask the Attorney General, which public telephone lines for the Law Officers Departments' services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111470","111470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784761","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111471","111471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784762","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department's 2013 guidance that ordered Departments to stop using higher-rate telephone lines for key services was ever revoked or updated.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111594","111594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784763","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 2 November 2017 to Question 109984, in public sector: cybercrime, if he will meet representatives of Deloitte to discuss the need for more timely reporting to Government.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111537","111537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784764","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of deaths in England caused by malnutrition in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111557","111557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784765","2017-11-15","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints have been received in relation to the Valuation Office's online system in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111706","111706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784766","2017-11-14","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the (a) average and (b) longest time taken to answer telephone calls from the public was at the Valuation Office in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111701","111701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784767","2017-11-14","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the proportion of (a) businesses whose lending and (b) funds lent to businesses which is regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111702","111702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784768","2017-11-14","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to extend the business lending element of the regulatory framework of the Financial Conduct Authority; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111703","111703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784769","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has assessed the effectiveness of the (a) Enterprise Investment Scheme and (b) Seed Enterprise Investment Scheme.","Biography information for Kit Malthouse","Kit Malthouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111582","111582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784770","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department or its executive agencies have had with the Welsh Government on the future of valuation offices in Wales.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111542","111542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784771","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's press release of 10 April 2016, entitled UK launches cross-government taskforce on the Panama Papers, how many leads the multi-agency taskforce is investigating; and how many of those leads have a direct link to the leaked documents relating to the operations of Mossack Fonseca.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111631","111631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784772","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Department's press release of 10 April 2016, entitled UK launches cross-government taskforce on the Panama Papers, how many full-time equivalent staff from each agency have been allocated to that taskforce; and whether any staff in that taskforce (a) have the power of arrest, (b) are authorised to access directly the contents of suspicious activity reports, (c) are able to request data on companies incorporated in foreign countries and (d) have powers fully to investigate any allegations of (i) non-compliance with sanctions, (ii) money laundering and (iii) terrorist financing.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111632","111632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784773","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) businesses and (b) people have accessed services at the Rhyl Valuation Office in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111680","111680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784774","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111487","111487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784775","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the annual savings to the public purse of limiting all personal pension contribution tax relief at the basic rate with contributions remaining unchanged.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111589","111589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784776","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many meetings he has had with (a) the University Alliance, (b) the Russell Group, (c) Universities UK and (d) MillionPlus in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111461","111461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784777","2017-11-20","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 7 September 2017 to Question 6591, on debts, what plans he has to implement a breathing space scheme.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111771","111771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784778","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has estimated the level of financial support that will be available to agriculture after 2022.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111738","111738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784779","2017-11-13","Cabinet Office","2017-11-06","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if the Government will implement a moratorium on those companies which are being investigated as a result of the Paradise Papers being awarded public sector contracts.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111733","111733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784780","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2017 to Question 110866, on HM Treasury, what types of query prompted the other 332 referrals to the Jointly Managed Engagement Team in September 2017.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111764","111764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784781","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111807","111807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784782","2017-11-13","HM Treasury","2017-11-06","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect reducing the top rate of tax from 50 per cent to 45 per cent has had on total tax receipts since 2012.","Biography information for Bim Afolami","Bim Afolami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111774","111774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784783","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111792","111792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784784","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 106036, on the United Kingdom Holocaust Memorial Foundation, how many and which of the organisations consulted in 2015 proposed or supported locating the memorial in Victoria Tower Gardens.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111729","111729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784785","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies on funding structures for short-term and long-term supported housing of the report by Rethink Mental Illness, Mental Health Supported Housing: Securing financial stability, supply and quality relating to the variety of length of stay of people within mental health supported housing.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111768","111768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784786","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Government's funding supported housing consultation, published on 31 October 2017, and the Government's proposal for a ring-fenced local grant fund for supported housing, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure that such ring-fenced funding will be maintained in the future.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111769","111769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784787","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 106036, on the United Kingdom Holocaust Memorial Foundation, whether the £50 million allocated from public funds is the full contribution from the public purse towards the capital and running costs of the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111731","111731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784788","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 16 October 2017 to Question 106036, on the United Kingdom Holocaust Memorial Foundation, for what reasons that Answer did not provide the date of the Government's decision on the learning centre's location in Victoria Tower Gardens.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111730","111730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784789","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Government's funding supported housing consultation, published on 31 October 2017, whether in the event that a tenant on a mental health supported housing scheme has an initial anticipated length of stay of less than two years, but this subsequently extends to more than two years within the same scheme, the Government proposes that such a tenant would move from one funding system to another.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111767","111767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784790","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate the Government has made of the proportion of visitors to the Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre who will arrive (a) on foot or by public transport and (b) by coach or car.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111707","111707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784791","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate the Government has made of the total cost to the public purse of the proposed Holocaust Memorial and Learning Centre.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111708","111708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784792","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2017 to Question 109734, on private rented housing: safety, whether he plans to undertake a consultation on the report and recommendations of the working group.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111500","111500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784793","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2017 to Question 109734, on private rented housing: safety, if he will place in the Library a copy of the minutes of the four meetings of the working group.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111501","111501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784794","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2017 to Question 109734, on private rented housing: safety, who the members of the working group are.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111502","111502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784795","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he  has to address the shortfall in mental health supported housing.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111453","111453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784796","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the current shortfall in mental health places in supported housing.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111454","111454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784797","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent assessment he has made of the number of children in temporary accommodation.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111516","111516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784798","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of people (a) served with a section 21 notice by a council or registered housing provider, who are universal credit claimants; and what information his Department holds on the number of people who have been served with such a notice as a result of delays in payment of a universal credit claim.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111546","111546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784799","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support people between 16 and 21 years old who are leaving social care but are not eligible for housing benefit.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111547","111547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784800","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111472","111472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784801","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2017 to Question 109734, on private rented housing: safety, if he will place in the Library a copy of the report and recommendations from the working group.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111496","111496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784802","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2017 to Question 106692, how many children who lived in Grenfell Tower are living in hotel accommodation as of 6 November 2017.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111603","111603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784803","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to his Department's consultation paper, Funding supported housing, published on 31 October 2017, whether the current projections of future need take account of population growth and demographic changes.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111593","111593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784804","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will introduce legislative proposals to prevent gazumping by compelling vendors to sell their properties to accepted bidders.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111624","111624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784805","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what support his Department provides to increase the number of modular housing built with timber frames.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111551","111551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784806","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 1 November 2017 to Question 109733, whether the Independent Review of Building Regulations and Fire Safety will include a review of the current guidance relating to safe means of exit for disabled residents in the event of an emergency.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111538","111538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784807","2017-11-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many (a) households and (b) children who previously lived in Grenfell Tower were still living in hotels or bed and breakfast accommodation as of 1 November 2017.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111568","111568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784808","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2017 to Question 109965, if she will place in the Library a copy of the letter sent to registered consultancies of the Government's Cyber Essentials scheme whose data was exposed owing to a configuration error in the Pervade Software platform.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111536","111536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784809","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has commissioned research on the prevalence of so-called fake news across social media and other internet platforms.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111685","111685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784810","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the contribution of access to superfast broadband services to trends in national productivity; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111686","111686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784811","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department has made an assessment of the cost to it of implementing additional measures to meet General Data Protection Regulation standards; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111687","111687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784812","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the average household spend on (a) internet, (b) landline and (c) mobile telephone contracts in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111688","111688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784813","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on changes to the short-term visa system to help support the needs of the creative industries.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111693","111693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784814","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of trends in the number of paid library staff on the quality of library services provided.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111691","111691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784815","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with representatives of the creative industries sector on the effect of the apprenticeship levy on that sector.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111692","111692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784816","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, which public telephone lines for her Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111474","111474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784817","2017-11-20","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what plans the Government has to commemorate the centenary of Armistice Day in November 2018.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111772","111772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784818","2017-11-13","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in her Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111794","111794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784819","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111793","111793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784820","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of staff working in the Bereavement and Aftercare Support Service have received training for their duties in that service since 2014; what training was provided; who delivered that training; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111719","111719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784821","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average length of service is for a Hawk T1 aircraft in a Red Arrows squadron.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111450","111450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784822","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the decision was made to extend the out-of-service date for the Red Arrows Hawk T1 aircraft to 2030.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111451","111451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784823","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reason the decision was made to extend the out-of-service date for the Red Arrows Hawk T1 aircraft to 2030.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111452","111452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784824","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to support armed services personnel and veterans who experience mental ill health.","Biography information for Mike Amesbury","Mike Amesbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111457","111457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784825","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations his Department has received from the Government of Turkey about that country's willingness to buy HMS Ocean if it is not sold to Brazil.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111467","111467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784826","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which organisations have responded to his Department's request for information as part of the bidding process for the Type 31e Frigate programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111468","111468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784827","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111473","111473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784828","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, to which countries his Department is supporting the sale of Typhoon aircraft; and to which countries such aircraft have already been sold.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111545","111545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784829","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his policy is on funding for the production of Captor-E active electronically scanned array radars; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111527","111527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784830","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he has taken to raise awareness amongst (a) serving, (b) reserve, and (c) families of service personnel of the work of the Bereavement and Aftercare Support Service since 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111509","111509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784831","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the training for casualty (a) notification and (b) visiting officers was last revised; whether a training needs analysis was conducted at the same time as that revision; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111510","111510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784832","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many welfare case officers have been appointed in the armed forces to support an individual on the Vulnerable Risk Management (VRM) system; and what changes to the VRM system his Department has made since 2014.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111511","111511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784833","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date the Army Drill Manual directions for military funerals were last revised; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111512","111512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784834","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what date he made it his policy to allow personal information to be passed from a Senior Medical Officer and a Regimental Medical Officer to civilian medical officers.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111513","111513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784835","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what changes have been made to his Department's guidance on insurance packages for reservists undertaking specialist forces training and selection since 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111514","111514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784836","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether a support mechanism has been developed with medical and welfare staff for the use of bereavement and aftercare support staff; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111645","111645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784837","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether his Department has conducted a review of its Welfare Groups examining the (a) relevance, (b) timeline and (c) methods by which information is delivered to families and next of kin following (i) bereavement and (ii) serious injury of (A) regular and (B) reserve personnel since 2013; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111644","111644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784838","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will undertake a review of access to information on the Special Forces by Parliament to enable effective scrutiny of those forces.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111620","111620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784839","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many air miles have been (a) earned by his Department's personnel flying on business, (b) collected by those personnel and (c) offset against his Department's business travel in the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111533","111533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784840","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2017 to Question 110561, on Joint Strike Fighter Aircraft, how many aircraft are planned to be in service with No. 617 Squadron RAF when the UK F-35 programme reaches initial operating capability.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111534","111534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784841","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much additional funding his Department has allocated to the Special Forces since the publication of the 2015 Strategic Defence and Security Review; and if he will make a statement on the delivery of that funding.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111621","111621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784842","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 3 November 2017 to Question 110561, on Joint Strike Fighter Aircraft, what the reasons are for initial commitments for integration of UK weapons on F-35 aircraft being funded through support funds instead of through initial procurement funds.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111535","111535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784843","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, for what reasons regular drug testing was not mandatory for the crews of Vanguard-class submarines before October 2017.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111628","111628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784844","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his current policy is on drug testing on all ships of the Royal Navy on operations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111629","111629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784845","2017-11-13","Ministry of Defence","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he is taking to recruit soldiers to the Army.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111625","111625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784846","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to allow parents to remove their child from relationships education classes in primary schools.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111583","111583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784847","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many and what proportion of children were eligible for free school meals in (a) York and (b) the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111581","111581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784848","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate she has made of the number of children in England who are eligible for free school meals and pupil premium but are not registered.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111683","111683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784849","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much pupil premium funding remained unclaimed in 2016-17.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111684","111684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784850","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department has available in its Annually Managed Expenditure Budget to provide financial cover for anticipated policy changes in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111604","111604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784851","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what statutory support is provided in schools for young people with mental health conditions.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111515","111515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784852","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many care leavers there were in (a) West Sussex and (b) Mid Sussex constituencies in 2015-16; and how many of those care leavers were not in education, employment or training at that time.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111544","111544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784853","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the effectiveness of steps taken by Oxford and Cambridge Universities to improve access and widen participation from under-represented groups; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111507","111507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784854","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which public telephone lines for her Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111475","111475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784855","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria her Department used to decide whether to intervene in the (a) financial management and (b) governance of multi-academy trusts as a result of concerns reported to her by the Education and Skills Funding Agency.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111463","111463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784856","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional financial support she plans to make available to schools that are rebrokered as a result of the collapse of Wakefield City Academies Trust.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111464","111464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784857","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what consultation has taken place between the families and communities served by schools that were previously in Wakefield City Academies Trust and the preferred sponsors identified by her Department.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111465","111465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784858","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many schools received a visit from a qualified and registered nutritionist in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111490","111490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784859","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the oral Answer from the Minister for Children and Families of 6 November 2017, on free childcare, what proportion of early years providers (a) can provide and (b) are outliers who are unable to deliver 30 hours of free childcare on Government funding.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111770","111770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784860","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 24 April 2017 to Question 71222, on children's centres: closures, how her Department defines the most disadvantaged people; and what steps she is taking to ensure that the most disadvantaged people are not affected by the closure of Sure Start centres.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111762","111762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784861","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Answer of 24 April 2017 to Question 71222, on children's centres: closures, how many people are currently served by a Sure Start centre.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111761","111761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784862","2017-11-13","Department for Education","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in her Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111795","111795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784863","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff appointed after 24 June 2016 in his Department hold a post that includes work on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111796","111796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784864","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which public telephone lines for his Department's services are charged at higher rates; and how much was taken by each such telephone line in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111476","111476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784865","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to his Department's press release of 24 October 2017, on new steps to tackle littering, whether he plans for funds raised from the increase in litter fines to  be used to tackle (a) fly-tipping on farmland and (b) other local environmental issues.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111611","111611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784866","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information his Department holds on the number of playgrounds which are within 150 metres of roads with above legal levels of air pollution.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111517","111517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784867","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to retain and protect meadowlands habitats in the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111639","111639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784868","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans he has to measure progress on achieving Sustainable Development Goal 2 on food insecurity in the UK.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111587","111587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784869","2017-11-13","Department of Health","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce farmers' suicide rates.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111642","111642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/784870","2017-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-11-06","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to retain and protect butterfly habitats.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111640","111640"
