"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625923","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to extend funding for maintained nursery schools beyond the two years indicated in the consultation on the Early Years National Funding Formula, published in August 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50975","50975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625924","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department has considered funding maintained nursery schools under the School National Funding Formula instead of the Early Years National Funding Formula.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50976","50976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625925","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of GCSE students studied creative subjects in the last five years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50977","50977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625926","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to respond to Questions (a) 48764, 48763 and 48762, tabled on 14 October 2016, (b) 48383, tabled on 12 October 2016, (c) 46707, tabled on 7 October 2016 and (d) 48933, tabled on 17 October 2016 by the hon. Member for Birmingham, Yardley.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51215","51215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625927","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the take-up of technology-based subjects in secondary schools.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51222","51222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625928","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to Answer Questions 48788, 48789 and 48790, tabled on 14 October 2016 by the hon. Member for Ellesmere Port and Neston.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51085","51085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625929","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many officials of her Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51129","51129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625930","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what incentives are in place for teachers to achieve early-years teaching status rather than qualified teaching status.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51169","51169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625931","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, for what reasons teachers with early-years teacher status do not have qualified teaching status.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51167","51167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625932","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what promotion opportunities are available to teachers with qualified teaching status but not to teachers with early-years teacher status.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51168","51168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625933","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) selective and (b) non-selective schools (i) she and (ii) the Minister for School Standards has visited since taking office.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51233","51233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625934","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the Government's policy is on whether schools with no religious character can be run by religious multi-academy trusts.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51242","51242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625935","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, in how many of the foster for adoption placements initiated since 25 July 2014 the children were looked after pursuant to a section 20 Children Act 1989 voluntary accommodation arrangement; how many of those children were subject to (a) care proceedings at the time that the fostering for adoption placement began and (b) a pre-proceedings process during which parents were entitled to legal advice under Regulation 5(1)(e) of the Civil Legal Aid (Financial Resources and Payment for Services) Regulations 2013.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51244","51244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625936","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many (a) looked after children and (b) care leavers have had a child placed in foster for adoption under section 22C(9A)-(9C) of the Children Act 1989; and how many of those children were voluntarily accommodated under section 20 of the Children Act 1989 at the time the placement commenced in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51245","51245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625937","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many of the looked after children who were cared for in a friends and family foster placement were placed there under a section 20 of the Children Act 1989 voluntary agreement (a) as at 31 March 2016 and (b) for each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51246","51246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625938","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many civil servants in her Department work primarily on policy and practice for child welfare and family justice; and how many of those civil servants work primarily on (a) adoption and (b) children in care (i) under a care order, (ii) under section 20 of the Children Act 1989 and (iii) kinship care.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51243","51243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625939","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people with a home postcode in (a) the West Midlands, (b) Birmingham and (c) Birmingham, Northfield constituency have undertaken an apprenticeship in each of the last 10 academic years.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51180","51180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625940","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many higher-education students are living in (a) Birmingham and (b) Birmingham, Northfield constituency.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51176","51176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625941","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase the take-up of humanities subjects in secondary schools.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51224","51224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625942","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many nominations for an appreciation letter for being an exceptional teacher on retirement her Department has received since 2010.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51276","51276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625943","2016-11-03","Department for Education","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many independent schools sponsor (a) academy schools, (b) free schools and (c) multi-academy trusts; and what the Ofsted grade is for each of those sponsored schools.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51277","51277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625944","2016-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with her French counterpart on that country's global initiative to increase carbon levels in soil.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51275","51275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625945","2016-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether it is her policy for the Government to remain part of the UN ECE Aarhus Convention regardless of the outcome of the UK's negotiations to leave the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51239","51239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625946","2016-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many officials of her Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51130","51130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625947","2016-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much the Government has paid from the public purse in compensation to farmers for animals culled in efforts to control bovine tuberculosis since 1998.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51165","51165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625948","2016-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many gamekeepers there were in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51070","51070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625949","2016-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the value of grouse-shooting to the UK economy was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51071","51071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625950","2016-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had on the potential merits of heather burning for countryside habitats.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51077","51077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625951","2016-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to improve the habitat for the green woodpecker.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51078","51078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625952","2016-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to improve the habitat for the grey partridge.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51079","51079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625953","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the government of Pakistan on the cases of Abdul Shakoor and Mazhar Sipra.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51044","51044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625954","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many officials of his Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51131","51131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625955","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which projects in Venezuela have received funds from the Conflict, Stability and Security Fund.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51145","51145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625956","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of Conflict Stability and Security funding in Israel supports Israel-Palestinian coexistence work.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51146","51146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625957","2016-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government's policy is on UK embassies, high commissions and consulates accepting donations from private companies and for hosting events.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51179","51179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625958","2016-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has made a request to participate in the Joint Incident Assessment Team investigation into the Sana's funeral hall attack in Yemen on 8 October 2016; and how many requests in total the Government has made to participate in such investigations.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51256","51256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625959","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the treatment of Christians in Syria.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51271","51271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625961","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to enable Christians to stay in Syria.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51269","51269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625962","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to enable Christians to stay in Iraq.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51270","51270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625963","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the treatment of Christians in Iraq.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51272","51272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625964","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, by what date he expects all UK Overseas Territories to have adopted central registers of beneficial ownership accessible to UK Law enforcement.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51267","51267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625965","2016-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what basis the home of Abdullah Adbo in the Al-Salw district of Taiz, and adjacent homes, were attacked by the Saudi-led coalition forces in Yemen on 28 or 29 October 2016; and when he expects to receive the report of the Joint Incident Assessment Team into that incident.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51229","51229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625966","2016-11-03","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what basis the prison complex within the Red Sea port of Hodeida was attacked by the Saudi-led coalition forces in Yemen on 29 October 2016; and when he expects to receive the report of the Joint Incident Assessment Team into that incident.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51230","51230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625967","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with leaders of UK Overseas Territories on publicly accessible central registers of beneficial ownership since his appointment.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51266","51266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625968","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44420, whether he has sought advice from Fertility Fairness on the improvement of in vitro fertilisation services.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51274","51274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625969","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of NICE's and NHS England's proposals for changes to the arrangements for evaluating and funding drugs and other health technologies appraised through NICE's technology appraisal and highly specialised technologies programme, published in October 2016, on the right to drugs and treatments that have been recommended by NICE for use in the NHS, as set out in the NHS Constitution.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51261","51261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625970","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 1.233 of the Budget 2015, how much of the £1.25 billion allocated to children and adolescent mental health services (a) has been and (b) is due to be allocated to Redditch constituency.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51254","51254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625971","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to NICE's and NHS England's proposals for changes to the arrangements for evaluating and funding drugs and other health technologies appraised through NICE's technology appraisal and highly specialised technologies programme, published in October 2016, what assessment he has made of the potential benefits of introducing a fast track NICE technology appraisal process for technologies with an incremental cost-effectiveness ratio of up to (a) £10,000 per quality adjusted life year (QALY) and (b) £30,000 per QALY.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51262","51262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625972","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many medicines approved through the highly specialised technologies programme to date had a budget effect above the threshold proposed in NICE's and NHS England's proposals for changes to the arrangements for evaluating and funding drugs and other health technologies appraised through NICE's technology appraisal and highly specialised technologies programme, published in October 2016.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51263","51263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625973","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to NICE's and NHS England's proposals for changes to the arrangements for evaluating and funding drugs and other health technologies appraised through NICE's technology appraisal and highly specialised technologies programme, published in October 2016, on what basis the affordability threshold of £20 million per year was arrived at.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51264","51264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625974","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how much and (b) what proportion of the total NHS budget was spent on imports in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51231","51231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625975","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential effect of recent changes in the exchange rate on NHS budgets for each of the next three years.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51232","51232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625976","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that medical research involving the use of animals is only being undertaken where there is no alternative.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51241","51241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625977","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of NICE and NHS England's proposals to change arrangements for evaluating and funding drugs and other health technologies appraised through NICE's technology appraisal and highly specialised technologies programme, published in October 2016, for patients with (a) rare and (b) ultra-rare diseases.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51257","51257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625978","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that NHS priority treatment for armed forces veterans is delivered by private health care providers when HNS services are contracted out to such providers.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51249","51249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625979","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he or officials of his Department have had with NHS England on the operation of its specialised commissioning prioritisation process in 2016.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51258","51258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625980","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons NHS England (a) proposed and (b) abandoned the introduction of a soft market testing exercise as part of its specialised commissioning prioritisation process in September 2016.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51259","51259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625981","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how health care professionals assess whether a veteran's illness or condition is related to service in the armed forces and therefore eligible for priority NHS treatment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51250","51250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625982","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether recommendations made by NHS England's Clinical Priorities Advisory Group on the basis of inaccurate costings provided by NHS England are subject to an appeals process.","Biography information for Crispin Blunt","Crispin Blunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51260","51260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625983","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many calls the NHS 111 helpline received from people experiencing mental illness in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51183","51183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625984","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions the NHS 111 helpline has made recommendations for people experiencing mental illness in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51184","51184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625985","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to page 317 of the NHS Digital report, Mental health and wellbeing in England, Adult Psychiatric Morbidity Survey 2014, published on 29 September 2016, if he will commission research into the causes of the increase in self-harming among young women.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51182","51182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625986","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he has given to clinical commissioning groups on the issuing of prescriptions for people diagnosed with coeliac disease; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51227","51227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625987","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to increase public awareness of mental health in Worcestershire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51190","51190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625988","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to talking therapies in Worcestershire.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51191","51191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625989","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Home Affairs on changes in the level of use of section 136 of the Mental Health Act 1983.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51214","51214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625990","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the average length of stay in hospital for people with (a) Alzheimer's disease and (b) dementia in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51199","51199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625991","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that mental health service practitioners routinely enquire about women's experience of violence and abuse as standard practice and offer appropriate support and pathways into care.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51197","51197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625992","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of children and young people being detained under section 136 of the Mental Health Act 1983 in police cells in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51213","51213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625993","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress his Department has made towards meeting the 2020 challenge on dementia in Worcestershire.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51198","51198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625994","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking in response to the findings of the Healthcare Quality Improvement Partnership response report, National Confidential Inquiry into Suicide and Homicide with Mental Illness: Making Mental Health Care Safer, published in October 2016.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51201","51201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625995","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to signpost mental health patients with financial difficulties to specialised support services.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51149","51149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625996","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to improve the services offered by crisis resolution and home treatment teams to reduce the number of patients who die by suicide while under that care.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51150","51150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625997","2016-11-02","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many referrals have been made by GPs to the Veterans and Reserves Mental Health programme in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51192","51192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625998","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44420, whether his Department has met Fertility Fairness to discuss fertility treatment in England.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51151","51151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/625999","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the equality impact assessment on the proposed reduction to staff levels in his Department.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51221","51221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626000","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many officials of his Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51132","51132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626001","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of high drug prices on NHS funding.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51143","51143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626002","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department has issued on acceptable waiting times for patients prescribed talking therapies by their GP.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51092","51092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626003","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of patients who have used mental health services in (a) Worcestershire and (b) Redditch in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51093","51093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626004","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what accountability mechanisms are in place for the scrutiny of decisions made by a clinical commissioning group's medicine management team.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50972","50972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626005","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients are receiving natural desiccated thyroid on NHS prescription.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50985","50985"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626006","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding provided to researching age-related macular degeneration.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50999","50999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626007","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many citizens of non-UK EU countries work in his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51005","51005"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626008","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the time it will take community pharmacies to make adequate preparations for planned changes to their funding.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51015","51015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626009","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that clinicians have the opportunity formally to engage in discussions on NHS sustainability and transformation plans.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51056","51056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626010","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that all NHS mental health trusts consider the needs of women in service planning and delivery; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51057","51057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626011","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has considered introducing refundable charges for GP visits.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51058","51058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626012","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Chinese government on safety standards for UK citizens travelling to China to have cosmetic surgery.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51072","51072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626013","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with medical companies on the potential merits of using 3D printers to help those with broken bones.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51074","51074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626014","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2016 to Question 41185, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that hospital-initiated postponement or cancellation of ophthalmology follow-up appointments do not result in sight loss.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51038","51038"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626015","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to improve access to specialist employment services for young disabled people.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51039","51039"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626016","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to make high definition cameras available on the NHS to detect and treat stomach cancer.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51076","51076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626017","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been paid out to each NHS sustainability and transformation plan footprint lead in (a) total and (b) each footprint area.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51067","51067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626018","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to improve knowledge and awareness among NHS staff on how to deliver the NHS Constitution's commitment on priority treatment for armed forces veterans.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51020","51020"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626019","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how NHS England ensures that every GP practice uses patient medical record codes to identify veteran status; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51019","51019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626020","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which person or body has overall ownership and copyright of Health Records in (a) England, (b) Wales, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51028","51028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626021","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve GP appointment waiting times.","Biography information for Sir Hugo Swire","Sir Hugo Swire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51068","51068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626022","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Mental Health Five Year Forward View Dashboard, when his Department plans to publish data relating to the indicator, clinical commissioning group spend on specialist perinatal community service.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51080","51080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626023","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Mental Health Five Year Forward View Dashboard, when his Department plans to publish data relating to the indicator, proportion of children and young adults showing reliable improvement in outcomes following treatment.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51081","51081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626024","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Mental Health Five Year Forward View Dashboard, when his Department plans to publish data relating to the indicator, proportion of children and young people aged 0 to 18 inclusive meeting their mutually agreed goals against the number of children and young pepple accessing services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51082","51082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626025","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Mental Health Five Year Forward View Dashboard, when his Department plans to publish data relating to the indicator, referral to perinatal mental health treatment waiting times for access to evidence-based care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51083","51083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626026","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Mental Health Five Year Forward View Dashboard, when his Department plans to publish data relating to the indicator, collection and recording of routine outcomes measures for perinatal mental health.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51084","51084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626027","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department is taking steps to make angioplasty available on the NHS to people with untreatable angina.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51069","51069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626028","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on the use of eculizumab to treat a patient with dense deposit disease at Evelina Children's Hospital.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51102","51102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626029","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the case of Abi Longfellow and her access to eculizumab for the treatment of dense deposit disease.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51103","51103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626030","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of whether current levels of social care provision are sufficient to support young disabled people living independently.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51099","51099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626031","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what average home-to-hospital journey time his Department uses as its benchmark for acceptable travelling time for patients using (a) accident and emergency and (b) maternity services.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51117","51117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626032","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the proportion of GP appointments that are currently used for diagnosing and treating mental health illness.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51118","51118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626033","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many non-UK born nurses have worked in the NHS and social care services in each year for which data has been collected.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51121","51121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626034","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) people enrolled as student nurses and (b) applications were received for such enrolment in each year for which data has been collected.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51122","51122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626035","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse has been of (a) capital and (b) private finance initiative projects in the NHS and social care services in England in each year for which data is recorded.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51123","51123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626036","2016-11-03","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many agency staff have been assigned to the NHS and social care services in England in each year for which data is available; and what the cost to the public purse of such staff has been in each such year.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51124","51124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626037","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has had discussions with Fertility Fairness on clinical commissioning groups' adherence to NICE guidelines on the provision of NHS funded infertility services.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51034","51034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626038","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the average waiting times for access to child and adult mental health services.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51043","51043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626039","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps are being taken to ensure continuity in the child sexual abuse inquiry.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51024","51024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626040","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, for how long and by what method young people are recorded onto the crime data integrity programme.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51033","51033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626041","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many tasers have been used by the police in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51075","51075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626042","2016-11-03","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which UK Sikh organisations she consulted in the development of her Department's publication, Action Against Hate: The UK Government's plan for tackling hate crime, published in July 2016.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51009","51009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626043","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many equality impact assessments her Department carried out in each year between 2010 and 2016.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50980","50980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626044","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance her Department has issued to caseworkers on issuing and renewing HC2 forms for asylum seekers.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50978","50978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626045","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will add care staff to the shortage occupation list.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51091","51091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626046","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many officials of her Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51133","51133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626047","2016-11-03","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans her Department has to maintain frontline police officer numbers in Cumbria under the revised funding formula.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51173","51173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626048","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to reply to the letter of 29 September 2016 from the Rt hon. Member for Warley on QA Liftrucks Ltd.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51188","51188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626049","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 October 2016 to Question 47816, if she will publish details of any (a) policy equality statement, (b) equality impact assessment and (c) equality monitoring that the Government has carried out on its contracts with Compass to provide accommodation to asylum seekers (i) prior to those contracts being signed in 2012 and (ii) in the years since those contracts were signed.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51208","51208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626050","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the list of vulnerabilities and warning signs tutors are advised to look out for as part of Workshop to Raise Awareness of Prevent training.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51247","51247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626051","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Prevent Strategy in countering radicalisation.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51248","51248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626052","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to stop thieves using software to override keyless car entry systems to steal vehicles and contents.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51236","51236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626053","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who from her Department was involved in the recruitment process for the appointment of Dame Lowell Goddard to the post of chair of the Independent Inquiry into Child Sexual Abuse; and what the names were of the people on the interview panel.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51273","51273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626054","2016-11-03","House of Commons Commission","2016-10-31","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, what estimate has been made of how many rooms on the Parliamentary estate are not wheelchair accessible.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51170","51170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626055","2016-11-02","Department for International Development","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment her Department has made of the need to tackle HIV and AIDS in its youth strategy.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51141","51141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626056","2016-11-02","Department for International Development","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many officials of her Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51134","51134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626057","2016-11-02","Department for International Development","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what priority her Department's strategy on women and girls accords to tackling HIV and AIDS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51142","51142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626058","2016-11-02","Department for International Development","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, in which countries and for how many projects her Department provides microloans to local communities or small businesses.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51237","51237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626059","2016-11-02","Department for International Development","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many citizens of non-UK EU countries work in her Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51003","51003"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626060","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) staff and (b) inmates there were at HM Prison Pentonville in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50979","50979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626061","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many citizens of non-UK EU countries work in her Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51000","51000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626062","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what representations her Department has received on conditions at HM Prison Pentonville in the last five years; and if she will place those representations in the Library.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50974","50974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626063","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking in response to the conclusion of HM Inspectorate of Probation in its report of 29 September 2016, A thematic inspection of the provision and quality of services in the community for women who offend, that services for women are undervalued and under threat.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50998","50998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626064","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the availability of dental services in prisons.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51040","51040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626065","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what her policy is on the treatment of women with mental health problems in the justice system.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51109","51109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626066","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness the Government's policy on reintegrating prisoners into society.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51110","51110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626067","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps she is taking to improve resettlement activity at HM Prison Littlehey.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51111","51111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626068","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when her Department plans to publish its response to the consultation on costs protection in environmental claims.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51238","51238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626069","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many children (a) under one year old, (b) between one and four years old, (c) between five and nine years old, (d) between 10 and 15 years old and (e) 16 years old or more have been the subject of care order applications in each year since 2008-09.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51210","51210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626070","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to her Department's report entitled Our Commitment to Victims, published in September 2014, whether the national roll-out of pre-trial cross-examination for child victims will be completed by March 2017.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51255","51255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626071","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests were made for registered intermediaries in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51226","51226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626072","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many officials of her Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51135","51135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626073","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what discussions she has had with Cabinet colleagues on the implications of adopting advisory status of judgments of the European Court of Human Rights for UK membership of the European Convention on Human Rights.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51086","51086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626074","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of prisoners failed to find accommodation upon release in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51090","51090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626075","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what her policy is on the UK remaining a signatory to the European Convention on Human Rights.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51087","51087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626076","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2016 to Question 49615, on Employment Tribunals Service: fees and charges, if she will provide further information on the progress made by the review; and how her Department defines the term in due course.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51088","51088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626077","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoner escapes there were in (a) England and (b) Cumbria in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51171","51171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626078","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time prison officers were employed in (a) England, (b) Cumbria and (c) Copeland constituency in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51172","51172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626079","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which locations her Department has identified as potential candidates for the first stages of the roll-out of section 28 of the Youth Justice Criminal Evidence Act 1999, announced in her Department's publication, Transforming Our Justice System, published in September 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51218","51218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626080","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to her Department's publication, Our Commitment to Victims, published in September 2014, what steps she has taken to ensure there are greater opportunities for vulnerable witnesses to give evidence at a location away from court.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51219","51219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626081","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Ministry of Justice paper, Our Commitment to Victims, published in September 2014, what plans she has made to ensure that all publicly funded advocates involved in serious sexual offences have undertaken approved specialist training on working with vulnerable victims; and whether her Department plans to update that training to take account of national roll-out of pre-trial cross-examination for vulnerable witnesses.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51202","51202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626082","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress her Department has made on implementing the reintegration planning recommendations outlined in the report on an unannounced inspection of HM Prison Littlehey  of March 2015.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51154","51154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626083","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, by what date she expects all UK Crown Dependencies to have adopted central registers of beneficial ownership accessible to UK law enforcement.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51265","51265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626084","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if she will implement the outstanding recommendations of the Corston report on the treatment of women in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51253","51253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626085","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to page 1 of the Independent Monitoring Board's Annual Report 2015-16 on HM Prison Pentonville, whether she has met that Board to discuss the conclusion that Pentonville urgently needs a timetable for its replacement or for reducing the population and upgrading the facilities.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51252","51252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626086","2016-11-03","Scotland Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, whether progress was made in discussions on the apprenticeship levy at the meeting of the Joint Ministerial Council on 24 October 2016.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51018","51018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626087","2016-11-02","Scotland Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many officials of his Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51136","51136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626088","2016-11-02","Department for Transport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many officials of his Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51137","51137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626089","2016-11-03","Department for Transport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2016 to Question 50202, on Heathrow Airport: night flying, what (a) flexibility and (b) penalties for violation the Government plans to put in place in respect of the six-and-a-half hour ban on night flights from an expanded Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51174","51174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626090","2016-11-02","Department for Transport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many trains have been taken out of circulation due to graffiti in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51189","51189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626091","2016-11-03","Department for Transport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer  of 28 October 2016 to Question 50200, on Heathrow Airport: air routes, what legal mechanisms the Government plans to use to protect existing domestic routes and provide additional connectivity across the UK with new routes from Scotland, Northern Ireland and the South West and North East of England.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51175","51175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626092","2016-11-03","Department for Transport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to include provisions on the regulation of drones in the Modern Transport Bill; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51177","51177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626093","2016-11-02","Department for Transport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to recent research on pollution particles potentially triggering Alzheimer's and other degenerative diseases, whether his Department has re-assessed the potential merits of measures to expand the use of electric-powered public transport.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51027","51027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626094","2016-11-02","Department for Transport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2016 to Question 44451, if the Government will carry out a detailed assessment of trends in the level of the fuel efficiency of buses.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51023","51023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626095","2016-11-03","Department for Transport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential merits of lowering the drink-drive limit to 50mg alcohol per 100ml blood.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51013","51013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626096","2016-11-03","Department for Transport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many deaths were caused in Wiltshire by people driving over the prescribed alcohol limit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51014","51014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626097","2016-11-02","Department for Transport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the potential proportion of High Speed 2 journeys that will be taken by passengers who plan to fly through Birmingham International Airport.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51031","51031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626098","2016-11-02","Wales Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51049","51049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626099","2016-11-02","Wales Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many officials of his Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51139","51139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626100","2016-11-02","Wales Office","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of potential new investment opportunities between Wales and Israel since the Israeli business delegation visit to Wales in 2015.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51147","51147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626101","2016-11-03","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people whose initial personal independence claim was unsuccessful died before their appeal was heard in each year from 2013 to date.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51216","51216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626102","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many officials of his Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51140","51140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626103","2016-11-02","HM Treasury","2016-10-31","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to protect public sector pension funds from changes in the value of sterling (a) while the UK is negotiating to withdraw from the EU and (b) when the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51195","51195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626104","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of personal independence payment applications from addresses in the London Borough of Newham were accepted at the first stage without submitting a mandatory reconsideration or appeal between April 2015 and October 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51223","51223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626105","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department's assessment contractors receive any penalty or fine when a claimant has been initially refused (a) personal independence payment and (b) employment and support allowance and is later awarded the relevant benefit on appeal at tribunal.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51158","51158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626106","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment and support allowance (ESA) claimants with (a) chronic disabilities and (b) illnesses were declared fit to work and had their ESA payments stopped in each month of (i) 2013, (ii) 2014, (iii) 2015 and (iv) 2016 to date.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51157","51157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626107","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department is putting in place to support people currently in receipt of Access to Work awards over the annual cap and their employers to prepare them for the end of the transition phase of the annual cap for existing scheme users.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51055","51055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626108","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department's assessment contractors received any (a) penalty, (b) bonus and (c) incentive to deny individual claims for (i) personal independence payment and (ii) employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51156","51156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626109","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) parents with care and (b) non-resident parents there are in Inverclyde constituency with a current (i) Child Support Agency case and (b) child maintenance case.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51094","51094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626110","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what targets his Department's assessment contractors have  for conducting (a) personal independence payments and (b) employment and support allowance assessments.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51155","51155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626111","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 28 October 2016 to Question 50222, how many members of the public in (a) Scotland and (b) the rest of the UK have contacted his Department on the implementation of the Pensions Act 1995, the Pension Act 2011 and the campaign to equalise state pensions for women in 2016; and what proportion of those people have received a response from his Department.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51209","51209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626112","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department collects data on referrals to food banks by jobcentre staff.","Biography information for Dr Philippa Whitford","Dr Philippa Whitford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51212","51212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626113","2016-11-03","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of all personal independence payment applicants have been accepted at the first stage without submitting a mandatory reconsideration or appeal in the period between April 2015 and October 2016.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51225","51225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626114","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people whose initial claim for employment and support allowance was unsuccessful died before their appeal was heard in each year from 2013 to 2016 to date.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51185","51185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626115","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of unsuccessful claims for personal independence payment were overturned on appeal in each year from 2013 to 2016 to date.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51186","51186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626116","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people died within a year of an unsuccessful personal independence payment in each year from 2013 to 2016 to date.","Biography information for Mr David Lammy","Mr David Lammy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51187","51187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626117","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51050","51050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626118","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when his Department plans to release information on the 2012 statutory child maintenance scheme by (a) geographical area and (b) parliamentary constituency.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51095","51095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626119","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Answer of 21 July 2016 to Question 43098, what steps officials of his Department are required to take when they are satisfied that a customer faces clear and significant risks to their welfare or safety.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51112","51112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626120","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Child Support Agency (a) arrears-only and (b) arrears cases involving a current liability for a child there are in Inverclyde constituency.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51096","51096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626121","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people in the support group for employment and support allowance can access specialist employment advice.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51113","51113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626122","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time is between a complaint being lodged with the Independent Case Examiner and being allocated to an Investigation Case Manager.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51046","51046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626123","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people by type of disability who have applied for Access to Work since the imposition of the annual cap have been given awards equal to that cap.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51054","51054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626124","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people by type of disability are in receipt of Access to Work grants worth more than the annual cap.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51036","51036"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626125","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Access to Work scheme users by type of disability are taking part in the pilot of personal budgets.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51037","51037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626126","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employers are currently accredited under the Two Ticks scheme.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50986","50986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626127","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that disabled people are made aware that the Two Ticks scheme is being transferred to the Disability Confident scheme.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50987","50987"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626128","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that employers transferred from the Two Ticks scheme to the Disability Confident scheme are meeting the requirements for which they are being accredited.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50988","50988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626129","2016-11-02","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what evaluation he has made of the effectiveness of the Disability Confident scheme.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50989","50989"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626130","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he plans to announce the results of the consultation on proposals to remove solar panels from the Renewable Heat Incentive scheme.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51017","51017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626131","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government has made an assessment of future levels of research funding in the UK after the UK leaves the EU and existing projects have been completed.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51022","51022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626132","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many citizens of non-UK EU countries work in his Department, its agencies and non-departmental public bodies.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51001","51001"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626133","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many equality impact assessments his Department carried out in 2016; and how many such assessments the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills carried out in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50981","50981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626134","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2016 to Question 48677, how much the Government has received from the Mineworkers' Pensions Scheme since 1994 net of payments from the Government arising from its guarantee.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51065","51065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626135","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what research is being conducted by the Government on carbon capture technologies.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51064","51064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626136","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government has made direct payments to the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme under the guarantee arrangements.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51063","51063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626137","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has for invigorating high street trading in the West Midlands in the next 12 months.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51029","51029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626138","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent discussions he has had with industry on hydraulic fracturing in the North West.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51097","51097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626139","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment his Department has made of the relative efficiency of combined cycle gas turbines and reciprocating gas and diesel engines.","Biography information for James Heappey","James Heappey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51205","51205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626140","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate his Department has made of the (a) number of gas or diesel reciprocating engines and (b) generating capacity likely to qualify in the T4 Capacity Market auction.","Biography information for James Heappey","James Heappey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51204","51204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626141","2016-11-03","Department for Transport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the oral contribution of the Minister for Climate Change and Industry of 13 September 2016, Official Report, columns 757-8, what progress the Government has made on assessing options to help tackle the misuse of laser pens (a) on aircraft, (b) on transport infrastructure and (c) generally.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51178","51178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626142","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many sub-1000MW reciprocating engines have prequalified for the Third T4 Capacity Market auction; and whether his Department has made an assessment of the effect of such pre-qualifications on the UK's ability to meet its carbon emission targets.","Biography information for James Heappey","James Heappey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51207","51207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626143","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what gigawatt capacity of gas or diesel reciprocating engines won 15-year contracts in the first two T4 Capacity Market auctions.","Biography information for James Heappey","James Heappey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51206","51206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626144","2016-11-03","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to simplify planning and administrative processes required before exploratory drilling can take place for shale gas.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51120","51120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626145","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many officials of his Department have opted out of the EU Working Time Directive.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51125","51125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626146","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what analysis his Department has made of the effect of reciprocating gas and diesel generation on (a) the likely Third T4 auction price and (b) the likelihood of securing new combined cycle gas turbine generation capacity.","Biography information for James Heappey","James Heappey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51203","51203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626147","2016-11-03","Department for International Trade","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to establish and facilitate civil society dialogue when negotiating trade agreements between the UK and other countries (a) during negotiations on the UK leaving the EU and (b) after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51217","51217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626148","2016-11-02","Department for International Trade","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps he is taking to ensure that the UK secures a trade agreement with Israel for pharmaceutical products after the UK ceases to be party to the EU-Israel mutual recognition agreement on pharmaceutical certificates.","Biography information for Craig Williams","Craig Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51148","51148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626149","2016-11-02","Department for International Trade","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many jobs were created in the UK by Israeli companies in 2015; and what steps his Department is taking to encourage more Israeli companies to trade in the UK.","Biography information for David Mackintosh","David Mackintosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51251","51251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626150","2016-11-02","Department for International Trade","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, with which African countries his Department plans to prioritise trade deals after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51107","51107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626151","2016-11-02","Department for International Development","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of launching a second phase of the Africa Free Trade initiative after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51108","51108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626152","2016-11-02","Department for International Development","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on the development of an African Union Continental Free Trade Area.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51104","51104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626153","2016-11-02","Department for International Trade","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to promote the ratification of World Trade Organisation rules and improve border and custom clearance procedures within the African continent.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51105","51105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626154","2016-11-02","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her policy is on importing genetically modified organisms after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Grant Shapps","Grant Shapps","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51106","51106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626155","2016-11-03","Department for International Trade","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, how many freedom of information requests have been submitted to his Department since July 2016; how many such requests the Department has responded to; how many such requests the Department has responded to within 20 working days; and for what number of days the longest outstanding request has been awaiting response.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51062","51062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626156","2016-11-03","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff in his Department are currently on loan from the Ministry of Defence.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51011","51011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626157","2016-11-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether her Department plans to ensure that UK residents continue to be subject to caps on mobile telephone roaming charges when abroad after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51196","51196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626158","2016-11-03","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2016 to Question 49977, on UK withdrawal from the EU, when he expects the analysis of the UK economy to be completed; and if he will make it his policy to publish the results of that analysis upon its completion.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51181","51181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626159","2016-11-03","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the higher education sector in Scotland of the UK leaving the EU; what recent discussions his Department has had with Ministers of the Scottish Government on that potential effect; and what assessment his Department has made of the availability of different options for the higher education sector in Scotland after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51228","51228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/626160","2016-11-03","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what representations he has received from the governments of other EU member states on the status of students after the 2018-19 academic year; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 51220","51220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/627329","2016-11-03","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment her Department has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on food prices for products sourced from developing countries.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907069","907069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/628054","2016-11-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress her Department has made on its commitment to end unsupervised high-stakes gambling on fixed odds betting terminals.","Biography information for Jonathan Reynolds","Jonathan Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907014","907014"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/628055","2016-11-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to support library provision.","Biography information for Mike Wood","Mike Wood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907016","907016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/628056","2016-11-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if the Government will fund accessible physical activity sessions during school holidays from the proceeds of the soft drinks industry levy.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907011","907011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/628057","2016-11-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps she has taken to improve access to cultural experiences for young people from low-income households; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Fiona Mactaggart","Fiona Mactaggart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907010","907010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/628058","2016-11-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure that all parts of the UK can access superfast broadband.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907015","907015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/628059","2016-11-03","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on the creative industries of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907009","907009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/628060","2016-11-03","Department for International Trade","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what estimate he has made of the potential cost to businesses of no longer having access to tariff-free trade with other EU Member States.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907077","907077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/628061","2016-11-03","Department for International Trade","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what steps his Department is taking to increase food and farming exports.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907071","907071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/628062","2016-11-03","Department for International Trade","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of different possible trading arrangements with the EU for pharmaceuticals exports after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907073","907073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/628063","2016-11-03","Department for International Trade","2016-10-31","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the potential effect of trade tariffs on agricultural products on the agriculture industry after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 907075","907075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623394","2016-11-02","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many and which social impact boards have been promoted by government departments since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50912","50912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623395","2016-11-02","HM Treasury","2016-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the national living wage on charities who are not subject to corporation tax in the (a) care home and (b) heritage sector.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50913","50913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623396","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of reducing the rate of VAT for small businesses.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50899","50899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623397","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Garston and Halewood constituency have had a tax credit claim stopped by Concentrix.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50948","50948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623398","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what data HM Revenue and Customs and Concentrix have relied upon to identify fraud and error in tax credit claims.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50949","50949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623399","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Revenue and Customs plans to continue to use current data sources to identify fraud and error in tax credit claims in the future; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50950","50950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623400","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the cost and benefits of HM Revenue and Customs' employment of Concentrix to identify fraud and error in tax credit claims.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50951","50951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623401","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to ensure that HM Revenue and Customs adheres to section 16 of the Tax Credits Act 2002 in respect of the employment of Concentrix to identify fraud and error in tax credit claims.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50952","50952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623402","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the accuracy and reliability of data sets used to identify fraud and error in tax credit claims.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50953","50953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623403","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, why some tax credits have been stopped prior to recipients being asked to deal with apparent discrepancies in information about their claims.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50954","50954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623404","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the reasons are for recipients of tax credits being erroneously told a (a) previous tenant of the recipient's property and (c) close family member was an undisclosed partner.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50955","50955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623405","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-28","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which sources Concentrix used to inform its checking of fraud and error in tax credit claims.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50956","50956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623406","2016-11-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of local authority refuse collection points to dispose of white goods.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50943","50943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623407","2016-11-08","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Written Ministerial Statement of 18 December 2014, HCWS154, what progress has been made on the grave restoration campaign to restore the graves of First World War recipients who are buried in the UK but not under the care of the Commonwealth War Graves Commission's restoration project, including the numbers and locations of the graves in question.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50915","50915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623408","2016-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question 49363, what the technical issue which triggered the revise or confirm offer procedure was; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50966","50966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623409","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to respond to Question 48855, tabled on 17 October 2016 by the hon. Member for Wolverhampton South West.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50944","50944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623410","2016-11-01","Department for Education","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2016 to Question 48637, how the Government Equalities Office ensures compliance with its obligations under Section 149 of the Equality Act 2010 relating to the public sector equality duty.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50936","50936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623411","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2016 to Question 47994, what estimate she has made of the cost to the adult education budget of providing training in basic digital skills for adults.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50906","50906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623412","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2016 to Question 49543, what assessment she has made of the effect on UK (a) GDP and (b) productivity of 3 million apprenticeships starts taking place by 2020.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50910","50910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623413","2016-11-01","Department for Education","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to increase uptake of creative subjects in secondary schools.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50935","50935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623414","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect on funding for higher education institutions in Greater London of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50932","50932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623415","2016-11-02","Department for Education","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of demand for school places in the London Borough of Newham for (a) boys and (b) girls in the next five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50933","50933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623416","2016-11-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many live (a) sheep and (b) cattle have been exported from the UK to other European countries in 2016; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50924","50924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623417","2016-11-01","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many pairs of hen harriers nested in the Bowland Fells and North Pennine Moors special protection areas for birds in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50898","50898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623418","2016-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the British High Commissioner to Kenya on the acceptance of donations for corporate sponsorship for parties and drinks events held at the British High Commission and consulates in Kenya.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50896","50896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623419","2016-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the British High Commissioner to Uganda on the acceptance of donations for corporate sponsorship for parties and drinks events held at the British High Commission in Uganda.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50894","50894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623420","2016-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the British High Commissioner to Tanzania on the acceptance of donations for corporate sponsorship for parties and drinks events held at the British High Commission in Tanzania.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50895","50895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623421","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether UK embassies, high commissions and consulates are required to declare donations they have received in their annual accounts.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50890","50890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623422","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the British High Commissioner to Namibia on the acceptance of donations for corporate sponsorship for parties and drinks events held at the British High Commission in Namibia.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50891","50891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623423","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the British High Commissioner to Malawi on the acceptance of donations for corporate sponsorship for parties and drinks events held at the British High Commission in Malawi.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50892","50892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623424","2016-11-02","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the British Ambassador to Ethiopia on the acceptance of donations for corporate sponsorship for parties and drinks events held at the British Embassy in Ethiopia.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50893","50893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623425","2016-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of Libya on compensation for UK victims of Gaddafi-sponsored IRA violence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50925","50925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623426","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of clinical commissioning groups that have undertaken an equality impact assessment before making changes to their prescription policy.","Biography information for Nicky Morgan","Nicky Morgan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50904","50904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623427","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to paragraph 1.86 of the Autumn Statement 2014, how much of the £150 million made available for child and adolescent eating disorder services has been allocated to each clinical commissioning group for 2016-17.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50911","50911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623428","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with (a) NHS England, (b) clinical commissioning groups and (c) local authorities in London on ensuring appropriate services are in place to increase the number of people who use or have used drugs who are tested for and diagnosed with hepatitis C.","Biography information for Victoria Borwick","Victoria Borwick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50902","50902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623429","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with NHS England and operational delivery networks in London on ensuring that the new hepatitis C treatments are available to people who use or have used drugs.","Biography information for Victoria Borwick","Victoria Borwick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50903","50903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623430","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to NHS England's announcement on 27 September 2016, of an additional £25 million for children and young people's mental health services, when he expects that funding to be allocated to clinical commissioning groups; and how his Department plans to ensure that the full allocation of that funding is spent in 2016.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50905","50905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623431","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the budget deficit for Cheshire and Merseyside if the current sustainability and transformation plans are implemented.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50959","50959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623432","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made toward the publication of NHS transformation and sustainability plans for Cheshire and Merseyside.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50957","50957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623433","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what procedures are in place to allow public consultation after the publication of NHS transformation and sustainability plans for Cheshire and Merseyside.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50958","50958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623434","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of care and treatment available to patients diagnosed with motor neurone disease.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50968","50968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623435","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish the review by Dame Louise Casey on opportunity and integration in isolated communities in its original form.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50969","50969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623436","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her policy is on charging for calls from mobile telephones to the police non-emergency number 101.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50970","50970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623437","2016-11-01","Home Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken as a result of the conclusion made in the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales, submitted to the Minister for Crime Prevention in March 2015, that the coronial autopsy rate in England and Wales could be reduced by up to 40 per cent.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50881","50881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623438","2016-11-01","Home Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government records the number of fires caused by electrical appliances in domestic dwellings.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50884","50884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623439","2016-11-01","Home Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions she has had with stakeholders on introducing a national strategy to reduce electrical fires.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50886","50886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623440","2016-11-01","Home Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures the Government uses for the recording of fire statistics; and when the next review of the Incident Reporting System is scheduled.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50887","50887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623441","2016-11-01","Home Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans the Government has to assess the cost to the economy of fire.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50885","50885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623442","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2016 to Question 49108, what assessment she has made of the proportion of visa refusals that relate to university admissions; and how many visa applications have related to such admissions in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50908","50908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623443","2016-11-01","Home Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to protect people in rural areas against radicalisation.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50901","50901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623444","2016-11-01","Department for International Development","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what external meetings on HIV and AIDS she has had since July 2016.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50961","50961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623445","2016-11-02","Department for International Development","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether her Department plans to renew its HIV and Aids strategy, Towards Zero Infections, which came to an end in 2015.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50946","50946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623446","2016-11-02","Department for International Development","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, of the expenditure that her Department has allocated to its HIV and Aids response, what direct spend has not been coded under HIV prevention, treatment and care; and under what sectors that expenditure has been coded, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50947","50947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623447","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is her policy to sign protocol 16 of the European Court of Human Rights, as set out after the Brighton Declaration.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50960","50960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623448","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is her policy to introduce legislative proposals to replace the Human Rights Act 1998.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50967","50967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623449","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to her Department's press release of 12 May 2016, entitled New plans to tackle corporate fraud, when she plans to launch a consultation on plans to extend the scope of the corporate offence of failing to prevent to economic crimes beyond bribery and tax evasion.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50909","50909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623450","2016-11-02","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many care cases there have been in the English Family Courts in each of the last 10 years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50914","50914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623451","2016-11-02","Home Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which UK Sikh organisations her Department consulted in the development of its policy paper Action against hate: the UK Government's plan for tackling hate crime, published in July 2016.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50931","50931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623452","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether it is her policy to introduce legislative proposals to make the UK Supreme Court the ultimate arbiter of human rights in the UK.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50919","50919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623453","2016-11-01","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the Government has sought legal advice about the impact on the Belfast Agreement of 1998 of the UK's decision to leave the EU; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50926","50926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623454","2016-11-01","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment the Northern Ireland Office has made of the performance to date of Charter N.I; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50927","50927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623455","2016-11-01","Northern Ireland Office","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) exports from and (b) imports into Northern Ireland of the recent drop in the value of sterling; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50928","50928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623456","2016-11-01","Department for Transport","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 September 2016 to Question 44675, if he will carry out an assessment of the effect of an increase in the number of private hire vehicles on (a) congestion and (b) consumer safety.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50921","50921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623457","2016-11-01","Department for Transport","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 September 2016 to Question 44454, when he plans to publish research on non-London bus passenger attitudes towards contactless payments.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50922","50922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623458","2016-11-01","Department for Transport","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many officials of his Department are working on the Government's response to the Law Commission's review of taxi and private hire services, published in May 2014.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50923","50923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623459","2016-11-02","Department for Transport","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the effect on the physical and mental health of rail users of overcrowding on trains.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50907","50907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623460","2016-11-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the capacity of small businesses to pay statutory sick pay for up to 28 weeks.","Biography information for Michelle Donelan","Michelle Donelan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50900","50900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623461","2016-11-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment applications have been accepted at the first stage, without submission of a mandatory reconsideration or appeal, between April 2015 and October 2016.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50929","50929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623462","2016-11-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many mandatory reconsiderations for personal independence payment claims have been (a) submitted and (b) successful in each year from April 2013 to October 2016.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50962","50962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623463","2016-11-01","Ministry of Justice","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many personal independence payment decisions were appealed after the mandatory reconsideration stage between April 2015 and October 2016; and how many such decisions have been accepted.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50963","50963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623464","2016-11-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many personal independence payment applications were received between April 2015 and October 2016.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50964","50964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623465","2016-11-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken has been for a decision to be made on a (a) personal independence payment (PIP) and (b) mandatory reconsideration for PIP from the date his Department receives the relevant documentation from the claimant in each year from the introduction of that process.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50965","50965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623466","2016-11-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of losing the European Social Fund on the provision of employment support; and what plans the Government has to replace the funding from that Fund.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50942","50942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623467","2016-11-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many small businesses in (a) Hornsey and Wood Green constituency and (b) London have claimed small business rate relief in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50937","50937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623468","2016-11-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to review the level of small business rate relief.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50971","50971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623469","2016-11-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the proportion of installed smart meters that cannot work because they do not have adequate mobile signal.","Biography information for James Heappey","James Heappey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50930","50930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623470","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on the potential effect of the Government's fracking strategy on local communities.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50945","50945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623471","2016-11-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 16 September 2016 to Question 45694, how much the Government spent on space funding in each year from 2010 to 2016.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50920","50920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623472","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to ensure energy imported from the EU is not subject to tariffs after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50888","50888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623473","2016-11-02","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2016 to Question 49056, when he was made aware that French steel was being used to build the Trident successor submarines.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50889","50889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623474","2016-11-01","Department for International Trade","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of products and produce exported from Scotland to the rest of the UK are passported for consumption in nations that are members of the EU.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50882","50882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623475","2016-11-01","Department for International Trade","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what proportion of products and produce manufactured in Scotland are exported from Scotland to the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50883","50883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623476","2016-11-01","Department for International Trade","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans he has to promote trade with other Commonwealth nations.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50897","50897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623477","2016-11-02","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what meetings (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department have had with representatives of the City of London financial sector since his Department was created.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50934","50934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623478","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what potential (a) costs and (b) regulation costs the Government anticipates for medicines manufacturers in securing separate regulatory approval for products for the UK and the EU after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50916","50916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623479","2016-11-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how compliance with the UN Global Harmonised System of classifying and labelling chemical processes will be regulated after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50917","50917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623480","2016-11-01","Department for Exiting the European Union","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether he has had discussions with the (a) Swiss, (b) Norwegian and (c) Icelandic governments since his appointment.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50918","50918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623481","2016-11-01","Department for Transport","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on securing access to (a) pollution notifications delivered by the European Maritime Safety Agency and (b) the EU's pollution prevention, response and intervention data after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50938","50938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623482","2016-11-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect on the retention of automatic EU-wide marketing licences for chemical companies whose products are notified at a national level in the UK of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50941","50941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623483","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to negotiate continued access to the EU's rapid alert procedure on recall for medicinal products after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50940","50940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/623484","2016-11-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-28","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his policy is on the recognition of UK firms' trademarks and patents in the EU after the UK has left the EU.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50939","50939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622494","2016-10-31","Attorney General","2016-10-27","To ask the Attorney General, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by the Law Officers' Departments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50631","50631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622495","2016-10-31","Attorney General","2016-10-27","To ask the Attorney General, how many apprenticeships have been created in the Law Officers' Departments in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50861","50861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622496","2016-10-31","Cabinet Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50632","50632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622497","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2016 to Question 48873, whether he plans to backdate the commencement date of secondary legislation to bring a £95,000 cap into force before 1 October 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50658","50658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622498","2016-10-31","Cabinet Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether his Department plans to change the way in which it measures the socio-economic background of (a) Fast Stream and (b) Fast Track apprentice scheme applicants.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50777","50777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622499","2016-10-31","Cabinet Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what progress he has made on re-designing the Fast Stream selection process to reduce its length from 18-31 weeks to 12 weeks.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50778","50778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622500","2016-10-31","Cabinet Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many apprenticeships have been created in his Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50802","50802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622501","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will conduct a review of the effect of erroneous decisions by Concentrix on people in (a) Bristol West and (b) the UK.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50844","50844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622502","2016-10-31","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the value for money case for Swansea Bay Tidal Lagoon; and whether that assessment  has been shared with the Hendy Review team.","Biography information for Roger Mullin","Roger Mullin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50847","50847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622503","2016-11-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 1.137 of the Summer Budget 2015, if he will make an assessment of the effect of recent changes in the level of inflation on the proposed freeze of working age benefits.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50697","50697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622504","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of tax credit cases awaiting consideration by Concentrix in Bristol West constituency.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50719","50719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622505","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people in Bristol West constituency have had a tax credit claim stopped by Concentrix; and how many such people have subsequently had their claim reinstated by HM Revenue and Customs.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50720","50720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622506","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on (a) Bristol West and (b) Bristol City Council area of the shortfall in funding from the European Regional Development Fund and European Social Fund after the 2014 to 2020 programme has ended.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50723","50723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622507","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government is conducting a regional assessment of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on (a) Bristol West, (b) Bristol City Council area and (c) the region covered by the Counties formerly known as Avon.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50724","50724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622508","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that high net worth footballers pay the correct amount of income tax.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50728","50728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622509","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on Wells Fargo bank.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50756","50756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622510","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects the review by the Financial Conduct Authority into the Royal Bank of Scotland's Global Restructuring Group to be published; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Tugendhat","Tom Tugendhat","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50757","50757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622511","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has made an estimate of the potential effect on Total Managed Expenditure in 2017-18 of the UK's decision to leave the EU.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50696","50696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622512","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50645","50645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622513","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to allow payments of child tax credits to bereaved partners to be backdated to the date of the death of their partner.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50628","50628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622514","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans he has to give non-transport borrowing powers to combined authorities.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50654","50654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622515","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government on giving non-transport borrowing powers to combined authorities.","Biography information for Rob Marris","Rob Marris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50655","50655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622516","2016-11-01","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of stamp duty reform on the availability of affordable accommodation; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50856","50856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622517","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has met representatives of Wells Fargo bank to discuss the selling of financial products by that bank.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50870","50870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622518","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Financial Conduct Authority on the reported £16 billion set aside by Lloyds Banking Group for the mis-selling of payment protection insurance.","Biography information for Philip Boswell","Phil Boswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50871","50871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622519","2016-11-01","Church Commissioners","2016-10-27","To ask the right hon. Member for Meriden, representing the Church Commissioners, what progress has been made on disposing of land at the urban extension at Norwood Peterborough with a view to submitting an outline planning application for residential development to Peterborough City Council; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stewart Jackson","Mr Stewart Jackson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50857","50857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622520","2016-10-31","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50633","50633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622521","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the economic contribution of speedway to the economy.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50686","50686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622522","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effectiveness of the Government's five point plan for tourism in achieving its aims.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50675","50675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622523","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many officials of her Department are employed to work specifically on developing new technologies.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50676","50676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622524","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with Visit England on increasing tourism outside London.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50677","50677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622525","2016-10-31","HM Treasury","2016-10-27","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to reduce the level of regulation on community and amateur sports clubs.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50685","50685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622526","2016-11-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) participants and (b) people who have completed the National Citizenship Service received financial assistance for the £50 application fee since that service was introduced.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50746","50746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622527","2016-11-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to publish an impact assessment for the National Citizen Service Bill [HL].","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50747","50747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622528","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress her Department has made on developing capacity to implement the policy of making the UK a world leader in the development of 5G technologies.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50674","50674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622529","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect on the tourism industry of the introduction of visa charges on travel to and from the UK after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50735","50735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622530","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps to ensure that low income families have free access to museums and galleries.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50673","50673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622531","2016-11-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on consumers of the time taken to implement switching in the mobile market to a gaining provider-led system.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50703","50703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622532","2016-11-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what information she holds of when Ofcom plans to bring forward its proposals to reform switching in the mobile market.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50704","50704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622533","2016-11-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on vulnerable consumers of the current switching regime in the mobile market.","Biography information for Jeff Smith","Jeff Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50705","50705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622534","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, to which journals and periodicals her Department currently subscribes.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50671","50671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622535","2016-11-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of National Citizen Service participants are from independent schools.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50706","50706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622536","2016-11-01","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the social and economic benefits of the National Citizen Service; and when she plans to publish an evaluation report on that service.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50707","50707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622537","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will take steps to increase the numbers of visits to museums and galleries outside London.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50672","50672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622538","2016-10-31","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many apprenticeships have been created in her Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50803","50803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622539","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many apprenticeships have been created in his Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50804","50804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622540","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Viking BVS10 vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50765","50765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622541","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Wolfhound vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50766","50766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622542","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Quad bike vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50767","50767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622543","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Guided Multiple Launch Rocket System (GMLRS) are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50758","50758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622544","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many L118 light guns are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50759","50759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622545","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many AS90 self-propelled guns are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50760","50760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622546","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Demountable rack offload and pickup systems (DROPS) vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50761","50761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622547","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Panther vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50762","50762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622548","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Snatch 2 Land Rover vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50763","50763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622549","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many RWMIK Land Rover vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50764","50764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622550","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Mastiff vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50768","50768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622551","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Ridgeback vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50769","50769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622552","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Foxhound vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50770","50770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622553","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Husky vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50771","50771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622554","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Coyote TSV (light) vehicles are (a) in operational service, (b) used for training, (c) held in reserve, (d) in the inspection and repair process and (e) mothballed or in storage.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50772","50772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622555","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to support veterans into employment.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50679","50679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622556","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when Ministers of his Department were first made aware of the Iraq Historic Allegations team's contract with the recruitment agency Red Snapper.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50650","50650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622557","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50634","50634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622558","2016-10-31","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 27 October 2016 to Question 49642, on the Iraq Historic Allegations Team, when he was first made aware of the contract; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Sir Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50849","50849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622559","2016-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much his Department has paid in incentive bonuses to trained regular armed forces personnel who have transferred to the reserve forces in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50872","50872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622560","2016-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained regular (a) sailors and (b) officers transferred into the Royal Naval Reserve in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50874","50874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622561","2016-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many trained regular (a) airmen, (b) airwomen and (c) officers transferred into the Royal Air Force Reserve in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50875","50875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622562","2016-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many former soldiers and officers who have now left the regular Army in each year since 2001 have subsequently joined the Army Reserves.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50876","50876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622563","2016-11-01","Ministry of Defence","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers and officers who started their service in the regular Army in each year since 2001 have left that service.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50877","50877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622564","2016-11-01","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the relative level of pupil performance in West Sussex at key stage (a) 1, (b) 2, (c) 3 and (d) 4 compared to the average such performance in England.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50873","50873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622565","2016-11-01","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the date and most recent Ofsted rating was of each children's services department.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50878","50878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622566","2016-11-01","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local authority children's services departments are not run directly by the local authority; and what the nature is of the structure within which each such department operates.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50879","50879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622567","2016-11-01","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it remains the Government's policy to publish a life chances strategy.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50880","50880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622568","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate she has made of the level of procurement of British steel by her Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50635","50635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622569","2016-11-01","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to her Department's training guide video for autumn 2016, whether schools do not need to obtain pupil or parental consent to share information on pupils' nationality collected through the school census; and whether those schools are protected from legal challenge about breaching a duty of confidence.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50649","50649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622570","2016-11-01","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many teachers who signed up to take part in the National Teaching Service pilot in the North West beginning in January 2017 have subsequently withdrawn from that pilot.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50653","50653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622571","2016-11-01","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the data collected by schools on pupils' country of birth and nationality to be included in the National Pupil Database are to be made accessible to (a) the Home Office, (b) media bodies, (c) citizens and (d) other third parties.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50659","50659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622572","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to expand the teaching of financial education in schools.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50681","50681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622573","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what provision is in place for a new school to alter its published admission number between being approved and being built.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50687","50687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622574","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made, other than by using passenger survey data, of the number of international students each year who break their visa obligations by remaining in the UK after their course has ended.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50734","50734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622575","2016-11-01","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which local safeguarding children's boards have been inspected by Ofsted; and what the ratings of those boards are.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50790","50790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622576","2016-11-01","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what grants her Department has made to (a) children and young people's charities and (b) children and young people's organisations in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50791","50791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622577","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what terms of reference and objectives have been set for her Department's Gypsy, Roma and Traveller expert panel.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50729","50729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622578","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of atypical employment contracts used by universities for (a) research and (b) teaching as a proportion of all employment contracts in that sector.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50738","50738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622579","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many apprenticeships have been created in her Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50805","50805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622580","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of provision within the school system for the needs of students who are young carers.","Biography information for Mr Marcus Fysh","Marcus Fysh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50843","50843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622581","2016-10-31","Department for Education","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 October 2016 to Question 49242, what organisations and community groups have been invited to provide expertise on the drivers for raising the educational attainment of gypsy, roma and traveller pupils.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50782","50782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622582","2016-10-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many apprenticeships have been created in her Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50806","50806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622583","2016-11-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether his Department is on track to meet the UK target under the Climate Change Act 2008 to reduce greenhouse gas emissions by at least 80 per cent from the 1990 baseline by 2050.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50798","50798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622584","2016-11-01","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has to improve the resolution of weather warning systems.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50742","50742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622585","2016-10-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent estimate she has made of the level of procurement of British steel by her Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50636","50636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622586","2016-11-01","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether there is a process in place for local authorities to challenge central government decisions in relation to the allowing of hydraulic fracturing activities.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50858","50858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622587","2016-10-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 August 2016 to Question 45523, for what reasons the Government has not ratified the Convention for extension to the British Indian Ocean Territory.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50835","50835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622588","2016-10-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 August 2016 to Question 45523, what plans he has to provide a response to the UN Committee on the Elimination of Racial Discrimination's recommendation (CERD/C/GBR//CO18-20) on the British Indian Ocean Territory and the Chagossians.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50837","50837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622589","2016-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his assessment is of the effectiveness of the EU-China Human Rights Dialogue.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50854","50854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622590","2016-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his assessment is of the effectiveness of the UK-China Human Rights Dialogue.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50853","50853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622591","2016-10-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 26 August 2016 to Question 45523, what steps he plans to take to update Parliament, Chagossians and others on progress on the issues discussed in that Answer.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50834","50834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622592","2016-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his counterpart in the People's Republic of China on the detention of human rights lawyers since July 2015.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50855","50855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622593","2016-10-31","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make it her policy to prevent ferry companies from requiring companion animals, such as dogs and cats, to remain inside vehicles and unattended during ferry journeys.","Biography information for Dr Paul Monaghan","Dr Paul Monaghan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50836","50836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622594","2016-10-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50637","50637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622595","2016-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when a UK diplomat last visited Yemen.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50700","50700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622596","2016-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many UK diplomats have visited Yemen in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50701","50701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622597","2016-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on how many occasions Ministers or officials of his Department have raised the case of Mrs Nazanin Ratcliffe with their Iranian counterparts since her arrest on 3 April 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50752","50752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622598","2016-10-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many apprenticeships have been created in his Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50808","50808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622599","2016-10-31","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will have discussions with his counterparts in other EU member states on ensuring that the observance of the right to freedom of belief and religion is being upheld in Ukraine.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50775","50775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622600","2016-11-01","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the implications for political and human rights in Hong Kong of the election held there in September 2016.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50852","50852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622601","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that private abortion clinics are registered; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure that deregistered clinics cease operation.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50851","50851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622602","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 26 October 2016 to Question 49779, whether he has ordered an investigation into whether, at any point since 1 April 2016, any other patient transport services were provided without the required registration with the Care Quality Commission; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50845","50845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622603","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with NHS England on the effectiveness of eculizumab for the treatment of dense deposit disease.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50841","50841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622604","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Clinical Priorities Advisory Group on the funding of eculizumab for the treatment of dense deposit disease.","Biography information for Andrea Jenkyns","Andrea Jenkyns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50842","50842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622605","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many apprenticeships have been created in his Department in each region in each of the last five years; and how many participants in those apprenticeships subsequently secured a job within the Civil Service.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50810","50810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622606","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to publish a third annual suicide prevention report.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50776","50776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622607","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Adult Psychiatric Morbidity Survey: Survey of Mental Health and Wellbeing, England, 2014, published on 29 September 2016, what plans he has to address the increase in self-harm among young women aged 16 to 24; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50748","50748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622608","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2016 to Question 48238 on cancer: diagnosis, how he plans to allocated the £300 million per year to improve cancer diagnostics in 2016-17.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50780","50780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622609","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance he has issued on patients' travel distance to GP services.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50753","50753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622610","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has had discussions with Wiltshire CCG on a new GP Outreach surgery in Wiltshire.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50754","50754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622611","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 October 2016 to Question 48113, what proportion of funding for health services received by teenagers and young adults with cancer and leukaemia in (a) Bristol and (b) England comes from charitable trusts.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50795","50795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622612","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 20 October 2016 to Question 48238 on cancer: diagnosis, how and by what criteria he plans to evaluate the effectiveness of the spending of £300 million per year to improve diagnostic capacity of cancers.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50788","50788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622613","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether NHS England monitors clinical commissioning group incentive schemes for evidence of payments to GPs for the reduction of outpatient referrals.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50692","50692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622614","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether (a) proposals for outreach GP surgeries and (b) the proposed   outreach GP surgery at Lyneham require approval by his Department.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50739","50739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622615","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the reasons for life expectancy of residents of Ashfield being lower than the national average.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50740","50740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622616","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) consultations and (b) inspections took place at Royal Brampton and Harefield NHS Foundation Trust prior to that Trust being notified on 30 June 2016 that it did not meet the new standards for congenital heart disease services.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50741","50741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622617","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many health visitors commissioned by local authorities since October 2015 are employed in non-NHS organisations.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50710","50710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622618","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent health visitors were in post in September 2015 prior to transfer of commissioning to local authorities.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50711","50711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622619","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many commissioned health visitor student places had been filled by September 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50708","50708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622620","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many commissions for health visitor students there were for the academic year starting September 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50709","50709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622621","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce regulations to prevent clinical commissioning groups incentivising the reduction of outpatient referrals by GPs.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50698","50698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622622","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people are employed in NHS Improvement's Operational Productivity Directorate; what the total salary cost is for employing all such people; and how many employees in that Directorate earn more than £100,000.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50699","50699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622623","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which hospitals providing congenital heart disease services (a) do not meet the standard for the co-location of paediatric services and (b) have been informed that they may be required to cease to provide those services as a result of not meeting that standard.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50744","50744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622624","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect on the Royal Brompton Hospital as a national specialist referral centre for children with lung disorders of the proposed closure of its paediatric congenital heart disease services.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50743","50743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622625","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on what evidence the Clinical Priorities Advisory Board based its decision to not fund the use of Afinitor for the treatment of breast cancer.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50731","50731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622626","2016-11-02","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has had discussions with the Secretary of State for Defence on provision for a families and civilian GP surgery outside the wire at MOD Lyneham.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50712","50712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622627","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had on the provision of GP surgeries in Wiltshire.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50725","50725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622628","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will visit Wiltshire to assess the need for a GP surgery in Lyneham.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50726","50726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622629","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Adult Psychiatric Morbidity Survey: Survey of Mental Health and Wellbeing, England, 2014, published on 29 September 2016, what plans he has to address the increase in the incidence of post-traumatic stress disorder in young women; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50751","50751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622630","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many families have been assisted by the Family Nurse Partnership in (a) Liverpool, Wavertree constituency, (b) Liverpool, (c) the Liverpool City Region and (d) each region in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50750","50750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622631","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent estimate he has made of the level of procurement of British steel by his Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50638","50638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622632","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the number of accident and emergency departments that will reduce their opening hours by 2020; and which accident and emergency departments a decision has been reached on reducing open hours.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50656","50656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622633","2016-11-04","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of its staff being unable to work because of lack of availability of medical treatment funded by clinical commissioning groups.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50657","50657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622634","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of funding for people with high cholesterol to access PCSK9 inhibitors for the treatment of that condition.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50629","50629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622635","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average number of patients per GP surgery is in (a) England, (b) Wiltshire, (c) Royal Wootton Bassett and (d) Calne.","Biography information for James Gray","James Gray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50693","50693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622636","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether a formal assessment of the effect of awarding the contract for provision of muscular skeletal services to Circle Health at Lewisham and Greenwich NHS Trusts was carried out by (a) Greenwich Clinical Commissioning Group and (b) NHS England.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50660","50660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622637","2016-10-31","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase the use of clinical answering services for commissioning and decommissioning of treatment and support relating to mental health.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50680","50680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622638","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times DNA testing has been used in immigration cases in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50678","50678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622639","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many times her Department has disputed the age of someone claiming to be a child when making an asylum application in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50665","50665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622640","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department plans to change the £18,600 income threshold for immigration of non-EEA partners of British citizens.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50651","50651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622641","2016-11-01","Department of Health","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether mental health providers are required in recording data on the use of physical restraint to record the ethnicity of the person against whom such restraint is used.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50661","50661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622642","2016-11-01","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department holds information on the number of times (a) territorial support groups and (b) other police officers have been deployed to a mental health unit in response to a request from a provider in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50662","50662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622643","2016-11-01","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department holds information on the number of times (a) territorial support groups and (b) other police officers have been deployed to recall a person on a mental heath treatment order in the community and to return them to hospital in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50663","50663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622644","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress has been made on the rollout of body-worn cameras to police officers for the collection of evidence.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50684","50684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622645","2016-11-04","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was spent on (a) food, (b) drinks, (c) rail fares, (d) air fares, (e) mileage allowances, (f) taxis, (g) other travel costs, (h) room hire and (i) accommodation for staff by UK Visas and Immigration in the first nine months of 2016.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50714","50714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622646","2016-11-01","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 21 October 2016 to Question 49304, on correspondence with Judge Goddard, when she plans to provide a substantive reply to that Question.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50694","50694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622647","2016-11-01","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what training asylum caseworkers receive on processing and considering asylum claims involving allegations of torture or serious harm where a Medico-Legal report from the Medical Foundation Medico-Legal Report Service at Freedom from Torture or the Helen Bamber Foundation forms part of the evidence.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50648","50648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622648","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate she has made of the level of procurement of British steel by her Department in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50639","50639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622649","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the implications for her policy on migrant detention of the report published by Detention Action entitled, Without detention, on 26 September 2016.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50733","50733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622650","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people under the age of 18 have been found in possession of a knife in (a) London and (b) Bethnal Green and Bow constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50727","50727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622651","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to consult on regulations to be made under section 95A of the Immigration and Asylum Act 1999 as inserted by Schedule 11 of the Immigration Act 2016.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50722","50722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622652","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish her Department's Immigration Enforcement Business Plan for 2016-17.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50732","50732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622653","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken as a result of the recommendation made in the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales, submitted to the Minister of State for Crime and Prevention in March 2015, that second post-mortems are only authorised following a formal application to a coroner or judge and become a desktop review of the first report.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50716","50716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/622654","2016-10-31","Home Office","2016-10-27","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government has taken as a result of the recommendation made in the Hutton review of forensic pathology in England and Wales, submitted to the Minister of State for Crime and Prevention in March 2015, that regional centres should be established.","Biography information for Shabana Mahmood","Shabana Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2016/17 50717","50717"
