"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33862","2014-01-22","Home Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of the policing of the pilot badger culls was carried out on public land; and if he will separately calculate the costs of such policing.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184162","184162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33863","2014-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for what reasons fish consumers are subject to a levy to fund the Sea Fish Industry Authority (Seafish).","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184145","184145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33864","2014-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to protect Sites of Specific Scientific Interest which have been affected by recent floods.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184146","184146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33865","2014-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will takes steps to protect Sites of Specific Scientific Interest and other wildlife sites from flooding.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184147","184147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33866","2014-01-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if the Government will conduct an impact assessment of the recent flooding on Britain's wildlife.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184148","184148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33867","2014-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what research the Government is undertaking or funding into solar flares.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184149","184149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33868","2014-01-23","Cabinet Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what contingency plans the Government has in the event of large solar flares.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184150","184150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33869","2014-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funds his Department made available to protect homes, businesses and agricultural land to the east of Lytham St Annes from flooding.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183999","183999"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33870","2014-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether his Department has any plans to consult on banning or restricting the use of animal snares.","Biography information for Graeme Morrice","Graeme Morrice","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183986","183986"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33873","2014-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will (a) discuss with the Moroccan ambassador to the UK and (b) instruct HM ambassador in Rabat to report on the incidents in El Aaiún, Western Sahara, on 15 January 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184000","184000"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33874","2014-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the vote in the House of Commons of 30 August 2013 on military intervention in Syria on the UK's (a) diplomatic and (b) trade objectives in respect of (i) Saudi Arabia and (ii) the United Arab Emirates.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184021","184021"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33875","2014-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 16 January 2014, Official Report, column 607W, on Iran, if he will take steps to develop and seek agreement on a mechanism for the inclusion of Saudi Arabia formally in the process.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184019","184019"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33876","2014-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Government's contract with Veolia Environmental Services in respect of the destruction of chemical weapons at Ellesmere Port, what the nature is of the material to be destroyed; whether it is all in solid or liquid phase; and whether any ordnance will come to Ellesmere Port.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184024","184024"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33877","2014-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Government's contract with Veolia Environmental Services in respect of the destruction of chemical weapons at Ellesmere Port, what steps he is taking to ensure the safe transit of the chemical weapons within the UK; and which other sites are being utilised for this purpose.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184025","184025"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33878","2014-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Government's contract with Veolia Environmental Services in respect of the destruction of chemical weapons at Ellesmere Port, whether the process involves any (a) discharge to local water courses and (b) risk of any of the material venting to the atmosphere in a toxic state.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184026","184026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33879","2014-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Government's contract with Veolia Environmental Services in respect of the destruction of chemical weapons at Ellesmere Port, whether the Government will require any oversight of the process other than that previously applied to the site.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184027","184027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33880","2014-01-23","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the nature is of the contract between the Government and Veolia Environmental Services in respect of the destruction of chemical weapons at Ellesmere Port.","Biography information for Andrew Miller","Andrew Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184023","184023"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33881","2014-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the UK will send a representative to the conference on the Humanitarian Consequences of Nuclear Weapons in Nayarit, Mexico on 13 to 14 February 2014.","Biography information for Katy Clark","Katy Clark","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184084","184084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33882","2014-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what conditions the UK is seeking before the arms embargo on Burma is lifted; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184165","184165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33883","2014-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether Kyaw Hla Aung was raised when a Minister in his Department last met the new Burmese Ambassador to the UK: and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184164","184164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33884","2014-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make it his policy that the UK take steps to ensure the renewal of the mandate of the UN Special Rapporteur on Burma; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184166","184166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33885","2014-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his policy is on the UK training of military police in Burma; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184167","184167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33886","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when (a) he, (b) Ministers in his Department and (c) officials in his Department have met representatives of Sanofi to discuss sodium valproate in pregnancy.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184168","184168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33887","2014-01-23","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of levels of adherence to minimum wage legislation in the home care sector.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184180","184180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33888","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 19 December 2013, Official Report, column 728W, on vaccination: immigrants, which body is responsible for commissioning to meet the needs for specific vaccination programmes among migrants who are not registered with a GP when such needs have been identified by a local clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Lord Blunkett","Mr David Blunkett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184133","184133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33889","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on proposals for EU-level regulation of e-cigarettes as medicinal items.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184105","184105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33890","2014-01-23","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what consideration has been given to the use of a national identity card system for determining eligibility for treatment by the National Health Service.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184112","184112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33891","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions (a) he and (b) his officials have had with counterparts at the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on any requirement to compensate tobacco companies for deprivation of their intellectual property.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184141","184141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33892","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what (a) meetings he has had with and (b) representations he has received from the (i) Electronic Cigarette Industry Trade Association and (ii) Electronic Cigarette Consumer Association.","Biography information for Steve Brine","Steve Brine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184143","184143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33893","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to explore the potential for safeguarding care home residents through the installation of covert CCTV.","Biography information for Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","Mr Gerry Sutcliffe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184139","184139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33894","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of cases of (a) suicide, (b) possible suicide and (c) attempted suicide that have occurred in each year since Sertraline was introduced in the UK in which Sertraline was a possible factor.","Biography information for James Wharton","James Wharton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184049","184049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33895","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what advice his Department gives to doctors prescribing Sertraline.","Biography information for James Wharton","James Wharton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184050","184050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33896","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received about the use of Sertraline and side effects such as behaviour changes.","Biography information for James Wharton","James Wharton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184047","184047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33897","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he has taken to implement the recommendations of the McCracken review.","Biography information for Mark Tami","Mark Tami","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184085","184085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33898","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his Department's paper, Sustaining services, ensuring fairness, whether his intention is for chargeable migrants to pay the full costs of primary healthcare treatments beyond the initial GP or nurse consultation.","Biography information for Pamela Nash","Pamela Nash","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184086","184086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33899","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to monitor cases of attempted suicide, suicide and possible suicide in which Sertraline was a possible factor.","Biography information for James Wharton","James Wharton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184048","184048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33900","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 May 2013, Official Report, column 159W, on babies: screening, when he expects a recommendation to be made on the accuracy of pulse oximetry as a screening test for congenital heart disease.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184006","184006"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33901","2014-01-23","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many patients waited longer than four hours at University Hospitals Coventry and Warwickshire NHS Trust accident and emergency department in the latest period for which figures are available; and how long the longest wait was during that period.","Biography information for Mr Bob Ainsworth","Mr Bob Ainsworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184035","184035"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33902","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received on drug-drug interactions resulting from the concurrent prescriptions of multiple psychotropic drugs in children.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184016","184016"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33903","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations his Department has received on the prescription of methylphenidate hydrochloride for children.","Biography information for Paul Uppal","Paul Uppal","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184017","184017"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33904","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to assist GPs to tackle obesity.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183995","183995"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33905","2014-01-22","Home Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many non-British EU nationals were convicted of a serious crime in the UK in each of the last three years; and how many such people have been successfully deported.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184010","184010"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33906","2014-01-22","Home Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that EU nationals convicted of serious crimes are deported; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184011","184011"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33907","2014-01-23","Home Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many roadside drug analysis machines are in active use in (a) total and (b) each police force.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184033","184033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33908","2014-01-22","Home Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many complaints the Passport Office received about the performance of (a) Elucidate Contractor Services and (b) other private sector passport intermediary companies in (i) 2011-12, (ii) 2012-13 and (iii) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184012","184012"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33909","2014-01-22","Home Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will include autism in the mandate for Health Education England.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184051","184051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33910","2014-01-22","Home Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much was paid by her Department to Raytheon plc in relation to the e-borders scheme.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184052","184052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33911","2014-01-23","Home Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the terms of reference are of Her Majesty's Inspectorate of Constabulary's inspection of the effectiveness of the police response to domestic violence and abuse across England and Wales.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184081","184081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33912","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason three months was chosen as the length of time before an EU migrant can claim benefits.","Biography information for Dominic Raab","Mr Dominic Raab","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184151","184151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33913","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign nationals were convicted of criminal offences committed in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184173","184173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33914","2014-01-22","Home Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether the Government stores telephone communications data on British citizens against whom no evidence of criminal activity is held.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184176","184176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33915","2014-01-23","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-20","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what the value of sugar purchased for consumption in the House of Commons was in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184115","184115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33916","2014-01-23","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-20","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what proportion of beverages sold in the House of Commons were sugar-free in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184116","184116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33917","2014-01-23","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-20","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what the value of chocolate confectionery products purchased in the House was in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184117","184117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33918","2014-01-23","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-20","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what proportion of the products on sale in vending machines in the House are sugar-free or low in sugar.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184118","184118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33919","2014-01-23","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-20","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what guidelines are issued to catering outlets in the House on the provision of healthy food and drink.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184119","184119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33920","2014-01-23","Department for International Development","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the effectiveness of her Department's work in Rwanda.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184018","184018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33921","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to introduce the HM Prison Kirkham Drug and Rehabilitation programme nationally.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183992","183992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33922","2014-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of the staff working at HM Prison Oakwood when it took its first prisoners had previous experience of working in a prison.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184028","184028"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33923","2014-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of the staff working at HM Prison Oakwood had (a) no, (b) up to six months, (c) between six and 12 months and (d) over 12 months previous experience working in a prison when it took its first prisoners.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184029","184029"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33924","2014-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of the senior management working at HM Prison Oakwood when it took its first prisoners had previous experience of working in a prison.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184030","184030"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33925","2014-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many of the senior management at HM Prison Oakwood had (a) no, (b) up to six months, (c) between six and 12 months and (d) over 12 months previous experience working in a prison at the time of that prison's opening.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184031","184031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33926","2014-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what relevant prior experience each member of senior management working in HM Prison Oakwood possesses.","Biography information for Sadiq Khan","Sadiq Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184032","184032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33927","2014-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many drug-driving convictions have been secured through the use of roadside drug analysis, also known as drugalyser, machines (a) in total and (b) by police force, in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184022","184022"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33928","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of arson in each of the last seven years; and of those how many were convicted of arson with intent.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184055","184055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33929","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of malicious wounding offences in each of the last seven years; and of those how many were convicted of malicious wounding with intent.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184056","184056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33930","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of grievous bodily harm offences in each of the last seven years; and of those how many were convicted of grievous bodily harm with intent.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184057","184057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33931","2014-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to clarify the position under the Human Rights Act 1998 of people paying for their own care in care homes.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184107","184107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33932","2014-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what guidelines his Department gives for the contents of a young offender's cell.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184125","184125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33933","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the inherent and post-mitigation risk is to the Transforming Rehabilitation programme from insufficient or delayed guidance to probation trusts from his Department.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184130","184130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33934","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the inherent and pre-mitigation risk is to the Transforming Rehabilitation programme from insufficient attention and support from his Department owing to other demands.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184129","184129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33935","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the changes announced by the Sentencing Council to the sentencing guidelines of 12 December 2013, what assessment he has made of the likely effect of such changes on the prison population.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Mr Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184102","184102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33936","2014-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the role of special advisers is in the process of sign-off of answers to parliamentary questions in his Department.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184053","184053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33937","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the inherent and post-mitigation risk is to the Transforming Rehabilitation programme from insufficient capacity in his Department to manage the process owing to their scale and lack of co-ordination between different work streams in his Department.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184131","184131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33938","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the inherent and post-mitigation risk is to the Transforming Rehabilitation programme from a failure of the programme to be delivered either in scope or within the time scale set by Ministers.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184132","184132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33939","2014-01-23","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average daily cost of feeding a prisoner is.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184157","184157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33940","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many holders of a foreign-issued driving licence were prosecuted for non-speeding road traffic offences in the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184169","184169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33941","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many holders of a foreign-issued driving licence were prosecuted for speeding offences in the last year.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184170","184170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33942","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many owners of foreign-registered vehicles have been prosecuted for failure to register their vehicles after remaining in the UK beyond six months in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184171","184171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33943","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many holders of a foreign-issued driving licence were convicted of drink driving offences in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184172","184172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33944","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) active and (b) inactive registered intermediaries there were in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184186","184186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33945","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests were made for registered intermediaries in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184187","184187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33946","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many requests were made for each age group of vulnerable witnesses for registered intermediaries by (a) the police, (b) the Crown Prosecution Service, (c) courts, (d) solicitors and (e) other groups in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184188","184188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33947","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) matched and (b) unmatched registered intermediaries there were for each age group of vulnerable witnesses in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184189","184189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33948","2014-01-22","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many sexual offences were prosecuted which involved a person aged under 18 years old where that person was (a) matched and (b) unmatched with a registered intermediary since 2010.","Biography information for Ann Coffey","Ann Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184190","184190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33949","2014-01-28","Leader of the House","2014-01-20","To ask the Leader of the House, what consultations he had with Westminster City Council before work commenced on the reduction of the highway width around Parliament Square; what assessment he has made of the potential for delays to hon. Members travelling to the Palace of Westminster to vote; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184159","184159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33950","2014-01-22","Scotland Office","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he makes of the extent to which the Scottish Government makes use of the powers already devolved to it when he decides on proposals for the further devolution of powers to Scotland.","Biography information for Mr Tom Clarke","Mr Tom Clarke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184163","184163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33951","2014-01-23","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many previously foreign registered vehicles were re-registered with the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184184","184184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33952","2014-01-23","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to record details of foreign registered vehicles as they (a) enter and (b) exit the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184181","184181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33953","2014-01-28","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the new guidance on street clutter, including road humps, produced by the Department for Communities and Local Government, and published on 28 August 2013, what plans he has to update his Department's guidance on the installation of road humps.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184160","184160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33954","2014-01-22","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Advertising Standards Agency on counteracting misleading advertising claims for driving licence renewals.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184142","184142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33955","2014-01-23","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how the power required for High Speed 2 will be generated; and whether any new power stations will be needed to ensure there is sufficient capacity in the energy network for High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184158","184158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33956","2014-01-23","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many train operating companies (TOCs) have (a) applied for and (b) been awarded funding from the Access for All programme; to which TOCs such funding has been awarded; and for what purposes such funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184113","184113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33957","2014-01-23","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which railway stations do not have step free access; and what the annual footfall at each such station is.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184114","184114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33958","2014-01-22","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to upgrade railway stations on the South Fylde line.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183993","183993"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33959","2014-01-22","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps are being taken to limit disruption for rail passengers on the West Coast mainline during periods of extreme weather.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183994","183994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33960","2014-01-23","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support local economic partnerships in the application process for the local sustainable transport and walking schemes 2015-16.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184037","184037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33961","2014-01-22","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2014, Official Report, column 458W, on bus services: disability, if he will place a copy of the letter from the Parliamentary Under-Secretary of State to bus industry representatives on audio-visual systems for buses in the Library.","Biography information for Bridget Phillipson","Bridget Phillipson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184008","184008"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33962","2014-01-22","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the proportion of passenger rail journeys requiring (a) no change of train, (b) one change of train and (c) more than one change of train (i) in the last year for which data is available and (ii) in 1994.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184013","184013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33963","2014-01-23","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the benefits of open access for (a) the consumer and (b) the public purse.","Biography information for Dr Thérèse  Coffey","Dr Thérèse Coffey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184046","184046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33964","2014-01-22","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with representatives of the medical profession on the effect of drug driving legislation on patients; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184082","184082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33965","2014-01-23","Department for Transport","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an estimate of the cost to the public use of the Law Commission review of taxis and private hire vehicles over the life of the review.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184044","184044"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33966","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 6 January 2014, Official Report, column 50W, on EU social policy, which UK public funds are classified by the Government as (a) social assistance and (b) social security for the purposes of interpreting requirements of the EU Treaty.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184045","184045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33967","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many apprentices have been hired due to his Department's new contract for procurement.","Biography information for Robert Halfon","Robert Halfon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184083","184083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33968","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what support his Department provides to vulnerable people with filling in forms in order to ensure they receive the benefits to which they are entitled.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184092","184092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33969","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to housing benefit bulletin U1/2014, how many people who have wrongly had their housing benefit reduced have subsequently died.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184095","184095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33970","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to housing benefit bulletin U1/2014, what provision exists for reimbursing the estates of people who have wrongly had their housing benefit reduced and have subsequently died.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184096","184096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33971","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the quality and effectiveness of literacy and numeracy training provided by Jobcentre Plus and its training providers; and how such information is gathered.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184089","184089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33972","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance is provided to Jobcentre Plus advisers to help them advise customers who have been sanctioned of alternative sources of financial assistance or general advice.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184090","184090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33973","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average number of telephones was in each jobcentre to enable jobseekers to contact officials in his Department free of charge with benefit queries on 1 January (a) 2010, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184109","184109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33974","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what decision he has made on the case for using 03 telephone numbers for calls from members of the public with benefit queries.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184110","184110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33975","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's Annual Report and Accounts 2012-13, what the value of the funding that is subject to dual key arrangements is referred to in Table 1 on page 172.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184111","184111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33976","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what role he envisages for local authorities in the administration of universal credit.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184126","184126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33977","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what total number of telephones was available in the Jobcentre Plus network to enable jobseekers to contact officials in his Department free of charge with benefit queries on 1 January (a) 2010, (b) 2013 and (c) 2014.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184108","184108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33978","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many Remploy workers were made redundant as a result of the closure of Remploy in South Gyle, Edinburgh.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184100","184100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33979","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the quality and effectiveness of digital skills training provided by (a) Jobcentre Plus and (b) its training providers; and how this information is gathered.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184099","184099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33980","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether Jobcentre Plus districts are required to report on (a) the numbers of claimants they have identified as having a skills gap in ICT and (b) the number of these claimants who successfully complete a digital skills training course.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184098","184098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33981","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseekers were (a) identified as lacking basic ICT skills and (b) referred to training within Jobcentre Plus or with a training provider in each of the last two years.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184097","184097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33982","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what consideration has been given to the use of a national identity card system for determining eligibility for receipt of welfare payments.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184120","184120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33983","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on costs and compensation relating to legal action taken against it in each of the last five years for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184009","184009"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33984","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce unemployment among black and ethnic minority young people.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184040","184040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33985","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many times he has met the Mayor of London to discuss unemployment in London since May 2010.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184041","184041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33986","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of Atos using computer equipment on his Department's premises owing to data protection issues with the use of their own networks; and what comparative assessment he has made of this cost and the original tender price.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183988","183988"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33987","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that the Health and Safety Executive conduct regular inspections to ensure existing regulations are adhered to in the shale gas industry.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183996","183996"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33988","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons Atos is classified as a data processor rather than a data controller when carrying out work capability assessments.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184015","184015"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33989","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to safeguard the rights of UK pension holders whose pensions have been placed in the hands of companies that are based abroad.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184153","184153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33990","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the adequacy of resources provided to the Pensions Regulator.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184154","184154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33991","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received in relation to the application of Article 6 of the European Convention on Human Rights with regard to the lack of right of appeal against the imposition of ongoing child maintenance collection charge by the Child Maintenance Service.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184135","184135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33992","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will carry out an assessment of the potential effect of the under-occupancy penalty on foster carers who look after more than one child.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184106","184106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33993","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, by what date the Child Maintenance Service self-service portal for parents using the collect and pay service will be fully operational.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184137","184137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33994","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, in what circumstances the Child Maintenance Service will consider withdrawal of its collect and pay service from a parent with care who is using it and wishes to continue to use it; and what mechanism will be made available to parents with care to appeal a decision by the Secretary of State to withdraw access to the collect and pay service should they wish to continue using it.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184136","184136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33995","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria will be used by his Department in its operational readiness review in March 2014 to determine whether the new statutory child maintenance service is working sufficiently well to permit the introduction of fees to use the service and to begin to close down all Child Support Agency cases.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184134","184134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33996","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether Jobcentre Plus adviser skills workshops are part of a formal and mandatory training programme.","Biography information for Mike Crockart","Mike Crockart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184144","184144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33997","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Brigg and Goole constituency have had their benefit withdrawn for refusing to work in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Percy","Andrew Percy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 184183","184183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34037","2014-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to help build partnerships between businesses and universities.","Biography information for Eric Ollerenshaw","Eric Ollerenshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902138","902138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34082","2014-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of high street vacancy rates.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902130","902130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34303","2014-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-20","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of statistics on student participation in higher education.","Biography information for Mr Rob Wilson","Mr Rob Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902145","902145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33667","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he takes to ensure that there are not discrepancies between the number of people (a) paid employment and support allowance and (b) the number that work capability providers are paid to assess.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183955","183955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33668","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he takes to ensure that his Department's contracted providers do not charge for work capability assessments or work programme placements which people do not attend as they are no longer claiming benefit.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183956","183956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33669","2014-01-21","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress he has made on developing integrated risk management planning guidance since publication of the Fire and Rescue National Framework for England in July 2012; when the Integrated Risk Management Plan Steering Group has met since May 2010; and what plans he has to deliver the Fire and Rescue National Framework for England and associated risk management planning.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183948","183948"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33670","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of correlation between increased sanctioning and (a) jobseeking success rates, (b) incidents of abuse and assaults committed against staff in jobcentres and (c) referrals of claimants to foodbanks.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183949","183949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33671","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance and support his Department provides to people assessed as fit for work by ATOS and declined employment support allowance whilst awaiting reconsideration.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183950","183950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33672","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what definition he uses for (a) expectations for sanctions referrals and (b) targets for Jobcentre Plus staff.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183945","183945"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33673","2014-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the annual cost is to the Probation Service in England and Wales of supervising a person on licence for (a) 12, (b) 24 and (c) 36 months.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183946","183946"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33674","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his assessment of the effectiveness of the Work Programme will include (a) data on claimants returning to Jobcentre services and (b) a survey of the experiences of those completing the Work Programme.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183947","183947"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33675","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's statistics on sanctions published on 6 November 2013, if he will provide a breakdown of those statistics by (a) region and (b) equality groups as proportion of the claimant count.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183969","183969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33676","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) jobseeker's allowance and (b) employment and support allowance hardship claims have been made since July 2012.","Biography information for John McDonnell","John McDonnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183970","183970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33677","2014-01-21","Church Commissioners","2014-01-17","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what heirlooms of the see there are in relation to the Bishop's Palace at Wells.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183920","183920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33678","2014-01-21","Church Commissioners","2014-01-17","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what repairs or maintenance to the living accommodation of the Bishop of Bath and Wells in the Bishop's Palace in Wells were identified in the Church Commissioners' most recent Quinquennial Review; what the date was of that review; and what the anticipated costs were of any such repairs or maintenance.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183921","183921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33679","2014-01-21","Church Commissioners","2014-01-17","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, with reference to the future of the Bishop's Palace in Wells, what consultation has taken place between the Church Commissioners and (a) English Heritage and (b) any other individual or body qualified to advise the Commissioners under section 4 of the Episcopal Endowment and Stipend Measure 1943.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183934","183934"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33680","2014-01-21","Church Commissioners","2014-01-17","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, what consultation has taken place between the Church Commissioners and the Diocesan Advisory Committee in accordance with the terms of the Episcopal Endowment and Stipend Measure 1943 section 3(1) over the proposed new residence of the Bishop of Bath and Wells and the proposed change of use of the Bishop's Palace at Wells.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183937","183937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33681","2014-01-21","Church Commissioners","2014-01-17","To ask the right hon. Member for Banbury, representing the Church Commissioners, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2014, Official Report, column 1502W, on Bishop of Bath and Wells, what estimated (a) stamp duty and (b) other associated costs will be paid by the Church Commissioners for their purchase or proposed purchase of property to accommodate the new Bishop of Bath and Wells.","Biography information for Tessa Munt","Tessa Munt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183938","183938"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33682","2014-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what capital and revenue spend the Environment Agency has made in (a) Crawley and (b) Horsham parliamentary constituencies from May 2010 up to the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183933","183933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33683","2014-01-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had to bring forward a local television licence on the freeview platform for Leicester and Leicestershire.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183928","183928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33684","2014-01-22","Department for International Development","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether funds from her Department to support education in the Gaza Strip (a) support or (b) are ring fenced from the Pioneers of Liberation programme for school-aged children run by the Gazan ministries for education and the interior.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183930","183930"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33685","2014-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what (a) animal feeding and (b) toxicology trials have been undertaken on golden rice according to Codex Alimentarious guidelines.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183971","183971"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33686","2014-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he made of the total cost of the development of golden rice between 2000 and 2014.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183972","183972"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33687","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish the data his Department holds on the number of immigrants who have claimed benefits within three months of registering for a national insurance number in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183979","183979"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33688","2014-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of whether the genetically modified variety referred to as Golden Rice 3 is safe for human consumption.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183980","183980"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33689","2014-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information he holds concerning the uniformity, stability, yields and beta-carotene levels of the latest Indica varieties of golden rice.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183981","183981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33690","2014-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what information he holds relating to the persistence and availability of beta-carotene in golden rice which has been harvested, stored and cooked in normal domestic situations.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183982","183982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33691","2014-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what human feeding trials there have been relating to golden rice; and what information has been obtained from those trials relating to the safety of that form of rice for long-term consumption.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183973","183973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33692","2014-01-22","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make a comparative assessment of the merits of (a) golden rice and (b) green leafy vegetables in the diets of people with vitamin deficiency.","Biography information for Mr Michael Meacher","Mr Michael Meacher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183983","183983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33693","2014-01-21","Home Office","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the report by HM Chief Inspector of Prisons on an unannounced inspection of Harmondsworth Immigration Removal Centre on 5 to 16 August 2013, what assessment she has made of that report; and whether, and to what timescale, her Department will implement the recommendations in the report.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183953","183953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33694","2014-01-21","Home Office","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the report by HM Chief Inspector of Prisons on an unannounced inspection of Harmondsworth Immigration Removal Centre on 5 to 16 August 2013, what steps her Department plans to take to improve scrutiny of GEO Group UK Ltd management of Harmondsworth Immigration Removal Centre.","Biography information for Pete Wishart","Pete Wishart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183954","183954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33695","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what artwork is on display in the offices of each Minister in his Department; and what the estimated value is of each such artwork.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183940","183940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33696","2014-01-21","Cabinet Office","2014-01-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to improve the level of voluntary action around the safe use of Chinese lanterns.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183935","183935"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33697","2014-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure people are better aware of the risks of Chinese lanterns.","Biography information for Julian Sturdy","Julian Sturdy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183936","183936"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33698","2014-01-22","Department for International Development","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will increase her Department's support to the health systems of developing countries to help reduce migration of health workers from the developing world.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183939","183939"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33699","2014-01-22","Department for International Development","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the November 2013 report by the World Health Organisation entitled A Universal Truth: No Health Without a Workforce.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183963","183963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33700","2014-01-21","Department for Transport","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the draft scope for the A303 feasibility study.","Biography information for Sir Nick Harvey","Sir Nick Harvey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183926","183926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33701","2014-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will discuss the security of the Hazara community in Afghanistan and the effect on this community of the withdrawal of foreign troops from Afghanistan in 2014 at the Foreign Affairs Council planned for 20 January 2014.","Biography information for Mr Mike Thornton","Mr Michael Thornton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183951","183951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33702","2014-01-22","Department for Transport","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the most recent meeting of his Department's Cycle Safety Stakeholder Forum was held; and when the next such meeting is scheduled.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183925","183925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33703","2014-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of whether the UN is likely to approve a body to provide independent oversight to political reform in Bahrain following opposition to the National Commission appointed after the BICI report.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183923","183923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33704","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many complaints his Department received about the cost of telephone calls made by members of the public to officials in his Department in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183952","183952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33705","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the average cost of a telephone call from a member of the public to his Department.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183957","183957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33706","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects to publish his response to the consultation on Better Workplace Pensions: a consultation on charging, Cm 8738.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183929","183929"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33707","2014-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the average length of time taken by graduates to repay student loan debt under (a) the current fees and loan system and (b) its predecessor systems.","Biography information for Jeremy Lefroy","Jeremy Lefroy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183932","183932"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33708","2014-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions he has had with ministerial colleagues in other government departments regarding the use of Common Agricultural Policy Pillar 2 funding.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183927","183927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33709","2014-01-27","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when the main gate decision will be taken for the next generation of the Royal Navy's airborne surveillance and control capability; whether the Royal Navy's existing capability will continue at current levels until the successor system is available; what assessment he has made of the risks involved in any future gap in the Royal Navy's airborne surveillance and control capability; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Lewis","Dr Julian Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183965","183965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33710","2014-01-22","HM Treasury","2014-01-17","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each such contract following the contract award.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183962","183962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33711","2014-01-22","Cabinet Office","2014-01-17","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each such contract following the contract award.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183958","183958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33712","2014-01-22","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each such contract following the contract award.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183959","183959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33713","2014-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each such contract following the contract award.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183960","183960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33714","2014-01-22","Home Office","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what her Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps her Department has taken to monitor the performance of each such contract following the contract award.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183961","183961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33715","2014-01-21","Home Office","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent steps she has taken to ensure proper use of Government procurement cards in her Department; and what system is in place to prevent abuse of such cards.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183931","183931"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33716","2014-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish a list of all paper and electronic correspondence between (a) Ministers, (b) officials and (c) special advisers in his Department and Andrew Lyman, head of Public Affairs at William Hill plc, in the last three years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183924","183924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33717","2014-01-22","Prime Minister","2014-01-17","To ask the Prime Minister, if the review into events in Amritsar in 1984 will examine the role played by Gary Sazena and R.N. Kao of the Research and Analysis Wing of the Indian secret service; whether each such man visited the UK at any time; whether each such man received training in the UK; and what the nature was of intelligence provided to those individuals from the Government.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183943","183943"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33718","2014-01-22","Department for Transport","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what research he has recently commissioned on the safety and legality of the sale of part-worn tyres; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183944","183944"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33719","2014-01-22","Prime Minister","2014-01-17","To ask the Prime Minister, if he will place in the Library a copy of the correspondence dated 3 February 1984 from the Secretary of State for Foreign Affairs to the then Prime Minister proposing a response to the Indian government's request for advice on their plans for the Golden Temple; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183941","183941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33720","2014-01-22","Prime Minister","2014-01-17","To ask the Prime Minister, when he expects the review into the events in Amritsar in 1984 to be completed; if he will publish all withheld files on the matter that were not placed in the National Archives under the 30 Year Rule; and if copies of that review will be placed in the Library.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Mr Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183942","183942"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33721","2014-01-22","Department of Health","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients waited longer than four hours to be seen in accident and emergency in each of the first four weeks of January in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183964","183964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33722","2014-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether it is his policy to encourage social housing tenants to use HomeSwapper.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183975","183975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33723","2014-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that the UK is prepared for potential future diseases that may affect crops and livestock.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183966","183966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33724","2014-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what research his Department is currently conducting into potential diseases affecting wildlife which may arrive in the UK from overseas.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183967","183967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33725","2014-01-21","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he has taken to ensure that the UK is prepared for the arrival from overseas of diseases affecting crops and livestock.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183968","183968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33726","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent meetings officials in his Department have held with representatives of HomeSwapper.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183974","183974"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33727","2014-01-22","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to ensure that social housing tenants liable for the under-occupancy penalty are assisted in downsizing.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183978","183978"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33728","2014-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether it is his policy to encourage social housing landlords to pay for access to HomeSwapper.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183976","183976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33729","2014-01-22","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will encourage social housing landlords to inform tenants of the company HomeSwapper.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183977","183977"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33730","2014-01-21","Home Office","2014-01-17","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what target she has set for the uptake of the Disclosure and Barring Service's Update Service by employers and organisations; and what assessment she has made of the rate of progress towards that target.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183922","183922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33465","2014-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will publish all relevant documents outlining the extent of the UK's involvement in the 1984 Amritsar attack.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183797","183797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33466","2014-01-21","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Indian government about the release of Sikh prisoners.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183846","183846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33467","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 October 2013, Official Report, column 292, on maintaining the current appearance of uplands, if he will amend his policy so as to support farmers to reforest upland areas across the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183722","183722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33468","2014-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representation the UK intends to send to the second conference on the Humanitarian Consequences of Nuclear Weapons in Nayarit, Mexico on 13-14 February 2014.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183740","183740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33469","2014-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether any plutonium created in UK civilian (a) commercial reactors and (b) research reactors has been put to use in (i) nuclear weapons in the UK or elsewhere and (ii) other military uses since each reactor type first started operating in the UK.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183738","183738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33470","2014-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much plutonium arising from civil commercial reactors has been exported, to which countries and for which end-use since May 2010.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183739","183739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33471","2014-01-21","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients waited longer than four hours to be seen in accident and emergency departments in the first week of January in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183849","183849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33472","2014-01-20","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-16","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2014, Official Report, column 477W, on occupational health, what budgets were available for services provided to staff of the House to enhance their health and well-being by outside providers including occupational therapists, counselling, classes and other activities.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183758","183758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33473","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the NHS of prescriptions was for anti-depressant drugs in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183737","183737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33474","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions for anti-depressants were issued in (a) England, (b) each region of England and (c) each health authority area in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183743","183743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33475","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) men, (b) women and (c) children were referred through the NHS for counselling to treat depression and anxiety in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183744","183744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33476","2014-01-20","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-16","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps he has taken in advance of National Registration Day; and if he will create a National Registration (a) Week and (b) Month.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183756","183756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33477","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which drugs are the five most frequently prescribed in the NHS for treatment of anxiety and depression.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183732","183732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33478","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average waiting time was for access to NHS counselling services in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183727","183727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33479","2014-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports the Government has received of violations of international law taking place in Burma.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183719","183719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33480","2014-01-20","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the training of the Burmese army provided by his Department was (a) requested by the government of Burma or (b) initiated by the UK Government.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183720","183720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33481","2014-01-20","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what monitoring his Department plans to undertake to ensure that Burmese army soldiers trained by the UK are not subsequently involved in human rights abuses.","Biography information for Yasmin Qureshi","Yasmin Qureshi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183721","183721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33482","2014-01-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to improve the transparency of national governing bodies of lottery-funded sports.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183809","183809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33483","2014-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to enable remote attendance at meetings of English local authorities under conditions similar to those provided in section 4 provided in the Local Government (Wales) Measure 2011.","Biography information for Bob Stewart","Bob Stewart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183810","183810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33484","2014-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many times he has made representations to his Israeli counterpart on the situation in the Occupied Palestinian Territories in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183766","183766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33485","2014-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the financial effect of Ofgem's decision to remove the prompt payment discount.","Biography information for Sir Henry Bellingham","Mr Henry Bellingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183767","183767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33486","2014-01-21","Home Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many residential raids for immigration purposes were carried out between midnight and 8 am in the last 12 months; in how many of those cases children were expected to be present; and in how many of those cases one or more parent or guardian was removed.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183730","183730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33487","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department has met representatives to the Action on Smoking and Health charity since July 2013; how many such meetings have been held to discuss proposals for standardised tobacco packaging; and who was present at each such meeting.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183770","183770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33488","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding the Action on Smoking and Health charity received from his Department in the last year; and what assessment he has made of how these funds have been spent.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183771","183771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33489","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions he or his Department met an organisation, group or person to discuss tobacco control regulation in the last year; who attended each such meeting; which aspect of tobacco control was discussed at each such meeting; and what the date was of each such meeting.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183781","183781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33490","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, on how many occasions his Department met representatives of the charity Action on Smoking and Health to discuss the Tobacco Products Directive in the last year; and who was present at each such meeting.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183785","183785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33491","2014-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on the sale of Royal Navy buildings in Greenock which were formerly occupied by the Coastguard; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183775","183775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33492","2014-01-21","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many unfilled coastguard vacancies there are at Belfast Coastguard station.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183776","183776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33493","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the current performance of the Work Programme.","Biography information for Iain McKenzie","Iain McKenzie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183814","183814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33494","2014-01-21","Cabinet Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2014, Official Report, column 507W, on public sector: fraud, if he will provide details of the various data-sharing projects across government and the wider public sector that seek to access and share data in support of operational delivery, developing public services and improving efficiency; and if he will indicate how the work of each such project specifically relates to fraud.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183793","183793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33495","2014-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the effect of the rules limiting claimants of jobseeker's allowance taking up training on a part-time basis of less than 16 hours per week on levels of participation in training programmes in those constituent parts of the UK where the youth unemployment rate exceeds 7 per cent.","Biography information for Mr William Bain","Mr William Bain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183780","183780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33496","2014-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 10 December 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr K Joslin.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183746","183746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33497","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she intends to reply to the letter to her dated 2 December 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr Muhammad Asif.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183747","183747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33498","2014-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he intends to reply to the letter to him dated 13 November 2013 from the right hon. Member for Manchester, Gorton with regard to Mr A Ali.","Biography information for Sir Gerald Kaufman","Sir Gerald Kaufman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183745","183745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33499","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when Mr Wetherick of Christchurch will receive a decision from the Atos Medical Service Centre in Bristol as to whether he needs a medical assessment following the referral of his case by his Department on 16 May 2013; and when he expects Mr Wetherick's benefit application to be resolved.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183731","183731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33500","2014-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which local authority and obligated energy company partnerships planning to undertake solid wall house insulation through the Energy Company Obligation (ECO) which had been agreed in principle are now suspended or cancelled following changes to the configuration of the ECO.","Biography information for Dr Alan Whitehead","Dr Alan Whitehead","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183748","183748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33501","2014-01-21","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve enforcement of the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Mark Reckless","Mark Reckless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183816","183816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33502","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to (a) maximise the biodiversity benefits of high nature value (HNV) farming; and what steps he is taking to ensure that HNV farming is effectively monitored.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183890","183890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33503","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2014, Official Report, columns 470-1W, on bovine tuberculosis, how many of the 120 badgers which were subject to post mortem examination were found to have bovine tuberculosis.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183898","183898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33504","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2014, Official Report, columns 470-1W, on bovine tuberculosis, what steps he is taking to ensure the independence of the assessment of the effectiveness of the trials.","Biography information for Andrew George","Andrew George","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183899","183899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33505","2014-01-21","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will review his Department's guidance on the provision of insulin pumps on the NHS in light of National Institute for Health and Care Excellence recommendations on the use of pump therapy to treat Type 1 diabetes.","Biography information for Baroness Blackwood of North Oxford","Nicola Blackwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183817","183817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33506","2014-01-20","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-16","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what recent discussions he has had with contractors providing services to the House on their duty to monitor the undertakings of subcontractors, including payment of the London Living Wage to all staff.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183751","183751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33507","2014-01-21","Department for Education","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking to narrow the gap between the educational achievement of children in care and other young people.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183777","183777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33508","2014-01-21","Department for Education","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 18 November 2013, Official Report, columns 730-1W, on children in care, how many children's homes were run by (a) local authorities and (b) private or voluntary organisations in each region in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183778","183778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33509","2014-01-21","Department for Education","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2013, Official Report, columns 652-3W, on special educational needs, whether he holds any information on the numbers of First-tier Tribunal (Special Education Needs and Disability) appeals taking place in local authority areas across England.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183800","183800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33510","2014-01-21","Department for Education","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 3 December 2013, Official Report, columns 652-3W, on special educational needs, what measures his Department uses to identify best practice and value for money when collecting data.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183799","183799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33511","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his letter to the right hon. Member for North Somerset of 15 May 2013, what the evidential basis is for the statement that (a) muscular dystrophy is caused by mitochondrial disease and (b) cases of muscular dystrophy could be prevented by new techniques which aim to prevent mitochondrial disorders.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183835","183835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33512","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his letter to the right hon. Member for North Somerset of 15 May 2013, for what reason it was (a) stated that muscular dystrophy is caused by mitochondrial disease and (b) implied that cases of muscular dystrophy could be prevented by new techniques which aim to prevent mitochondrial disorders.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183836","183836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33513","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to his letter to the right hon. Member for North Somerset of 15 May 2013, what the evidential basis is for the statement that proposed new treatments to prevent mitochondrial disorders are not similar to cloning; and under what activities the Newcastle licence for pronuclear transfer (R0153) is covered.","Biography information for Dr Liam Fox","Dr Liam Fox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183837","183837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33514","2014-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will exclude war disablement pensions as a source of income when assessing benefits.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183742","183742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33515","2014-01-20","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many fixed rate business loans which have embedded swaps sold along with the loan have been made by Clydesdale and Yorkshire Banks in the last five years.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183784","183784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33516","2014-01-20","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of job losses arising through the alleged misselling of embedded swaps to businesses by the Clydesdale and Yorkshire Banks.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183783","183783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33517","2014-01-20","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what information he has received from the Financial Conduct Authority in relation to the misselling of embedded swaps in fixed rate business loans by (a) Clydesdale Bank and (b) Yorkshire Bank.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183782","183782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33518","2014-01-20","Women and Equalities","2014-01-16","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, if the Inspiring Women Campaign will be extended to Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183741","183741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33519","2014-01-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations she has received from amateur swimming clubs that closed because they have not been permitted to teach swimming to beginners through the ASA Aquatics Pathway scheme.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183827","183827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33520","2014-01-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many amateur swimming clubs operated in local authority swimming pools in (a) 2013, (b) 2012 and (c) 2011.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183828","183828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33521","2014-01-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many local authority swimming pool operators in the UK have implemented the ASA Aquatics Pathway scheme since its introduction.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183825","183825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33522","2014-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to encourage local enterprise partnerships (LEPs) to encourage inward investment to their area; and what guidance he gives LEPs on steps they should take to differentiate their area from other parts of the UK.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183764","183764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33523","2014-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions were brought under the Data Protection Act 1998 in relation to unsolicited telephone calls in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183853","183853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33524","2014-01-21","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether specifications for the replacement of Northern and Transpennine franchises will require prospective operators to maintain or improve (a) station staffing levels and (b) ticket office provision and opening hours.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183854","183854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33525","2014-01-21","Cabinet Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many redundancy payments were made to employees of central government departments in each of the last three years; and what the total expenditure on redundancy payments was in each such year.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183850","183850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33526","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) full-time and (b) part-time vacancies were advertised in Jobcentre Plus in Barrow and Furness constituency in each quarter in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183851","183851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33527","2014-01-21","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people in Cumbria joined the Territorial Army in each of the last five years.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183852","183852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33528","2014-01-22","Department for International Development","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what humanitarian assistance her Department gives the Philippines to help prevent online sex abuse of Filipino children in poverty by paedophiles based in the UK.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183919","183919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33529","2014-01-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to reply to the letter from the right hon. Member for Hazel Grove of 23 July 2013 regarding funding for junior potential paralympians.","Biography information for Lord Stunell","Sir Andrew Stunell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183896","183896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33530","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent general practitioners were employed in general practices in Fareham constituency in (a) 2008-09, (b) 2009-10, (c) 2010-11, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14 to date.","Biography information for Mr Mark Hoban","Mr Mark Hoban","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183811","183811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33531","2014-01-21","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether additional electric rolling stock will be fully operational in passenger service in the North West before the December 2014 timetable change.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183845","183845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33532","2014-01-21","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the recent Request for Proposals to Northern Rail included an option for modern or refurbished electric rolling stock.","Biography information for Julie Hilling","Julie Hilling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183844","183844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33533","2014-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 9 January 2014, Official Report, column 330W, on National Careers Service, what estimate has been made of the proportion of careers advisers who will be qualified to level six by January 2015.","Biography information for Graham Stuart","Mr Graham Stuart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183903","183903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33534","2014-01-21","Department for International Development","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what aid the Government gives to countries with laws that discriminate against homosexuality.","Biography information for Mr Jim Murphy","Mr Jim Murphy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183902","183902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33535","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were seconded from the private sector to his Department in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183789","183789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33536","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on boosting the literacy and numeracy of jobseekers in each Government Office region in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183790","183790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33537","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether, in a case where a Work Programme participant has an appointment with a provider but then agrees with the provider to attend at a different date, and does so, the provider should make a report which could lead to a benefit sanction; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183791","183791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33538","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many jobseekers received a sanction from Jobcentre Plus in each of the last five years; and how many such sanctions were initiated by a report from a private-sector provider.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183792","183792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33539","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the cost to (a) the Exchequer and (b) individual incomes if eligibility for universal credit were established using gross rather than net income.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183772","183772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33540","2014-01-21","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent progress he has made against his target of increasing the number of health visitors by 50 per cent by 2015.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183813","183813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33541","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2014, Official Report, column 414W, on health: children, if he will commission a sample study or a review of sample studies to discover the levels of unfitness in school children.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183886","183886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33542","2014-01-20","Attorney General","2014-01-16","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2014, Official Report, column 428W, on the Serious Fraud Office (SFO), what responses the Director of the SFO has received to his letters.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183889","183889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33543","2014-01-20","Department for International Development","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2013, Official Report, column 366W, on developing countries: genetically modified organisms, when she expects to be able to assess the results of those independent studies.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183887","183887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33544","2014-01-20","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 8 January 2014, Official Report, column 444W, on piracy, what discussions he has had with his counterparts in partner nations on extending the mandates of the anti-piracy operations beyond 2014.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183888","183888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33545","2014-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2014, Official Report, column 337W, on electricity: ICT, what discussions he has had with other government departments on working with data centres to reduce energy usage.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183885","183885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33546","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2013, Official Report, column 438W, on offenders: deportation, what steps she is taking to deport Paulo Sapstyn.","Biography information for John Spellar","Mr John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183897","183897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33547","2014-01-20","Department for Education","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many qualified school nurses there were in (a) Portsmouth South constituency and (b) Hampshire in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183754","183754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33548","2014-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Portsmouth South constituency under the age of 25 years old are recipients of housing benefit.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183755","183755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33549","2014-01-21","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the written Answer of 14 January 2014, Official Report, column 544W, on Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation, what the membership of the meningococcal sub-committee was; and who was responsible for appointment to that committee.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183904","183904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33550","2014-01-21","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the draft Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation minutes of 2 October 2013, was assessment has been made of how many children would be ineligible for the Bexsero vaccine under the proposed formula.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183905","183905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33551","2014-01-21","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings he has held with representatives of the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation since 2 October 2013.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183906","183906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33552","2014-01-21","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of signatories to the Public Health Responsibility Deal with regard to the pledges dealing with (a) construction and civil engineering industries, (b) domestic violence, (c) improving the health of young employees, (d) mental health and well-being, (e) staff health checks and (f) smoking cessation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183907","183907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33553","2014-01-21","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department as an employer has signed up to (a) the Public Health Responsibility Deal and (b) the sub-pledges regarding (i) construction and civil engineering industries, (ii) domestic violence, (iii) improving the health of young employees, (iv) mental health and well-being, (v) staff health checks and (f) smoking cessation.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183908","183908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33554","2014-01-21","Cabinet Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what representations the Minister without Portfolio, the right hon. Member for Rushcliffe, received from representatives of British American Tobacco; and how many meetings he has held with such representatives since May 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183819","183819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33555","2014-01-21","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions his Department has had with Ministers or officials from the Scottish Government on (a) new taxes and (b) devolution of taxes under provisions contained in the Scotland Act 2012 since that Act came into force.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183839","183839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33556","2014-01-21","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of legal action by the Government on the proposed EU cap on bankers' bonuses.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183840","183840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33557","2014-01-21","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of (a) internal and (b) external legal work on the Government's court action against the EU plan to cap bonus payments in the financial industries.","Biography information for Gregg McClymont","Gregg McClymont","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183841","183841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33558","2014-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of trends in levels of manufacturing activity in Leicester and Leicestershire.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183794","183794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33559","2014-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many UK Trade & Investment employees based in the East Midlands were employed on attracting inward investment to Leicester in 2013.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183795","183795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33560","2014-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many companies registered in (a) Leicester South constituency and (b) Leicester city are classified as (i) small and (ii) medium-sized as defined by the Companies Act 1985.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183796","183796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33561","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the additional £120 million allocated in Autumn Statement 2012 for flood protection in England in 2013-14 and 2014-15 that has been allocated to the (a) Lower Don Valley in Sheffield, (b) Ipswich tidal barrier, (c) Derby riverside area and (d) Exeter flood defence schemes will come (i) from departmental revenue and capital expenditure and (ii) through a standard partnership funding framework.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183874","183874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33562","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the additional £120 million provided in Autumn Statement 2012 for flood protection in England in 2013-14 and 2014-15 has been allocated to the (a) Lower Don Valley in Sheffield, (b) Ipswich tidal barrier, (c) Derby riverside area and (d) Exeter flood defence schemes; and what stage of construction each such scheme has reached.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183875","183875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33563","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of the £148 million proposed to be secured from external non-governmental funding for anti-flooding measures in 2011-12 to 2014-15 is proposed to be generated by (a) income, (b) income committed from each source and (c) allocated to each flood protection scheme.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183876","183876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33564","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding for flood protection had been raised through a standard partnership funding framework on 31 December 2013.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183877","183877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33565","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much funding for flood protection in planned to be raised through a standard partnership funding framework in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183878","183878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33566","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which 50 flood defence schemes have been prioritised by the Environment Agency; how much has been allocated to each scheme; and what the construction status is of each such scheme.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183879","183879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33567","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the additional £120 million provided in Autumn Statement 2012 for flood protection in England for 2013-14 and 2014-15 is intended to be secured through a standard partnership funding framework.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183880","183880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33568","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the additional £120 million provided in Autumn Statement 2012 for flood protection in England for (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15 had been secured through a standard partnership funding framework on 31 December 2013.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183881","183881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33569","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which projects and schemes have (a) been allocated and (b) received how much funding from the additional £120 million provided in Autumn Statement 2012 for flood protection in England in (i) 2013-14 and (ii) 2014-15.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183883","183883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33570","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much of the additional £120 million provided in Autumn Statement 2012 for flood protection in England for (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014-15 has been allocated to a specific flood defence scheme to date.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183882","183882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33571","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much and what proportion of Common Agricultural Policy Pillar 2 funding he plans to allocate to (a) fostering knowledge transfer and innovation, (b) enhancing competitiveness, productivity and farm viability, (c) promoting food chain organisation and risk management, (d) restoring, preserving and enhancing ecosystems, (e) promoting resource efficiency and supporting the shift towards a low carbon and (f) promoting social inclusion, poverty reduction and economic development in rural areas in each year to 2017-18.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183900","183900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33572","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much his Department spend on (a) maintaining existing flood defences and (b) new flood defences in each year between 2009-10 and 2013-14; and what his Department's (i) revenue, (ii) capital and (iii) total expenditure on flood protection is planned for each year to 2024-25.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183901","183901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33573","2014-01-20","Department for Education","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183863","183863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33574","2014-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183857","183857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33575","2014-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183864","183864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33576","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183865","183865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33577","2014-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183866","183866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33578","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183867","183867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33579","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many EU directives her Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in her Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183868","183868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33580","2014-01-20","Department for International Development","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many EU directives her Department and non-departmental public body has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in her Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183869","183869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33581","2014-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183870","183870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33582","2014-01-20","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183871","183871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33583","2014-01-20","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183872","183872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33584","2014-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183873","183873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33585","2014-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183860","183860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33586","2014-01-20","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many EU directives her Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in her Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183861","183861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33587","2014-01-20","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183862","183862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33588","2014-01-20","Attorney General","2014-01-16","To ask the Attorney General, how many EU directives the Law Officers' Departments have transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183858","183858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33589","2014-01-20","Cabinet Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many EU directives his Department has transposed into UK law since 2010; and how many directly acting EU regulations have come into effect in his Department's area of responsibility in the same period.","Biography information for John Redwood","Mr John Redwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183859","183859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33590","2014-01-20","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, in what order the Surface Common Combat System Version 1 will be installed on the Type 23 fleet.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183894","183894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33591","2014-01-20","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions his Department's IT system used for emails has failed in the East of Scotland in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183895","183895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33592","2014-01-20","Cabinet Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government is taking to relocate public sector jobs to areas of England with low rates of gross value added.","Biography information for Mr Adrian Sanders","Mr Adrian Sanders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183723","183723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33593","2014-01-21","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on extending existing financial guarantees to the Energy Technologies Institute; and what recent discussions he has had about extending such guarantees.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183779","183779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33594","2014-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when his letter to the Skills Funding Agency on funding for 2014-15 will be published; and what the reasons are for the time taken to publish that letter.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183729","183729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33595","2014-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the Resource Accounting and Budgeting charge for each cohort of students entering university from 2005 to 2012.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Mr Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183815","183815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33596","2014-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives of the Skills Funding Agency on the number of qualifications that have been removed in the last three years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183752","183752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33597","2014-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Skills Funding Agency on the provision of specialist courses that attract fewer than 100 entrants in an academic year.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183734","183734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33598","2014-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment his Department has made of the range of qualifications available for the study of fashion and textiles.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183733","183733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33599","2014-01-21","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will meet Google to discuss the profits that company makes from copycat websites which charge for the tax return service and appear above Government department and agency websites in search results; and if he will highlight to them the importance of taking steps to ensure that websites with the .gov.uk domain are used solely for these services.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183801","183801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33600","2014-01-21","Home Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will meet Google to discuss the profits they make from copycat websites which charge for passport renewals and appear above Government department and agency websites in search results.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183798","183798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33601","2014-01-20","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions he has had with the rail industry on the maintenance of electronic ticket machines at stations.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183763","183763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33602","2014-01-20","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent steps his Department has taken to (a) publicise and (b) support debt advice services.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183759","183759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33603","2014-01-20","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he intends to take against train operators who do not decrease the time taken to buy a ticket.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183762","183762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33604","2014-01-20","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many times since May 2010 he has used his statutory powers to require train operators to comply with the terms of their franchise agreements to use reasonable endeavours to ensure that passengers do not have to queue at a ticket office for more than five minutes during periods of peak demand or for more than three minutes at any other time.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183761","183761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33605","2014-01-20","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent meetings his Department has held with civil society organisations on personal debt advice; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Mr David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183760","183760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33606","2014-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received on the importing of furniture that does not meet the requirements in the Furniture and Furnishings (Fire) (Safety) Regulations 1988; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183749","183749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33607","2014-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the inherent and post-mitigation risk is to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme of a failure to have in place a robust operational design.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183802","183802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33608","2014-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the inherent and post-mitigation risk is to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme if complex human resource issues such as grievances cannot be resolved within the exact timescales.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183803","183803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33609","2014-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the inherent and post-mitigation risk is to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme from difficult and protracted union negotiations.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183804","183804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33610","2014-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the inherent and post-mitigation risk is to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme if the Payment by Results model does not encourage contract providers to invest in services.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183805","183805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33611","2014-01-20","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the inherent and post-mitigation risk is to the Transforming Rehabilitation Probation programme from increased costs, lack of funding and pension issues which are unresolved.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183806","183806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33613","2014-01-20","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reasons the Government asked for the removal of Article 6(e) from the EU Commission's proposal for a revision of Regulation 2027/97/EC; and what his Department's policy is on Article 6(e) of that proposal.","Biography information for Sir Peter Luff","Sir Peter Luff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183765","183765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33614","2014-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what assessment he has made of the potential contribution of fracking to the energy mix in the UK.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183892","183892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33615","2014-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent representations he has received on planning applications in respect of fracking; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183893","183893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33616","2014-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he has made on the review of the balance of competitiveness of the EU.","Biography information for Baroness McIntosh of Pickering","Miss Anne McIntosh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183891","183891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33617","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to raise awareness of the prevention, early identification and treatment of hepatitis C.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183787","183787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33618","2014-01-20","Department for Education","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the conclusions of the research commissioned by the Association of Colleges on the effect of the reduction in funding for 18 year olds on students from disadvantaged areas and Black, minority and ethnic students.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183807","183807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33619","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the number of adults with high blood cholesterol in England.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183736","183736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33620","2014-01-20","Department for Education","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the quality assurance auditing process for the new Traineeship Programme is; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183769","183769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33621","2014-01-20","Department for Education","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many small and medium-sized enterprises have offered placements to people aged 16 to 23 years old as part of the Traineeship Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183768","183768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33622","2014-01-20","Department for International Development","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she has made to her Burmese counterpart on minimising threats to humanitarian staff and aid operations in Rakhine state.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183725","183725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33623","2014-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his counterpart in Thailand to encourage that country to provide safe shelter to Rohingya children and their families who arrive there by boat.","Biography information for Rushanara Ali","Rushanara Ali","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183726","183726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33624","2014-01-20","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he is satisfied that the guidance contained in the Chief Medical Officer's letter to GPs and hospitals on the illegality of sex-selective abortions has been followed; and if he will publish the evidence upon which he bases that judgement.","Biography information for Jim Dobbin","Jim Dobbin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183812","183812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33625","2014-01-20","Department for International Development","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much Official Development Assistance funding, adjusted participation was allocated to the Ministry of Defence in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12 and (d) 2012-13.","Biography information for Mr Gavin Shuker","Gavin Shuker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183757","183757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33626","2014-01-21","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what terms of reference were used by his Department in selecting a preferred candidate for the role of Independent Assessor with responsibility for reviewing contributions made to the Phase 1 HS2 Environmental Statement consultation.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183773","183773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33627","2014-01-21","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, who has been chosen to act as Independent Assessor in respect of the current Phase 1 HS2 Environmental Statement consultation; whether his Department chose the candidates to fulfil the role of Independent Assessor; and what compensation is payable to the Independent Assessor.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183774","183774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33628","2014-01-21","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether further changes will be made to the HS2 Phase one Environmental Statement in the event of mistakes of fact being identified in that document.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183728","183728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33629","2014-01-23","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much private sector investment the Government has attracted since 2010 to help provide long-term sustainable energy solutions.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183914","183914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33630","2014-01-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress has been made on plans to increase house building by 2030.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183915","183915"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33631","2014-01-23","Attorney General","2014-01-16","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions in 2013 he referred a criminal sentence to the Court of Appeal for review because it was felt to be unduly lenient.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183916","183916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33632","2014-01-23","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what progress his Department has made on addressing issues regarding ATOS testing for disability benefit claimants.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183917","183917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33633","2014-01-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how the Greater Birmingham City Deal will address the imbalance of private sector growth; and what effect it will have on neighbouring towns.","Biography information for Karen Lumley","Karen Lumley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183918","183918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33634","2014-01-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she is taking to ensure that housing estates sited across council boundaries have access to uniform broadband speeds.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183847","183847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33635","2014-01-21","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the availability and speed of broadband in housing estates sited across council boundaries.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183848","183848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33636","2014-01-20","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to enable the hydrogen fuel industry to compete effectively and secure a position for itself as a viable part of the transport mix.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183786","183786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33637","2014-01-20","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to support the hydrogen fuelling market; and what the Government's proposed timeline for implementing these measures is.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183808","183808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33638","2014-01-21","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether Learn Direct will receive compensation following the legal challenge by Pearson Driving Assessments to the awarding of the theory test contract.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183818","183818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33639","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will order an inquiry into the police handling of the fatal shooting of Mark Duggan.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183788","183788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33640","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she has taken to identify and discipline (a) Metropolitan Police officers and (b) members of the Independent Police Complaints Commission who claimed after his death that Mark Duggan had exchanged gunfire with officers.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183753","183753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33641","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, who ordered the vehicle in which Mark Duggan had been travelling to be removed from the crime scene without forensic examination.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183750","183750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33642","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make it her policy that when police officers are involved in the shooting of civilians, the officers involved are immediately interviewed separately about the incident.","Biography information for Mr George Galloway","Mr George Galloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183724","183724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33643","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how his Department will measure benefits to farmers from the implementation of the recommendations of the MacDonald Taskforce.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183821","183821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33644","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how he intends to implement those recommendations of the MacDonald report concerned with earned recognition.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183822","183822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33645","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the cost to the public purse has been of policing the badger cull for the (a) original six week period and (b) extension period in (i) Gloucestershire and (ii) Somerset.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183823","183823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33646","2014-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps he plans to take to increase the number of Energy Company Obligation installations in rural areas; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183824","183824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33647","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how his Department plans to measure any benefits to farmers arising from implementation of the recommendations of the Macdonald Taskforce on farming regulation.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183838","183838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33648","2014-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, on which sites in the UK fracking for oil has taken place in the last five years; how many complaints have been received by the Envrionment Agency about such fracking; and what assessments the Environment Agency has made of the risks (a) of earthquakes or tremors and (b) associated with waste water disposal in each site.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183884","183884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33649","2014-01-20","Northern Ireland Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, when she or Ministers in her Department have discussed banking issues with the Co-operative Bank since 2010.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183830","183830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33650","2014-01-20","Attorney General","2014-01-16","To ask the Attorney General, how many bankers have been prosecuted by the (a) Serious Fraud Office and (b) Crown Prosecution Service for financial crimes in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183831","183831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33651","2014-01-20","Prime Minister","2014-01-16","To ask the Prime Minister, what resources of his Office were used to invite Conservative councillors to a meeting in Beckingham on 13 January 2014.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183832","183832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33652","2014-01-20","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions on fracking he has had with his European counterparts.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183833","183833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33653","2014-01-21","HM Treasury","2014-01-16","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what changes in business rates for power stations have been made in the last three months; and on what date those changes were published.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183842","183842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33654","2014-01-21","Department for Education","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which academy schools in Bassetlaw constituency have been referred to his Department for investigation in the last 12 months; and what the (a) reasons for and (b) outcomes of such investigations were.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183843","183843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33655","2014-01-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what financial assistance was given to Bassetlaw council for the (a) police commissioner elections in 2013, (b) Parliamentary elections in 2010 and (c) European elections in 2009.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183829","183829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33656","2014-01-20","Attorney General","2014-01-16","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions have been initiated by each Crown Prosecution Service area in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183826","183826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33657","2014-01-20","Prime Minister","2014-01-16","To ask the Prime Minister, in what capacity he met local Conservative councillors in Beckingham on 13 January 2014; and on how many occasions in 2013 he met Conservative councillors without inviting the hon. Member or councillors for the area in which the meeting took place.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183834","183834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33658","2014-01-21","Department for Transport","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on what occasions since May 2010 disaster planning arrangements have been initiated as a result of an aeroplane having difficulty landing at UK airports.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183820","183820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33659","2014-01-21","Department of Health","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each supplier of such contract following the contract award.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183909","183909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33660","2014-01-21","Department for Education","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each supplier of such contract following the contract award.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183910","183910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33661","2014-01-21","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each supplier of such contract following the contract award.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183911","183911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33662","2014-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each supplier of such contract following the contract award.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183912","183912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33663","2014-01-21","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his Department's 10 largest contracts let since the financial year 2010-11 are; what savings have been made in such contracts; what the level of overspend or underspend was in each such contract; and what steps his Department has taken to monitor the performance of each supplier of such contract following the contract award.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183913","183913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33664","2014-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many non-medical scientists have been found to have committed research misconduct in the last 30 years.","Biography information for Lord Lilley","Mr Peter Lilley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183735","183735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33665","2014-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the Malaysian government about the confiscation of Bibles by Islamic authorities in that country.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183855","183855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33666","2014-01-23","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the extent of religious freedom in Malaysia.","Biography information for John Glen","John Glen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183856","183856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33871","2014-01-22","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the human rights situation in Bahrain.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902110","902110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/34200","2014-01-22","Department for International Development","2014-01-16","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department has taken relating to the effect of dementia on developing countries to support the Prime Minister's Dementia Challenge and the Dementia Summit.","Biography information for Paul Burstow","Paul Burstow","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 902101","902101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33024","2014-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make changes to the Atos assessment system to make sure that those with severe progressive conditions, who would struggle to find employment, are not deemed fit to work by Atos.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183620","183620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33025","2014-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department has issued to Atos Healthcare on the fitness to work of those with (a) multiple scelrosis and (b) other severe progressive conditions.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183621","183621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33026","2014-01-21","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what conditions his Department places on Post Office Ltd to provide services in the event of the retirement of a sub-postmaster.","Biography information for Sir Robert Smith","Sir Robert Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183452","183452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33027","2014-01-17","HM Treasury","2014-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria have been set by each bank in receipt of public money for qualification for senior staff bonuses; whether the Prudential Regulation Authority plays a role in the ratification of such criteria; and whether his Department has provided any guidance to the remuneration committees of such banks on bonus payments.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183487","183487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33028","2014-01-17","HM Treasury","2014-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent representations he has received opposing the payment of bonuses to employees of banks in receipt of funds from the public purse.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183488","183488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33029","2014-01-17","HM Treasury","2014-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what guidelines (a) UK Financial Investments and (b) the Prudential Regulation Authority have established to govern bonuses paid to senior bank executives.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183489","183489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33030","2014-01-17","HM Treasury","2014-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it the policy of UK Financial Investments that any financial institutions in receipt of public money which have a policy of paying end-of-year bonuses publish the payments and their recipients at the time the payment is made.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183490","183490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33031","2014-01-17","HM Treasury","2014-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on placing a Minister or other departmental representative on the board of directors of those banks in receipt of public funds and support; and if he will consider appointing as non-executive directors to the boards of banks in receipt of public funds for recapitalisation representatives from the (a) bankworkers' trade union and (b) third sector.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183491","183491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33032","2014-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 29 October 2013, Official Report, column 415W, on Children and Young Persons Act 1933, what consultation or other steps he has taken on legislating to bring social and electronic media explicitly within section 39 of the Children and Young Persons Act 1933.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183569","183569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33033","2014-01-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183630","183630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33034","2014-01-17","Attorney General","2014-01-15","To ask the Attorney General, which buildings occupied by the Law Officers' Departments are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183631","183631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33035","2014-01-17","Cabinet Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183632","183632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33036","2014-01-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183633","183633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33037","2014-01-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, which buildings occupied by her Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183634","183634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33038","2014-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183635","183635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33039","2014-01-17","Department for Education","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183636","183636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33040","2014-01-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183637","183637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33041","2014-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183638","183638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33042","2014-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183639","183639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33043","2014-01-17","Department of Health","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183640","183640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33044","2014-01-17","Home Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which buildings occupied by her Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183641","183641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33045","2014-01-17","Department for International Development","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which buildings occupied by her Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183642","183642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33046","2014-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183643","183643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33047","2014-01-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, which buildings occupied by her Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183644","183644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33048","2014-01-17","Scotland Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183645","183645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33049","2014-01-17","Department for Transport","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183646","183646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33050","2014-01-17","HM Treasury","2014-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183647","183647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33051","2014-01-17","Wales Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183648","183648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33052","2014-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which buildings occupied by his Department are owned or part-owned privately; what the total value is of the rent paid to private landlords for the use of such buildings for official duties; and to whom such rent is paid.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183649","183649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33053","2014-01-17","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-15","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what assessment he has made of the potential for the provision of mindfulness for the staff of the House in improving wellbeing.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183714","183714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33054","2014-01-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-15","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what the average cost of registering additional non-voters was in each of the last six years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183571","183571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33055","2014-01-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-01-15","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, which electoral registration campaigns have been the most successful in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183572","183572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33056","2014-01-17","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-15","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, what assessment he has made of (a) job satisfaction, (b) absenteeism rates and (c) staff turnover rates of staff of the House.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183557","183557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33057","2014-01-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-15","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of voter registration drives run by Bite the Ballot and of whether there are any lessons for his Department's policy in such drives.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183568","183568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33058","2014-01-17","Speaker's Committee on the Electorial Commission","2014-01-15","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how much was spent on each electoral registration campaign in each of the last 10 years; and how many voters were registered as a result of each such campaign.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183573","183573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33059","2014-01-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-15","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what meetings his Department has had with the National Union of Students on increasing electoral registration rates for students.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183565","183565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33060","2014-01-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-15","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what the registration rates were for attainers in each year for which data are available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183555","183555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33061","2014-01-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-15","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what assessment he has made of levels of co-operation between (a) the Student Loans Company, (b) local authority student council tax exemption departments and (c) the national insurance card department in automatically sending out voter registration forms to all their clients.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183566","183566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33062","2014-01-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-15","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what support his Department has given to the National Voter Registration Day run by Bite the Ballot.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183567","183567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33063","2014-01-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment he has made of the effect on registration levels of attainers in Northern Ireland of the introduction of individual voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183431","183431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33064","2014-01-17","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-01-15","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what steps his Department has taken to engage with young people to increase voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183453","183453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33065","2014-01-20","Department for International Development","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether she plans to allocate development aid equal to 0.7 per cent of UK Gross National Income in 2014-15; and what estimate she has made of this allocation in cash terms.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183675","183675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33066","2014-01-20","Cabinet Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the change in the aggregate household debt in the UK was between 1 July 2010 and 1 July 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183676","183676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33067","2014-01-20","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, following a recent report on the significant reduction in numbers of the West African lion in recent years, if she will take steps to assist in the prevention of the continuation of the significant decline.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183677","183677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33068","2014-01-20","Cabinet Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to his Department's freedom of information case FOI318708, on what date he plans to publish the latest review of the Precedent Book.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183404","183404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33069","2014-01-20","Cabinet Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, from whom clearance for his Department's response to freedom of information case FOI318708 was required; and for what reason such clearance was required.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183405","183405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33070","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average and (b) maximum length of time is that a person who has been defined as an age dispute case has been held in an immigration removal centre pending release to local authority care in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183483","183483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33071","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been detained in immigration removal centres for the purpose of age assessment in the last 12 months; and how many were found to be (a) adults and (b) children.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183481","183481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33072","2014-01-20","Home Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the (a) average and (b) maximum length of time is that a person has been held in an immigration removal centre pending an age assessment in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183482","183482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33073","2014-01-17","Department for Transport","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason buses are not required to have audio-visual announcements for accessibility in the same way as trains; and if he will make it his policy to introduce such a requirement.","Biography information for Dr Julian Huppert","Dr Julian Huppert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183530","183530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33074","2014-01-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent progress has been made on establishing EU free trade agreements.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183425","183425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33075","2014-01-17","Department for Education","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what his policy is on extending the pupil premium plus to school children adopted before December 2005.","Biography information for Steve Brine","Steve Brine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183510","183510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33076","2014-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2014, Official Report, column 447W, on employment and support allowance, if his Department will collect data on mandatory reconsiderations of employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183536","183536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33077","2014-01-17","Department of Health","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what his policy is on extending access to proton beam therapy on the NHS.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183423","183423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33078","2014-01-17","Department of Health","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, for what reasons UK patients are only funded to undergo proton beam therapy in US and not other countries.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183424","183424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33079","2014-01-17","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183650","183650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33080","2014-01-17","Women and Equalities","2014-01-15","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in the Government Equalities Office in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183661","183661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33081","2014-01-17","Department of Health","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183662","183662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33082","2014-01-17","Home Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183663","183663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33083","2014-01-17","House of Commons Commission","2014-01-15","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in the House of Commons Service in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183664","183664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33084","2014-01-17","Department for International Development","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183665","183665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33085","2014-01-17","Ministry of Justice","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183666","183666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33086","2014-01-17","Northern Ireland Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183667","183667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33087","2014-01-17","Cabinet Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in No. 10 Downing Street in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183668","183668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33088","2014-01-17","Scotland Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183669","183669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33089","2014-01-17","Department for Transport","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183670","183670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33090","2014-01-17","HM Treasury","2014-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183671","183671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33091","2014-01-17","Wales Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183672","183672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33092","2014-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183673","183673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33093","2014-01-17","Attorney General","2014-01-15","To ask the Attorney General, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in the Law Officers' Departments in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183651","183651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33094","2014-01-17","Cabinet Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183652","183652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33095","2014-01-17","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183653","183653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33096","2014-01-17","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in her Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183654","183654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33097","2014-01-17","Ministry of Defence","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183655","183655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33098","2014-01-17","Cabinet Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in =the Deputy Prime Minister's Office in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183656","183656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33099","2014-01-17","Department for Education","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183657","183657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33100","2014-01-17","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183658","183658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33101","2014-01-17","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183659","183659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33102","2014-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many people aged (a) 16 and under and (b) over 16 years old undertook work experience in his Department in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183660","183660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33103","2014-01-20","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 13 January 2014, Official Report, column 374W, on Perkins Engineering Review, whether he plans to make a formal response to the review.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183683","183683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33104","2014-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on the firing on civilians by the Burmese Army at Nam Lin Pa Internally Displaced Person camp in Kachin State when they attacked it in November 2013.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183580","183580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33105","2014-01-17","Department for International Development","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether any (a) rice and (b) other humanitarian aid stolen by Burmese Army soldiers in the Nam Lin Pa Internally Displaced Person camp in Kachin State, Burma, in November 2013 was supplied by any agency or organisation funded by her Department.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183581","183581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33106","2014-01-17","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government has taken to ensure that Burmese Army soldiers committing acts of sexual violence in conflict are held accountable for their crimes.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183564","183564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33107","2014-01-17","Department of Health","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will introduce a free-of-charge vaccination programme for children under five for meningococcal B meningitis.","Biography information for Naomi Long","Naomi Long","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183579","183579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33108","2014-01-17","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what advice he has given to ATOS relating to the Armed Forces Covenant when considering assessments in relation to the work capability assessments of former members of HM armed forces; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183393","183393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33109","2014-01-17","Home Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether she plans to change the tendering process for statutory recovery contracts during the current Parliament.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183421","183421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33110","2014-01-17","Home Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what procedures are in place for her Department to oversee the statutory recovery contract tendering process.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183422","183422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33111","2014-01-17","Home Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when her Department plans to complete and publish the national anti-corruption action plan.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183394","183394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33112","2014-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if the Government will assist the Overseas Territories to set up public registers of beneficial company ownership.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183409","183409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33113","2014-01-20","Department for International Development","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to reduce preventable newborn mortality in Liberia.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183410","183410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33114","2014-01-20","Department for International Development","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps her Department is taking to reduce preventable newborn mortality in Sierra Leone.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183411","183411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33115","2014-01-20","HM Treasury","2014-01-15","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what advice his Department has given to the Overseas Territories on public registers of beneficial ownership.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183412","183412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33116","2014-01-20","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has (a) written or (b) spoken to the leaders of any of the Overseas Territories to encourage them to create public registries of beneficial company ownership.","Biography information for Anas Sarwar","Anas Sarwar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183413","183413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33117","2014-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to complete a review of the operation of local discretionary welfare provision in 2013-14 before discontinuing funding for such provision.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183548","183548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33118","2014-01-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations he has received from local authorities on the effect of changes to local discretionary welfare provision on the local provision of food banks.","Biography information for Simon Danczuk","Simon Danczuk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183549","183549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/33119","2014-01-17","Department for International Development","2014-01-15","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much (a) food aid and (b) other aid her Department gave to North Korea in the most recent period for which figures are available; and how much aid has been given to North Korea in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mark Reckless","Mark Reckless","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2013/14 183432","183432"
