"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91562","2014-09-12","Department for Transport","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what structures are in place within the Civil Aviation Authority to hold employees to account for (a) incompetence, (b) issuing erroneous advice and (c) malicious actions.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209032","209032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91563","2014-09-12","Department for Transport","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many overseas visits Ministers and officials in his Department have made in (a) 2013-14 and (b) 2014 to date; and what the (i) total cost and (ii) cost of (A) flights, (B) internal travel, (C) hotel accommodation and (D) subsistence was for each such visit.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209013","209013"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91564","2014-09-12","Department for Transport","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, to whom the Civil Aviation Authority is accountable.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209031","209031"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91565","2014-09-12","Wales Office","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many copies of his Department's report, Building a more prosperous Wales: Infrastructure for a modern economy, were distributed; and what feedback he has received on that report.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208952","208952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91566","2014-09-12","Wales Office","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what costs arose from the publication of his Department's report, Building a more prosperous Wales: Infrastructure for a modern economy.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208953","208953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91567","2014-09-12","Wales Office","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, with reference to the Prime Minister's speech of 15 August 2011 calling for a family test to be applied to all domestic policy, which policies of his Department have been so assessed to date.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208863","208863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91568","2014-09-12","Wales Office","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, how many staff the Wales Office employs on zero hour contracts.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208893","208893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91569","2014-09-12","Wales Office","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what recent representations he has made to his Cabinet colleagues about the cost of gas and electricity in Wales.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208870","208870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91570","2014-09-12","Cabinet Office","2014-09-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Wales working (a) for the minimum wage and (b) below the living wage.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208871","208871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91571","2014-09-12","Wales Office","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what the real term change in the Welsh Government's block grant has been since the start of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208867","208867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91572","2014-09-12","Wales Office","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, which official engagements have been held in the Wales Office in the last three months.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208868","208868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91573","2014-09-12","Women and Equalities","2014-09-10","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, with reference to the Prime Minister's speech of 15 August 2011 calling for a family test applied to all domestic policy, which policies of the Government Equalities Office have been so assessed to date.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208853","208853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91574","2014-09-12","Women and Equalities","2014-09-10","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, when she expects the Government's programme of research into caste discrimination to be completed.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209041","209041"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91575","2014-09-12","Women and Equalities","2014-09-10","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what discussions the Government has had with the Equalities and Human Rights Commission on research into caste discrimination.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 209040","209040"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91576","2014-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what has been the median age of people (a) entering the Work Programme, (b) securing six months of employment through that programme and (c) completing two years on that programme and returning to their jobcentre.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208981","208981"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91577","2014-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on job outcome payments for Work Programme participants aged (a) 18 to 24, (b) 25 to 34, (c) 35 to 44, (d) 45 to 49, (e) 50 to 54, (f) 55 to 59 and (g) 60 and over since June 2011.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208982","208982"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91578","2014-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department has spent on job outcome payments for each Work Programme Payment Group since June 2011.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208983","208983"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91579","2014-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of employment and support allowance claimants was in the (a) Support group and (b) Work Related Activity group in each quarter since October 2008.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208992","208992"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91580","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken to process financial assistance claims for specialist equipment through the Access to Work scheme was in each year since 1994.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208955","208955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91581","2014-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate he has made of the number of parents (a) in receipt of child maintenance paid via the Child Support Agency (CSA) who will elect not to use the Child Maintenance Service's Collect and Pay service and (b) who currently use the CSA but who will elect to reach their own child maintenance arrangements following the changes introduced from 30 June 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208926","208926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91582","2014-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many (a) parents with care commitments and (b) non-resident parents have (i) registered with the Child Maintenance Service since 30 June 2014 and (ii) chosen to use the new Collect and Pay service since 11 August 2014.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208927","208927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91583","2014-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the number of children in poverty affected by the changes to the child maintenance system introduced from 30 June 2014; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208928","208928"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91584","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the Prime Minister's speech of 15 August 2011 calling for a family test applied to all domestic policy, which policies of his Department have been so assessed to date.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208864","208864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91585","2014-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average weekly child maintenance payment received via the Child Support Agency was for parents with care commitments in 2013-14.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208925","208925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91586","2014-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many parents with (a) care commitments and (b) children were in receipt of child maintenance paid via the Child Support Agency on 29 June 2014.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208924","208924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91587","2014-10-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance the Health and Safety Executive has issued on the use of e-cigarettes in the workplace.","Biography information for David T. C. Davies","David T. C. Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208910","208910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91588","2014-10-16","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if the Government will change regulations to provide a war widow's pension for life for those who were awarded war widows' pensions between 31 March 1973 and 5 April 2005.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208933","208933"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91134","2014-09-11","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government supported the recent invitation from the Financial Action Task Force for Israel to become a member of that body.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208651","208651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91135","2014-09-11","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, who the Government's representative is on the Financial Action Task Force.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208652","208652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91136","2014-09-12","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue loss from tobacco smuggling has been prevented as a result of increasing assessments and civil penalties in each year since 2010-11; and what operational targets were set for this activity in each of those years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208670","208670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91137","2014-09-12","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much revenue loss has has been prevented as a result of targeting and disrupting criminal gangs behind tobacco fraud; and what operational targets were set for this activity in each year since 2010-11.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208671","208671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91138","2014-09-12","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what operational targets were set for the seizure of illicit (a) cigarettes and (b) hand-rolling tobacco in each year since 2010-11; and whether those targets were met in each of those years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208672","208672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91139","2014-09-12","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what operational targets were set for reducing the supply of genuine tobacco products for fraud in each year since 2010-11; and whether those targets were met in each of those years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208673","208673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91140","2014-09-11","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the (a) size and (b) potential risk posed to the economy from (i) the UK and (ii) the international shadow banking system.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208723","208723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91141","2014-09-11","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent change there has been in the average wage of UK workers.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208724","208724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91142","2014-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to increase military aid being sent to Kurdish fighters in Iraq.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208740","208740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91143","2014-09-11","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-09","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what proportion of his Department's budget for Electoral Registration Transformation Programme has been spent on registering additional citizens to vote in the current financial year; and what assessment he has made of the performance of that Programme in that function.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208701","208701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91144","2014-09-11","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-09","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what proportion of his Department's Election and Democracy Division budget has been spent on registering additional voters in the 2014-15 financial year.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208725","208725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91145","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many fully qualified teachers who have completed their studies within the last three years in England have not obtained a permanent teaching post.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208690","208690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91146","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance she issues to (a) maintained and (b) independent schools on recording instances where staff have verbally abused a special educational needs student.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208631","208631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91147","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance is given by her Department to (a) maintained schools and (b) independent schools on what action to take when a student attempts suicide as a result of bullying.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208632","208632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91148","2014-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effects of solar farms on nearby wildlife.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208643","208643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91149","2014-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with Ministers in the Scottish Government on the future of the country sports industry in Scotland after 2014.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208645","208645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91150","2014-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with Ministers of the Scottish Government on the future of deer hunting in Scotland after 2014.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208646","208646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91151","2014-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with Ministers of the Scottish Government on land reform in Scotland after 2014.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208647","208647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91152","2014-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to institute infraction proceedings where Water Framework Directive river quality standards are not met.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208674","208674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91153","2014-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance her Department provides on (a) the future funding of catchment management partnerships and (b) the role of water companies; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208675","208675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91154","2014-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance her Department provides on the level of phosphate discharge allowable from sewage treatment works under the Water Framework Directive; and what plans she has to review this guidance.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208676","208676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91155","2014-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance her Department provides on the determination of allowable increases in phosphate pollution levels in English rivers.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208635","208635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91156","2014-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the likelihood of nations to which the UK exports for incineration introducing similar measures to the Dutch government's planned incineration tax.","Biography information for Dame Caroline Spelman","Mrs Caroline Spelman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208718","208718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91157","2014-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of Russia's ban on EU fish products on the pelagic industry in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208737","208737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91158","2014-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with which states he has discussed the future of US tactical nuclear weapons in Europe since the Chicago NATO Summit.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208729","208729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91159","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what future plans he has to continue engaging with non-governmental organisations concerned with gender equality and women's rights over the next year.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208689","208689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91160","2014-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, on what date the renewal of the US-UK Mutual Defence Agreement was agreed.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208730","208730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91161","2014-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what role the implementation of Article VI of the Non-Proliferation Treaty has had in any negotiation on the renewal of the US-UK Mutual Defence Agreement.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208731","208731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91162","2014-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has received an invitation to attend the third conference on the humanitarian consequences of nuclear weapons in Vienna on 8 to 9 December 2014; and what representation the UK plans to send.","Biography information for Jeremy Corbyn","Jeremy Corbyn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208732","208732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91163","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to respond to the report by Sir John Jenkins on the Muslim Brotherhood.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208636","208636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91164","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will publish the report by Sir John Jenkins on the Muslim Brotherhood.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208637","208637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91165","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his French and German counterparts about assistance to the Kurdistan regional government.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208638","208638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91166","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security threat to Israel from Hamas.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208639","208639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91167","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Israeli authorities on the entry to Gaza of construction materials.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208640","208640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91168","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to ensure all UN member states commit not to take military action in Iraq or Syria without either the consent of the governments of those countries or a supporting UNSC Resolution.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208633","208633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91169","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to the Israeli government on an end to the blockade of Gaza.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208662","208662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91170","2014-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Palestinian Authority about reconstruction in Gaza.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208679","208679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91171","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government is giving to the UN's call for accountability from the Israeli authorities for deaths in Gaza of UNRWA personnel, medical staff, firefighters and technicians, injuries to aid workers and the damage or destruction of UN premises and hospitals and clinics.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208663","208663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91172","2014-09-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will allocate funding to support the work of UN Women UK.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208687","208687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91173","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to monitor the effectiveness of the commitments given by his Department during the Girls Summit 2014.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208693","208693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91174","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps the Government has taken to help to end the blockade of Gaza.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208648","208648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91175","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the role of international observers in monitoring ceasefire arrangements in Gaza and protecting the security of Palestinians and Israelis.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208649","208649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91176","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the government of Israel on implementation of the findings of the Turkel Commission.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208650","208650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91177","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what contribution his Department made to the Egyptian-mediated negotiations between Israel and the Palestinians on achieving a sustainable ceasefire.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208656","208656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91178","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking (a) unilaterally and (b) multilaterally to achieve the aims set out in the Foreign Affairs Council conclusions of 15 August 2014 of (i) immediate and unimpeded humanitarian access to Gaza and (ii) the lifting of the Gaza closure regime.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208657","208657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91179","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the timetable is for the study of options for an internationally-supervised mechanism to enable full access and movement through all Gaza ports of entry agreed at the Foreign Affairs Council of 15 August 2014.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208658","208658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91180","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the Government is giving to the efforts of the Palestinian National Unity Government to reconnect Gaza and the West Bank.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208659","208659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91181","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on plans to develop a new prevalence survey for Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208642","208642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91182","2014-09-12","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many times his Department has received applications for (a) additional funding or (b) other support from the funds and trusts which provide support to people with contaminated blood in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208727","208727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91183","2014-09-12","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in which locations mental health patients have been sent for out-of-area treatments since May 2010.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208736","208736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91184","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the role of mitrochondrial DNA in addition to energy-related functions.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208700","208700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91185","2014-09-12","Home Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what data her Department holds on the number, region and countries of origin of male and female victims of modern slavery and human trafficking who have been referred to the Salvation Army in the last 10 years; if she will publish the data in a medium which hon. Members can readily access; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208741","208741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91186","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which Minister in her Department took the decision to terminate the contract with Raytheon to build an immigration computer system; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208634","208634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91187","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will commission an assessment of the effect on civil liberties of current statutory definitions of terrorism and the proportionality and necessity of the range of those definitions.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208686","208686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91188","2014-09-11","Department for International Development","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the increase in UK aid to Gaza (a) directly and (b) through contributions to UK non-governmental organisations and to international organisations has been since the start of Operation Protective Edge.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208660","208660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91189","2014-09-11","Department for International Development","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what representations she has made to the Israeli government on reparations for the damage caused by Operation Protective Edge to UN and civilian facilities in Gaza.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208661","208661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91190","2014-09-11","Department for International Development","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what projects funded by her Department in Gaza have been (a) damaged and (b) destroyed as a result of Israeli military action during Operation Protective Edge.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208653","208653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91191","2014-09-11","Department for International Development","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what contribution her Department will offer at the donors' conference on the reconstruction of Gaza.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208654","208654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91192","2014-09-11","Department for International Development","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assessment she has made of the importance to a sustainable economy in Gaza of the re-opening of (a) Gaza airport and (b) the sea-port.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208655","208655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91193","2014-09-11","Department for International Development","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on projects solely for the benefit of (a) males and (b) females in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208716","208716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91194","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders convicted of a single offence of possession of class C drugs received (a) a discharge, (b) a fine, (c) a community order, (d) a suspended prison sentence and (e) an immediate prison sentence in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208715","208715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91195","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much in victim surcharge has been (a) imposed and (b) collected in cases involving Crown Court sentences of imprisonment since 1 October 2012.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208712","208712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91196","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) sentenced and (b) remand prisoners were held in HMP Belmarsh for the offence of criminal damage from 23 December 2013 to 9 January 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208717","208717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91197","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what grounds offenders who received the maximum prison sentences for the possession of (a) class A and (b) class B drugs received those sentences in 2012.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208719","208719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91198","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders convicted of a single offence of possession of class B drugs received (a) a discharge, (b) a fine, (c) a community order, (d) a suspended prison sentence and (e) an immediate prison sentence in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208720","208720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91199","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners held in HMP Belmarsh for what offences were (a) over 70, (b) in a wheelchair, (c) using a walking frame and (d) recorded as having hernia problems from 23 December 2013 to 9 January 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208709","208709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91200","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many previous convictions at the time of sentence each offender sentenced to immediate custody for a single offence of possession of (a) class A, (b) class B and (c) class C drugs had in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208713","208713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91201","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the (a) age and (b) offence type of prisoners held in HMP Belmarsh who were under the age of 21 from 23 December 2013 to 9 January 2014 is.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208707","208707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91202","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners held in HMP Belmarsh for what offences were first time offenders from 23 December 2013 to 9 January 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208708","208708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91203","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people received a caution for the possession of (a) class A, (b) class B and (c) class C drugs in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208710","208710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91204","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners convicted of what offence and with what period of sentence left to serve who were released from prison in error (a) have and (b) have not been returned to custody in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208714","208714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91205","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much in victim surcharge has been (a) imposed and (b) collected on all Crown Court sentences (i) since 1 October 2012 and (ii) for the equivalent period up to that date.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208705","208705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91206","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners sentenced for what offence have been released from prison in error while (a) being held on remand and (b) serving a custodial sentence in each of the last five years; and what the nature of the error was in each case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208711","208711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91207","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking to encourage more people to make a will.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208644","208644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91208","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners held in HMP Brixton for what offences were (a) over 70, (b) in a wheelchair, (c) using a walking frame and (d) recorded as having hernia problems from 9 January 2014 to 7 February 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208706","208706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91209","2014-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for a domestic violence protection order were made to the Bury and Rochdale Magistrates' Court in the most recent 12 month period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208677","208677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91210","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve conditions for prisoners with mental health problems in prisons in England; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208641","208641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91211","2014-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will have discussions with religious groups on reintroducing a National Day of Prayer to reflect on the terrorist threats the UK faces.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208699","208699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91212","2014-09-12","Scotland Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2014, Official Report, column 53W, on official visits, what domestic visits he and his predecessor have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208669","208669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91213","2014-09-11","Women and Equalities","2014-09-09","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what meetings (a) she, (b) Ministers in her Department and (c) officials in her Department have had with individuals or groups representing intersex people.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208685","208685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91214","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to release work programme provider performance data according to the age of participant.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208688","208688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91215","2014-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will bring forward proposals to prioritise funding for second qualifications for those with the lowest levels of work experience and skills.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208697","208697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91216","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to support older jobseekers in going through online recruitment processes.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208698","208698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91217","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to allow early entry to the work programme for unemployed older people.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208691","208691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91218","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disabled people have received new support from the Access to Work scheme to participate in internships, traineeships and work placements in each month since September 2013.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208695","208695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91219","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will bring forward proposals for a new Work Programme payment group for older jobseekers.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208694","208694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91220","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many new beneficiaries of the Access to Work scheme had (a) mental health conditions, (b) physical impairments and (c) sensory impairments as the main disabling condition recorded by his Department in each of the last 24 months.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208696","208696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91221","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how the costs of administering and providing personal independence payment decisions are monitored and value for money reviewed for improvement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208739","208739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91222","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many full-time Health and Safety Executive officers were employed to monitor asbestos removal in each month since May 2010.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208726","208726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91223","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the average cost of a personal independence payment decision, including assessment costs and departmental administration.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208738","208738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91224","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what records his Department holds on the number of occasions on which Health and Safety Executive asbestos removal inspectors have undertaken visits to sites outside normal business working hours.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208728","208728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91225","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many disabled people are using Access to Work support for a (a) work trial, (b) work experience opportunity under the Youth contract, (c)  supported internship, (d) traineeship and (e) pre-employment training work placement.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208692","208692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91226","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to help Jobcentre Plus, Work Programme and voluntary providers to tackle age discrimination.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208702","208702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91227","2014-09-11","Attorney General","2014-09-09","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 1 September 2014, Official Report, column 32W, on Crown Courts, what the reasons were for the (a) Crown Prosecution Service offering no evidence and (b) judge ordering acquittals in each of the cases in the homicide category.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208789","208789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91228","2014-09-11","Attorney General","2014-09-09","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 16 July 2014, Official Report, column 678W, on Crown Courts, how many defendants included in the figures for each of the years from 2008 to 2013 were charged with homicide.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208790","208790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91229","2014-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the letter he received in February 2014 from the law firm Hodge Jones and Allen setting out alleged breaches of law at the Defence and Security Equipment International arms fair in 2013; whether any enforcement actions have been taken in response to this letter; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208783","208783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91230","2014-09-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of pupils from each ethnic group were admitted to (a) the University of Oxford, (b) the University of Cambridge and (c) other Russell Group universities in the last six years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208742","208742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91231","2014-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of the UK manufacturing sector since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208722","208722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91232","2014-09-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of students from each ethnic group were (a) working, (b) studying and (c) unemployed six months after leaving higher education.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208743","208743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91233","2014-09-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many construction workers claimed subsistence allowances in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208733","208733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91234","2014-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2014, Official Report, column 348W, on arms trade: trade fairs, what consideration his Department gave to any previous breaches of arms control legislation by exhibitors during the process of agreeing the Memorandum of Understanding between his Department and Clarion; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208807","208807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91235","2014-09-12","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what UK Trade and Industry's most recent (a) estimate and (b) target is for business generated for UK companies as a result of the London 2012 Olympic and Paralympic Games.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Robertson","Sir Hugh Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208831","208831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91236","2014-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many Russian-owned companies are currently located in the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208819","208819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91237","2014-09-11","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-09","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what the decision-making process was for the distribution of his Department's 4.2 million Innovation Fund to improve voter registration.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208794","208794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91238","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if his Department will consider using powers under Section 5 of the Freedom of Information Act 2000 for the purpose of ensuring that Electoral Registration Officers are covered by the provisions of that Act.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208795","208795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91240","2014-09-12","Cabinet Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the number of births that will take place in England in each of the next 10 years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208775","208775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91241","2014-09-11","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the performance of the economy of the North East since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Nicholas Brown","Mr Nicholas Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208721","208721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91242","2014-09-11","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to tackle excess credit card charging; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208770","208770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91243","2014-09-11","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will consider including information about bone marrow donation within correspondence informing people of their National Insurance number.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208684","208684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91244","2014-09-11","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent discussions he has had with Ministers in the Northern Ireland Executive on ensuring adequate levels of funding for public services in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208821","208821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91245","2014-09-12","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the forecast cost is of tax relief arising from the (a) petroleum revenue tax oil allowance, (b) petroleum revenue tax tariff receipts allowance and (c) Ring Fence Expenditure Supplement and (i) ultra-heavy oil field, (ii) ultra-high pressure/high temperature field, (iii) small or gas field, (iv) deep water gas field, (v) large-deep water oil field, (vi) large-shallow water gas field, (vii) brownfield and (viii) remote deep-water gas field allowances in each year from 2014-15 to 2017-18.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208801","208801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91246","2014-09-12","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total cost of tax relief from the (a) petroleum revenue tax oil allowance, (b) petroleum revenue tax tariff receipts allowance and (c) Ring Fence Expenditure Supplement and (i) ultra-heavy oil field, (ii) ultra-high pressure/high temperature field, (iii) small or gas field, (iv) deep water gas field, (v) large-deep water oil field, (vi) large-shallow water gas field, (vii) brownfield and (viii) remote deep-water gas field allowances in each year from 2014-15 to 2017-18.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208802","208802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91247","2014-09-12","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the forecast cost is of tax relief arising from Decommissioning Relief Deeds provided to companies operating in the UK and UK Continental Shelf in each year from 2014-15 to 2017-18.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208800","208800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91248","2014-09-12","HM Treasury","2014-09-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much the Government spent on bringing a legal challenge against the European Council on the decision to establish enhanced cooperation to implement a Financial Transaction Tax; what proportion of the total cost is (a) costs the UK will have to pay as a result of having lost the legal challenge, (b) staff time, (c) transport to and from Brussels, (d) legal fees and (e) other costs; what the names are of any external lawyers employed on this case; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208809","208809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91249","2014-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many local authorities have a policy requiring that some or all homes in their area should be built to Lifetime Homes Standards, or to a comparable standard; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208792","208792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91250","2014-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he has any plans to strengthen local democratic oversight of planning decisions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208798","208798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91251","2014-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what representations he has received from town councils regarding paragraph 7(2) of the draft Openness of Local Government Bodies Regulations 2014.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208760","208760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91252","2014-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the Openness of Local Bodies Regulations 2014 on bureaucracy and the cost of services provided by town councils.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208759","208759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91253","2014-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many shops in Westmorland and Lonsdale constituency have benefited from the reduction in business rates.","Biography information for Tim Farron","Tim Farron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208777","208777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91254","2014-09-12","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the full-year expenditure in each identified category of the Ring-fenced Public Health Grant was for (a) each local authority and (b) England in 2013-14.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208799","208799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91255","2014-09-12","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what his most recent estimate is for tourist (a) numbers and (b) spend delivered as a result of the London 2012 Olympic and Paralympic Games.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Robertson","Sir Hugh Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208830","208830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91256","2014-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 8 September 2014, UIN 208084, on Army Reserve, what the current size of the Regular Army Reserve of Officers (RARO) is; if he will encourage RARO to join the Army Reserve as part of the plans to increase the strength of the reserve; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Robertson","Sir Hugh Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208829","208829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91257","2014-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what contingency planning has been undertaken by his Department for any potential UK military involvement to tackle Islamic State in (a) Iraq and (b) Syria; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208813","208813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91258","2014-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether funds have been allocated for the purchase of new F-35s for the aircraft carrier HMS Prince of Wales; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208814","208814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91259","2014-09-12","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average time between completing online application forms and successful applicants starting training is for each of the reserve forces.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208824","208824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91260","2014-09-11","Deputy Prime Minister","2014-09-09","To ask the Deputy Prime Minister, what proportion of his Department's Parliament and Constitution Division's budget has been spent on registering additional voters in the 2014-15 financial year.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208703","208703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91261","2014-09-12","Department for Education","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress she has made on increasing the use of digital engagement in the development and implementation of policy.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208680","208680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91262","2014-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the relationship between the construction industry and colleges in providing courses that meet the skills requirements of employers within the construction industry.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208668","208668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91263","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many fostered children have been separated from their siblings in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208773","208773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91264","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to reunite siblings who have been placed in separate foster homes.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208774","208774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91265","2014-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how much oil and gas the UK purchased from the Russian Federation in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208820","208820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91266","2014-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether case trapping is being used in the (a) Gloucestershire and (b) Somerset badger cull.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208808","208808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91267","2014-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many stray dogs were put down in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208772","208772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91268","2014-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she has taken to ensure that the best available technology is used to reduce phosphate discharges into rivers at sewage treatment works in England.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208678","208678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91269","2014-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to reduce the incidence of paroxysms in puppies.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208769","208769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91270","2014-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will seek a derogation from the proposed prohibition on driftnet fisheries, amending Council Regulations (EC) No. 850/98, (EC) No. 812/2004, (EC) No. 2187/2005 and (EC) No. 1967/2006 and repealing Council Regulation (EC) No. 894/97 for the purpose of preventing the elimination of local inshore herring fishery in northern Devon.","Biography information for Mr Geoffrey Cox","Mr Geoffrey Cox","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208758","208758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91271","2014-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the number of stray dogs in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208771","208771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91272","2014-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the incidence of myxomatosis in Britain; what change there has been in such levels in the last five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208745","208745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91273","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the UK has drawn down from the Fund for European Aid to the Most Deprived to date.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208734","208734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91274","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the UK was entitled to draw down from the Fund for European Aid to the Most Deprived to date.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208735","208735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91275","2014-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress he has made on improving the quality and transparency of management information across frontline services within his Department's Digital Service's Performance Platform tool.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208681","208681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91276","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will work with other EU member states to address any legitimate security constraints affecting Israel that could prevent the lifting of the Gaza blockade.","Biography information for Mr Andrew Smith","Mr Andrew Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208664","208664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91277","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has met representatives of the Women's League of Burma to discuss rape and sexual violence in that country.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208754","208754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91278","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to protect the health of UK diplomatic staff and their dependents in West African nations affected by the ebola outbreak; and what monitoring of their health is available to them on their return to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Lee Scott","Mr Lee Scott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208755","208755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91279","2014-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made following the recent reports of further illegal settlement building by the government of Israel in the West Bank; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208803","208803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91280","2014-09-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made representations following the ceasefire for an easing of the blockades of Gaza; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208804","208804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91281","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to assist persecuted Christians around the world; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208812","208812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91282","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what meetings Ministers or officials in his Department have had with individuals or groups representing intersex people about NHS services for and the needs of intersex people.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208810","208810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91283","2014-09-12","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to address the shortage of junior doctors at Barnsley Hospital NHS Foundation Trust.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208823","208823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91284","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to set national recruitment targets for NHS community and district nurses.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208753","208753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91285","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost of carpal tunnel syndrome (a) to the NHS and (b) in terms of employee days lost.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208762","208762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91286","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with gout in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208763","208763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91287","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of the additional 10,000 primary and community health and care professionals which his Department plans to make available by 2020 will be (a) existing NHS staff and (b) new starters.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208752","208752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91288","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have suffered sporting injuries that have led to cartilage problems in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208767","208767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91289","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of how many people with gout subsequently develop arthritis in their joints.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208765","208765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91290","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans the NHS has to introduce stem-cell treatment as a substitute for hip and knee replacements.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208766","208766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91291","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the cost to the NHS of drug treatments for gout in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208764","208764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91292","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which clinical commissioning groups have awarded contracts to provide community services to non-NHS providers or consortia that include non-NHS providers; and what the estimated or confirmed lifetime value of each of those contracts is.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208791","208791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91293","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2014, Official Report, column 382W, on General Practitioners, for what reason the figure for financial year 2009-10 (the figure as at September 2009) was not included in that answer.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208788","208788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91294","2014-09-12","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the national Child and Adolescent Mental Health Services' budget is for the present financial year.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208785","208785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91295","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what annual funding per head of population was provided to the South Worcestershire Clinical Commissioning Group in each of the last five years; and what the average such spend was on all Clinical Commissioning Groups in England.","Biography information for Mr Robin Walker","Mr Robin Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208786","208786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91296","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve awareness of stem cell donation among 16 and 17 year olds.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208683","208683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91297","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on interpreters in England and Wales in the last three years.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208666","208666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91298","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve recruitment and retention in NHS community and district nursing.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208748","208748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91299","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure adequate staffing levels and skill mix within NHS community nursing teams.","Biography information for Teresa Pearce","Teresa Pearce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208749","208749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91300","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with carpal tunnel syndrome in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208761","208761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91301","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the neonatal conditions were that accounted for successful wrongful birth claims between 2003 and 2013.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208751","208751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91302","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS has paid out for wrongful birth claims in each year between 2003 and 2013; how many successful claims for wrongful birth were made in each year between 2008 and 2012.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208750","208750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91303","2014-09-12","Home Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what guidance she gives to UK police forces on using the European Arrest Warrant in respect of people against whom there is no evidence an offence has been committed under UK law; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208746","208746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91304","2014-09-12","Home Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, further to her Answers of 8 September 2014, Official Report, column 467W and 22 July 2014, Official Report, column 1105W, if she will make available the number of victims referred to the Salvation Army in May and August 2014 in a format which can be downloaded and printed.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208744","208744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91305","2014-09-12","Home Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to her contribution of 8 July 2014, Official Report, column 168, on the Modern Slavery Bill, if she will publish the interim review of the National Referral Mechanism before the Committee stage of that Bill is completed; and when she will publish the final review.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208780","208780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91306","2014-09-12","Home Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many domestic violence incidents have been reported to the police in the last 12 months; and in how many such cases the police (a) took no further action, (b) charged perpetrators with a criminal offence and (c) secured a prosecution.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208825","208825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91307","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many investor visas have been granted by the UK Government to Russian citizens since May 2010; how many of those visas were issued after January 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208816","208816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91308","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to improve security between the UK and the Republic of Ireland to prevent the return through Ireland of British-born jihadists; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208817","208817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91309","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the process is for setting remuneration for police and crime commissioners; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208818","208818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91310","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what representation her Department will have on the On-The-Runs Oversight Board established after the publication of the Hallett Report on 17 July 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208815","208815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91311","2014-09-11","Department for International Development","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of her Departments funding is spent on providing adequate housing; and how much such funding is available to be spent in Sierra Leone.","Biography information for Sir Tony Cunningham","Sir Tony Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208747","208747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91312","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if she will raise with her Somali counterpart allegations of sexual exploitation and rape including against young children by African Union soldiers who were on peacekeeping duties during 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208782","208782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91313","2014-09-11","Department for International Development","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2014, UIN 206962, on Afghanistan, what memoranda of understanding have been signed between her Department and the Afghan Investment Support Agency in regards to the Bost Agri and Bost Airfield projects covering the period 2009 to present; and if she will place in the Library copies of such memoranda.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208787","208787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91314","2014-09-11","Department for International Development","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what assistance her Department provides to ethnic Chin refugees in India who are victims of sexual violence.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208756","208756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91315","2014-09-11","Department for International Development","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the cost to the public purse was of the Girl Effect Art Installation in her Departmental offices.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208704","208704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91316","2014-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 19 June 2014, Official Report, column 711W, on official visits, what domestic visits he has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208682","208682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91317","2014-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the national youth justice budget was in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208784","208784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91318","2014-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effects on Victim Impact Statements on sentencing decisions made by judges in the criminal justice system.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208826","208826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91319","2014-09-12","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what domestic violence training programmes are available for probation staff; and how many probation staff have undertaken domestic violence training in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208827","208827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91320","2014-09-12","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, for what reason she has declined to disclose the number of recipients of On-The-Run comfort letters who have fled the jurisdiction of the UK since her statement following the Hallett Report on 17 July 2014; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208832","208832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91321","2014-09-11","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answers of 4 September 2014, to UIN numbers 207794, 207797 and 207798, who the individual members of the On-The-Runs Policy Oversight Board will be; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208822","208822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91322","2014-09-11","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made of potential direct consequences for the Northern Ireland economy of a Scottish vote in favour of independence.","Biography information for David Simpson","David Simpson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208665","208665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91323","2014-09-11","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what discussions she has had with Ministers in the Northern Ireland Executive about measures to bring the level of car insurance premiums in Northern Ireland in line with those in the rest of the UK.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208768","208768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91324","2014-09-12","Department for Transport","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many Blue Badges were issued in (a) Ribble Valley constituency, (b) Lancashire and (c) the UK in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208776","208776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91325","2014-09-12","Department for Transport","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many foreign HGV lorries entered the UK in the last period for which figures are available; and how much revenue has been raised through the HGV Road Levy User since its introduction.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Robertson","Sir Hugh Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208828","208828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91326","2014-09-11","Women and Equalities","2014-09-09","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what assessments have been made since 2010 of the potential merits of establishing the Government Equalities Office within a permanent parent department or as a standalone department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208811","208811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91327","2014-09-11","Women and Equalities","2014-09-09","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the Equality and Human Rights Commission's publication entitled Appointments to Boards and Equality Law, published in August 2014.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208793","208793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91328","2014-09-12","Women and Equalities","2014-09-09","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2014, Official Report, column 409W, on domestic visits, what domestic visits (a) she and (b) her predecessors have made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208779","208779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91329","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of (a) capital cost and (b) maintenance and upgrading costs of a new IT system which would be required by the Northern Ireland Assembly's Department of Social Development to administer welfare-related matters in the event of Northern Ireland not proceeding with the current UK-wide welfare reform programme.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208781","208781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91330","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the contribution of 5 September 2014 by the Minister of State for Disabled People, of 5 September 2014, Official Report, columns 554-64, if he will publish the evidential basis for the statement that implementation of the Affordable Homes Bill would cost 1 billion; when those calculations were made; and by whom they were calculated.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208796","208796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91331","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether a claimant refused Employment and Support Allowance (ESA) by a decision maker on the grounds that their health had improved by the time of the decision, having obtained sufficient points to receive ESA in an earlier Work Capability Assessment, should be paid ESA in arrears for the period of their ill health; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208797","208797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91332","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people have made at least one claim for out of work benefits in each region and constituent part of the UK since May 2010.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208778","208778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91333","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Flexible Support Fund in supporting older jobseekers.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208757","208757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91334","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost of assessing the eligibility of (a) people with learning disabilities, (b) deaf people, (c) blind people, (d) people with primary or secondary MS, (e) people with Alzheimer's disease, (f) people with motor neurone disease, (g) people with muscular dystrophy and (h) deafblind people who are in receipt of disability living allowance for the personal independence payment (PIP); and how often each will be expected to be reassessed for continued eligibility for PIP.","Biography information for Dame Anne McGuire","Mrs Anne McGuire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208667","208667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91335","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment he has made of local authority involvement in the Work Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208805","208805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91336","2014-09-12","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what comparative assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Youth Contract Wage Incentive scheme in the 20 Hotspot areas and in other areas.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208806","208806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90936","2014-09-10","Attorney General","2014-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, what steps his Department has taken to ensure that a victim of crime who is under 18 years of age and who has no legal guardian or person with parental responsibility can gain access to the Crown Prosecution Service Victims' Right to Review Scheme; and by what means such a victim would gain such access.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208464","208464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90937","2014-09-11","Attorney General","2014-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many successful prosecutions for forced labour there were in each of the last three financial years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208480","208480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90938","2014-09-11","Attorney General","2014-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many times prosecutions have been brought against those who have had their licence revoked by the Gangmasters Licensing Authority in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208482","208482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90939","2014-09-11","Attorney General","2014-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many prosecutions of offences under the Indecent Displays (Control) Act 1981 there have been in each year between 2009-10 and 2013-14.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208553","208553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90940","2014-09-11","Attorney General","2014-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, when the Crown Prosection Service last (a) issued and (b) reviewed guidelines for prosecutions under the Indecent Displays (Control) Act 1981; and whether a further review of those guidelines is planned.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208554","208554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90941","2014-09-10","Attorney General","2014-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, how many (a) successful and (b) unsuccessful appeals against bail were made by prosecutors in Crown courts since 3 December 2012.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208542","208542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90942","2014-09-10","Attorney General","2014-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions in each region the Crown Prosecution Service has issued a charging authority denied decision against a police request to charge under section 4 of the Asylum and Immigration (Treatment of Claimants, etc) Act 2004 since 2004.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208607","208607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90943","2014-09-10","Attorney General","2014-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions the Crown Prosecution Service London region has issued a charging authority denied decision against a police request to charge under section 4 of the Asylum and Immigration (Treatment of Claimants, etc) Act 2004 where the victim was under 18 years of age in the last five years.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208608","208608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90944","2014-09-10","Attorney General","2014-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions in each region the Crown Prosecution Service has issued a charging authority denied decision against a police request to charge under sections 57, 58 and 59 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 in the last five years.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208609","208609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90945","2014-09-10","Attorney General","2014-09-08","To ask the Attorney General, on how many occasions in each region the Crown Prosecution Service has issued a charging authority denied decision against a police request to charge under sections 57, 58 and 59 of the Sexual Offences Act 2003 where the victim was under 18 years in the last five years.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208610","208610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90946","2014-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many apprentices there were in Ashfield constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208541","208541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90947","2014-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many employers have been issued with a Notice of Underpayment since 1 October 2013; and of those how many have been identified under the Department's National Minimum Wage naming scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208599","208599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90948","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect on young people in (a) Wirral, (b) Liverpool City Region and (c) England of devolving the duty to deliver careers guidance.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208499","208499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90950","2014-09-10","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he is taking to make it easier for small businesses to access the tendering process for government contracts.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208517","208517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90951","2014-09-10","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have participated in National Citizen Service schemes in (a) England and (b) North Swindon in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208518","208518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90952","2014-09-10","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what university each intern on the Summer Diversity Internship Programme attended in each year since that programme started.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208530","208530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90953","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what representations the Social Investment Business made to his Department about its proposal to alter the criteria which ensured that the Get In project of the Society Network Foundation received funds when they already had been turned down.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208557","208557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90954","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to the National Audit Office report, Investigation into grants from the Big Lottery Fund and the Cabinet Office to the Big Society Network and the Society Network Foundation, HC 572, paragraph 3.13, for what reason his Department did not request details of the actual expenditure incurred on the Get In project.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208556","208556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90955","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many interns each department has accepted as part of the Summer Diversity Internship Programme; and how many such interns have been (a) women and (b) men in each year since that programme started.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208565","208565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90956","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Prime Minister's Office about the decision to fund the Big Society Network and its charity arm, the Society Network Foundation, by the Social Investment Business and the Big Lottery Fund.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208555","208555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90957","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many apprentices each department has accepted as part of the Civil Service Fast Track Apprenticeship Scheme; and how many such apprenticeships were taken up by (a) women and (b) men in each year since that scheme started.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208566","208566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90958","2014-09-12","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what savings the Efficiency and Reform Group has identified in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208570","208570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90959","2014-09-10","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people were self-employed in Ashfield constituency in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208537","208537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90960","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, for what reason a second payment to the Society Network Foundation for the Get In project was made when the Get In project had a surplus of 60,800 in October 2012.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208598","208598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90961","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what town or city each intern on the Summer Diversity Internship Programme was from in each year since that programme started.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208564","208564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90962","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent steps he has taken to reduce waste across Government.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208558","208558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90963","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many interns each Department has accepted as part of the Summer Diversity Internship Programme who were (a) from each black and minority ethnic background, (b) socio-economically disadvantaged and (c) disabled in each year since that programme started.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208562","208562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90964","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what monitoring his Department carried out on the Summer Diversity Internship Programme.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208563","208563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90965","2014-09-10","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many meetings he had with Nesta between 2010 and 2012.","Biography information for Lisa Nandy","Lisa Nandy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208580","208580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90966","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent steps he has taken to ensure that people in Northern Ireland who were 14 and 15 years of age in 1947 and who paid national insurance have these contributions recognised in their pensions.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208525","208525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90967","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what additional funding is being allocated to local authorities for their commissioning responsibility for the Healthy Child Programme from October 2015; and what steps his Department is taking to ensure a smooth transition to that commissioning responsibility.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208583","208583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90968","2014-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what progress the Permanent Secretary of his Department has made on his objective for delivery of information and transactional services to his Department's users by taking the Digital by Default approach.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208589","208589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90969","2014-09-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department issues on using the planning system to prevent concentrations of fast food outlets in deprived areas in order to reduce obesity.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208593","208593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90970","2014-09-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to promote competition in the provision of 4G services.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208600","208600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90971","2014-09-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the number of homophobic incidents that have occurred in professional football in each year since 2010; and what steps he is taking to improve access to football for LGBT people.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208617","208617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90972","2014-09-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will ensure that a single Minister in his Department is responsible for tourism.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208548","208548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90973","2014-09-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what targets the Government has set for tackling homophobia in sports; and what steps have been taken to achieve those targets in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208533","208533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90974","2014-09-11","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps his Department has taken to provide protection to people suffering from nuisance telephone calls.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208547","208547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90975","2014-09-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much has been spent in each region and constituent part of the UK in each year as part of the Olympic legacy.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208497","208497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90976","2014-09-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how much was invested in each region or constituent part of the UK as a result of London hosting the 2012 Olympic and Paralympic Games.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208490","208490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90977","2014-09-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the sports participation figures in each sport in each region and constituent part of the UK were in the (a) two years before and (b) two years after the 2012 Olympic and Paralympic Games.","Biography information for Ian Lavery","Ian Lavery","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208491","208491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90978","2014-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Covenant Annual Report 2013, page 67, what progress has been made on the review of public transport issues affecting service families living in remote areas; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208502","208502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90979","2014-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Covenant Annual Report 2013, page 25, when his Department plans to publish the initial findings of its study of the causes of death of veterans of operations in Iraq and Afghanistan.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208503","208503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90980","2014-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Covenant Annual Report 2013, page 7, what progress has been made on the introduction of pupil information profiles to help with the transfer of key information when service children move from one school to another; and whether he plans to introduce that programme on a nationwide basis.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208504","208504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90981","2014-09-11","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Armed Forces Covenant Annual Report 2013, page 13, what progress has been made on the Partner Employment Project; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208498","208498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90982","2014-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with which NATO allies the UK is working to establish a Joint Expeditionary Force; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208516","208516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90983","2014-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which UK units he plans to allocate to the NATO Joint Expeditionary Force.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208519","208519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90984","2014-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what size the NATO Joint Expeditionary Force will be.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208520","208520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90985","2014-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much (a) his Department and (b) BAE Systems have paid for work on HMS Dauntless since she was handed over to the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208507","208507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90986","2014-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much (a) his Department and (b) BAE Systems has paid for work on HMS Diamond since she was handed over to the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208508","208508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90987","2014-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place in the Library a copy of the (a) NATO Readiness Action Plan, (b) Alliance's Review of the Arrangements for NATO Interim Ballistic Missile Defence Capability, (c) NATO Framework Nations Concept and (d) NATO Enhanced Cyber Defence Policy.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208524","208524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90988","2014-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much (a) his Department and (b) BAE Systems have paid for work on HMS Daring since she was handed over to the Royal Navy.","Biography information for Mr Mike Hancock","Mr Mike Hancock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208506","208506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90989","2014-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, when he expects to make a decision on the Royal Navy's long-term heavyweight torpedo requirement.","Biography information for Vernon Coaker","Vernon Coaker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208467","208467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90990","2014-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many former service personnel have received the Arctic Star medal.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208544","208544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90991","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which Free Schools are currently open; and what the admission number of each school was planned for September 2014.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208473","208473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90992","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which Free Schools are pre-approved to open; and what the planned admission  number is for each school in the first year of opening.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208474","208474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90993","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which Free Schools that had planned to open in (a) September 2011, (b) September 2012, (c) September 2013 and (d) September 2014 have had their funding withdrawn between their intended day of opening and 1 March in that year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208476","208476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90994","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which Free Schools that had planned to open in September 2014 have had their opening delayed (a) since they were pre-approved and (b) since 1 March 2014.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208475","208475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90995","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how may teachers in state-funded schools did not hold a degree in (a) 2010, (b) 2011, (c) 2012 and (d) 2013.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208477","208477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90996","2014-09-10","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what targets the Government has set for tackling homophobia in schools; and what steps have been taken to achieve those targets in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208535","208535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90997","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she expects her Department to meet its target of all 16 year olds being in employment, education or training.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208596","208596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90998","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when the National College of Teaching and Learning will publish the final initial teacher training allocations for 2014-15.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208627","208627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90999","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the final number of trainee teachers recruited in each region was in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13 and (d) 2013-14.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208628","208628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91000","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of trainee teachers required in each region in (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12, (c) 2012-13, (d) 2013-14 and (e) 2014-15.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208630","208630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91001","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the significance is of the award of an ICT Mark to a school; and how many schools received such an award in 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208621","208621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91002","2014-09-11","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the number of trainee teachers required through the School Direct programme in 2014-15.","Biography information for Tristram Hunt","Tristram Hunt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208629","208629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91003","2014-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what estimate he has made of the proportion of Green Deal Home Improvement funding that has been allocated to deprived areas.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208505","208505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91004","2014-09-10","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what discussions he has had with (a) the Health and Safety Executive, (b) offshore trade unions and (c) Oil and Gas UK on accommodation standards for offshore oil and gas workers on installations in the North Sea.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208466","208466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91005","2014-09-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the statement by the Minister of State at his Department on 2 September 2014 in the Second Delegated Legislation Committee, that in winter 2013-14 average bills being paid by British Gas customers were 90 lower, what the evidential basis was for that statement.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208471","208471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91006","2014-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions her Department has had with EU institutions on the ban on the import of mangoes from India.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208521","208521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91007","2014-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps her Department has taken to help UK businesses adversely affected by the ban on the import of mangoes from India.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208522","208522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91008","2014-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps her Department has taken to reverse the EU ban on import of mangoes from India.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208523","208523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91009","2014-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent assessment she has made of the effect of changes to safety requirements for the 2014 badger cull on the safety of that cull.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208550","208550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91010","2014-09-12","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will bring forward proposals to ensure that licence holders not local authorities pay costs arising from fires at waste disposal sites.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208571","208571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91011","2014-09-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will place in the Library an unredacted copy of the Rural Community Policy Unit report on Shale Gas Rural Economy Impacts, published in March 2014.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208622","208622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91012","2014-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on what basis parts of the (a) body and (b) conclusions of the Rural Community Policy Unit report on Shale Gas Rural Economy Impacts, published in March 2014, were redacted.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208611","208611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91013","2014-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which Minister determined the redactions to the Rural Community Policy Unit report on Shale Gas Rural Economy Impacts, published in March 2014.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208612","208612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91014","2014-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of the Rural Community Policy Unit report on Shale Gas Rural Economy Impacts, published in March 2014, was redacted.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208613","208613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91015","2014-09-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent steps his Department has taken to tackle religious persecution internationally.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208594","208594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91016","2014-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department has taken to end the persecution of Christians in Iraq by the Islamic State.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208526","208526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91017","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will bring forward proposals to enable Chinese nationals to make a single application for a UK and a Schengen visa.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208549","208549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91018","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much a UK tourist visa costs a Chinese national.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208545","208545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91019","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Chinese nationals visited the UK on tourist visas in (a) 2011, (b) 2012 and (c) 2013.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208546","208546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91020","2014-09-10","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government has requested the EU to implement targeted sanctions against people and organisations named in the UN Commission of Inquiry report on North Korea as being responsible for human rights violations in North Korea; and if he will discuss with his ministerial colleagues implementing sanctions in the event that the EU does not do so.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208489","208489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91021","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will investigate the best methods to minimise the number of patients who do not arrive for (a) hospital and (b) GP appointments; and what the cost of missed appointments to the NHS was in the last year.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208455","208455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91022","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was spent on cancer services per capita in  (a) real terms and (b) cash terms in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208470","208470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91023","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many individuals have been diagnosed with disorders of sexual development when they were aged (a) up to two, (b) two to five, (c) five to 11, (d) 11 to 16 and (e) over 16 years in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208496","208496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91024","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to obstetricians, gynaecologists, midwives, paediatricians and other medical professionals on disorders of sexual development.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208492","208492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91025","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what requirement he makes for education on disorders of sexual development as part of initial training and continuous professional development for obstetricians, gynaecologists, midwives, paediatricians and other medical professionals.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208493","208493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91026","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the findings of the recent Royal College of Midwives report, Postnatal Care Planning; and what steps he is taking to address shortages of midwives and ensure that the care received is based on clinical need of the mother.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208501","208501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91027","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of people were estimated to be binge-drinkers in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208551","208551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91028","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what support his Department provides to the Great Western Hospital NHS Trust for the building of a new radiotherapy centre.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208514","208514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91029","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment he has made of the quality and extent of postnatal care available during the first six to eight weeks after birth; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208582","208582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91030","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department has taken to implement the recommendations of Midwives 2020: Delivering Expectations, published in September 2010; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208595","208595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91031","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people waiting for a (a) hip replacement, (b) cataract operation and (c) knee replacement in May (i) 2010 and (ii) 2014 were on the imcomplete waiting list or zero to one week..","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208601","208601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91032","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many local authorities have (a) submitted satisfactory Statements of Assurance, (b) submitted unsatisfactory Statements of Assurance and (c) failed to submit Statements of Assurance for the Public Health Grant for 2013-14.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208590","208590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91033","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information his Department holds on the number of people who have received physiological or psychological treatment as a result of previous surgical procedures or other medical interventions intended to assign a gender to a person diagnosed with a disorder of sexual development.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208584","208584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91034","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses were employed in each Agenda for Change band in (a) May 2010 and (b) May 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208591","208591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91035","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many acute, elderly and general nurses were employed in (a) each NHS region and (b) each Agenda for Change band in (i) May 2010 and (ii) May 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208592","208592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91036","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of whether NHS clinical guidance on gender assignment surgery on infants conforms with Yogyakarta Principles on human rights laws in relation to sexual orientation and gender identity; and what steps he has taken to ensure that such guidance conforms to those principles.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208585","208585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91037","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of suspected cancer patients received first treatment within 62 days of GP referral at (a) Sherwood Forest Hospitals Trust and (b) Nottingham University Hospitals Trust in each quarter since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208539","208539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91038","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of the Government's Public Health Responsibility Deal in reducing alcohol-related harms.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208561","208561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91039","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of patients waited more than four hours at accident and emergency wards at (a) Sherwood Forest Hospitals Trust and (b) Nottingham University Hospitals Trust in (i) each week since 2013 and (ii) each quarter since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208540","208540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91040","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of suspected cancer patients were seen by a consultant within 14 days of GP referral at (a) Sherwood Forest Hospitals Trust and (b) Nottingham University Hospitals Trust in each quarter since 2010.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208538","208538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91041","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many surgical procedures or other medical interventions were carried out in the NHS on people diagnosed with disorders of sexual development aged (a) up to two, (b) two to five, (c) five to 11, (d) 11 to 16 and (e) over 16 years in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208614","208614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91042","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses were employed in each NHS region in May (a) 2010 and (b) 2014.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208624","208624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91043","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what change there has been in the number of children diagnosed with diabetes between 2005 and 2013.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208620","208620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91044","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of recent trends in annual statistics on unexplained deaths in infancy; what steps his Department is taking to encourage further reductions in the rates of such deaths; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208602","208602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91045","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many privately-funded (a) knee replacement procedures, (b) hip replacement procedures and (c) cataract operations were conducted in NHS hospitals in England in each year since 2009-10.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208625","208625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91046","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that all pregnant women have easy access to a midwife as a first point of professional contact.","Biography information for Tracey Crouch","Tracey Crouch","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208603","208603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91047","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 April 2014, Official Report, column 112W, what progress has been made on the review by an expert panel of the UK's response to new psychoactive substances announced on 12 December 2013.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208618","208618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91048","2014-09-11","Department of Health","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of young people hospitalised as a result of legal highs in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208619","208619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91049","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the maximum time spent in a detention centre for the purpose of immigration control by (a) women and (b) men in each category of detainee was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208560","208560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91050","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time spent in detention for the purposes of immigration control by (a) women and (b) men in each category of detainee was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208559","208559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91051","2014-09-10","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many requests under the Domestic Violence Disclosure Scheme by (a) women and (b) men have (i) been made and (ii) been successful in each police force since the introduction of that scheme.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208515","208515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91052","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of (a) violent and (b) other crime was attributable to alcohol in the last five years for which figures are available; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Griffiths","Andrew Griffiths","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208552","208552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91053","2014-09-10","Department for Education","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to support parents and children who were victims of forced adoptions in the 1950s, 1960s and 1970s.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208527","208527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91054","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were (a) charged and (b) convicted of homophobic hate crimes in the UK in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208536","208536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91055","2014-09-10","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police-instigated disclosures relating to (a) women and (b) men have been made under the Domestic Violence Disclosure Scheme in each police force since the introduction of that scheme.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208528","208528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91056","2014-09-10","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many men had convictions for offences related to consensual gay sex expunged from their criminal records in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208531","208531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91057","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will arrange for the hon. Member for Walsall North to receive a reply to his letter to the Director General, UK Visas and Immigration of 4 August 2014 on behalf of a constituent, CTS ref M11054/14.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208487","208487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91058","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many licences have been revoked by the Gangmasters Licensing Authority in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Barclay","Stephen Barclay","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208481","208481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91059","2014-09-11","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many  (a) thefts and (b) attempted thefts from vehicles have been (i) reported to and (ii) attended by the police in each local authority in Cumbria in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208478","208478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91060","2014-09-10","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of weddings conducted annually in (a) Hindu temples, (b) mosques, (c) synagogues, (d) unlicensed churches, (e) gurdwaras and (f) any other religious establishments.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208462","208462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91061","2014-09-10","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employers in each industry category set out in the Government's Office of National Statistics Standard Industrial Classification system hold a Tier 2 Sponsor Licence.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208458","208458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91062","2014-09-10","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many employers in the UK motorsport industries hold a Tier 2 Sponsor Licence.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208459","208459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91063","2014-09-10","Home Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to ratify the Istanbul Convention.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208460","208460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91064","2014-09-10","Department for International Development","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will make representations to her counterpart in the Israeli government to allow building materials to enter Gaza for the rebuilding of homes; and if she will make funding available towards the rebuilding of homes in Gaza.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208468","208468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91065","2014-09-11","Department for International Development","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps the Government is taking to help tackle the outbreak of the Ebola virus in Africa.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208479","208479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91066","2014-09-11","Department for International Development","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how much her Department has spent on media monitoring in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208568","208568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91067","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the total cost to the public purse was of the court hearings about the bail sureties given in the case of Julian Assange.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208510","208510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91068","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much has been collected in sureties when defendants breached their bail conditions and a surety had been given on their behalf before bail was granted in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208509","208509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91069","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list (a) how much and (b) what proportion of the surety offered by each individual to secure bail for Julian Assange has been collected.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208512","208512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91070","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2014, Official Report, column 386W, on licensing laws, how much was raised in fines on those convicted of offences contrary to sections 141, 142, 146, 147A, 149 (1, 3, 4, 7a and 7b), 151, 152 and 153 of the Licensing Act 2003 in each of the last four years.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208488","208488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91071","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the sale price was of magistrates' court buildings sold in 2014; and how long each was not used for court business before it was sold.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208529","208529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91072","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many cases are still unallocated to either the National Probation Service or to a community rehabilitation company in (a) the North West, (b) Cheshire and (c) Warrington.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208484","208484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91073","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will place in the Library a copy of the assessment of the Major Projects Authority on his plans for the Probation Service.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208483","208483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91074","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of an offence under sections 136, 137, 156 and 157 of the Licensing Act 2003 in each of the last four years; how many of those people fined, were fined the maximum amount stipulated in that Act for those offences; how many of those people imprisoned were imprisoned for the maximum sentence stipulated in that Act for those offences; and how much money overall was raised in fines from those convicted in each such year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208446","208446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91075","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many summary convictions there were for misuse of class (a) A, (b) B and (c) C drugs under sections 4(2&3), 5(2&3), 6(2), 8, 9, 9(A), 11(2), 12(6), 13(3), 17(3), 17(4), 18(1-4), 20 and 23(4) of the Misuse of Drugs Act 1971 in each of the last four years; how many people who were fined were fined the maximum amount stipulated for those offences; how many people who were imprisoned were imprisoned for the maximum sentence stipulated for those offences; and how much was raised in fines from those convicted in each year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208447","208447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91076","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were convicted of an offence under sections 138, 140, 143, 144, 145, 148, 150(1&2) and 158 of the Licensing Act 2003 in each of the last four years; how many people who were fined were fined the maximum amount stipulated in that Act for those offences; and how much overall was raised in fines from those convicted in each year.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208448","208448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91077","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders were released from Crown courts on post-conviction bail for the offences of (a) murder, (b) rape, (c) manslaughter, (d) attempted murder and (e) child sex abuse in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208543","208543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91078","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders of which offence type released from Crown Courts on post conviction bail subsequently failed to surrender for sentencing in the latest period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208575","208575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91079","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of (a) men and (b) women convicted of sexual activity with a child received a prison sentence in each of the last five years; and what the average prison sentence was for (i) men and (ii) women.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208573","208573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91080","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of states party to the European Convention on Human Rights whose prisons breach any term of that convention.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208572","208572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91081","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the average proportion of (a) male and (b) female prisoners held in (i) open, (ii) closed and (iii) resettlement prisons was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208511","208511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91082","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2014, Official Report, column 844W, on courts: fines, what offences were committed by those who were fined the maximum in magistrates' courts in the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208581","208581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91083","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) men and (b) women convicted of sexual activity with a child received (i) a conditional discharge, (ii) a fine, (iii) a community order and (iv) a suspended prison sentence in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208576","208576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91084","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders convicted of a single offence of possession of class A drugs received (a) a discharge, (b) a fine, (c) a community order, (d) a suspended prison sentence and (e) an immediate prison sentence in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208577","208577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91085","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many foreign national prisoners are serving sentences in prisons for offences committed outside the UK.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208578","208578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91086","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 21 July 2014, Official Report, column 851W, on prisoners' release: terrorism, what offences were committed by those released in those years; and what the length of sentence (a) awarded by the court and (b) served in prison was by each offender.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208579","208579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91087","2014-09-11","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 8 July 2014, Official Report, column 256W, on courts: video conferencing, if he will publish a list of the remote sites for giving evidence in England and Wales that are located away from court buildings.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208616","208616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91088","2014-09-10","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-08","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what recent assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the changes in accuracy of the electoral registers between December 2010 and March 2014.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208450","208450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91089","2014-09-10","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-08","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what the (a) number and (b) proportion is of eligible people who are not registered to vote in each nation and region of the UK.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208604","208604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91090","2014-09-10","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-08","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, what assessment the Electoral Commission has made of the effects of (a) increased internal population mobility, (b) increased immigration, (c) electoral registration practices, (d) financial motivation and (e) any failure of electoral registration officers to conduct full door-to-door canvass of non-responders on electoral registration levels.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208605","208605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91091","2014-09-10","Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission","2014-09-08","To ask the hon. Member for South West Devon, representing the Speaker's Committee on the Electoral Commission, how much and what proportion of the Electoral Commission's annual budget the Electoral Commission Report into Completeness and Accuracy of the Electoral Register 2014 cost to produce.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208606","208606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91092","2014-09-11","Department for Transport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he or Ministers in his Department have had with Ministers in the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on the proposed reform of apprenticeships and its potential effects on his Department's projects and the work of its supply chain; and whether officials in his Department sit on programme boards managing that reform.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208615","208615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91093","2014-09-11","Department for Transport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of pedestrians who are (a) male, (b) female, (c) children and (d) over 65 suffered (i) fatal and (ii) serious injuries in each of the last 10 years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208623","208623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91094","2014-09-10","Department for Transport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of people likely to take up the alternative cash offer under the High Speed 2 compensation scheme.","Biography information for Christopher Pincher","Christopher Pincher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208587","208587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91095","2014-09-10","Department for Transport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the comprehensiveness of coverage of London of charging points for electric cars.","Biography information for Sir Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","Geoffrey Clifton-Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208588","208588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91096","2014-09-11","Department for Transport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether electrification of the South Wales Main Line will include electrification of the relief lines between Severn Tunnel Junction and Cardiff Central stations.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208485","208485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91097","2014-09-10","Department for Transport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the progress made in electrifying the Great Western Rail route.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208513","208513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91098","2014-09-11","Department for Transport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to limit changes to rail fares for commuters in 2015; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Tomlinson","Justin Tomlinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208569","208569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91099","2014-09-10","Women and Equalities","2014-09-08","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what discussions the Government Equalities Office has had with hate crime prevention groups in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208532","208532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91100","2014-09-10","Women and Equalities","2014-09-08","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what assessment she has made of the effect on organisational capacity and productivity of moving the Government Equalities Office between parent Departments since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208494","208494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91101","2014-09-10","Women and Equalities","2014-09-08","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, what the financial cost has been of moving the Government Equalities Office between parent Departments since 2010.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208495","208495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91102","2014-09-10","Women and Equalities","2014-09-08","To ask the Ministers for Women and Equalities, if she will make an assessment of the extent to which government policy on gender identity conforms to the Yogyakarta Principles on human rights law in relation to sexual orientation and gender identity; and what steps she has taken to ensure that policy conforms to those principles.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208586","208586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91103","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of people claiming employment and support allowance who were previously self employed.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208597","208597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91104","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the employment rate is for people (a) born with a disability and (b) disabled later in life.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208574","208574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91105","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2014, by the Cabinet Secretary to Question 32 in oral evidence taken in the Committee of Public Accounts, when the Major Projects Authority informed him that the universal credit project was way off track.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208626","208626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91106","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department provides to benefit offices on referrals to food banks.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208567","208567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91107","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which of the tools, processes and techniques used by Monster on its commercial job search website to protect users from fraudulent activity are not used on Universal Jobmatch; and what changes Monster has proposed to his Department to improve anti-fraud protection on his Department's website.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208500","208500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91108","2014-09-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what targets the Government has set for tackling homophobia in the workplace; and what steps have been taken to achieve those targets in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208534","208534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91109","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he will reply to the hon. Member for Walsall North's letters of 6 August 2014 and 20 August 2014 on behalf of a constituent.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208486","208486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91110","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of funeral payment decisions were made within his Department's target time in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208463","208463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91111","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of (a) single, (b) two-person, (c) three-person and (d) four-person occupancy standards for accommodation cabins in the offshore oil and gas industry on (i) the health and safety of offshore workers and (ii) operational safety on offshore installations.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208451","208451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91112","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, which statutory safety tests the Health and Safety Executive apply to an application from an operator in the offshore oil and gas industry for an increase in the occupancy rates for accommodation cabins on installations in the North Sea.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208452","208452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91113","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what changes have been made by the Health and Safety Executive to accommodation standards for offshore oil and gas workers on installations in the North Sea in the last three years; on what grounds the decision was made to approve such changes; and on what dates those changes were made.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208453","208453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91114","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions (a) Ministers in his Departmant and (b) the Health and Safety Executive have had with trades union representatives on accommodation standards for offshore oil and gas workers on installations in the North Sea.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208454","208454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91115","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to record and publish the reasons for applications for budgeting loans.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208461","208461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91116","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent discussions (a) Ministers in his Department and (b) the Health and Safety Executive have had with representatives of Oil and Gas UK on accommodation standards for offshore oil and gas workers on installations in the North Sea.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208457","208457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91117","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the (a) average and (b) total cost was of processing claims for Social Fund Funeral Payments in the last year.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208465","208465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91118","2014-09-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applications were made for short benefit advances in 2013-14; how many such applications were successful; what average amount was awarded to successful claimants; and what reason was given for the rejection of each unsuccessful application.","Biography information for Frank Field","Mr Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208472","208472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91119","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time was for a personal independent payment assessment by Atos in (a) England, (b) the South West and (c) Gloucester over the last 12 months.","Biography information for Richard Graham","Richard Graham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208449","208449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91132","2014-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what safeguards for (a) the NHS and (b) other UK public services the Government is seeking to secure within the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Sir Hugh Bayley","Hugh Bayley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905326","905326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91133","2014-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to widen access to higher education.","Biography information for Jesse Norman","Jesse Norman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905330","905330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91239","2014-09-11","Cabinet Office","2014-09-08","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what guidance he issues to companies delivering publicly-funded projects on taking the national interest into account when awarding contracts and sub-contracts.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905311","905311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/91347","2014-09-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-08","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the availability of finance for small firms and the level of lending by banks to small businesses.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 905314","905314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90808","2014-09-09","Attorney General","2014-09-05","To ask the Attorney General, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by the Law Officers' Departments within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208417","208417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90809","2014-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208416","208416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90810","2014-09-09","Cabinet Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208418","208418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90811","2014-09-09","HM Treasury","2014-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208433","208433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90812","2014-09-09","HM Treasury","2014-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to reduce the level of VAT on kerosene home heating oil; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208438","208438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90813","2014-09-09","HM Treasury","2014-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the full burden of (a) demand, (b) construction and (c) availability risk for the Thames Tideway Tunnel project has been transferred from the Government to Thames Tideway Tunnel Limited; and what the effect of each such transfer has been on the UK national balance sheet under the guidance given in ESA 95 Manual Chapters VI.4 and VI.5.","Biography information for Charlie Elphicke","Charlie Elphicke","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208368","208368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90814","2014-09-09","HM Treasury","2014-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy that HM Revenue and Customs collect detailed statistics on tax avoidance separately from data on general compliance.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208369","208369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90815","2014-09-09","HM Treasury","2014-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will introduce a threshold for the maximum proportion of a persons assets HM Revenue and Customs should seek as advance payment on tax avoidance schemes to prevent people becoming bankrupt.","Biography information for Richard Fuller","Richard Fuller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208370","208370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90816","2014-09-10","HM Treasury","2014-09-05","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects HM Treasury to sign off the full and final business case for universal credit.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208391","208391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90817","2014-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will discuss with (a) the Royal Association for the Deaf and (b) the Royal National Institute for the Blind the consequences for people with disabilities of decisions by some local authorities to introduce policies of switching off street lights.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208394","208394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90818","2014-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with local authorities who have introduced policies of switching off street lights to ascertain what the consequences of those decisions have been.","Biography information for Sir Bob Russell","Sir Bob Russell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208395","208395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90819","2014-09-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208443","208443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90820","2014-09-09","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208419","208419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90821","2014-09-10","Department for Communities and Local Government","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what guidance his Department gives to planning authorities on applications for fast-food restaurants (a) near schools and (b) in residential areas.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208406","208406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90822","2014-09-10","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what progress his Department has made on the Broadband Delivery UK programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208407","208407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90823","2014-09-09","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208420","208420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90824","2014-09-09","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208421","208421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90825","2014-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to improve its Information and Information Communication Technology capability.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208408","208408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90826","2014-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many suitably qualified and experienced personnel staff are currently required and how many such positions are vacant in (a) Astute, (b) Vanguard and (c) Trafalgar class submarine crews.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208440","208440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90827","2014-09-10","Ministry of Defence","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the standard length was of deployment for service personnel aboard (a) frigates and (b) destroyers in 2012; and what the standard length of such deployments is at present.","Biography information for Angus Robertson","Angus Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208441","208441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90828","2014-09-09","Department for Education","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what sanctions are available to local authorities to encourage parents to ensure that children begin school on time each day.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208376","208376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90829","2014-09-09","Department for Education","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of the current provision for sex and relationship education in schools in England; if she will update her Department's sex education guidance to reflect the effects of children being exposed to pornography over the internet; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208399","208399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90830","2014-09-10","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Minister for Education in the Welsh Government on tackling extremism and radicalisation in UK universities; and if he will convene a meeting with his counterparts in the devolved administrations to discuss this matter.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208390","208390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90831","2014-09-09","Department for Education","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by her Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208422","208422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90832","2014-09-09","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208423","208423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90833","2014-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by her Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208424","208424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90834","2014-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when the levels of fines and sanctions for the illegal felling of trees were last reviewed and updated; and what steps her Department takes to ensure that fines and sanctions for the illegal felling of trees are kept up-to-date and are effective.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208409","208409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90835","2014-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many trees have been illegally felled in England and Wales; how many restocking orders have been issued by the Forestry Commission or other relevant body; how many enforcement notices have subsequently been issued following restocking orders not being completed; and how many prosecutions have been taken forward by the Forestry Commission as a result of illegal felling of trees in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208410","208410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90836","2014-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what guidance her Department issues on the time required to investigate cases where prosecution is being considered by the Forestry Commission for the illegal felling of trees.","Biography information for Mrs Maria Miller","Maria Miller","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208411","208411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90837","2014-09-10","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will discuss with her counterparts in the devolved administrations the need for discussions with the European Commission on the development of a relief package for farmers and the UK beef industry; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208444","208444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90838","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress he has made towards the establishment of a Food Crime Unit.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208405","208405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90839","2014-09-09","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many of the Macdonald Review's recommendations for regulation reduction have been implemented to date.","Biography information for Bill Wiggin","Bill Wiggin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208436","208436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90840","2014-09-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208425","208425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90841","2014-09-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the UK's priorities are for the meeting of regional foreign ministers in Abuja in September 2014.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208373","208373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90842","2014-09-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department is taking steps to effect swift and safe passage back to the UK for British nationals in Nigeria as a result of extremist activity in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208374","208374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90843","2014-09-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the threat to the stability of the Nigerian government currently posed by extremist activity in that country.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208375","208375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90844","2014-09-09","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether the Government recognises President Assad as the legitimate head of state of Syria.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208371","208371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90845","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the authorisation of mitochondrial transfer techniques on the incidence of ovarian hyper stimulation syndrome; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208396","208396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90846","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the increase in the number of donor eggs that is needed to make mitochondrial transfer techniques practicable.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208397","208397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90847","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much his Department spent on dementia training for NHS staff on services for deaf users of British Sign Language in the last year.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208385","208385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90848","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what policies his Department has implemented to improve the dementia diagnosis rates of deaf British Sign Language users since 2010.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208386","208386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90849","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what targets the Government has set to improve the dementia diagnosis rates of deaf British Sign Language users in the next five years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208382","208382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90850","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the current NHS pathway is for deaf British Sign Language users to obtain a formal dementia diagnosis.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208383","208383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90851","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many deaf British Sign Language users over the age of 65 presented themselves to a clinician showing key symptoms of dementia in 2013-14.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208384","208384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90852","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will revise his definition of genetic modification to include manipulations of mitochondrial DNA.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208378","208378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90853","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many babies who were born before 24 weeks gestation survived in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208380","208380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90854","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208426","208426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90855","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much the NHS spent on each method of fertility treatment in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208381","208381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90856","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to require NHS trusts to benchmark executive pay increases against salaries at similarly performing NHS trusts.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208403","208403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90857","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues on whether pay increases at NHS trusts should be linked to the performance of hospitals at those trusts.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208404","208404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90858","2014-09-10","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Royal College of Nursing on ensuring that nurses trained in the UK are able to obtain nursing posts at UK hospitals.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208400","208400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90859","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 May 2014, Official Report, column 231W, on abortion, when he expects the Royal College of Obstetricians and Gynaecologists to update its guidance on the possible consequences of abortion.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208437","208437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90860","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 24 June 2014, Official Report, columns 156-7W, on ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome (OHSS), if he will make it his policy that all cases of OHSS are recorded in official statistics and not only those that require hospital admission or are graded as severe.","Biography information for Mary Glindon","Mrs Mary Glindon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208439","208439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90861","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what additional security measures and at what additional cost are being installed at the UK-French border at Calais.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208389","208389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90862","2014-09-10","Home Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she last met Eurotunnel Group representatives to discuss illegal immigration into the UK through the Channel Tunnel.","Biography information for David Hanson","Mr David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208442","208442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90863","2014-09-10","Home Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many (a) arrests and (b) cautions have been made in each of the last five years relating to cycling on pavements.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208401","208401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90864","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by her Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208427","208427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90865","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will direct the General Medical Council to release papers relating to the pre-signing of abortion HSA1 certificates by doctors to the police for investigation under the Offences Against the Person Act 1861 and Perjury Act 1911.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208379","208379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90866","2014-09-09","Home Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether any teachers have been arrested in connection with Operation Trojan Horse.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208372","208372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90867","2014-09-10","House of Commons Commission","2014-09-05","To ask the hon. Member for Caithness, Sutherland and Easter Ross representing the House of Commons Commission, pursuant to the Answer of 5 September 2014 to Question 207883, if the Commission will make available to the right hon. Member for Chelmsford all the records of all the discussions of the panel considering the appointment of the new Clerk of the House and Chief Executive with the personal data of the applicants redacted.","Biography information for Sir Simon Burns","Mr Simon Burns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208377","208377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90868","2014-09-10","Department for International Development","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to encourage clothing retailers to interrogate their supply chains in China to assess the working conditions of people working in that country.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208392","208392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90869","2014-09-09","Department for International Development","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by her Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208428","208428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90870","2014-09-09","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208429","208429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90871","2014-09-10","Ministry of Justice","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what increase there has been in the salary of (a) Mary Archer and (b) Alan Hubbard for posts connected with probation services in Essex over the last 12 months.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Mr David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208402","208402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90873","2014-09-09","Department of Health","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mental healthcare provision is available for prison inmates in England; what assessment he has made of the performance and adequacy of this provision; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ms Diane Abbott","Ms Diane Abbott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208387","208387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90874","2014-09-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, whether the exercise of the Royal Prerogative of Mercy in relation to Mr Donal Donnelly in 1985 was published in the Belfast and London Gazettes; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208398","208398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90875","2014-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what her most recent assessment is of the adequacy of the budget provision for the Northern Ireland Human Rights Commission.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208393","208393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90876","2014-09-10","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2014, Official Report, column 462-3W, on domestic visits, what domestic visits she has made since January 2013; and what the purpose of each such visit was.","Biography information for Sheila Gilmore","Sheila Gilmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208445","208445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90877","2014-09-09","Northern Ireland Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by her Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208430","208430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90878","2014-09-09","Scotland Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208431","208431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90879","2014-09-09","Department for Transport","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent steps he has taken to improve transport connections between Windsor and Reading.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208388","208388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90880","2014-09-09","Department for Transport","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208432","208432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90881","2014-09-09","Wales Office","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208434","208434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90882","2014-09-09","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of named day written questions were answered by his Department within the prescribed period in the (a) 2012-13 session, (b) 2013-14 session and (c) 2014-15 session to date.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208435","208435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90883","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2014, Official Report, column 639W on employment schemes: young people, what estimate he has made of how much of the 183.8 million allocated for the Youth Contract wage incentive scheme in this financial year will be used by that scheme.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208412","208412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90884","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 4 September 2014, Official Report, column 327W on employment schemes: young people, who represents his Department on the Growth and Enterprise Committee.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208413","208413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90885","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many work clubs are being run from Jobcentre Plus offices.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208414","208414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90886","2014-09-10","Department for Work and Pensions","2014-09-05","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the median length of service of Jobcentre Plus staff was in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208415","208415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90583","2014-09-09","Attorney General","2014-09-04","To ask the Attorney General, when he passed the letter from the hon Member for Christchurch about Mrs Kirkhope of Ferndown to the Chief Constable for Hampshire; and what steps has been taken as a result of that letter.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208253","208253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90584","2014-09-09","Attorney General","2014-09-04","To ask the Attorney General, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) the Law Officers' Departments and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208301","208301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90585","2014-09-08","Attorney General","2014-09-04","To ask the Attorney General, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in the Law Officers' Departments; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208334","208334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90586","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to reduce energy costs in his Department; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Simon Kirby","Simon Kirby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208333","208333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90587","2014-09-09","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the (a) highest and (b) lowest full-time equivalent salary paid by (i) his Department and (ii) its public bodies was in (A) 2010-11, (B) 2011-12, (C) 2012-13, (D) 2013-14 and (E) 2014-15; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Mr Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208300","208300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/90588","2014-09-08","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2014-09-04","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of potential GDP growth resulting from the Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2014/15 208268","208268"
