"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732369","2017-06-28","Home Office","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the independent review of the deportation with assurances policy commissioned in November 2013 will be laid before the House.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 897","897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732370","2017-06-28","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the provisions of the Courts Bill as introduced will include measures on (a) new standards and league table for prisons, (b) a new commissioning structure for prisons and (c) new powers for prison governors.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 891","891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732371","2017-06-28","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the provisions of the Courts Bill as introduced will include measures to strengthen the (a) Inspectorate of Prisons and (b) Prisons and Probation Ombudsman.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 892","892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732372","2017-06-28","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the provisions of the Courts Bill as introduced will include measures to reduce the level of suicide and self-harm in prisons.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 893","893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732373","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what support his Department provides to local authorities to increase the roll-out of charging points for electric vehicles.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 924","924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732374","2017-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether the Government plans to increase funding for public libraries to enable more libraries to become digital community hubs.","Biography information for Darren Jones","Darren Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 916","916"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732375","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the cost to the public purse has been of installing charging points for electric vehicles in each year since 2010.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 925","925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732376","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many charging points for electric vehicles there are in (a) Wales, (b) England, (c) Scotland and (d) Northern Ireland at the latest date for which information is available.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 926","926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732377","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans his Department has to ensure that the roll-out of charging stations for electric vehicles is spread evenly across all regions and parts of the UK.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 927","927"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732378","2017-06-27","Department for Transport","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to cease collection of tolls for the Severn Bridges.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 940","940"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732379","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of hate crime have been reported in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 941","941"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732380","2017-06-28","Department for Education","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that all British sign language interpreters use the same set of standards.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 951","951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732381","2017-06-28","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have claimed universal credit received a benefit sanction in 2016-17.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 954","954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732382","2017-06-28","Department of Health","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the planned expenditure on mental health services in the NHS is in each year until 2020-21 expressed in 2016-17 prices.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 955","955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732383","2017-06-28","Home Office","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the report of the Daniel Morgan Independent Panel will be published.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 956","956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732384","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much was recharged to (a) EU and (b) non-EU countries for health treatment by the NHS in 2016.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 973","973"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732385","2017-06-27","Wales Office","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the effect on Wales of the confidence and supply agreement with the Democratic Unionist Party.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 975","975"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732386","2017-06-27","Wales Office","2017-06-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what his policy is on the need for legislative consent from the National Assembly for Wales in relation to the Repeal Bill announced in the Queen's Speech 2017.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 976","976"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732387","2017-06-28","House of Commons Commission","2017-06-23","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, for what reasons hon. Members were offered only tablets manufactured by Apple; and if the Commission will take steps to offer Android and other tablet devices to (a) new hon. Members and (b) other hon. Members.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 984","984"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731685","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what measures he is taking to ensure chemicals used in agriculture are not detrimental to the bee population.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 693","693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731686","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterpart in Russia on the alleged death of Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi, leader of Daesh.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 694","694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731687","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he plans to change the eligibility criteria for people seeking to rent large cars, vans and HGVs.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 836","836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731688","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what discussions her Department has had with hon. Members for London constituencies, councillors from London local authorities and Greater London Assembly members on school funding since 1 January 2017.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 873","873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731689","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to set out the circumstances under which local authorities may exercise discretion in transferring lifetime tenancies for those seeking escape from domestic violence.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 698","698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731690","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for disability living allowance that were refused at mandatory consideration were (a) appealed, (b) overturned at tribunal and (c) dismissed at tribunal in (i) Blackburn constituency, (ii) local authorities in Lancashire and (iii) the UK in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 867","867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731691","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for personal independence payments that were refused at mandatory consideration were (a) appealed, (b) overturned at tribunal and (c) dismissed at tribunal in (i) Blackburn constituency, (ii) local authorities in Lancashire and (iii) the UK in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 868","868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731692","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for incapacity benefit that were refused at mandatory consideration were (a) appealed, (b) overturned at tribunal and (c) dismissed at tribunal in (i) Blackburn constituency, (ii) local authorities in Lancashire and (iii) the UK in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 869","869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731693","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many applications for employment and support allowance that were refused at mandatory consideration were (a) appealed, (b) overturned at tribunal and (c) dismissed at tribunal in (i) Blackburn constituency, (ii) local authorities in Lancashire and (iii) the UK in each year since 2011.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 870","870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731694","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many social workers are directly employed by the NHS in adult social care.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 691","691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731695","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to clinical commissioning groups regarding workforce planning (a) across the board and (b) for social workers on hospital wards.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 697","697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731696","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many social workers are employed in the adult social care sector.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 743","743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731697","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many social workers are employed by private adult social care providers carrying out NHS contracts.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 744","744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731698","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse was of the Commission on funding of Care and Support which published its final report in July 2011.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 774","774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731699","2017-06-27","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to encourage train operating companies to introduce automatic compensation payments on delayed services; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 633","633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731700","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to publish school leaders' remuneration on school websites; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 634","634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731701","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to increase transparency in school budgets for parents; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 635","635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731702","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to extend the right to buy to Low Start Shared Ownership schemes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 636","636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731703","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to extend right to buy to local authority-owned garages; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen McPartland","Stephen McPartland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 637","637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731704","2017-06-28","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether her Department has discussed the stay put policy in relation to fires in tower blocks with West Midlands Fire Service since the fire at Grenfell Tower.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 880","880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731705","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, (a) what the budget was and (b) how many firefighters were employed by West Midlands Fire Service in each of the last seven years.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 871","871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731706","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on tower blocks in Wolverhampton which are clad in flammable substances.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 875","875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731707","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Tobacco Control Plan for England will provide sustainable funding for local tobacco control and stop-smoking services.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 603","603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731708","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps the Government is taking to reduce inequalities in health outcomes caused by higher rates of smoking among lower socioeconomic groups.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 604","604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731709","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment has been made of the potential effect on waiting times for operations of the capped expenditure process.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 650","650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731710","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has been made of the number of patients potentially affected by the capped expenditure process.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 651","651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731711","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what role he has played in identifying areas due to be subject to the capped expenditure process.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 652","652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731712","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what public consultation has taken place on the capped expenditure process.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 653","653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731713","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his policy is on reform of the House of Lords.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 613","613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731714","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his policy is on the 2018 constituency boundary review.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 614","614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731715","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of income to be received by the NHS in each of the next five years as a result of the implementation of the Naylor Review.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 824","824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731716","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it a requirement that local trusts consult with staff, patients and the public on the consequences of the implementation of the Naylor Review for local committees.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 825","825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731717","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the amount of publicly owned land that will be released to the private sector as a result of implementation of the Naylor Review.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 826","826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731718","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of trends in the number of beds available as a result of the implementation of the Naylor Review.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 827","827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731719","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been resettled in each constituency under the Vulnerable Person Resettlement scheme.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 742","742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731720","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to increase NHS spending in line with increases in GDP.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 820","820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731721","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will list accident and emergency departments that the NHS plans to close or downgrade in the next five years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 738","738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731722","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ensure that the promises and pledges set out in the NHS Constitution on waiting times are met.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 821","821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731723","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the total savings required to be made under the capped expenditure process.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 852","852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731724","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on meeting the target of introducing front-door clinical streaming in all accident and emergency departments by October 2017.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 822","822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731725","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the value of private sector profit that will be generated in each of the next five years as a result of the implementation of the Naylor Review.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 823","823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731726","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made in the number of podiatrists required to fully staff the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 814","814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731727","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made in the number of radiologists required to fully staff the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 815","815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731728","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made in the number of paramedics required to fully staff the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 816","816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731729","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made in the number of nurses as a percentage of the total nursing workforce who are at the top of their agenda for change pay band.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 817","817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731730","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to end NHS funding of homeopathy.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 818","818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731731","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made in the number of nurses who have left the NHS to work in the private sector in the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 819","819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731732","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of Brexit on NHS staffing and finance.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 808","808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731733","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to end any NHS pay restraints.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 809","809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731734","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will restore the bursary for nursing and health care students.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 810","810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731735","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make it his policy to centralise the PFI debt burden, removing it from individual NHS Trusts and Foundation Trusts.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 811","811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731736","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made in the number of nurses required to fully staff the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 812","812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731737","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made in the number of clinical psychologists required to fully staff the NHS.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 813","813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731738","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, through what mechanism sustainability and transformation plans will be made accountable to their local communities.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 688","688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731739","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to require that each sustainability and transformation plan establishes a public-facing website.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 690","690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731740","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will commission an independent review of the evidence base supporting the case for change before approving any sustainability and transformation plan.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 696","696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731741","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with health professionals on the capped expenditure process.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 735","735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731742","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, which criteria determine whether health economies are subject to capped expenditure processes.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 736","736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731743","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the names and full remuneration packages of each local enterprise partnership chair and chief officer for the last three years.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 737","737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731744","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he has undertaken a national risk assessment of the sustainability and transformation plan process.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 615","615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731745","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he has any plans to visit Neston train station.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 616","616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731746","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many clinical commissioning groups are subject to the capped expenditure process.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 681","681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731747","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that all new houses are sold on a freehold basis.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 684","684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731748","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support poorly performing multi-academy trusts.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 686","686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731749","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the performance of the University of Chester Academies Trust.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 687","687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731750","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if the Government will bring the Small Business Saturday 2017 roadshow to Inverclyde.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 627","627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731751","2017-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many community rehabilitation companies have been required to pay a service credit to recompense for the minimum level of loss or damage as a result of the reduced provision of services.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 872","872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731752","2017-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much community rehabilitation companies paid back in service credits in each year since 2015.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 876","876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731753","2017-06-27","Attorney General","2017-06-22","To ask the Attorney General, how many fraud prosecutions the Crown Prosecution Service has brought in Crown Courts in England and Wales in each of the last five years; and what the outcomes of those prosecutions were.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 879","879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731754","2017-06-26","Northern Ireland Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what representations he has received on whether the Hyde Park justice campaign should receive Legal Aid.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 700","700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731755","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he plans to publish the full list of ministerial responsibilities for his Department.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 555","555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731756","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps are being taken to ensure that children from lower-income families are reaching the same expected developmental milestones at the same age as other children in their peer group.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 559","559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731757","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government plans to take to improve the quality of nursery provision to ensure that all children are school-ready at the age of five.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 560","560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731758","2017-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether it is her Department's policy to retain the entitlement to free television licences for the over-75s for the period 2020 to 2022.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 574","574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731759","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make an assessment of the value of using overseas diplomatic facilities as polling stations, to help electors living abroad to vote.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 579","579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731760","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent estimate she has made of the average annual cost to a police authority of employing a (a) police officer and (b) police community support officer; and what estimate she has made of that cost for each year from 2017-18 to 2021-22.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 581","581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731761","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will make an assessment of different approaches to anaesthesiology for hysteroscopy procedures used by the NHS.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 582","582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731762","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the Answer of 7 February 2017 to Question 62846, if he will provide updated figures on the number of staff departures from the UK Green Investment Bank up to 12 June 2017.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 617","617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731763","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many households are classed as fuel poor in (a) Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 618","618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731764","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many households are using a pre-payment meter for electricity and gas in (a) the Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 619","619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731765","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of household expenditure was spent on energy bills in (a) the Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 620","620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731766","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to support micro-enterprises in Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 621","621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731767","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of companies which do not recognise trades unions in (a) the Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 622","622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731768","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much finance the Green Investment Bank has provided since its creation in (a) the Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 623","623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731769","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much finance the British Business Bank has provided since its creation in (a) the Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 624","624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731770","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, which Minister in her Department will have responsibility for school food.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 626","626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731771","2017-06-27","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what percentage of the UK's agricultural workforce in 2016 were non-British nationals.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 649","649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731772","2017-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps she will take to ensure the reliability and objectivity of information essential to our democracy and a free and independent press; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 643","643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731773","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has for the relocation of Channel 4 outside London.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 609","609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731774","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her Department's policy is on national museums charging for entry to temporary exhibitions.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 610","610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731775","2017-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to introduce an industry-wide levy from social media companies and communications service providers to support awareness and preventative activity to counter internet harms; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 644","644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731776","2017-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether she plans to institute an expert data use and ethics commission; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 645","645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731777","2017-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, when he last met his counterpart in (a) Sudan and (b) south Sudan to discuss human rights.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 646","646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731778","2017-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are in receipt of disability living allowance payments in Coventry South constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 647","647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731779","2017-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to tackle digital exclusion in Coventry South constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 648","648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731780","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he plans to introduce legislation banning the use of plastic microbeads in products for use in the home.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 682","682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731781","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to publish feedback from the consultation into driving offences and penalties relating to causing death or serious injury that closed on 1 February 2017.","Biography information for Naz Shah","Naz Shah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 683","683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731782","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will provide funding to local authorities to use rapid international postal services to send postal ballot packs to overseas electors, in particular where an election occurs unexpectedly.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 685","685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731783","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will exempt Local Community Energy Schemes from paying business rates; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 711","711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731784","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he intends to publish the report by Dame Louise Casey on integration.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 712","712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731785","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she intends to activate the Section 253 Maintenance of Technical Capability power contained in the Investigatory Powers Act 2016 in connection with messaging services featuring end-to-end encryption, such as Whatsapp or Telegram.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 716","716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731786","2017-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the US and Russia on extending the New Strategic Arms Reduction Treaty until 2026.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 722","722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731787","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his policy to ban the use of flammable cladding in new social housing developments.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 726","726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731788","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make it his Department's policy that all social housing is fitted with one hour fire doors.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 727","727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731789","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, if he will make it his policy to bring forward proposals to reduce the age for eligibility to vote in elections to 16.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 729","729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731790","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the number of statutory flexible working requests made in (a) Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK in each year since 2014.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 730","730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731791","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many places of worship that have applied for security support from the scheme for security funding for places of worship have had work completed in (a) Batley and Spen, (b) each region of the UK and (c) total.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 765","765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731792","2017-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) how many and (b) what level of fines have been levied against husbands or partners who avoided paying child maintenance in each year since the introduction of the Child Support Act 1991; and what other sanctions have been imposed on people in that period.","Biography information for Yvonne Fovargue","Yvonne Fovargue","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 708","708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731793","2017-06-26","Department for International Trade","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the value of exports from businesses in (a) Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency, (b) Scotland and (c) the UK to other EU member states in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 731","731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731794","2017-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will review the availability of assessments for Personal Independence Payment at weekends.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 766","766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731795","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans he has for carbon capture and storage.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 732","732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731796","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of future trends in the level of investment in the North Sea oil and gas sector.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 733","733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731797","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will change building regulations to make it compulsory for new buildings to be self-sufficient in energy through the fitting of solar panels; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 709","709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731798","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to promote domestic solar photovoltaic installations.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 734","734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731799","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps he is taking to encourage greater use of solar panels; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 710","710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731800","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many places of worship applied for security support from the scheme for security funding for places of worship in (a) Batley and Spen, (b) each region and constituent part of the United Kingdom and (c) total.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 770","770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731801","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what meetings he has planned on devolution for West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 771","771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731802","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Burmese authorities on developments in that country affecting the human rights of the Rohingya people.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 746","746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731803","2017-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason his Department did not undertake a consultation into the closure of Batley Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 772","772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731804","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he last met (a) the Secretary of State for Education and (b) Ministers of that Department to discuss fire sprinklers in schools and BB100.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 747","747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731805","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether an emergency disaster plan was implemented by Kensington and Chelsea Council on the night of 13 June 2017 at Grenfell Tower.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 756","756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731806","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department will undertake a full review of all social housing properties making an assessment of safety in terms of resilience in a potential disaster, safety for human habitation and fitness for purpose.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 757","757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731807","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what requirement there is on councils to ensure fire exits, emergency lighting and fire safety information is in place in all social housing properties.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 758","758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731808","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assistance his Department provides to support sufferers of fibrous dysplasia.","Biography information for Matt Warman","Matt Warman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 759","759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731809","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what financial support his Department provides for sufferers of fibrous dysplasia.","Biography information for Matt Warman","Matt Warman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 760","760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731810","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to issue a review of Approved Document B (fire safety) for public consultation.","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 750","750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731811","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the Building Regulations Advisory Committee will be recalled to consider the review of Approved Document B (fire safety).","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 751","751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731812","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the Building Regulations Advisory Committee last met to consider the building regulations and Approved Document B (fire safety).","Biography information for Jim Fitzpatrick","Jim Fitzpatrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 752","752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731813","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will make an assessment of the potential effect of re-prioritising funding for counter-terror policing on (a) community policing and (b) other policing functions.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 786","786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731814","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will increase the level of funding for counter-terror policing in areas where that function has been strengthened.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 787","787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731815","2017-06-27","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of postal votes were defined as spoiled ballots in the General Election 2017.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 788","788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731816","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to review the materials used in renovating and building social housing in terms of their quality, fitness for purpose and safety implications.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 755","755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731817","2017-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the alleged Russian violation of the INF Treaty.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 848","848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731818","2017-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what consideration the Government has given to supporting a pan-European nuclear cruise missile treaty, as proposed by the Swiss and Swedish governments in 2016.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 849","849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731819","2017-06-27","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the (a) delays and (b) knock-on delays caused to Southern services at peak time due to holding trains to prevent simultaneous arrivals on platforms 15-19 at London Victoria station.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 850","850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731820","2017-06-27","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps (a) his Department and (b) Network Rail are taking to ease peak-time overcrowding for Brighton Main Line passengers on platforms 15-19 at London Victoria.","Biography information for Sarah Jones","Sarah Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 851","851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731821","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assisted living accommodation is available for people with illness and disability who are below the age of 55; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 853","853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731822","2017-06-27","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what proportion of votes cast in the General Election 2017 were cast by absentee ballots.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 862","862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731823","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will publish the cost-benefit analysis conducted for the sale of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 740","740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731824","2017-06-27","HM Treasury","2017-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress the Financial Conduct Authority has made in the investigation of the Connaught Income Fund.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 863","863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731825","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many referrals under the Prevent strategy concerned far-right motives; and how many of those referrals have been acted upon.","Biography information for Tracy Brabin","Tracy Brabin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 864","864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731826","2017-06-27","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many new voters were added to the electoral register after the General Election 2017 was announced; and whether the change in the number of people registered to vote will affect the work of the Electoral Commission in its review of parliamentary constituencies.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 866","866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731827","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps will he take to prevent the sale of ivory.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 741","741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731828","2017-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the Israeli Government on its approval of the first new settlement in the West Bank in over 20 years, Amichai; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lyn Brown","Lyn Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 878","878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731829","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what proportion of the total Feed-in Tariff subsidy to date for solar PV installations has been given to installations in Scotland.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 552","552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731830","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what the total installed generating capacity is of those gas-powered generating stations which have been constructed in England since 2000.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 553","553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731831","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will proscribe the political wing of Hezbollah under section 13 of the Terrorism Act 2000.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 556","556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731832","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent reports he has received on the size of Hezbollah's weapons arsenal.","Biography information for Paul Masterton","Paul Masterton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 557","557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731833","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has any plans to extend the M5 from Exeter to the Tamar Bridge in Plymouth.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 558","558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731834","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to ensure that memorials located in the Stonehouse Barracks in Plymouth which are dedicated to Royal Marines who died serving their country will be preserved and protected.","Biography information for Luke Pollard","Luke Pollard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 561","561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731835","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what discussions he has had with the Fire and Rescue Services on the retro-fitting of sprinkler systems in residential tower blocks.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 575","575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731836","2017-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has had discussions with the Palestinian Authority on the naming of a square in Jenin after Khaled Nazzal.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 583","583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731837","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the risk to security of a reduction in front-line policing.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 584","584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731838","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made on the effect of a reduction in the Police Force budget on the police's capacity to tackle serious crime.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 585","585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731839","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people have been subject to Terrorism Prevention and Investigation Measures in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 586","586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731840","2017-06-27","Prime Minister","2017-06-22","To ask the Prime Minister, whether the independent public inquiry into the Grenfell Tower fire will have the power to compel witnesses; and how much funding has been set aside for (a) the inquiry and (b) legal representation to the inquiry for victims.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 587","587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731841","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government's undertaking to test cladding in high-rise residential tower blocks will extend to other tall buildings including those occupied by (a) hospitals and (b) businesses.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 588","588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731842","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding her Department provides for primary school breakfast provision; and how many (a) pupils and (b) schools receive such funding.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 629","629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731843","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what central Government funding was allocated to the London Borough of Redbridge in each year since May 2010.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 630","630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731844","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will reverse the decision made in 2011 to close King George Hospital Accident and Emergency Department.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 631","631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731845","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the cost of free school breakfast provision in every primary school in England.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 632","632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731846","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people are currently subject to terrorism prevention and investigation measures.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 625","625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731847","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will take steps to ensure that disabled children are not prevented from participating in school trips and other activities as a result of having medical appointments classified as absences.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 654","654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731848","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what additional fire safety arrangements will be put in place in tall residential tower blocks which may have flammable cladding; and what central Government funding is available to finance such arrangements.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 656","656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731849","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the proposals relating to independent schools in the Schools that Work for Everyone consultation document will be taken forward.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","Mr William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 713","713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731850","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the proposals relating to universities in the Schools that Work for Everyone consultation document will be taken forward.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","Mr William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 714","714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731851","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if the Government will introduce universal free breakfasts for primary school children.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","Mr William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 715","715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731852","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Queen's Speech 2017, how much financial support the Government will provide to councils where urgent fire-safety checks have identified buildings as high risk; and what is the application process for that support.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 721","721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731853","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many fire-safety checks have been carried out in high-rise residential blocks in Birmingham since the Grenfell Tower fire; and, of those checks, how many buildings have been identified as high risk.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 723","723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731854","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the findings of fire-safety checks carried out in high-rise residential blocks.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 724","724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731855","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, (a) how many private rented sector households have approached his Department for advice about the combustibility of their buildings, (b) in how many buildings tested since the Grenfell Tower fire have inflammable materials been identified and (c) what estimate he has made of the number of private rented sector properties that need to be investigated.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 707","707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731856","2017-06-27","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will provide a new funding stream to encourage cycling in small towns and rural areas.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 775","775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731857","2017-06-27","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what funding his Department has made available for cycling in (a) rural areas and (b) Cheshire East since 2010.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 776","776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731858","2017-06-27","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what sources of funding are available to small towns and rural areas to fund new cycling infrastructure.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 777","777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731859","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish the outcome of the consultation on the school funding formula.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 773","773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731860","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Queen's Speech 2017, who will sit on the commission for countering extremism and how does the Government plans to appoint the commissioners to the commission.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 778","778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731861","2017-06-27","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Queen's Speech 2017, what the timescale will be for the review of the Government's counter-terrorism strategy.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 779","779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731862","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will provide an update on how sensitive data is protected in the NHS; and what steps he has taken to improve cyber-security in the NHS since the ransomware attack on 12 May 2017.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 780","780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731863","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to establish an inquiry into the cyber-attack on the NHS on 12 May 2017.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 781","781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731864","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the total cost was of emergency measures put in place to address the NHS ransomware attack on 12 May 2017 and from which budgets those costs were met.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 782","782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731865","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much has been spent on IT infrastructure in the NHS in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 783","783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731866","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether money from the Grenfell Tower Residents' Discretionary Fund can be used to fund the legal costs of court challenges for those affected by the fire.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 748","748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731867","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many cyber-security incidents have taken place in the NHS since 2010; and how many incidents there have been where (a) patient data has been accessed or compromised and (b) patient care has been interrupted or halted.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 784","784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731868","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Answer of 6 March 2017 to Question 64994 on Department for Communities and Local Government: procurement, what estimate he has made of the amount spent on procurement management in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 761","761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731869","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 7 March 2017 to Question 65680 on Department for Culture, Media and Sport: procurement, how much of the procurement spending in each of those years related to the services of management consultants.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 762","762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731870","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the investigations into councils' residential tower blocks will assess the (a) flammability and poisonous elements contained in wall insulation and furniture, (b) operability of fire alarms and (c) whether central stairwells in towers are protected from fire and smoke.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 753","753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731871","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the Answer of 2 March 2017 to Question 64995, on Department for Culture, Media and Sport: procurement, what estimate she has made of the total budget for managing procurement in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 763","763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731872","2017-06-26","Prime Minister","2017-06-22","To ask the Prime Minister, whether the terms of reference for the independent public inquiry into the Grenfell Tower tragedy will include how victims were treated in the aftermath of that tragedy; and how homeless survivors are supported by councils.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 754","754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731873","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the Written Statement of 1 March 2017, HCWS509, on Sex and Relationships Education (SRE), what the timetable is for deciding the content of the new SRE.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 807","807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731874","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the proposal set out in Schools that work for everyone, published in September 2016, on the 50 per cent admissions cap on faith schools.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","Mr William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 847","847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731875","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many mindfulness-based interventions for repeat episode depression were approved in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 837","837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731876","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions for anti-depressants were issued in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 838","838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731877","2017-06-27","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many staff in his Department have worked on the Red Tape Challenge project since its inception; and what the paygrade was of those staff.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 857","857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731878","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what legal costs the Government has incurred as a result of the case of case of R (on application of A and B) v Secretary of State for Health (Respondent) [2017].","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 739","739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731879","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the (a) higher education and (b) further edcuation participation rates for young people aged 18 to 25 are in (i) the 100 poorest Lower Super Output areas (LSOA) and (ii) the 100 richest Lower Super Output areas in England in each year for which data is available; and what the (A) town, (B) local authority area and (C) constituency was of each LSOA.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 839","839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731880","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many renewable obligation certificates have been issued to date to accredited Scottish hydro stations built before 2000; and of those, how many were issued to hydro stations that, before 2000, had a generating capacity calculated in excess of 20MWs, but were subsequently calculated as having a net capacity of less than 20MWs.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 835","835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731881","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, (a) how many and (a) what proportion of houses of multiple occupation were registered under the mandatory HMO licensing scheme in each year since its introduction.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 840","840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731882","2017-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many violent incidents there were per 1,000 population in prisons in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 841","841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731883","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether the Government plans to consult on proposed changes to relationships and sex education in schools.","Biography information for Andrew Selous","Andrew Selous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 854","854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731884","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of young people aged 15 to 25 died from suicide in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 842","842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731885","2017-06-27","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how much has been spent on the Red Tape Challenge in each year since its inception.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 861","861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731886","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what proportion of prisoners have been diagnosed with one or more psychiatric conditions in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 843","843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731887","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many prescriptions for anti-depressants were issued in the prison system in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 844","844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731888","2017-06-27","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether it is his policy to continue with the Red Tape Challenge; and if he will provide an update of its work to date.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 856","856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731889","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an estimate of the cost of installing sprinkler systems in (a) new build domestic homes, (b) retrofitted domestic homes, (c) new tower blocks and (d) retrofitted tower blocks.","Biography information for Chris Ruane","Chris Ruane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 845","845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731890","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what information his Department holds on whether any survivors of the Grennfell Tower fire who have been made statutory homeless have been declared intentionally homeless by the Royal Borough of Kensington and Chelsea Council.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 745","745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731891","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will take steps to strengthen identification requirements, including proof of address, for businesses registering with Companies House.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 628","628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731892","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of convictions flagged as domestic abuse offences resulted in a (i) custodial sentence and (ii) fine in each month since 2015.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 605","605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731893","2017-06-27","HM Treasury","2017-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax exemption for personal tax credits in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 639","639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731894","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what sentences resulted for all convictions for the offence of coercive and controlling behaviour in each month since December 2015.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 606","606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731895","2017-06-27","HM Treasury","2017-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax exemption for the income of charities in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 640","640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731896","2017-06-27","HM Treasury","2017-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received income tax relief for wear and tear allowance in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 641","641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731897","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, (a) how many and (b) what proportion of convictions flagged as domestic abuse offences resulted in (i) a suspended sentence and (ii) a community sentence in each month since 2015.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 607","607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731898","2017-06-27","HM Treasury","2017-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received film tax relief in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 642","642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731899","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the effect of pre-charge bail reforms on the police's response to domestic abuse incidents.","Biography information for Jess Phillips","Jess Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 608","608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731900","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will ensure that people who lose access to benefits as a result of a PIP reassessment are eligible for legal aid for expenses for any appeal against that decision.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 611","611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731901","2017-06-27","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many prosecutions there have been for electoral fraud relating to postal votes in each of the last five years; and to which parliamentary constituencies such prosecutions related.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 655","655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731902","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that recommended fire safety standards are met in private sector housing.","Biography information for Rachel Reeves","Rachel Reeves","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 612","612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731903","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much additional (a) capital and (b) revenue funding her Department plans to allocate for opening a specialist maths school in every major city in England.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 657","657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731904","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department plans to allocate to the curriculum fund in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 658","658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731905","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much additional revenue funding her Department plans to make available for primary schools for new nursery staff in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 659","659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731906","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding his Department plans to make available for mental health first aid training for all school teachers by the end of the Parliament in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 660","660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731907","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to reform the way in which Neighbourhood Plans can be amended by (a) parish councils and (b) other sponsoring community groups; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 692","692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731908","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate her Department has made of the resources needed to provide a free breakfast to every primary school child in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 666","666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731909","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she has made an assessment of the further education provision that will be required to deliver a national retraining scheme.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 674","674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731910","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional funding her Department plans to make available to ensure that all schools have a single point of contact for mental health services in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 661","661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731911","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what additional funding her Department will make available to increase the number of teaching hours to an average of 900 hours a year in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 667","667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731912","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she plans to take to deliver lifelong learning in digital skills.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 675","675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731913","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to publish the results of the Schools that work for everyone consultation.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 662","662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731914","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is her Department's policy that all primary schools will include a nursery.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 676","676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731915","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to publish the Government's response to the second stage of the consultation on the schools national funding formula.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 663","663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731916","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when her Department plans to publish its Green Paper on children's mental health.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 677","677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731917","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to carry out further consultation on primary assessment in England.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 664","664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731918","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much additional (a) revenue and (b) capital funding her Department plans to invest in further education colleges in (i) 2017-18, (ii) 2018-19, (iii) 2019-20, (iv) 2020-21 and (v) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 668","668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731919","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the cost to the public purse of debt forgiveness on student loan repayments for teachers in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 678","678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731920","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her Department's policy is on the level of debt forgiveness on student loan repayments for teachers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 679","679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731921","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse will be of ensuring that no school will have its funding cut as part of the introduction of a new funding formula for schools in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 680","680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731922","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the cost to the public purse will be of protecting the pupil premium in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 695","695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731923","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what funding her Department plans to allocate to establish a national programme to attract experienced industry professionals to work in further education colleges in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 669","669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731924","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much capital funding her Department plans to allocated to deliver new institutes of technology in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 670","670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731925","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether her Department plans to carry out further consultation on analysing family circumstances and education.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 665","665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731926","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of introducing discounted train and bus travel for apprentices in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 671","671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731927","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to the Answer of 25 January 2017 to Question 60970, whether there have been more (a) racist incidents and (b) banning orders than those referred to for 1 July 2015 to 10 July 2016.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 828","828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731928","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on attracting experienced industry professionals to work in further education colleges.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 801","801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731929","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the Government's policy is on UK engagement with the Fundamental Rights Agency after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 829","829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731930","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new institutes of technology her Department plans to provide in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 802","802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731931","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will publish a Green Paper on funding for tertiary education.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 803","803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731932","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which programmes his Department currently funds will have their funding affected by the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 830","830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731933","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on a new right to request (a) paid and (b) unpaid leave for training for teachers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 804","804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731934","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential implications for the funding of anti-hate crime projects of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 831","831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731935","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on a national retraining scheme for teachers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 805","805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731936","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on improving the accountability of schools at Key Stage 3.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 806","806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731937","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions her Department has had with the Home Office on proposals for a ministerial seminar on hate on the internet.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 832","832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731938","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to convene the ministerial seminar on hate on the  internet referred to in Action Against Hate: The UK Government's plan for tackling hate crime, published in July 2016; and which Government departments will be consulted prior to that seminar on which victims' groups, stakeholders and industry representatives will be invited to attend.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 833","833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731939","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Russian counterpart on plans to combat anti-Semitism, Islamophobia, racism, homophobia and other forms of discrimination at the 2018 World Cup in that country.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 834","834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731940","2017-06-27","Department for International Development","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many civil servants of her Department will be employed to work in the private offices of the joint Department for International Development and Foreign and Commonwealth Office ministers.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 858","858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731941","2017-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many civil servants of his Department will be employed in the private offices of the joint Department for International Development and Foreign and Commonwealth Office ministers.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 859","859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731942","2017-06-27","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the ministerial responsibilities are of the new joint Department for International Development and Foreign and Commonwealth Office ministers.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 860","860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731943","2017-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many soldiers and officers have been recruited to the (a) army and (b) reserve forces in the last two years, broken down by regiment.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 855","855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731944","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, from which school year the proposed national funding formula for schools will apply.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 865","865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731945","2017-06-27","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will halt the proposals contained in the future of Southeastern Trains Franchise consultation to cut trains on the Bexleyheath line to Charing Cross and Victoria stations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Clive Efford","Clive Efford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 846","846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731946","2017-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if she will list the locations of all eight-lane athletics tracks constructed in England since the 2012 Olympics.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 874","874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731947","2017-06-27","HM Treasury","2017-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether HM Treasury officials have held meetings with other Government Departments in 2017 to discuss the removal of landfill tax from abandoned waste sites owned by the Crown Estate.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 877","877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731948","2017-06-26","Attorney General","2017-06-22","To ask the Attorney General, if he will provide an update on the status of the case of the hon. Member for Thirsk and Malton's constituent, as detailed in the letter of 14 December 2016 on the Serious Fraud Investigation into allegations concerning GPT and the conduct of its business in Saudi Arabia.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 554","554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731949","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will review the suitability of commercial to residential conversions through permitted development.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 572","572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731950","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether additional resources will be made available to local authorities to help ensure the safety of tenants living in high-rise residential buildings.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 573","573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731951","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on improving the accountability of schools at key stage 3.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 562","562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731952","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether additional funding will be made available to schools to ensure that every child can access an academic, knowledge-rich curriculum.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 564","564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731953","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on providing support for teachers throughout their careers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 565","565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731954","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on attracting experienced industry professionals to work in further education colleges.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 566","566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731955","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many new institutes of technology her Department plans to provide in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 567","567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731956","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will publish a green paper on funding for tertiary education.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 568","568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731957","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on a new right to request (a) paid and (b) unpaid leave for training for teachers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 569","569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731958","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on a national retraining scheme for teachers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 570","570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731959","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on improving the phonics screening test.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 571","571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731960","2017-06-27","HM Treasury","2017-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the Government has made a recent assessment of wage growth across the regions.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 578","578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731961","2017-06-26","House of Commons Commission","2017-06-22","To ask the right hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington, representing the House of Commons Commission, if the Commission will undertake an impact assessment of the effect of changes in funding to frontline policing on public safety.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 576","576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731962","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent estimate she has made of core school funding in each year from 2015 to 2019.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 577","577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731963","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether she plans to increase funding for primary and secondary schools in Harrow in (a) 2018-19 and (b) 2019-20; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 593","593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731964","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the Government's policy is on the future of the Northern Powerhouse.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 594","594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731965","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he plans to provide guidance on limiting the number of UK registered bankers earning over one million euros; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 580","580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731966","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will provide an update on the Opportunity Areas programme.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 595","595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731967","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the Government plans to issue consultation exercise on changes to business rates.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 596","596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731968","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether he plans to introduce restrictions on the overseas ownership of new properties in London; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 589","589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731969","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his Department's policy is for the provision of additional co-operative housing; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 590","590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731970","2017-06-27","Department for International Development","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department has provided to earthquake recovery efforts in Nepal; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 591","591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731971","2017-06-27","Department for International Development","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what support her Department is providing to famine relief operations in Somalia; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Gareth Thomas","Gareth Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 592","592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731972","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate she has made of the potential cost to the fire service in the event of a major fire at the waste site at Sandy Lane, Worksop.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 597","597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731973","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the potential costs of closure of the Northern rail line from Sheffield to Worksop in the event of a fire at the abandoned waste recycling site at Sandy Lane, Worksop.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 598","598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731974","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the value of the waste site at Sandy Lane, Worksop.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 599","599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731975","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate he has made of the cost of clearing waste from the waste site at Sandy Lane, Worksop (a) including and (b) not including landfill tax forgone.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 600","600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731976","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, for how many days the waste site at Sandy Lane, Worksop, has had no site management.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 601","601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731977","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the environmental and health risks posed by the abandoned waste site at Sandy Lane, Worksop.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 602","602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731978","2017-06-27","HM Treasury","2017-06-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people received research and development tax credits in (a) 2014-15, (b) 2015-16 and (c) 2016-17.","Biography information for Peter Dowd","Peter Dowd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 638","638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731979","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much (a) revenue and (b) capital funding her Department plans to allocate for the national retraining scheme in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 672","672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731980","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much funding her Department plans to allocate for delivering lifelong learning in digital skills in (a) 2017-18, (b) 2018-19, (c) 2019-20, (d) 2020-21 and (e) 2021-22.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 673","673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731981","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Government plans to pilot voter identification at the 2018 local elections.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 689","689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731982","2017-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that insurance requirements do not prevent (a) deaf and (b) other disabled people from entering employment.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 701","701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731983","2017-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to replicate the funding available to the creative industries through the European Regional Development Fund when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 717","717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731984","2017-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what recent discussions she has had with ministerial colleagues on the role of teaching creative subjects in schools in addressing any potential skills gap in the creative industries when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 718","718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731985","2017-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the effect of the UK leaving the EU on smaller creative and cultural organisations.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 719","719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731986","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when a decision will be made on the outstanding force majeure claims made by the Govia Thameslink Railway.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 725","725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731987","2017-06-27","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions she has had with representatives of smaller creative and cultural organisations on replacing EU funding when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 720","720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731988","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment she has made of the merits of the European Accessibility Act for deaf and disabled artists; and what plans she has to replicate or improve on this legislation when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 699","699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731989","2017-06-27","Department of Health","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what action the Government is taking to tackle the disproportionate levels of mental health issues among deaf children.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 702","702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731990","2017-06-27","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what plans he has to ensure that negotiations on the UK leaving the EU do not result in any job losses in the North East's manufacturing sector.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 703","703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731991","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans his Department has to review regulations on the purchase of (a) leasehold properties and (b) the sale of freeholds to third parties by property developers.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 704","704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731992","2017-06-27","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he plans to announce a decision on the future of Newton-le-Willows job centre.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 705","705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731993","2017-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's strategy and targets are for the remediation of contaminated land.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 706","706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731994","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what remedial actions he may take in the event of a franchised train-operating company's force majeure claim for relief from benchmarked contractual payments being (a) not agreed and (b) agreed only in part by his Department.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 728","728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731995","2017-06-27","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make it his policy to (a) record and (b) publish data on the number of incidents of self-harm.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 764","764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731996","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what consideration his Department has given to the recommendations in Appendix 9 of the independent report, Changes to improve the performance of the Southern network and train services, and restore passenger confidence, when assessing Govia Thameslink Railway's outstanding force majeure claims.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 794","794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731997","2017-06-27","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will list the Department's funding for projects supporting Armed Forces veterans by local authority area in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 767","767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731998","2017-06-27","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what progress he has made on agreeing a bilateral trade deal to export British lamb to the US since 27 July 2016.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 768","768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731999","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether any of the recommendations on the Govia Thameslink Railway (GTR) franchise agreement in Appendix 9 of the independent report by Chris Gibb have been taken forward with (a) GTR and (b) Network Rail; and if he will place a copy of that report in the Library.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 795","795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732000","2017-06-27","Attorney General","2017-06-22","To ask the Attorney General, if he will publish any legal advice sought by or given to the Government on the Unlawful Killing (Recovery of Remains) Bill.","Biography information for Conor McGinn","Conor McGinn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 769","769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732001","2017-06-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to publish the review of Fixed Odds Betting Terminals which closed in December 2016.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul J Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 792","792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732002","2017-06-29","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what her policy is on the provision of free television licences for over-75s.","Biography information for Mr Paul Sweeney","Mr Paul J Sweeney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 793","793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732003","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has provided relief to Govia Thameslink Railway from contractual payments against benchmark targets in the current franchise agreement for Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern passenger services.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 796","796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732004","2017-07-06","Department for Transport","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many of the force majeure claims from Govia Thameslink Railway for the current franchise agreement for Thameslink, Southern and Great Northern passenger services have been expedited by his Department; and for what periods those claims apply.","Biography information for Lloyd Russell-Moyle","Lloyd Russell-Moyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 797","797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732005","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans the Government has to increase funding for (a) primary, (b) secondary and (c) further education in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Jim McMahon","Jim McMahon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 749","749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732006","2017-06-27","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many investors who have brought back into use derelict town centre premises have been subject to the community infrastructure levy since it was was introduced.","Biography information for Lord Mann","John Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 785","785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732007","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the number of schools built since 2010 that are (a) not fitted with sprinkler systems and (b) have used flammable cladding.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 789","789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732008","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate she has made of the number of school buildings in England that contain asbestos.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 790","790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732009","2017-06-27","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans she has to review or amend Building Bulletin 100: design for fire safety in schools.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 791","791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732010","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on improving the phonics screening test.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 798","798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732011","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether additional funding will be made available to ensure that every child can access an academic, knowledge-rich curriculum.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 799","799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/732012","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on providing support for teachers throughout their careers.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 800","800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731108","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will provide a list of people and organisations which have lobbied him and his Department on the UK's requirements for seasonal workers.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 420","420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731109","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to announce the successful applications for the new station funding scheme.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 421","421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731110","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his Department's announcement of 26 August 2016, for what additional reasons the decision to award new station funding has been delayed.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 422","422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731111","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to support regional airports.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 423","423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731112","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions the Government has had with the Venezuelan Government on the political situation in that country; and what recent discussions his Department has had with the Department for International Development on foreign aid for citizens of Venezuela.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 291","291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731113","2017-06-26","Department for International Development","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what aid the UK has provided for the citizens of Venezuela in the past five years.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 431","431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731114","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that privately-owned tall buildings used for residential purposes are checked for fire safety.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 34","34"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731115","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the effect of the use of permitted development rules in Chipping Barnet constituency.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 35","35"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731116","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that residential buildings of 10 storeys and higher are re-inspected to ensure that fire regulations are being complied with.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 42","42"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731117","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish her plans for ensuring the content of relationships education in primary schools is age appropriate; and if she will place a copy of those plans in the Library.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 56","56"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731118","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will take steps to improve the enforcement of court orders made in animal cruelty cases.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 57","57"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731119","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will make it his policy to increase the maximum penalty for animal cruelty offences to five years.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 253","253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731120","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to assess the implications of the Grenfell Tower tragedy for limiting the use of permitted development rights to convert tall office buildings into residential accommodation.","Biography information for Theresa Villiers","Theresa Villiers","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 452","452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731121","2017-06-26","Department for International Trade","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what discussions he has had with (a) the Scottish Government and (b) external organisations on attracting trade and international investment to Glasgow East constituency.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 89","89"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731122","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps her Department is taking to tackle digital exclusion in Glasgow East constituency.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 90","90"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731123","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with officials of the Republic of Zimbabwe on human rights.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 91","91"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731124","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with officials of the Republic of Zimbabwe on that country's rate of inflation.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 92","92"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731125","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with counterparts in the EU on free and fair elections in the Republic of Zimbabwe in 2018.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 93","93"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731126","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are in receipt of child benefit payments in Glasgow East constituency.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 94","94"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731127","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants have been sanctioned; and for what reasons those claimants were sanctioned in Maidenhead constituency in each month since May 2015.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 113","113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731128","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants have been sanctioned; and for what reasons those claimants were sanctioned in Glasgow East constituency in each month since May 2015.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 114","114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731129","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on which date (a) he and (b) a Minister in his Department last visited Shettleston Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 115","115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731130","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, (a) on which dates and (b) by which means his Department has taken steps to raise awareness by way of publicity about changes to the UK state pension age for women born in the 1950s.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 107","107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731131","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Glasgow East constituency have transitioned from disability living allowance to personal independence payments in the last 12 months.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 108","108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731132","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are in receipt of carer's allowance in Glasgow East constituency.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 109","109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731133","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people are in receipt of disability living allowance payments in Glasgow East constituency.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 110","110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731134","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on which date (a) he and (b) a Minister in his Department last visited Easterhouse Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 111","111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731135","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on which date (a) he and (b) a Minister in his Department last visited Parkhead Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 112","112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731136","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with counterparts in the African Union on free and fair elections in the Republic of Zimbabwe in 2018.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 101","101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731137","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, on which date (a) he or (b) a Minister of his Department last visited a company headquartered in Glasgow East constituency.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 102","102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731138","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on which date a Minister of his Department last visited Baillieston DVSA test centre in Glasgow.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 103","103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731139","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many (a) part-time and (b) full-time employees are based at Baillieston DVSA test centre in Glasgow.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 104","104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731140","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, which landlord provides accommodation for Baillieston DVSA test centre in Glasgow.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 105","105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731141","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum seekers are resident in Glasgow East constituency.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 106","106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731142","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are in receipt of child tax credit payments in Glasgow East constituency.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 95","95"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731143","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people are in receipt of working tax credit payments in Glasgow East constituency.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 96","96"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731144","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many children live in poverty in Glasgow East constituency.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 97","97"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731145","2017-06-26","Scotland Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, on which dates (a) he and (b) a Minister of his Department last attended an official engagement in Glasgow East constituency.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 98","98"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731146","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, on which date the current property rental contract is due to expire for the Baillieston DVSA test centre in Glasgow.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 99","99"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731147","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the (a) part-time and (b) full-time staff headcount has been at Baillieston DVSA test centre, Glasgow in each year since 2007.","Biography information for David Linden","David Linden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 100","100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731148","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support his Department is providing for the food manufacturing sector to mitigate the effect of EU workforce shortages.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 231","231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731149","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what support his Department is providing to the farming sector to mitigate the effect of EU workforce shortages.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 232","232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731150","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what response her Department has made to the recommendations of the report entitled, Facing the future: tackling post-Brexit labour and skills shortages published in June 2017 by the CIPD and the National Institute for Economic and Social Research.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 233","233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731151","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people who have a diagnosis of autism have been in hospital for more than two years.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 124","124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731152","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland played a role in the post-election negotiations with the Democratic Unionist Party.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 320","320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731153","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what plans are in place to replicate or replace EU funding streams from the European Structural and Investment Funds; and when steps will be taken to ensure such funding is in place prior to the expiry of the current programming period in 2020.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 434","434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731154","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether all hospitals and NHS buildings are fully compliant with fire and building regulations; and if he will ensure that all NHS properties will be checked and signed-off as safe.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 436","436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731155","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether schools and education establishments are fully compliant with fire and safety regulations; and if she will ensure that checks will be made to ensure the safety of schools.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 437","437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731156","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to his Mansion House speech of 20 June 2017, what discussions he has had with the European Investment Bank in the last three months.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 306","306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731157","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Chancellor of the Exchequer's Mansion House speech of 20 June 2017, what assessment his Department has made of the (a) types and (b) cost of any new technology that needs to be deployed for customs border arrangements after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 290","290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731158","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, with reference to the Answer of 20 February 2017 to Question 63690, how many full-time equivalent staff his Department has.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 303","303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731159","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what the total number of (a) secondees and (b) contractors from the private sector is in his Department.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 304","304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731160","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, if he will list the civil servants and the meetings they attended in Brussels on 19 June 2017 for the first round of Article 50 negotiations.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 305","305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731161","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, when he intends to respond to the consultation on Furniture and furnishings fire safety regulations: proposed changes, which closed on 11 November 2016.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 158","158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731162","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will commission research to determine the take-up of shared parental leave; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jo Swinson","Jo Swinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 159","159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731163","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Government will publish the Tobacco Control Plan.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 43","43"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731164","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish the results of the consultation on a national funding formula for schools which closed in April 2016.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 286","286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731165","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what the real terms per pupil change in the overall schools budget will be in each of the next three years taking into account salary and national insurance increases, the apprenticeship levy and anticipated growth in pupil numbers.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 287","287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731166","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish the Gibb Report on the Southern Rail franchise before the end of June 2017.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 288","288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731167","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to bring forward proposals for a rail ombudsman.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 289","289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731168","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when the Government plans to publish a green paper on online safety for young people.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 60","60"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731169","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what progress the Government has made on allocating the Equitable Life Payment Scheme funds to policyholders.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 72","72"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731170","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment her Department has made of the adequacy of security at places of worship.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 426","426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731171","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether other mosques have been awarded funding in addition to those announced in 2016 under the scheme for security funding for places of worship.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 427","427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731172","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many incidents of hate crime resulted in convictions in (a) 2016 and (b) 2017.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 428","428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731173","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many places of worship chosen to benefit from the scheme for security funding for places of worship have had the work relating to that security completed; and what assessment her Department has made of the level of improvement in their security.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 429","429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731174","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications have been made to the scheme for security funding for places of worship since it was reopened early in 2017.","Biography information for Paula Sherriff","Paula Sherriff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 430","430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731175","2017-06-26","Attorney General","2017-06-21","To ask the Attorney General, what the cost is of (a) running and (b) administering the Serious Fraud Office online reporting tool.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 48","48"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731176","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much debt, including interest, remains outstanding under confiscation orders obtained where HM Courts and Tribunals Service has the lead enforcement role; and what recent estimate he has made of how much of that debt is recoverable.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 49","49"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731177","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners are serving public protection sentences at HM Prison Hull.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 50","50"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731178","2017-06-26","Attorney General","2017-06-21","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the Answer of 20 April 2017 to Question 70644, on confiscation orders, how much has been collected as a result of confiscation orders obtained by the Crown Prosecution Service in the 2016-17 financial year.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 295","295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731179","2017-06-26","Attorney General","2017-06-21","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the Answer of 20 April 2017 to Question 70644, on confiscation orders, what the outstanding debt is by Crown Prosecution Service Area.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 296","296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731180","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when the next stage of public consultation for Crossrail 2 is planned to take place.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 205","205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731181","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the Government's plans are for implementing Crossrail 2.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 206","206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731182","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of matching basic benefit levels to the Minimum Income Standards calculated annually by the Joseph Rowntree Foundation.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 207","207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731183","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to ensure that the UK Olympic team is referred to as Team UK rather than Team GB.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 229","229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731184","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to publish her response to her Department's consultation on the Leveson Inquiry and its implementation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 230","230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731185","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate the Government has made of the average cost per flat of retrofitting sprinkler systems for fire safety in tower blocks.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 381","381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731186","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what plans she has to repeal section 40 of the Crime and Courts Act 2013.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 432","432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731187","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many applications for partner visas for which the additional fee for fast track service has been paid are affected by the suspension on processing applications as a result of the legal challenge to the Government's minimum-income requirement.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 526","526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731188","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will ensure that information provided by survivors of Grenfell Tower about residency or immigration status will not be used for criminal investigation or affect rehousing rights.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 382","382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731189","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an estimate of the potential cost to extend entitlement to free travel passes to women born in the 1950s who have yet to reach state pension age.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 384","384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731190","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when the review of fire regulations and safety in tower blocks following the fire at Lakanal House in Lambeth began; who has been consulted in that review; and whether the review was delayed or postponed after it began.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 451","451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731191","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will ensure content creators are paid for the content they make available online.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 416","416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731192","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to publish her response to the consultation on Commercial Radio Deregulation which closed in May 2017; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 417","417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731193","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, when she plans to introduce the new cultural development fund to use cultural investment to turn around communities; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 418","418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731194","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with (a) the Secretary of State for International Development and (b) the Government of Iran on support for people with disabilities in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 503","503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731195","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the (a) Government of Israel and (b) Government of Lebanon on disputed mineral-rich areas of the eastern Mediterranean.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 504","504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731196","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with representatives of the Falkland Islands Government on that Government's role in discussions on the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 505","505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731197","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps her Department is taking to (a) monitor and (b) control increases in levels of (i) extremism and (ii) radicalised Islam in Birmingham.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 506","506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731198","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions the Government has had with the Governments of (a) Japan and (b) South Korea on recent missile launches conducted by North Korea.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 507","507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731199","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he has made representations to the Democratic Unionist Party leader, Arlene Foster on the extension of (a) civil partnerships and (b) same-sex marriage in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 508","508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731200","2017-06-26","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate she has made of the trends in the entrance fees charged for temporary exhibitions at national museums in England in the last five years.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 409","409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731201","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans to extend the period of the ring fence on the public health grant until plans to fund local authorities through 100 per cent business rates retention are implemented after 2020.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 551","551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731202","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 34 of the Government's Litter Strategy for England published in April 2017, whether the timeline for his Department's Working Group on Voluntary and Economic Incentives Reduce Litter to consider the advantages and disadvantages of different types of deposit and reward and return schemes for drinks containers, and to produce advice by the end of 2017, still stands.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 292","292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731203","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 34 of the Government's Litter Strategy for England published in April 2017, if he will provide regular updates to Parliament on the progress of discussions of his Department's Working Group on Voluntary and Economic Incentives to Reduce Litter considering the advantages and disadvantages of different types of deposit and reward and return schemes for drinks containers.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 293","293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731204","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, with reference to page 79 of the Government's Litter Strategy for England published in April 2017, if he will publish the membership  of his Department's Working Group on Voluntary and Economic Incentives Reduce Litter.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 294","294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731205","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with the Department of Communities and Local Government on the future administration of the public health grant.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 266","266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731206","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to increase capacity at medical schools to meet demand from applicants with high level qualifications.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 315","315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731207","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people have been diagnosed with chronic obstructive pulmonary disease in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 316","316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731208","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the timetable is for the roll-out of keyhole surgery for brain cancer patients on the NHS.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 317","317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731209","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to monitor and control the spread of Lyme disease by dog walkers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 318","318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731210","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to monitor and control kite-fighting contests.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 319","319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731211","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of having 27 separate supervisory bodies responsible for guarding against money laundering.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 321","321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731212","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the Democratic Unionist Party leader, Arlene Foster, on the land border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 322","322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731213","2017-06-26","Women and Equalities","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she had made representations to the Prime Minister on women's rights in Northern Ireland prior to the Prime Minister meeting with Democratic Unionist Party leader, Arlene Foster, on 13 June.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 323","323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731214","2017-06-26","Women and Equalities","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, whether she had made representations to the Prime Minister on LGBT rights in Northern Ireland prior to the Prime Minister meeting with Democratic Unionist Party leader, Arlene Foster, on 13 June.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 324","324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731215","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to hold discussions with representative organisations in public health on the mandated public health duties of local authorities in light of the Government's plan to devolve the public health grant.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 267","267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731216","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans he has to hold discussions with representative organisations in sexual health, drugs and alcohol services on the mandated public health duties of local authorities in light of the Government's plan to devolve the public health grant.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 268","268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731217","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans to lift the suspension on the processing of certain applications for partner visas that was introduced as a result of the legal challenge to the minimum income requirement.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 299","299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731218","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when his Department plans to publish the updated Tobacco Control Plan; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 269","269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731219","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many partner visa applications are affected by the suspension of processing applications as a result of the legal challenge to the Government's minimum income requirement.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 300","300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731220","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions his Department has had with the Hungarian Government on (a) refugee movements and (b) economic development in that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 270","270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731221","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with governments in the Middle East to encourage a better understanding of human rights provision relating to inter-faith marriages.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 271","271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731222","2017-06-26","Ministry of Defence","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what discussions he has had with the Government of the Falkland Islands on support for mine-clearing operations; and what the timetable is for all mine-fields in the Falkland Islands to be cleared.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 272","272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731223","2017-06-26","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to develop the fishery sector in the Falkland Islands in line with similar developments in the UK fishing sector.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 273","273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731224","2017-06-26","Home Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the Government plans for Unexplained Wealth Orders to come into operation.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 243","243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731225","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of regulations for small diesel power plants.","Biography information for Mr Ranil Jayawardena","Mr Ranil Jayawardena","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 200","200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731226","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether a timetable has been agreed for achieving the objectives of the Global Forum for Asset Recovery.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 199","199"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731227","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what estimate he has made of the number of treaties requiring renegotiation as a result of the UK's exit from the EU.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 250","250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731228","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of carrying out human rights impact assessments for each stage of the passage of a Bill.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 251","251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731229","2017-06-26","Attorney General","2017-06-21","To ask the Attorney General, with reference to the Serious Fraud Office's news release of 20 June 2017, SFO charges in Barclays Qatar capital raising case, whether he has re-assessed the merits of maintaining the Serious Fraud Office as a separate office.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 252","252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731230","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic and other support the Government has given to the Egyptian Government as a result of recent attacks on Christian churches in the country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 372","372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731231","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the then Prime Minister's speech on Life Chances on 11 January 2016, when the Government expects to implement the significant expansion in parenting programmes.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 201","201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731232","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent diplomatic and other support the Government has given to the Lebanese Government to assist it with the influx of refugees into that country.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 373","373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731233","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Lebanon on the planned demolition of historical buildings of international significance in Beirut.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 374","374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731234","2017-06-26","Department for Transport","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to respond to Transport for London's Strategic Outline Business Case for Crossrail 2.","Biography information for Stephen Hammond","Stephen Hammond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 204","204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731235","2017-06-26","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with the Israeli Government on encouraging more Palestinians to seek Israeli citizenship.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 375","375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731236","2017-06-26","HM Treasury","2017-06-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when the Government plans to bring forward legislative proposals on the breathing space mechanism for families in debt.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 121","121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731237","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to improve the (a) quality of attachment between parents and children aged under five, (b) home learning environments for children aged under five and (c) mental health of new and expectant mothers in low-income households.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 122","122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731238","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the protection and promotion of LGBT rights was discussed at recent meetings with the leadership of the Democratic Unionist Party.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 163","163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731239","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the protection and promotion of women's rights was discussed at recent meetings with the leadership of the Democratic Unionist Party.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 164","164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731240","2017-06-26","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the announcement made by his Department on 27 March 2017 on new guidance to support working mothers of premature babies, what progress has been made on drawing up of such guidance; and whether it is still the Government's policy to publish guidance for employers.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 165","165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731241","2017-06-26","Department of Health","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress has been made on the rollout of a new contract to dental care providers.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 167","167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731242","2017-06-26","Prime Minister","2017-06-21","To ask the Prime Minister, whether she plans to discuss the land border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland when she meets Taoiseach Leo Varadkar.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 143","143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731243","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to publish its Anti-Corruption Strategy.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 144","144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731244","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to review progress on the commitments made at the 2016 International Anti-Corruption Summit; and what the timetable is for further reviews of that progress.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 145","145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731245","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans to publish the consultation on the future of Sure Start children's centres.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 147","147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731246","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when the Government plans to publish the Anti-Corruption Strategy.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 149","149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731247","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, when he plans to appoint an anti-corruption champion.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 150","150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731248","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, whether it remains the position of the Government that the UK should withdraw from both the customs union and the single market.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 133","133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731249","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to publish the results of the call for evidence on corporate criminal liability for economic crime.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 151","151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731250","2017-06-26","Department for Work and Pensions","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what indicators his Department plans to use to measure the quality of assessment reports produced by personal independence payment assessment suppliers.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 123","123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731251","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many employment and training staff were employed by the Community Rehabilitation Company in (a) Wales and (b) Bristol, Gloucestershire, Somerset and Wiltshire Community Rehabilitation Company at the latest date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 125","125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731252","2017-06-26","Cabinet Office","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in Linlithgow and East Falkirk constituency are employed on zero-hours contracts; how many of those people are (a) aged between 16 and 24-years old and (b) women.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 152","152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731253","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of the Criminal Injuries Compensation Scheme's policy on consent to sexual assault on victims who are under 16 years of age and do not qualify for compensation.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 126","126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731254","2017-06-26","Department for Communities and Local Government","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of placing a requirement on councils to have emergency plans in place for rehousing and compensating residents in the event of a disaster.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 127","127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731255","2017-06-26","Department for Education","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it remains the Government's policy to allow the opening of new grammar schools.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 128","128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731256","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many offenders were seen each week by employment and training staff in the Community Rehabilitation Company in Wales in the last period for which figures are available; and what payment that company received for each person seen.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 129","129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731257","2017-06-26","Ministry of Justice","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many restraining orders were issued by courts in England and Wales during 2015; and of those orders how many prohibited online contact via any social media platform.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 130","130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731258","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, how many staff are employed by his Department.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 134","134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731259","2017-06-26","Department for Exiting the European Union","2017-06-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what assessment he has made of the effect of withdrawing from the Customs Union on the land border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 131","131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/731260","2017-06-26","Women and Equalities","2017-06-21","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, what recent discussions she has had with (a) the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland and (b) Members of Northern Ireland Executive on the protection and promotion of women's rights in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 135","135"
