"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389936","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on (a) Belfast City and (b) Belfast International Airport of a new runway at (i) Heathrow and (ii) Gatwick Airport.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6998","6998"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389937","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many buried bodies have been moved in each of the last five years from their lawful place of burial to facilitate development of highway work; and what processes highways contractors must follow to move bodies for that purpose.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7043","7043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389938","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had on the establishment of Transport for the North with transport unions.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6994","6994"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389939","2015-07-21","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, for what reason one lane of the three lane carriageway on the A41 southbound near Hendon is coned off; and for what reasons the work at that location is not being carried out on a 24-hour basis.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7042","7042"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389940","2015-07-20","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 14 July 2015 to Question 6453 and to the contribution of the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State in his Department, the hon. Member for Devizes, on 8 July 2015, Official Report, column 107WH, on which date the Chief Executive of Network Rail gave a presentation to his Department's Board.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7018","7018"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389941","2015-07-20","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 5807, what the cost-benefit ratio was for the overall Midland Main Line upgrade package, including electrification and other works, on the most recent date for which figures are available; and what the cost-benefit ratio for TransPennine electrification referred to in that Answer was on the most recent date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7026","7026"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389942","2015-07-20","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the total VAT payable or received by the Government from the Severn Bridges' tolls has been to date.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7027","7027"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389943","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations he has received from business groups in Sussex on increasing the range of destinations available from Gatwick Airport (a) in North America and (b) in the rest of the world; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7056","7056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389944","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on (a) deregulation, (b) liberalisation and (c) other reform of the global airline industry.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7101","7101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389945","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department had with representatives from the International Civil Aviation Organisation on a multilateral agreement to reform global airline regulation; and what the outcome of those discussions was.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7102","7102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389946","2015-07-20","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 5776, whether the routes covered by the existing Southern and Gatwick Express franchise, which will be migrating into Govia Thameslink Railway franchise on 26 July 2015, will also be obliged to introduce carnet-based season tickets based on ITSO certified smartmedia on or before 30 September 2015.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7106","7106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389947","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent discussions his Department has had with representatives from other UN member states on a multilateral agreement to reform global airline regulation; and what the outcome of those discussions was.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7103","7103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389948","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the likely effect of the proposed works to the Elstree Tunnels on commuter rail services.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7068","7068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389949","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that transport connections to Gatwick Airport remain fit for purpose; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7053","7053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389950","2015-07-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department can take if there is a breach of the conditions set out in the his approval of the Radlett Rail Freight Terminal.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7069","7069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389951","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the rate of growth of air traffic at Gatwick Airport in the next 10 years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7054","7054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389952","2015-07-16","HM Treasury","2015-07-14","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have accessed the Pension Wise service in each week since the inception of that service.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6990","6990"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389953","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the compliance with health and safety legislation of safety-critical maintenance work on offshore oil and gas installations in the North Sea.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6937","6937"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389954","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 6306, what the reasons are for his decision not to publish his Department's guidance on answering parliamentary questions.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7037","7037"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389955","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on the circumstances in which a young person aged under 21 will be entitled to support in future with housing costs.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7032","7032"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389956","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when a claimant who has received a loan for mortgage interest will be expected to commence repayment of that loan.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7033","7033"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389957","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reason the Government proposes in Clause 1 of the Welfare Reform and Work Bill that the full employment reporting obligation will be repealed at the dissolution of the present Parliament.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7034","7034"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389958","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make an assessment of the availability of doctor's appointments for employment and support allowance assessments in (a) the UK, (b) Wales and (c) Caerphilly County Borough area.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7160","7160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389959","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of Jobcentre Plus programmes in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7161","7161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389960","2015-07-20","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2015 to Question 3935, what assessment he has made of the compliance of his Department's practice in providing statistics in answers to parliamentary questions with paragraphs 7.37 and 7.38 of the Guide to Parliamentary Work issued by the Leader of the House in May 2010.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 7111","7111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391190","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her policy is on the refund of VAT costs to sixth form colleges.","Biography information for Jason McCartney","Jason McCartney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901107","901107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391191","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what her plans are for future funding of education and training for 16 to 19 year olds.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901105","901105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391192","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure high standards of teaching in maths and physics.","Biography information for Mark Menzies","Mark Menzies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901106","901106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391193","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to support recruitment and retention of high quality teachers.","Biography information for Wendy Morton","Wendy Morton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901103","901103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/391194","2015-07-20","Department for Education","2015-07-14","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to improve the provision of technical education.","Biography information for Steve Rotheram","Steve Rotheram","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901110","901110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389210","2015-07-16","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to review responsibilities within pay bands in the NHS; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Liz McInnes","Liz McInnes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6816","6816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389211","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will instigate an independent review of the performance of the Prevent strategy.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6772","6772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389212","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2015 to Question 5856, what the additional costs attached to the enforcement of the new legislation are expected to be.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6773","6773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389213","2015-07-16","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what plans she has to increase the number of counter-terrorism officers stationed abroad.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6875","6875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389214","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2015 to Question 3680, if she will ask the National Crime Agency to estimate the number of women who pose a potential risk of being a child abuser or of seeking out child sex images online.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6864","6864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389215","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to meet the recommendations set out in the UK report by the UN Special Rapporteur on Violence against Women.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6869","6869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389216","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2015 to Question 3489, on immigration: Olympic Games 2012, what the immigration status is of the 30 people who made a claim for asylum which has not been granted; and what enforcement action has been taken in each such case.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6885","6885"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389217","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2015 to Question 3770, if she will take steps to ensure that the DNA profiles of prisoners who have been imprisoned since before DNA profiles were taken on arrest are on the DNA database.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6878","6878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389218","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2015 to Question 3767, what estimate she has made of the likely time it will take enforcement action against the remaining individuals who have been identified as having participated in English language test fraud; and what estimate she has made of the number of removals that will result from such action.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6879","6879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389219","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 29 June 2015 to Question 3767, if she will name the 94 privately-operated further education colleges whose licences were suspended at the same point in quarter one of 2015 over English language testing irregularities; and for which such colleges the licence (a) was surrendered, (b) was revoked, (c) was reinstated and (d) remains suspended.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6880","6880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389220","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police community support officers were working in police forces in (a) Bristol, (b) Avon and Somerset and (c) England and Wales in (i) 2010 and (ii) according to the most recently available figures.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6723","6723"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389221","2015-07-16","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what progress the College of Policing has made on the development of training and investigative guidelines for the police on the new law of coercive control in a domestic setting.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6788","6788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389222","2015-07-16","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans for the powers to make coercive control in a domestic setting contained in the Serious Crime Act 2015 to come into effect.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6792","6792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389223","2015-07-16","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which police services in England and Wales have developed their own in-house training on coercive control in a domestic setting; and how she expects the effectiveness of such training to be measured.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6791","6791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389224","2015-07-16","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police officers in each police area have been trained on the new law of coercive control in a domestic setting to date.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6790","6790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389225","2015-07-16","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how she expects the effectiveness of any training on coercive control in a domestic setting to be monitored.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6789","6789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389226","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions have taken place between her Department and relevant authorities in the Republic of Ireland on co-operation with the National Crime Agency's investigation into allegations made in the Irish Parliament on the sale of properties in Northern Ireland owned by the National Asset Management Agency.","Biography information for Tom Elliott","Tom Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6564","6564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389227","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if she will make it her policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for her Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6665","6665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389228","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, in what circumstances a person liable to be arrested for deportation is notified in advance that they will be arrested.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6586","6586"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389229","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, which search organisations are in receipt of Prevent strategy funding; and how much such funding each such organisation is due to receive in 2015-16.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6618","6618"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389230","2015-07-15","Home Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many prosecutions have taken place as a result of English language test fraud in the last five years; and with what offences those prosecuted were charged with having committed.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6611","6611"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389231","2015-07-15","Department for International Development","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if she will make it her policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for her Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6666","6666"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389232","2015-07-15","Department for International Development","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, whether the Government has provided aid to the government of Colombia.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6593","6593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389233","2015-07-16","Department for International Development","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what her policy is on providing additional funds to the Regional Refugee Response Plan for the situation in Burundi.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6798","6798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389234","2015-07-21","Department for International Development","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what resources her Department plans to allocate to Yemen over the next six months in response to the UN Office for the Co-ordination of Humanitarian Affairs' level 3 emergency appeal.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6890","6890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389235","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what rules apply to membership of Magistrates' Courts' Benches by discharged bankrupts.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6787","6787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389236","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the effect on claims for compensation by prisoners of the coming into force of the Human Rights Act 1998.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6884","6884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389237","2015-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many fines have been (a) issued by courts and (b) collected in 2014-15 to date.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6817","6817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389238","2015-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department plans to take to increase the take-up of mediation for family disputes.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6861","6861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389239","2015-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to encourage the judiciary to make greater use of its existing powers in family procedure rules to refer people to family mediation at any stage in proceedings.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6853","6853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389240","2015-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the performance of the scheme which allows both parties in a family dispute to receive one free mediation session where just one party qualifies for legal aid.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6852","6852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389241","2015-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what his policy is on retaining legal aid for family mediation.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6851","6851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389242","2015-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many incidents of each type were recorded on the Incident Reporting System in (a) privately and (b) publicly run prisons in each month since 1 January 2014.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6820","6820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389243","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for theft was for an individual convicted of a further theft offence in the last 10 years; and what the sentence was for the most such recent offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6748","6748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389244","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for violence against the person offences was for an individual convicted of a further violence against the person offence in the last 10 years; and what the sentence was for the most such recent offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6749","6749"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389245","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for sexual offences involving a child was for an individual convicted of a further sexual offence involving a child in the last 10 years; and what the sentence was for the most recent such offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6750","6750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389246","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will take steps to improve faith and cultural training for coroners to assist in the (a) timely dealing with deaths, (b) type of post mortem used and (c) process for the release of the body for burial for those from minority faith groups.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6640","6640"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389247","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of offenders were sentenced to life imprisonment for the offence of rape in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6635","6635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389248","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2015 to Question 3782, in which prisons each of the (a) illegal items and (b) other items were found in each package that contained illegal items; and what each of those items were.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6636","6636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389249","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for robbery was for an individual convicted of a further offence of robbery in the last 10 years; and what the sentence was for the most recent offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6747","6747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389250","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to introduce a victims' right to review decisions taken by the police not to prosecute in accordance with Article 11 of Directive 2012/29/EU.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6762","6762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389251","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for rape was for an individual convicted of a further offence of rape in the last 10 years; and what the sentence was for the most recent offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6745","6745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389252","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for knife offences was for an individual convicted of a further knife offence in the last 10 years; and what the sentence was for the most recent offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6746","6746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389253","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to introduce victim awareness training for lawyers in accordance with Article 25 of Directive 2012/29/EU.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6763","6763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389254","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of the provision in the Children and Families Act 2014 making it compulsory for families to attend a mediation information and assessment meeting before being able to apply for a court order.","Biography information for Mr Ben Bradshaw","Mr Ben Bradshaw","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6822","6822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389255","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2015 to Question 3652, what was the (a) maximum and (b) average period of time for which offenders were released over the Christmas period.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6755","6755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389256","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure compliance with Directive 2012/29/EU on ensuring minimum rights for victims by 16 November 2015.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6761","6761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389257","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2015 to Question 3652, what the criteria are for eligibility for release from prison for Christmas.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6756","6756"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389258","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2015 to Question 3642, how many people were placed on life licence for murder in each year since 2007.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6754","6754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389259","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of existing victim support services to assess whether the UK will comply with Directive 2012/29/EU ensuring minimum rights for victims by 16 November 2015; and if he will publish the results of that assessment.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6764","6764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389260","2015-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, which barristers are employed by the Public Defence Service; and what day rates each such person charges.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6819","6819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389261","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many young offenders in custody (a) committed suicide and (b) self-harmed in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6765","6765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389262","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2015 to Question 4022, in how many of the cases in the table provided had the victim or the victim's family had an input into the decision to either move the offender to an open prison or to release them.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6752","6752"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389263","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2015 to Question 4022, how many of the cases in the negative outcomes category related to (a) transfer to an open prison and (b) release from prison.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6751","6751"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389264","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2015 to Question 3652, how many of the offenders released for Christmas were (a) male and (b) female.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6757","6757"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389265","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 30 June 2015 to Question 3497, for what reason his Department was able to provide this information on 29 August 2013, Official Report, column 1034W, in relation to earlier years but is now unable to do so.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6753","6753"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389266","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 1 July 2015 to Question 3652, which offences had been committed by each offender; what length of sentence was being served by each offender; and from which prisons was each such offender released over the Christmas period.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6758","6758"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389267","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if his will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6667","6667"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389268","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the effect on criminal court proceedings in North Wales has been of the withdrawal of legal services by legal aid solicitors in that region.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6589","6589"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389269","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many (a) fast and (b) part delivery pre-sentence reports were prepared in the latest year for which information is available for offenders with (i) no, (ii) one to 14, (iii) 15 to 49, (iv) 50 to 99 and (v) 100 or more previous convictions.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6584","6584"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389270","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to ensure the safety of court and security staff following the attack on a custody officer at Blackfriars Crown Court on 29 June 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6585","6585"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389271","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to help families protect a missing person's financial and legal affairs.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6577","6577"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389272","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people given a life sentence for a sexual offence involving a child who were released in the last 10 years have subsequently committed a further such offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6630","6630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389273","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will list all the possible requirements that can be attached to a community order or a suspended sentence order by sentencers (a) in all courts and (b) in certain courts as part of a trial or pilot scheme.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6609","6609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389274","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for burglary was for an individual convicted of a further burglary offence; and what the sentence was for the most recent offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6633","6633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389275","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the highest number of previous convictions for sexual offences was for an individual convicted of a further such offence; and what the sentence was for the most recent offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6634","6634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389276","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people given a life sentence for a homicide offence who were released in the last 10 years have subsequently committed a further such offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6631","6631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389277","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people given a life sentence for a violence against the person  offence who were released in the last 10 years have subsequently committed a further such offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6632","6632"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389278","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much compensation has been paid to prisoners in each of the last five years; for what reason the compensation was paid; and how many and what proportion of such cases were (a) settled and (b) ordered in court.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6612","6612"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389279","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the use of collaborative technology in criminal court proceedings.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6613","6613"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389280","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, in what circumstances the criminal courts charge can be deemed to have been paid as a result of time spent in custody at the time of the imposition of the charge.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6614","6614"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389281","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what recent representations he has received on the effect of the criminal courts charge.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6615","6615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389282","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners in HMP Springhill were Muslim on 16 May 2015.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6616","6616"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389283","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prisoners currently in open prisons have previously (a) absconded or failed to return to prison and (b) breached the conditions of their temporary licence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6617","6617"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389284","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people given a life sentence for rape who were released in the last 10 years have subsequently committed a further such offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6628","6628"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389285","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people given a life sentence for burglary who were released in the last 10 years have subsequently committed a further such offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6629","6629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389286","2015-07-16","Attorney General","2015-07-13","To ask the Attorney General, what recent estimate he has made of the trend in prosecutions relating to domestic abuse involving (a) female and (b) male victims.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6678","6678"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389287","2015-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for changes in the number of convictions for shoplifting food in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6600","6600"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389288","2015-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many full-time equivalent staff have been employed in HM Courts and Tribunals Service to deliver fine and compensation enforcement orders in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6684","6684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389289","2015-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how much his Department plans to spend on the Compliance and Enforcement Service project in the next year.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6685","6685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389290","2015-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, whether the successful bidder for the Compliance and Enforcement Service contract will have access to personal data held on defaulters by HM Revenue and Customs and |the Department for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6686","6686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389291","2015-07-16","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what the collection rates for (a) fines, (b) penalties and (c) confiscation orders have been in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6687","6687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389292","2015-07-16","Leader of the House","2015-07-13","To ask the Leader of the House, what discussions he has had with the National Assembly of Wales and the Welsh Government on English votes on English laws.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6603","6603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389293","2015-07-16","Leader of the House","2015-07-13","To ask the Leader of the House, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Wales on English votes on English laws; and on what dates such discussions took place.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6604","6604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389294","2015-07-15","Northern Ireland Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if she will make it her policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for her Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6668","6668"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389295","2015-07-15","Northern Ireland Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what her policy is on the prosecution of people who assist people in terminating a pregnancy.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6637","6637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389296","2015-07-15","Scotland Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what meetings his Department has had with (a) the Scottish Trades Union Congress and (b) individual affiliated trades unions in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6718","6718"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389297","2015-07-16","Scotland Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2015 to Question 5448 and to the contribution of the Leader of the House of 2 July 2015, Official Report, column 1644, what independent assessments the Government has taken into account when assessing whether the Scotland Bill will deliver the Smith Commission agreement in full.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6850","6850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389298","2015-07-16","Scotland Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of measures in the Summer Budget 2015 on the economy in Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6799","6799"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389299","2015-07-16","Scotland Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, what discussions he has had with the Chancellor of the Exchequer on the potential effects of measures in the Summer Budget 2015 on the economy in Scotland.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6800","6800"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389300","2015-07-15","Scotland Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Scotland, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6669","6669"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389301","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6670","6670"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389302","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the contribution of 14 January 1994 by the then Minister for Public Transport, Official Report, column 432, on Channel Tunnel Rail Link (Compensation), what conclusion the Government drew from its consideration of legal advice commissioned by local authorities.","Biography information for Stephen Phillips","Stephen Phillips","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6595","6595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389303","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has made an assessment of the potential effect of Crossrail development on existing retailers and traders in Tin Pan Alley, Denmark Street.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6591","6591"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389304","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what contract penalties will have to be paid as a result of the pause in the planned Manchester to Leeds electrification project.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6675","6675"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389305","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Department of Culture, Media and Sport on the proposed Electronic Communications Code.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6692","6692"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389306","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will estimate the number of apprenticeships that would have been created in (a) 2015, (b) 2016, (c) 2017, (d) 2018 and (e) 2019 if the planned Manchester to Leeds electrification had gone ahead.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6676","6676"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389307","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will publish his Department's assessment of the economic cost to Greater Manchester arising from the pause in the Manchester to Leeds electrification project in each year to 2019.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6677","6677"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389308","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the effect on the total cost of the electrification of the Manchester to Leeds line will be of a delay in the starting of the project of (a) six months, (b) 12 months, (c) two years and (d) three years.","Biography information for Lucy Powell","Lucy Powell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6674","6674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389309","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect of the (a) Mode Shift Revenue Support and (b) Waterborne Freight Grant schemes on modal shift of freight from road to rail and water since 2009-10.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6680","6680"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389310","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that any train station that has been the location of more than one serious suicide attempt in the last five years has a barrier installed.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6652","6652"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389311","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his policy is on changing the (a) frequency and (b) volume of freight moved by rail between Felixstowe and Tilbury ports.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6653","6653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389312","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether access for disabled people at Diss and Stowmarket stations will be a condition of the new franchise contract for the Eastern Main Line.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6625","6625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389313","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to the Answer of 26 March 2015 to Question 228876, whether he has at any point (a) requested a copy of Network Rail's list of projects that could be stopped or refused due to capital funding constraints and (b) otherwise had sight of such a list.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6793","6793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389314","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraph 1.256 of the Summer Budget 2015, HC 264, what resources his Department plans to make available to Nicola Shaw during her investigation into the future shape and financing of Network Rail; how many of his Department's officials will work on that inquiry; whether a report summarising that work will be published; and if he will publish the terms of reference for that inquiry.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6794","6794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389315","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what salaries or other financial incentives will be paid to (a) Peter Hendy, (b) Colette Bowe and (c) Nicola Shaw for their inquiries into Network Rail.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6797","6797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389316","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to paragraphs 1.255 and 2.193 of the Summer Budget 2015, HC 264, whether he plans for his Department to be the parent department of the new rail land and property body; when he plans to publish the remit of that body; and whether he plans for that body to have ownership over, or responsibility for, determining the ownership of (a) the Old Dalby Test Track and (b) the Railway Technical Centre Business Park, Derby.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6795","6795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389317","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2015 to Question 5102, what funding his Department plans to make available to promote the construction of charging points for electric cars over the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6809","6809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389318","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the number of flights from Leeds-Bradford Airport of the expansion of (a) Heathrow, (b) Gatwick and (c) neither airport.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6642","6642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389319","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to increase the provision of public transport in (a) Bradford and (b) Yorkshire and the Humber.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6641","6641"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389320","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of road and rail access to regional airports; and which airports he rates as inadequate in this respect.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6770","6770"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389321","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what representations his Department received from Network Rail between July 2014 and 7 May 2015 on the potential deferral or pausing of major rail enhancement projects.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6796","6796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389322","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 6 July 2015 to Question 5101, what representations his Department has received from automotive manufacturers on the future rollout of autonomous vehicles on UK roads.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6810","6810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389323","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his oral statement of 25 June 2015, Official Report, columns 1067-8, whether Network Rail will be liable to incur fines or other penalties in respect of (a) changes to the projects Network Rail is expected to deliver in Control Period 5 compared to the 2012 High Level Output specification and (b) variations to the Regulated Outputs Network Rail was committed to meeting relating to Midland Main Line electrification and TransPennine electrification as a result of the changes announced in that statement.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6893","6893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389324","2015-07-15","Wales Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6672","6672"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389325","2015-07-15","Women and Equalities","2015-07-13","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if she will make it her policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for the Government Equalities Office from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6663","6663"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389326","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of progress on increasing equality of access to employment opportunities for people from Black and minority ethnic communities.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6785","6785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389327","2015-07-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, in how many and what proportion of families supported by the Troubled Families Programme have unemployed family members entered employment.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6813","6813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389328","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 7 July 2015 to Question 5455, on universal credit, where the trial which began on 20 April 2015 is taking place; how many claimants are involved in that trial; how long that trial is expected to last; and what forms of support are being provided under that trial.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6814","6814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389329","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of children living in households in (a) Bristol South constituency, (b) Bristol and (c) England and Wales that will be affected by a reduction of the benefit cap to 20,000.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6882","6882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389330","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance he has given to staff working for his Department on dealing with claimants with chronic, incurable diseases.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6596","6596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389331","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6673","6673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389332","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will make it his policy to ensure that people with incurable, chronic conditions do not undertake repeated fit-for-work assessments.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6597","6597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389333","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance he has given to staff working for, or contracted by, his Department on dealing with people who have a history of suicide attempts; and if he will place a copy of such guidance in the Library.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6598","6598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389334","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of how many claimants will be affected by the changes to employment and support allowance announced in the Summer Budget 2015 in (a) Wakefield constituency, (b) Wakefield Metropolitan District Council area and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6578","6578"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389335","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants there were in the employment and support allowance work related activity group in (a) Wakefield constituency, (b) Wakefield Metropolitan District Council area and (c) the UK in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6579","6579"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389336","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the contribution by the Prime Minister of 24 June 2015, Official Report, column 886, when the data on public spending referred to in that contribution will be published.","Biography information for Helen Goodman","Helen Goodman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6682","6682"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389337","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households in (a) England, (b) Scotland, (c) Wales, (d) Greater London, (e) the London Borough of Islington and (f) Islington South and Finsbury constituency, which are not currently subject to the benefit cap, will be subject to caps at the levels proposed in the Welfare Reform and Work Bill.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6707","6707"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389338","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, for what reasons he has set the benefit cap at the levels stated in Clause 7(2) of the Welfare Reform and Work Bill.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6709","6709"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389340","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to the draft Welfare Reform and Work Bill, for what reasons the Welfare Reform and Work Bill proposes to repeal section 96(6) to (8) of the Welfare Reform Act 2012 on the link between the benefit cap and average earnings.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6710","6710"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389341","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the support component of employment and support allowance is excluded from calculations of a household's income for the purposes of the benefit cap under the provisions proposed in the Welfare Reform and Work Bill.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6708","6708"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389343","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of changes to tax credits on the poorest families.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6649","6649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389345","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how his Department will monitor the effect of the changes to tax credits on the poorest (a) in-work and (b) out-of-work families.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6650","6650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389346","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the measures in Budget Statement 2015 on levels of child poverty in (a) in-work and (b) out-of-work families.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6651","6651"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389362","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many households will be affected (a) in London by a household benefit cap of 23,000 per year and (b) in each other country and region by a household benefit cap of 20,000 per year.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6688","6688"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389364","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of people in receipt of carers allowance do not live with the person they are caring for.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6689","6689"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389365","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what his policy is on the interest and repayment requirements for loans under the Support for Mortgage Interest scheme; in what circumstances such loans will be payable; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6690","6690"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389367","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect on people waiting for an employment and support allowance assessment of the transition of supplier from Atos to Maximus in (a) the UK, (b) Wales and (c) Caerphilly County Borough.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6823","6823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389369","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much the Government spent on legal fees in the case of Mathieson v Secretary of State for Work and Pensions.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6818","6818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389371","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate his Department has made of the average annual change in the income of households which are (a) subject and (b) not subject to the benefit cap as a result of lowering the benefits cap to the levels proposed in the Welfare Reform and Work Bill in (i) England, (ii) Scotland, (iii) Wales, (iv) Greater London, (v) the London Borough of Islington and (vi) Islington South and Finsbury constituency in each of the next three years.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6703","6703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389372","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether it is his policy that existing exemptions for (a) disability living allowance, (b) personal independence payments, (c) discretionary housing payments, (d) working tax credit and (e) other benefits that have been specified in regulations under the Welfare Reform Act 2012 will continue to be disregarded from a household's income under the proposed new framework for the benefit cap.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6704","6704"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389373","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions he has had with (a) his ministerial colleagues and (b) officials in the Department for Communities and Local Government on the effect of the Welfare Reform and Work Bill on social landlords' ability to finance construction of new homes for social rent.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6711","6711"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389374","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether housing benefit paid to claimants living in supported exempt accommodation will be excluded from calculations of a household's income for the benefit cap under the provisions proposed in the Welfare Reform and Work Bill.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6702","6702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389375","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when everyone currently registered for receipt of state benefits in (a) Bristol South constituency and (b) England will have been fully transferred to universal credit.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6729","6729"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389376","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the timescale is for the introduction of universal credit to jobcentres in Bristol South constituency.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6730","6730"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389377","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to section 96A(3)(a) of the Welfare Reform Act 2012 which it is proposed will be inserted by Clause 8 of the Welfare Reform and Work Bill, how he plans to define the national economic situation.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6705","6705"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389378","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people aged 18 to 21 in Bristol South constituency are in receipt of local housing allowance.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6727","6727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389379","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Bristol South constituency have waited longer than six months for the final outcome of their personal independent payment application.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6728","6728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389380","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to section 96A(3)(b) of the Welfare Reform Act 2012 which it is proposed will be inserted by Clause 8 of the Welfare Reform and Work Bill, how he plans to identify the matters which are relevant to setting the level of the benefit cap.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6706","6706"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389382","2015-07-16","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance is provided for staff (a) working for and (b) contracted by his Department on dealing with clients who are or may be suicidal; and if he will place a copy of such guidance in the Library.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6804","6804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389385","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of jobseeker's allowance claims took (a) 10 days or fewer, (b) between 11 and 16 days inclusive and (c) over 16 days to process in (i) Nottingham North constituency, (ii) Nottingham local authority area and (iii) Great Britain in each financial year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Graham Allen","Mr Graham Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6767","6767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389387","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley and (c) South Yorkshire have claimed the enhanced disability premium component of employment support allowance in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6848","6848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389388","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people were enrolled on the Work Programme in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley and (c) South Yorkshire in each of the last five years; and how many such people found employment through that Programme.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6847","6847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389389","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment has been made of the adequacy of employment and support allowance assessment waiting times in Wales.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6824","6824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389390","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the number of outstanding employment and support allowance assessments in (a) the UK, (b) Wales and (c) Caerphilly County Borough.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6825","6825"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389393","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the number of priority employment and support allowance cases in (a) the UK, (b) Wales and (c) Caerphilly County Borough.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6826","6826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389394","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the contribution of the 24 June 2015, Official Report, columns 885-86, when his Department will publish statistics on the deaths of people declared fit for work since May 2010.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6821","6821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389395","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of progress in clearing the backlog of employment and support allowance assessments in (a) the UK, (b) Wales and (c) Caerphilly County Borough.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6827","6827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389396","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who gained employment through Jobcentre Plus between 2005 and 2015 were again unemployed after (a) eight months and (b) a year.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6828","6828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389398","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what targets his Department has set for Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6832","6832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389400","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average appointment length is for jobseekers at a Jobcentre Plus.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6833","6833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389402","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what average length of time was taken by jobseekers between their first appointment at a Jobcentre Plus and entry into employment between 2005 and 2015.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6829","6829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389404","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average length of employment gained through Jobcentre Plus was between 2005 and 2015.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6830","6830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389405","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the annual budget was for Jobcentre Plus between 2005 and 2015.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6831","6831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389407","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the annual cost of (a) youth unemployment and (b) long-term unemployment to the public purse.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6834","6834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389408","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the impact assessment for the Welfare Reform and Work Bill will be published.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6647","6647"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389410","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what proportion of Jobcentre Plus offices have met his Department's targets in the last six months.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6835","6835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389412","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley and (c) South Yorkshire were in receipt of housing benefit in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6842","6842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389413","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when he expects universal credit to be fully rolled out to claimants in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley and (c) South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6843","6843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389414","2015-07-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what representations he has received from journalists on the practice of regional publications not recruiting journalists who have qualifications equivalent to the National Council for the Training of Journalists from EU member states other than the UK; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6892","6892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389415","2015-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the statement of the President of the US of 7 April 2015 on negotiations with Iran, what assessment he has made of the implication for his policy of Iran's breakout period shrinking to almost zero after the first decade of a possible nuclear deal.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6891","6891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389419","2015-07-15","Attorney General","2015-07-13","To ask the Attorney General, what procedures are in place to ensure that prosecutors make courts aware of overseas criminal convictions of (a) foreign and (b) British criminals for the purposes of bail and sentencing.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6587","6587"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389420","2015-07-15","Attorney General","2015-07-13","To ask the Attorney General, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for the Law Officers Departments from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6655","6655"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389421","2015-07-15","Attorney General","2015-07-13","To ask the Attorney General, in what proportion of cases in a domestic setting the Crown Prosecutor requests (a) a witness summons or (b) special measures; and what proportion of such applications are granted.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6608","6608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389422","2015-07-15","Attorney General","2015-07-13","To ask the Attorney General, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of prosecutors using computerised prosecution court files; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6610","6610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389423","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport on the reform of the Electronic Communication.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6622","6622"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389424","2015-07-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students received maintenance grants in each local authority in the last academic year for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6607","6607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389425","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6654","6654"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389426","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to support (a) small cider producers and (b) microbreweries in the UK.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6648","6648"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389427","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the availability of finance for entrepreneurs who are discharged bankrupts.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6588","6588"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389428","2015-07-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will meet the Minister of State for Care and Support to discuss enforcement of the minimum wage in the care sector.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6582","6582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389429","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will assess the effect of discharged bankruptcy on the ability of entrepreneurs to set up new businesses.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6590","6590"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389430","2015-07-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the contribution to Bradford's economy made by the (a) digital sector, (b) animation industry, (c) fashion and textiles industry and (d) games industry.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6592","6592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389431","2015-07-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on the estimated RAB charge on student loans of replacing university maintenance grants with maintenance loan support up to 8,400 per year.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6580","6580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389432","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent meetings he has had with the Trades Union Congress on trade union reform.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6722","6722"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389433","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what legislation governs the sale of second-hand electrical goods; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6738","6738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389434","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to prevent consumers purchasing unsafe second-hand electrical goods in the UK.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6739","6739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389435","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the efficacy of the Plugs and Sockets Regulations 1994 in regulating online trading of electrical products.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6740","6740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389436","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to prevent counterfeit electrical goods from being sold in the UK to protect consumers from electrical accidents; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6741","6741"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389437","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what his policy is on restricting the sale of second-hand electrical goods; and what assessment he has made of the effect of such policies on the number of electrical accidents.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6742","6742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389438","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the number of counterfeit electrical goods that are sold in the UK.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6743","6743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389439","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the Electrical Equipment (Safety) Regulations 1994 in reducing the number of non-compliant electrical products being sold in the UK.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6744","6744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389440","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he will publish the review of extant export licensing and the licensing of new applications for Israel.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6646","6646"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389441","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many students at each university receive maintenance grants.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6839","6839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389442","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of students receiving maintenance grants in (a) 2013-14, (b) 2014-15 and (c) 2015-16.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6840","6840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389443","2015-07-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 13 July 2015 to Question 6273, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that people who complete apprenticeship programmes receive a full-time job soon after completion of their apprenticeship.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6808","6808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389444","2015-07-16","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received from automotive manufacturers on promoting UK automotive exports.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6812","6812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389445","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many (a) applicants and (b) successful applicants there have been in each (i) UK region and (ii) local authority area to the Government's Start Up Loan Scheme since its establishment.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6771","6771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389446","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many people under the age of 25 started an apprenticeship in each of the last 24 months in (a) Bristol South constituency, (b) Bristol and (c) England.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6883","6883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389447","2015-07-15","Cabinet Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport on reform of the Electronic Communications Code.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6759","6759"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389448","2015-07-15","Cabinet Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many cases of domestic violence were recorded in (a) Barnsley East constituency, (b) Barnsley and (c) South Yorkshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6844","6844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389449","2015-07-15","Cabinet Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what information his Department holds on the number of carers in (a) Bristol South constituency and (b) Bristol in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6734","6734"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389450","2015-07-15","Cabinet Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of aggregate household debt in (a) Bristol South constituency, (b) Bristol, (c) the South West and (d) the UK in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6731","6731"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389451","2015-07-15","Cabinet Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6656","6656"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389452","2015-07-15","Cabinet Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what his policy is on introducing elections to the House of Lords.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6619","6619"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389453","2015-07-16","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish a distributional impact analysis of each of the benefit and tax credit announcements made in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6694","6694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389454","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations he has received from Citizens UK on the living wage.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6627","6627"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389455","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will postpone any sales of shares in RBS by UK Financial Investments until all interest rate cases with sophisticated customers have been resolved or subject to an independent inquiry.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6697","6697"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389456","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is towards any director of UK Financial Investments who had not disclosed a conflict of interest in relation to RBS customers.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6698","6698"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389457","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will investigate whether senior employees of RBS have acted fraudulently in relation to interest swap arrangements with customers deemed to be sophisticated.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6699","6699"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389458","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6671","6671"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389459","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether the one per cent cap on public sector pay rises will apply to people earning the statutory minimum wage.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6571","6571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389460","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will investigate the conduct of RBS in relation to interest rate mis-selling to customers deemed to be sophisticated.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6700","6700"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389461","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he takes to ensure that no conflicts of interest arise between directors of UK Financial Investments and customers of RBS.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6701","6701"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389462","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the apprenticeship levy will benefit those already in apprenticeships.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6714","6714"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389463","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how funding from the apprenticeship levy will be distributed.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6715","6715"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389464","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will hold a consultation on the introduction of the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6716","6716"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389465","2015-07-16","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the level of change in applications for rent-a-room tax relief as a result of changes introduced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6859","6859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389466","2015-07-16","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the total corporation tax receipts have been in each year since 2005.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6860","6860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389467","2015-07-16","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many and what proportion of (a) individuals and (b) families in each region of the UK will be affected by the reduction of the threshold for withdrawal of tax credits from 6420 to 3850; and what proportion of all tax credit recipients in each region such figures represent.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6857","6857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389468","2015-07-16","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) households and (b) individuals have (i) applied for and (ii) received rent-a-room relief in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6858","6858"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389469","2015-07-21","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when his Department plans to publish the 2013 HM Revenue and Customs Equal Pay Audit; what the reasons are for the time taken to publish that audit; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Danny Kinahan","Danny Kinahan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6863","6863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389470","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the implications for his policies of the statement by the Institute for Fiscal Studies that increases in the minimum wage will not fully compensate for changes made to the tax credits system.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6778","6778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389471","2015-07-16","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Summer Budget 2015, what estimate of the level of profits to be generated by UK banks was used to estimate the reserves to be derived from the corporation tax surcharge on banks.","Biography information for Owen Smith","Owen Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6886","6886"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389472","2015-07-16","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.213 of the Summer Budget 2015, if he will publish the analysis by HM Revenue and Customs that showed that a tobacco levy of 150 million would raise 25 million.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6888","6888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389473","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect the introduction of a new fuel marker has had on the level of fuel duty fraud.","Biography information for Luke Hall","Luke Hall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6786","6786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389474","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 June 2015 to Question 261, what progress has been made on the inquiry into tax avoidance facilitated by HSBC.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6781","6781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389475","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the quantitative easing programme put in place by the Bank of England.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6775","6775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389476","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the quantitative easing programme on (a) bank lending generally and (b) M4 lending.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6776","6776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389477","2015-07-16","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department is taking to support people who (a) do not have access to a computer or the internet or (b) are not computer and internet literate to access HM Revenue and Customs' services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6872","6872"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389478","2015-07-16","HM Treasury","2015-07-13","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, when he expects to publish the responses to the consultation on the tobacco levy.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6873","6873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389479","2015-07-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will devolve powers to local authorities on determining the type of voting system used in local elections.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6865","6865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389480","2015-07-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 July 2015 to Question 5507, what recent representations he has received from local authorities on shortages in (a) social and (b) private housing.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6811","6811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389481","2015-07-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to improve the timely delivery of a local plan in areas where a local authority has not produced such a plan.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6802","6802"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389482","2015-07-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) starting and (b) completion rates for affordable housing were in (i) Bristol, (ii) the South West and (iii) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6837","6837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389483","2015-07-15","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how funding for adoption services will be distributed to local authorities once joint arrangements have been made for carrying out local authority adoption functions.","Biography information for John Pugh","John Pugh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6766","6766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389484","2015-07-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the (a) starting and (b) completion rates for housing were in (i) Bristol, (ii) the South West and (iii) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6838","6838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389485","2015-07-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what meetings his Department has had with trades unions in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6719","6719"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389486","2015-07-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what forecast his Department has made of (a) starting and (b) completion rates of affordable homes in (i) Bristol, (ii) the South West and (iii) England in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6733","6733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389487","2015-07-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6657","6657"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389488","2015-07-16","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will bring forward legislative proposals to protect leaseholders who are not protected under the Landlord and Tenant Act 1985 or Mobile Homes Act 2013 from compound increases in service charges.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6606","6606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389489","2015-07-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with the mobile network operators on (a) digital infrastructure and inclusion and (b) reform of the Electronic Communications Code since May 2015.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6621","6621"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389490","2015-07-15","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6658","6658"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389491","2015-07-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what discussions he has had with mobile network operators on (a) digital infrastructure and inclusion and (b) reform of the Electronic Communications Code since May 2015.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6760","6760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389492","2015-07-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold discussions with the music industry on a voluntary video rating and classification code for music videos.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6639","6639"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389493","2015-07-15","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what meetings his Department has had with trades unions in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6721","6721"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389494","2015-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what amount his Department spent on external consultants in (a) 2014-15 and (b) each month of 2015-16 to date.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6889","6889"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389495","2015-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, with reference to the Minister for Defence Personnel and Veterans' letter to the hon. Member for Leeds North West of 4 June 2015, whether his Department estimated the cost of reinstating pensions for widows of armed forces personnel who remarried between 1973 and 2005 prior to the Government's decision on such pensions.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6874","6874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389496","2015-07-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what ministerial visits to sites involved in defence manufacturing there have been since 7 May 2010; and whether the local hon. Member was present at each such visit.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6717","6717"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389497","2015-07-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the operational viability of the UK's Trident programme as part of the continuous at-sea deterrent.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6841","6841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389498","2015-07-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6659","6659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389499","2015-07-16","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether any spending counted towards the two per cent of GNI target for defence spending will also be counted towards the 0.7 per cent target for ODA spending.","Biography information for Patrick Grady","Patrick Grady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6583","6583"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389500","2015-07-15","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if she will make it her policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for her Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6660","6660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389501","2015-07-15","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will incorporate education on mental health issues into the national curriculum.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6624","6624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389502","2015-07-16","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many primary schools are engaged in Primary School Sport Partnerships.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6679","6679"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389503","2015-07-16","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many Primary School Sport Partnerships there are in each local authority.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6605","6605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389504","2015-07-16","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the reasons for changes in the number of children eligible for free school meals in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6599","6599"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389505","2015-07-15","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to maintain the current provision of children's centre services.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6849","6849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389506","2015-07-15","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what meetings her Department has had with trades unions in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6720","6720"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389507","2015-07-15","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of primary schools in (a) Bristol South constituency, (b) Bristol and (c) England received a mark of good or outstanding according to their most recent inspections.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6737","6737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389508","2015-07-15","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that parents of children and young people with autism receive appropriate support, guidance and information.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6736","6736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389509","2015-07-15","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will implement the recommendations of the report published by the NSPCC in June 2015 entitled Achieving emotional wellbeing for looked after children, on the mental health needs of children in care.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6866","6866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389510","2015-07-16","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the effect of Primary School Sport Partnerships on participation in sport.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6815","6815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389511","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2015 to Question 842, with which organisations she has met in connection with ensuring that awarding organisations are liaising effectively with Ofqual; and what further steps her Department has taken to safeguard the future of modern languages at GCSE and A-level in subjects (a) Turkish, (b) Greek, (c) Gujarati, (d) Modern Hebrew, (e) Panjabi, (f) Polish, (g) Bengali and (h) other community languages.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6877","6877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389512","2015-07-21","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 10 June 2015 to Question 842, what the timescale is, and what methodology is being used for, the consultation on the future of modern languages teaching.","Biography information for Mr David Burrowes","Mr David Burrowes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6876","6876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389513","2015-07-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether her Department has conducted an impact assessment for the removal of onshore wind from the Renewables Obligation.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6881","6881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389514","2015-07-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what freedom of information (FOI) requests her Department has received on evidence submitted to the European Commission as part of the UK's challenge to the decision made by the European Commission on the application for state aid for Hinkley Point C; and what responses have been made to each such FOI request.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6774","6774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389515","2015-07-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, which recommendations of the report by HM Chief Nuclear Inspector on the implications for the UK nuclear industry of the Japanese earthquake and tsunami have not yet been acted upon; and what the reasons are for not having acted on each such recommendation.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6871","6871"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389516","2015-07-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many children were living in households classed as being in fuel poverty in (a) Bristol South constituency, (b) Bristol, (c) the South West and (d) England in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6735","6735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389517","2015-07-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the implications are for her Department's policies of the findings of the Lancet Commission on Health and Climate Change, published on 23 June 2015.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6725","6725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389518","2015-07-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the timetable is for the UK to respond to the application made by the Austrian government to the European Court of Justice against the decision by the European Commission to grant state aid status for the Hinkley Point C project.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6713","6713"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389519","2015-07-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many Generation III reactors of the type currently in development in the UK are currently operating worldwide; and what assessment she has made of the economic and operational effectiveness of those reactors.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6712","6712"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389520","2015-07-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how the recent changes made to onshore wind farm subsidies will affect the Glen Ullinish Wind Farm Development on the Isle of Skye.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6777","6777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389521","2015-07-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will estimate the amount of gigawatts of onshore wind that will not be built as a result of the changes to the Renewables Obligation.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6803","6803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389522","2015-07-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will take steps to merge the 14 regional markets for energy distribution to create a national energy market for electricity distribution and reduce the price paid by consumers and businesses in the Highlands and Islands.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6779","6779"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389523","2015-07-16","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how many gigawatts of onshore wind will be eligible for grace periods following planned changes to the Renewables Obligation.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6691","6691"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389524","2015-07-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if she will make it her policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for her Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6661","6661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389525","2015-07-15","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, whether there will be a licensing round in the North Sea in 2016.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6576","6576"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389526","2015-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with representatives of (a) the EU and (b) each of its member states on promotion of recycling.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6569","6569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389527","2015-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to encourage the recycling of food waste in schools and hospitals.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6565","6565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389528","2015-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what plans she has to reduce the amount of waste that goes in to landfill.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6566","6566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389529","2015-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the amount of waste disposed in landfill sites in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6567","6567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389530","2015-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what new incentives she is offering to promote the circular economy and reduce waste.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6568","6568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389531","2015-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether her Department (a) has submitted and (b) plans to submit data to the European Food Safety Authority's investigation into the consequences of the European Commission's restrictions on the use of neonicotinoids.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6845","6845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389532","2015-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many square kilometres of landfill there were in (a) the UK, (b) England and (c) Yorkshire in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6626","6626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389533","2015-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what discussions she has had with her counterpart in the Scottish Government on seal (a) culls and (b) conservation; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6784","6784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389534","2015-07-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department is taking to support pollinators on farmland.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6868","6868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389535","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect on British Overseas Territories of the repeal of the Human Rights Act 1998.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6870","6870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389536","2015-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of the implications of its policies of the Human Rights Watch report on the airstrikes on Saada city in Northern Yemen published on 30 June 2015.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6867","6867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389537","2015-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the Report of the Commission of Inquiry on Human Rights in Eritrea brought before the UN Human Rights Council on 4 June 2015, what steps he has taken to (a) ensure that no UK or EU funding is provided to Eritrea that in any way strengthens or enhances their capability to repress or oppress the Eritrean people, (b) follow up the Commission's finding within the UN and (c) provide assistance to the UN Somali/Eritrea Monitoring Group in investigating alleged abuses by the Eritrean government.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6782","6782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389538","2015-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what support the UK is giving to interfaith peacebuilding and reconciliation initiatives in the Central African Republic.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6783","6783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389539","2015-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the value of UK exports to (a) the EU, (b) the US, (c) China and (d) India in (i) 2000 and (ii) the most recent year available.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6768","6768"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389540","2015-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of (a) the role the UK has played in reducing the danger of piracy off the coast of Somalia and (b) the potential for such international efforts to be successfully replicated in other at-risk areas.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6854","6854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389541","2015-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of progress in talks between the Afghan government and the Taliban; and what he would consider a successful outcome to be to those negotiations.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6855","6855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389542","2015-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of links between the Iran nuclear negotiations and wider nuclear non-proliferation in the Middle East.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6856","6856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389543","2015-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment his Department has made of whether Saudi Arabia is adhering to the laws of war in the context of its military action in Yemen.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6862","6862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389544","2015-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received of the conditions faced by migrant workers  on construction of the Saadiyat Island project in the United Arab Emirates.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6573","6573"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389545","2015-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the treatment of women by the legal system of the United Arab Emirates.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6574","6574"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389546","2015-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his United Arab Emirates counterpart about the timescale for democratic reform in that country.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6575","6575"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389547","2015-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with the government of Kyrgyzstan on (a) the Foreign Agents Bill and (b) freedom of expression and association in that country.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6581","6581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389548","2015-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6662","6662"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389549","2015-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the government of the United Arab Emirates on the unlawful detainment of political activists in that country.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6620","6620"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389550","2015-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of (a) freedom of opinion and expression, (b) freedom of peaceful assembly and association and (c) the position of civil society in Egypt.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6693","6693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389551","2015-07-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to assist faith and community-led reconciliation efforts in South Sudan.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6638","6638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389552","2015-07-16","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what reports he has received on (a) attacks and threats against human rights defenders in Guatemala and (b) the implementation of protection measures requested by the Office of the UNHCR for members of the Nuevo Dia Ch'orti Indigenous Association in Guatemala.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6681","6681"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389553","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had on increasing training for GPs by one year to include a compulsory rotation in mental health.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6623","6623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389554","2015-07-16","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many children in Cumbria have presented at accident and emergency with dental problems in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6683","6683"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389555","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received about development of a commissioning policy for microprocessor knees by NHS England.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6563","6563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389556","2015-07-16","Department for Education","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will introduce a diagnostic assessment pathway for (a) dyslexia and dyspraxia and (b) other specific learning difficulties.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6695","6695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389557","2015-07-16","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the reasons for changes in the number of cases of malnutrition in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Margaret Ferrier","Margaret Ferrier","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6601","6601"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389558","2015-07-16","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many foundation hospitals include on their council of governors elected members from Wales.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6602","6602"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389559","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent meetings (a) Ministers and (b) officials in his Department have had with health staff trades unions in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6594","6594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389560","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy to secure accredited Living Wage Employer status for his Department from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6664","6664"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389561","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the criteria and processes are for a technology to be considered for NHS England's evaluation through commissioning programme.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6559","6559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389562","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how NHS England's evaluation through commissioning programme will align with the Accelerated Access Review and the test bed programme outlined in the NHS five year forward review.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6560","6560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389563","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much funding NHS England's evaluation through commissioning programme has received; and how much is allocated for future programmes.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6561","6561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389564","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the number of GP surgeries in Sheffield, Heeley constituency that will have to (a) reduce patient services and (b) close as a result of the phased withdrawal of the Minimum Practice Income Guarantee.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6570","6570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389565","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP surgeries in Sheffield, Heeley constituency will be affected by the phased withdrawal of the Minimum Practice Income Guarantee.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6572","6572"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389566","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will ask NHS England to reconsider a commissioning policy on (a) microprocessor knees, (b) muti-articulating prosthetic hands and (c) custom made silicon covers.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6562","6562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389567","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what progress NHS strategic clinical networks have made against the indicator in the Clinical Commissioning Group Outcomes Indicator Set on reducing the number of emergency admissions for diabetic ketoacidosis and lower limb amputations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6555","6555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389568","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of unplanned emergency admissions to hospital attributed to (a) blocked catheters, (b) heart failure and (c) diabetic ketoacidosis in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6556","6556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389569","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase awareness of the symptoms of oesophageal cancer among (a) GPs and (b) the wider public.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6557","6557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389570","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effectiveness of NHS England's evaluation through commissioning programme to date; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6558","6558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389571","2015-07-16","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many ambulances have waited 30 minutes or longer to hand over patients at (a) West Cumberland Hospital and (b) Cumberland Infirmary, Carlisle in each of the last 60 months.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6806","6806"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389572","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will assess the potential effect of a reduction in VAT on sunscreen on public health.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6780","6780"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389573","2015-07-16","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 9 February 2015 to Question 223479, what recent discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues in HM Treasury and the Department for Business, Innovation and Skills on targeted National Minimum Wage enforcement work in the care sector.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6801","6801"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389574","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to maintain the current level of funding of child and adolescent mental health services.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6836","6836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389575","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department issues on ensuring the continual provision of GP services in the event of a lease-holding GP practice withdrawing its services; and what the minimum specifications are for the interim provision of GP services in a case where a lease-holding GP practice withdraws its services.","Biography information for Michael Dugher","Michael Dugher","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6846","6846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389576","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to support people diagnosed with diabetes to manage their own care.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6724","6724"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389577","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the results of the Be Clear on Cancer pilot scheme in 2014; and if this scheme will be repeated nationally in the future.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6643","6643"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389578","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the implications for his Department's policies are of the recommendations of the Lancet Commission on Health and Climate Change, published on 23 June 2015.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6726","6726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389579","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to ensure that commissioners and hospital trusts work together to reduce hospital admissions associated with diabetes.","Biography information for Karin Smyth","Karin Smyth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6732","6732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389580","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with NHS England on providing additional funding for skin cancer specialist nurses.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6645","6645"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389581","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had on the availability of new treatments for (a) skin cancer patients and (b) patients with advanced melanoma.","Biography information for Carolyn Harris","Carolyn Harris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6644","6644"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389582","2015-07-16","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects Public Health England's advice to the Government on sugar reduction to be published.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6887","6887"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389583","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to increase the number of children who are partaking in 60 minutes of daily exercise.","Biography information for Ian Paisley","Ian Paisley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6769","6769"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389584","2015-07-16","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how much North Cumbria University Hospital Trust spent on agency medical staff in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6807","6807"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389585","2015-07-16","Department of Health","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many medical staff of each pay band have been recruited by North Cumbria University Hospital Trust in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6805","6805"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389928","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what the timetable is for the publication of the feasibility studies on the rail line at Dawlish and the potential route via Okehampton and Tavistock.","Biography information for Johnny Mercer","Johnny Mercer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901043","901043"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390509","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent representations he has received on development of rail infrastructure in the North West; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901062","901062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390510","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to promote cycling.","Biography information for Graham Evans","Graham Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901058","901058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390511","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to promote cycling.","Biography information for Andrew Stephenson","Andrew Stephenson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901064","901064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390512","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the cessation of work on the electrification of the TransPennine route and the Midland Main Line on the Northern Powerhouse initiative.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901061","901061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/390513","2015-07-16","Department for Transport","2015-07-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans he has to promote direct flights to international destinations from airports outside London and the South East.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 901063","901063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389031","2015-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all users of electromagnetic radiation emitting devices comply fully with IEC/EN62471 regarding Photobiological Safety of Lamps and Lamp Systems.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6502","6502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389032","2015-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to collect and publish data on whether students who make complaints to Student Finance England are satisfied with the way their complaints are dealt with.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6517","6517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389033","2015-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much support the British Business Bank has provided to small and medium-sized enterprises in Bradford since its creation.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6519","6519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389034","2015-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what 10 sectors received most support from the British Business Bank in (a) Bradford, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) the UK since that bank was established.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6530","6530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389035","2015-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will take steps to  ensure that children under 13 are aware of producers' of virtual reality headsets recommendations that such children do not use these headsets.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6531","6531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389036","2015-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will take steps to ensure that users of virtual reality headsets are aware of the producers' recommendations that some users should see a doctor before using such a headset.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6532","6532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389037","2015-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if his Department will take steps to ensure that users of virtual reality headsets are aware of producers' recommendations on the length of use of such headsets and the length of breaks before their re-use.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6533","6533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389038","2015-07-14","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect of broadband speed and coverage on local economies.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6529","6529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389039","2015-07-14","Cabinet Office","2015-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, in what ways his Department is supporting the mediation of a standardised pre-qualification questionnaire to help businesses access public sector contracts.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr   Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6537","6537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389040","2015-07-14","HM Treasury","2015-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much he forecasts will be collected from the bank levy in each year of the current Parliament.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6495","6495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389041","2015-07-14","HM Treasury","2015-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how HM Revenue and Customs plans to spend the additional funding allocated to it in the Summer Budget 2015 to tackle tax avoidance.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6496","6496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389042","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he had with the Living Wage Foundation on the National Living Wage before the 2015 summer budget.","Biography information for Kirsty Blackman","Kirsty Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6526","6526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389043","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of whether the legal basis of the Low Pay Commission will need to be changed in order to set and implement the National Living Wage; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6507","6507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389044","2015-07-14","HM Treasury","2015-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.213 of the Summer Budget 2015, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Health on the decision not to introduce a levy on tobacco manufacturers; and what steps he took to assess the potential effects of that decision on public health.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6506","6506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389045","2015-07-14","HM Treasury","2015-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to allocate funds raised by vehicle excise duty to renewable energy and green transport initiatives.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6505","6505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389046","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of likely savings to the public purse in each of the next five years as a result of changed to tax credits as announced in the Summer Budget 2015; and if he will estimate what those savings would be if those changes were applied only to new tax credit claimants.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6516","6516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389047","2015-07-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether the requirement on local authorities to pay staff the National Living Wage will be treated as a new burden.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6511","6511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389048","2015-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether councils will be required to sell off any property assets in addition to high-value residential council houses to fund his Department's proposed changes to housing policy.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6542","6542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389049","2015-07-15","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of (a) how many and (b) what proportion of all completions of new homes sold in England and Wales have received an A grade for energy efficiency in their Energy Performance Certificate since 2010.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6552","6552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389050","2015-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, by what mechanism he plans to reduce the time period between the sale of social housing under right to buy and the receipt by housing associations of compensation from the Government.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6541","6541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389051","2015-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the overall proportion of local authority housing stock that will be sold off as high-value properties under the Department's proposed changes to housing policy.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6540","6540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389052","2015-07-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will hold discussions with Airbnb on ensuring that their suppliers comply with the requirement not to let their properties for more than 90 days each year.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6546","6546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389053","2015-07-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of DAB radio reception across Wales; what information his Department holds on which areas in Wales have poor DAB reception; what steps his Department has taken to improve poor reception in such areas; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mrs Madeleine Moon","Mrs Madeleine Moon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6504","6504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389054","2015-07-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, whether it is his policy to retain the BBC Licence fee (a) until 2020 and (b) for the entirety of the next Charter period.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6503","6503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389055","2015-07-14","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what steps he is taking to increase broadband coverage and speed in Bradford.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6524","6524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389056","2015-07-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will take steps to ensure that war widows who remarried between 1973 and 2005 have their war widows' pension reinstated.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6523","6523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389057","2015-07-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of women in receipt of the war widows' pension who remarried between 1973 and 2005.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6522","6522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389058","2015-07-15","Ministry of Defence","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations his Department has received from the War Widows' Association of Britain on war widows' pensions.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6509","6509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389059","2015-07-14","Department for Education","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make an assessment of the implications for her policies of the findings of the study funded by the Education Endowment Foundation into the effect on primary schools pupils' ability in mathematics and literacy of weekly philosophy classes.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6528","6528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389060","2015-07-14","Cabinet Office","2015-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which 10 job sectors employed the most people from black and minority ethnic communities in (a) Bradford, (b) Yorkshire and the Humber and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6539","6539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389061","2015-07-14","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her Department is doing to provide support for and encourage investment in renewable energy projects in (a) Bradford and (b) West Yorkshire.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6538","6538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389063","2015-07-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the government of China on the alleged harvesting of organs from Falun Gong prisoners held in China.","Biography information for Sammy Wilson","Sammy Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6494","6494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389064","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department is taking to improve access to radiotherapy in Copeland constituency.","Biography information for Mr Jamie Reed","Mr Jamie Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6510","6510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389065","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what legal costs the Government has incurred to date relating to the Freedom of Information request for the former Secretary of State for Health's diary of engagements referred to in Information Commissioner Decision Notice No. FS50406024 and the subsequent appeals.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6508","6508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389066","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the Answer of 27 November 2014 to Question 215787, health services: Greater London, whether he plans to publish the independent review referred to in that Answer.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6548","6548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389067","2015-07-15","Department of Health","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when the Keogh Review on Urgent and Emergency Care plans to report.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6551","6551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389068","2015-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he plans to answer Question 3159 tabled on 18 June 2015 by the right hon. Member for Hammersmith.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6527","6527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389069","2015-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 5439 on open prisons, how many prisoners had committed each offence.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6518","6518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389070","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 9 July 2015 to Question 5710, what the cost to the public purse has been of his Department's spending on the Secure College programme to date.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6553","6553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389071","2015-07-15","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of occasions when due to the loss or theft of keys, a prison has had to be relocked since May 2010; and what the cost to the public purse was of such incidents.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6550","6550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389072","2015-07-14","Ministry of Justice","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of legislation enabling families of missing people to protect financial and legal affairs of such people.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6543","6543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389073","2015-07-15","Cabinet Office","2015-07-10","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to his Answer of 10 July 2015 to Question 2952, if he will make it his policy that all Government departments pursue accreditation from the Living Wage Foundation.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6547","6547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389074","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with mobile network operators on (a) digital infrastructure and inclusion and (b) reform of the Electronic Communications Code since 7 May 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6549","6549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389075","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what proportion of the 3.4 billion reduction in capital expenditure for his Department he plans will apply to (a) the roads budget, (b) the rail budget and (c) other budgets; and what proportion of the reduction to the roads budget will apply to (i) the Highways Agency, (ii) local authority maintenance, (iii) local authority major projects and (iv) other areas.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6525","6525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389076","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what safeguards are in place to ensure that the DVLA only provides its data to car parking companies which are registered by the British Parking Association.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6512","6512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389077","2015-07-15","Department for Transport","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what discussions he has had with the Department of Culture, Media and Sport on improving wifi coverage and mobile connectivity across the UK rail network.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6554","6554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389078","2015-07-14","Department for Transport","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of renovating Bradford Interchange station.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6536","6536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389079","2015-07-14","Department for Transport","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will take steps to (a) shorten journey times and (b) increase train speeds on the Calder Valley Line between Bradford Interchange and Manchester Victoria.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6535","6535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389080","2015-07-14","Department for Transport","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on negotiations between the Government and Sheffield City region for a new City Deal of the suspension of work on the electrification of the TransPennine route and the Midland Main Line.","Biography information for Harry Harpham","Harry Harpham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6534","6534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389081","2015-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to (a) increase the national minimum wage for 18 to 20 year olds to 6.86 by 2020 and (b) open the national minimum wage entitlement for apprentices to that rate.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6545","6545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389082","2015-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to help people with learning difficulties find work.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6544","6544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389083","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether he plans that people aged 18 to 21 who are (a) homeless or (b) at risk of homelessness will be eligible for housing benefit after the implementation of changes announced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6499","6499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389084","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to the eligibility for housing benefit of people aged 18 to 21 announced in the Summer Budget 2015 on the level of homelessness.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6500","6500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389085","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, on what date he plans for changes to tax credit entitlements announced in the Summer Budget 2015 to take effect.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6501","6501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389086","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the number of people with multiple sclerosis who have claimed personal independence payment to date; and what proportion of those people have had (a) a repeat assessment and (b) more than three assessments.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6513","6513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389087","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the number of people with multiple sclerosis who have claimed personal independence payment to date and have received an award of (a) up to six months, (b) between six and 12 months, (c) between one and two years, (d) between two and five years, (e) more than five years and (f) more than 10 years.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6514","6514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389088","2015-07-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the number of people with multiple sclerosis who have moved from disability living allowance to personal independence payment; and what proportion of those people have received a reduced mobility award as a result of that change.","Biography information for Catherine McKinnell","Catherine McKinnell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6515","6515"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389089","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to introduce an online calculator or helpline for people in receipt of tax credits to calculate how their entitlement will change under the new system announced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6497","6497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389090","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-10","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people who will experience a net loss in income as a result of the changes to in-work benefits and the minimum wage announced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6498","6498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389091","2015-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants of employment and support allowance his Department has classified as unfit to work in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6520","6520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/389092","2015-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-10","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department has made a forecast of the number of employment and support allowance claimants that his Department will classify as unfit to work in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6521","6521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388834","2015-07-13","Attorney General","2015-07-09","To ask the Attorney General, what the name, responsibilities and pay band are of each special adviser in the Law Officers' Departments.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6321","6321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388835","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the name, responsibilities and pay band are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6320","6320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388836","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent assessment he has made of the effect of business rates on micro-businesses.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6340","6340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388837","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many complaints about (a) pre-pack sales and (b) connected party pre-pack sales were received in each year from 2010 to 2014.","Biography information for Toby Perkins","Toby Perkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6360","6360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388838","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he plans to take to maintain excellence in scientific research and development in the Midlothian constituency.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6353","6353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388839","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many jobs in Midlothian constituency are supported by science funding from his Department.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6354","6354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388840","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many jobs in Scotland are supported by science funding from his Department.","Biography information for Owen Thompson","Owen Thompson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6355","6355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388841","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with large-scale retailers on potential changes to the law relating to Sunday trading.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6379","6379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388842","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment the Government has made of the effect on student numbers of ending maintenance grants.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6380","6380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388843","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion  of invoices from suppliers his Department paid within 10 days of receipt in (a) March 2014, (b) April 2014, (c) September 2014 and (d) September 2013.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6412","6412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388844","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 23 June 2015 to Question 3264, how many businesses were not paid within 10 days of each month; what the value was of those invoices (a) in total, (b) on average and (c) as a proportion of the total value of all invoices.","Biography information for Alan Brown","Alan Brown","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6413","6413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388845","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what (a) processes, (b) timeframe and (c) deadlines he has set for the establishment of science and innovation audits; what support his Department and its agencies plan to provide to people undertaking such audits; whether he plans for all local enterprise partnerships to conduct such audits; and what guidance he plans to issue on such audits.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6482","6482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388846","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to HM Treasury's press release, Chancellor announces 4.5 billion of measures to bring down debt, published on 4 June 2015, what savings he forecasts will be made from funds allocated by his Department to support energy-intensive industries.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6421","6421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388847","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether he plans to devolve powers on Sunday trading to (a) top-tier authorities, (b) district councils and (c) London boroughs.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6483","6483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388848","2015-07-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what outputs have been delivered under the TechNorth programme since its announcement on 23 October 2014; how many officials are working on delivery of that scheme; what key performance indicators have been set for that programme; and how much public funding has been allocated under that programme to date.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6422","6422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388849","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, by what date he expects a network of national colleges to be in place; and what national colleges are planned to be established.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6484","6484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388850","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to the Answer of 6 March 2015 to Question 225778, how many Growth Hubs are currently in operation; where each such hub is located and whether it has premises; when each such hub began operation; what public monies have been provided for each such hub; and what plans his Department has for further Growth Hubs in other local enterprise partnership areas.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6423","6423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388851","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what plans he has for opening new Catapult centres.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6485","6485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388852","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress his Department has made on its consultation on clarifying the employment status of workers, launched on 6 October 2014.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6424","6424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388853","2015-07-15","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, by what date he plans for each of the six next generation digital economy centres to be operational.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6486","6486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388854","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, by what date he plans for the Collaboration for Research in Infrastructure and Cities hub to be operational; and what funds have been provided from the public purse to establish that hub.","Biography information for Chuka Umunna","Mr Chuka Umunna","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6425","6425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388855","2015-07-13","Cabinet Office","2015-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the name, responsibilities and pay band are of each special adviser in (a) his Department and (b) the Prime Minister's Office.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6322","6322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388856","2015-07-14","Cabinet Office","2015-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, which Ministers in which departments are special advisers in other departments; and what roles each such Minister holds.","Biography information for Chris Law","Chris Law","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6314","6314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388857","2015-07-13","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the name, responsibilities and pay band are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6336","6336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388858","2015-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, by what process his Department plans to bring forward proposals for the establishment of further next generation digital economy centres.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6398","6398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388859","2015-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what discussions he has had with Ministers in the Welsh Government on the establishment of next generation digital economy centres in Wales.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6399","6399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388860","2015-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Ogmore constituency receive between 20,000 and 26,000 in benefit payments each year.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6393","6393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388861","2015-07-14","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the potential effect of the tax credit changes announced in the Summer Budget 2015 on families with two parents who work full-time on minimum wage with (a) two and (b) three or more children.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6401","6401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388862","2015-07-13","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to page 57 of the Information Commission's office's annual report 2014-15, under what statutory provision the Treasury imposes a financial penalty on that office; how the amount of that penalty was arrived at; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6395","6395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388863","2015-07-14","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions on the potential effect of the tax credit changes announced in Summer Budget 2015 on lone parent families in which the parent works full time on minimum wage with (a) two and (b) three or more children.","Biography information for Gavin Newlands","Gavin Newlands","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6402","6402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388864","2015-07-13","Cabinet Office","2015-07-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people in Ogmore constituency earn between 3,850 and 6,420 annually.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6361","6361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388865","2015-07-13","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many families with more than two children in Ogmore constituency claim (a) child tax credits and (b) universal credit; if he will estimate the number of such families who will no longer be eligible to receive benefits for a child by the end of 2017; and if he will estimate the average amount by which the benefits received by such families will be reduced.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6362","6362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388866","2015-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will estimate the number of 18 to 21 year olds in Ogmore constituency after April 2017 who will be unemployed and who will not be entitled to claim the housing element of universal credit.","Biography information for Huw Irranca-Davies","Huw Irranca-Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6363","6363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388867","2015-07-13","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will attend the Financing for Development summit in Addis Ababa from 13 to 16 July 2015.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6357","6357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388868","2015-07-13","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his Budget Statement of 8 July 2015, Official Report, column 338, what estimate he has made of how many of the 60,000 jobs which the Office for Budget Responsibility estimates will be lost as a result of the introduction of the National Living Wage are based in each (a) sector and (b) region.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6434","6434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388869","2015-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of measures announced in the Summer Budget 2015 on the level of child poverty among families who are (a) in and (b) out of work.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6441","6441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388870","2015-07-14","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what criteria were applied in selecting the next generation digital economy centres announced in the Summer Budget 2015.","Biography information for Ian C. Lucas","Ian C. Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6470","6470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388871","2015-07-13","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to monitor the effects of changes to tax credits on families with very low incomes.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6437","6437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388872","2015-07-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of measures announced in the Summer Budget 2015 on child poverty.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6428","6428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388873","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the average call response time to calls made to the (a) tax credit helpline and (b) general HM Revenue and Customs helpline for hon. Members was in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6487","6487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388874","2015-07-13","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of reductions in tax credits on families with very low incomes.","Biography information for Ian Blackford","Ian Blackford","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6438","6438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388875","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many staff have been employed to work on the (a) tax credit helpline and (b) general HM Revenue and Customs helpline for hon. Members in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6488","6488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388876","2015-07-13","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effects of reductions in tax credits on families on very low incomes.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6440","6440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388877","2015-07-14","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what the amount of planned DEL departmental expenditure for 2015-16 defined as overseas development aid was in each Department in (a) the March and (b) the July 2015 budget.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6475","6475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388878","2015-07-14","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to his Budget Statement of 8 July 2015, Official Report, column 338, what proportion of the 60,000 jobs that the Office for Budget Responsibility estimates will be lost as a result of the national living wage are forecast to be from (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) South West England.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6477","6477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388879","2015-07-13","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, with reference to paragraph 2.201 of the Summer Budget 2015, HC 264, if he will hold a consultation on the introduction of the apprenticeship levy.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6449","6449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388880","2015-07-15","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what service level agreements HM Revenue and Customs has with Concentrix for turnaround time on tax credit queries; and what assessment he has made of the contractor's performance in meeting those targets in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Mike Weir","Mike Weir","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6489","6489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388881","2015-07-13","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will take steps to ensure that additional support and financial assistance is provided to Equitable Life policy holders to ensure full payments to all policy holders.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6429","6429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388882","2015-07-13","HM Treasury","2015-07-09","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he plans to take to monitor the effects of changes to tax credits on families with very low incomes who are (a) in and (b) out of work.","Biography information for Mr David Anderson","Mr David Anderson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6439","6439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388883","2015-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans he has to establish a team within his Department dedicated to facilitating combined authority devolution negotiations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6457","6457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388884","2015-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what resources his Department plans to make available to facilitate combined authority devolution negotiations; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6459","6459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388885","2015-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to publish the results of its consultation on extending the remit of the Local Government Ombudsman to include larger parish and town councils.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Mrs Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6460","6460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388886","2015-07-20","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, which newspapers, journals and periodicals his Department subscribes to; and how much his Department spent on newspapers, journals and periodicals in 2014.","Biography information for Sir Mark Hendrick","Mr Mark Hendrick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6490","6490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388887","2015-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the total cost to the public purse of holding devolution negotiations for combined authorities in the next 12 months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6465","6465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388888","2015-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that major property developers provide affordable housing in urban areas.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6427","6427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388889","2015-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of specifying that new council homes be allocated half to existing residents on waiting lists and half to new foreign residents.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6426","6426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388890","2015-07-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effect of the removal of the work-related activity component of employment and support allowance on disabled people.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6369","6369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388891","2015-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his estimate is of the cost to local authorities of the increased minimum wage announced in the 2015 Summer Budget payable to (a) local authority employees and (b) employees of private contractors and service providers in each year from 2016-17 to 2019-20.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6384","6384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388892","2015-07-14","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his estimate is of the cost to (a) local authorities and (b) housing associations of the administration involved in charging market rents to higher-earning social housing tenants.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6385","6385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388893","2015-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the level of consistency in the way five-year housing supply is calculated by developers and local authorities.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6316","6316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388894","2015-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that housing associations aim to maintain a social mix in an area when selecting tenants.","Biography information for Charlotte Leslie","Charlotte Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6317","6317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388895","2015-07-13","Department for Communities and Local Government","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what the name, responsibilities and pay band are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6323","6323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388896","2015-07-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what the name, responsibilities and pay band are of each special adviser in his Department.","Biography information for Stuart Blair Donaldson","Stuart Blair Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6324","6324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388897","2015-07-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to paragraph 1.318, of Summer Budget 2015, to what ends the Government plans to spend the 10 million for broadband in addition to the existing rural rollout programme.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6339","6339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/388898","2015-07-13","Department for Culture Media and Sport","2015-07-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many public buildings have been provided with free public wifi in each of the super-connected cities.","Biography information for Chris Bryant","Chris Bryant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 6389","6389"
