"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487158","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to implement recommendation 8 in the executive summary of Public Health England's March 2015 report entitled, Public mental health leadership and workforce development framework, on working with relevant colleges, faculties and boards overseeing professional training to include mental health within public health curricula.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32630","32630"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487159","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost is per patient attending a GP's surgery in Southampton.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32592","32592"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487160","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to implement recommendation 12 in the executive summary of Public Health England's March 2015 report entitled, Public mental health leadership and workforce development framework, on supporting increased access to a range of mental health promotion training for frontline public health practitioners.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32629","32629"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487161","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will estimate how many and what proportion of all women with mental health issues in the UK have been internally or internationally trafficked.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32631","32631"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487162","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the final local government finance settlement 2016-17, published on 8 February 2016, if he will place a copy of the (a) methodology used for calculating the distribution  and (b) detailed model used to calculate the allocation to each individual authority of the 2016-17 transitional grant in the Library; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Chris Leslie","Chris Leslie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32596","32596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487163","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many cases of (a) human trafficking and (b) forced labour have been recorded by Humberside Police for each year from 2010 to 2014; in how many such cases prosecutions were brought; and what the outcomes were of those prosecutions.","Biography information for Diana Johnson","Diana Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32595","32595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487164","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will publish all correspondence between her Department and ETS relating to allegations of English language text fraud.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32637","32637"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487165","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will commission an independent inquiry into the role of (a) her Department and (b) ETS related to allegations of English Language Test fraud.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32636","32636"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487166","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what independent scrutiny her Department commissioned of reports of invalid and questionable results in English Language tests conducted by ETS.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32659","32659"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487167","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of barriers to humanitarian agencies reaching people in need in Yemen.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32642","32642"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487168","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking ensure that UK overseas aid is spent effectively and transparently.","Biography information for Mr William Wragg","William Wragg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32665","32665"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487169","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, which (a) ministers and (b) officials of her Department will be present at the International Aids Conference in Durban in July 2016.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32615","32615"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487170","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what contribution his Department is making to Government steps to reduce the incidence of serious youth violence.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32649","32649"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487171","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Network Rail has paid to Southern Rail in compensation for late running and skipped stopping in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32653","32653"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487172","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how much Southern Rail/GTR has paid in compensation payments to passengers in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32660","32660"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487173","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of the effect on traffic congestion in (a) Brentford and Isleworth constituency and (b) the London borough of Hounslow of the proposed third runway at Heathrow.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32635","32635"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487174","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will discuss with the European Aviation Safety Agency agreeing a minimum numbers of hours for airline pilots between each flight for EU and non-EU carriers entering EU airspace.","Biography information for Mark Pritchard","Mark Pritchard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32623","32623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487175","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many emergency landings there have been at Heathrow Airport in the last five years.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32633","32633"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487176","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to increase capacity on public transport links to Heathrow Airport from central London.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32634","32634"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/487177","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to his oral contribution of 21 March 2016, Official Report, column 1284, whether an impact assessment has been carried out on the effect of social security reform on employees in his Department.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32638","32638"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/508949","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the adequacy of police funding after service reorganisation.","Biography information for Rachael Maskell","Rachael Maskell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904394","904394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/508950","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of trends in the level of demand for police services.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904395","904395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/508951","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to tackle people trafficking.","Biography information for James Cartlidge","James Cartlidge","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904392","904392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/508952","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent assessment she has made of the adequacy of neighbourhood policing capacity.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904391","904391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/508953","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the Government is taking to (a) stop firearms, drugs and other contraband from entering the UK and (b) tackle human trafficking in UK waters.","Biography information for Suella Braverman","Suella Fernandes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904396","904396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/510067","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has been made on implementation of the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action with Iran.","Biography information for Oliver Dowden","Oliver Dowden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904418","904418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/510395","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to support efforts to bring an end to the conflict in Syria.","Biography information for Sir Edward Leigh","Sir Edward Leigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904416","904416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/510396","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with his Burmese counterpart on prisoners of conscience in that country.","Biography information for Angela Smith","Angela Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904420","904420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/510397","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps the Government is taking to promote trade and diplomatic connections between the UK and other Commonwealth countries.","Biography information for Mary Robinson","Mary Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904411","904411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/510398","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on the use of administrative detention in that country.","Biography information for Tommy Sheppard","Tommy Sheppard","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904414","904414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/510399","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions his Department has had with HM Treasury on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on the economy.","Biography information for Anna Turley","Anna Turley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904417","904417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/510400","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to encourage greater diplomatic co-operation between Afghanistan and Pakistan.","Biography information for Rehman Chishti","Rehman Chishti","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904419","904419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/510401","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he has taken to support the formation of the transitional government of national unity in South Sudan.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904415","904415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/510402","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the strength of diplomatic and economic relations between China and the UK.","Biography information for Alan Mak","Mr Alan Mak","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904413","904413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/510403","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote the participation of women in the Syrian peace negotiations.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904412","904412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/510404","2016-04-12","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what progress has  been made on implementation of the UN Human Rights Council Resolution 30/1 on Sri Lanka.","Biography information for Wes Streeting","Wes Streeting","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904421","904421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/511663","2016-04-13","Wales Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on Wales of measures announced in the Budget 2016.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904368","904368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/511664","2016-04-13","Wales Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, whether he has had discussions with the Welsh Government on strengthening and extending the remit of the Children's Commissioner for Wales.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904369","904369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/511665","2016-04-13","Wales Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the financial accountability of government in Wales.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904374","904374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/511666","2016-04-13","Wales Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent changes to universal credit on families in Wales.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904367","904367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/511667","2016-04-13","Wales Office","2016-03-24","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what representations he has received from the Welsh Government on the fuel duty rebate scheme.","Biography information for Peter Grant","Peter Grant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 904371","904371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485485","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of differences in mortality rates for (a) permanent and (b) temporary workers.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32249","32249"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485487","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he takes to monitor the economic effect of projects his Department has funded.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32258","32258"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485488","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of businesses that have registered for (a) VAT and (b) PAYE in each region and nation of the UK between 2010 and 2014.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32250","32250"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485489","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to make (a) apprenticeships and (b) vocational education accessible for young people with hearing impairments.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32292","32292"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485490","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of the number of public houses which have gone out of business since 1 July 2007.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32265","32265"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485492","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to ensure that people with disabilities receive support to start small business enterprises.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32309","32309"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485493","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many staff in his Department were in receipt of Continuity of Education Allowance in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15; and what the cost to his Department was of providing that allowance for staff based (i) in the UK and (ii) overseas in each such year.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32311","32311"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485494","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when he plans to respond to the recommendation in the Low Pay Commission's Spring 2016 report on the National Minimum Wage (NMW) that HM Revenue and Customs investigation of third party reports of NMW breaches be subject to a public protocol.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32327","32327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485495","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what representations his Department has (a) received and (b) made on guidance on volume controls of mobile phones and other devices using headphones.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32346","32346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485496","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information he holds on the number of private sector employment agencies in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32343","32343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485497","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the reasons are for the government policy not to support the progress of the European Commission's proposed reforms to (a) trade and defence instruments and (b) the lesser duty rule.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32344","32344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485499","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent discussions he has had with his ministerial colleagues on convening a cross-government and stakeholder working party on the application of the national minimum wage for seafarers; and when he expects that working party to meet.","Biography information for Ian Mearns","Ian Mearns","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32367","32367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485500","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how the proposed cost savings outlined in the BIS 2020 programme have been calculated; and what estimate he has made of projected savings of relocating staff from the office in Sheffield to London.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32384","32384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485501","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on the number of agency workers in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32389","32389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485503","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether his Department has undertaken a cost-benefit analysis of retaining  his Department's office at St Paul's Palace, Sheffield.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32390","32390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485504","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, which universities have opened a Confucius Institute on campus; and what guidance he has issued to those universities on relations with the Chinese government.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32445","32445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485505","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what information his Department holds on the powers of appointment of university vice-chancellors for staff working in Confucius Institutes on their university campus.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32446","32446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485507","2016-04-11","Cabinet Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what value and proportion of central government procurement was made by each department in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32388","32388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485509","2016-04-11","Cabinet Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure institutions and organisations in receipt of public funds do not express a corporate opinion on the forthcoming EU referendum.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32422","32422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485511","2016-04-11","Cabinet Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps the Government plans to take to ensure charities in receipt of public funds do not express a view on the forthcoming European Union Referendum.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32336","32336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485513","2016-04-11","Cabinet Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what steps he plans to take to help give the views of young people greater prominence in policy decisions in their community.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32234","32234"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485516","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if his Department will offer tax relief on home insurance payments for occupants of council housing.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32237","32237"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485517","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what steps he is taking to improve national minimum wage enforcement in the shipping industry.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32257","32257"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485518","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what proportion of the Tampon Tax Fund was allocated to (a) Women's Aid and (b) other women's charities in Northern Ireland; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32279","32279"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485519","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, which women's organisations in Northern Ireland received funding from the Tampon Tax Fund; what the amount was that each such organisation received; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Lady Hermon","Lady Hermon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32280","32280"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485521","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of implementation of the Fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849 on trade between US and European banks and financial service companies and their UK equivalents which include on their Board a Member of the House of Lords.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32251","32251"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485522","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.228 of Budget 2016, when he expects the new pensions guidance body to be established.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32332","32332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485524","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.228 of Budget 2016, on what date he plans to close the Money Advice Service.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32333","32333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485525","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how he assessed the levels of consumption by children of drinks products affected by the sugar levy.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32330","32330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485526","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, for what reason exemptions were granted from the sugar levy for 100 per cent fruit juice and milk; and if he will publish the evidence on which that decision was taken.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32329","32329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485528","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish and place in the Library his correspondence on the (a) sale of Government's Dividend Access Share and (b) proposed sale of Government shares in Royal Bank of Scotland since August 2015.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32361","32361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485529","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will place a full copy of Lord Justice Bingham's report Inquiry into the Supervision of The Bank of Credit and Commerce International, published in October 1992, on the closure of The Bank of Credit and Commerce International (HC 198 1992/93), in the Library.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32378","32378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485531","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.228 of Budget 2016, what the timetable is for the restructuring of the Money Advice Service, the Pensions Advisory Service and Pension Wise.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32334","32334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485532","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what advice he has received from the Office for Budget Responsibility on the effect on the economy in the event of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32317","32317"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485534","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cumulative loss in revenue to HM Treasury has been as a result of the effect of tobacco control measures over the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32263","32263"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485535","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the potential reduction in revenue to the public purse resulting from the EU Tobacco Products Directive.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32264","32264"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485536","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Office for Budget Responsibility on the potential implications of the UK withdrawing from the EU.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32404","32404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485537","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the likely effect of the Fourth Money Laundering Directive on the ability in future of members of the House of Lords to continue to serve on the boards of banks and financial services companies; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32274","32274"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485538","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 23 March 2016 to Question 31494, what recent discussions he has had with the Home Secretary on immigration policy; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32407","32407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485539","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 2.228 of Budget 2016, when he expects the new money guidance body to be established.","Biography information for Seema Malhotra","Seema Malhotra","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32331","32331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485540","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of the initial disposal of Government shares in Royal Bank of Scotland in August 2015 on (a) the share price and (b) the proposed future sale of shares.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32360","32360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485541","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what advice he has received from (a) the Governor of the Bank of England and (b) Rothschilds Bank on the proposed sale of Government shares in Royal Bank of Scotland since August 2015; and if he will place a copy of such advice in the Library.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32362","32362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485545","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make it his policy to establish a minimum price below which Government shares in Royal Bank of Scotland will not be sold.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32363","32363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485548","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what criteria he plans to use to ensure sales of Government shares in Royal Bank of Scotland maximise value for the public purse.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32364","32364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485550","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many employers in the social care sector have been found to be non-compliant with national minimum wage legislation in each of the last three years; how much was owed in arrears by each such employer to how many underpaid workers; and what the total value of penalties levied on those employers is.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32382","32382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485552","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to his visit to the Mersey Gateway on 23 April 2015, what progress has been made on ensuring support will be provided to small businesses in Runcorn and Widnes when that bridge opens in 2017 related to the cost of tolls crossing the Mersey Gateway.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32463","32463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485556","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-23","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 29 February 2016 to Question 27454, on banks, what the (a) date of, (b) details of who attended and (c) organisations represented were at each meeting.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32427","32427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485560","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to the local government finance settlement 2016-17, whether he consulted the Office for Budget Responsibility on the distribution of the transitional grant.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32457","32457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485561","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the methodology used by his Department to calculate the distribution of the Transitional Grant announced in the local government finance settlement 2016-17.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32459","32459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485562","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 9 March 2016 to Question 29831, on how many occasions his Department has provided advice and support upon request from local authorities who wish to undertake post-implementation value for money assessments.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32297","32297"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485564","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate he has made of the number of disabled people living in social housing who will be affected by the cap to local housing allowance.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32321","32321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485565","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, with reference to page 2 of Budget 2016, whether the £3.5 billion savings to public spending to be achieved by 2012-20 will affect the four year funding settlement to local councils announced by his Department in December 2015.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32326","32326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485566","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how he plans that the section 31 grant to compensate councils for the extension of small business rate relief will be funded.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32229","32229"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485569","2016-04-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the likely effect of the Fourth Money Laundering Directive on the ability in future of Members of the House of Lords to continue to serve on the board of the BBC; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32275","32275"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485571","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he plans to take to ensure that no bank accounts of military personnel are closed as a result of the Fourth Money Laundering Directive while they are on active service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32276","32276"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485573","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what reports he has received on which other countries plan to deploy troops in Libya.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32273","32273"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485574","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to deploy the armed forces in Libya to provide security for the Libyan Government of National Accord.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32425","32425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485575","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans his Department has to deploy the armed forces in Libya to train the Libyan army.","Biography information for Adam Holloway","Adam Holloway","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32426","32426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485577","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many members of the armed forces have been employed specialising in the repair and maintenance of survival equipment in the RAF in the last twenty years; and how many former such staff have (a) received a medical discharge and (b) submitted a claim for compensation on the grounds of occupational related ill-health.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32375","32375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485578","2016-04-12","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what representations he has received on British service personnel being served food which contains mould and maggots; and what monitoring his Department undertakes to ensure that all food served to such service personnel is of a satisfactory standard.","Biography information for Sir Greg Knight","Sir Greg Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32298","32298"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485579","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the extent to which members of the armed forces work with trichloroethylene in the line of duty and the suitability of existing health and safety arrangements when this takes place.","Biography information for Kirsten Oswald","Kirsten  Oswald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32245","32245"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485580","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which Ministry of Defence live ammunition ranges have safety wardens present on site.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32319","32319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485581","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential implications for safety on live ammunition ranges of changes in the numbers of safety wardens present on site.","Biography information for Kate Hollern","Kate Hollern","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32320","32320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485582","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many staff in his Department were in receipt of Continuity of Education Allowance in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15; and what the cost to his Department was of providing that allowance for staff based (i) in the UK and (ii) overseas in each such year.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32312","32312"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485583","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what further investment he plans to provide for the hardened aircraft shelters used by the Quick Reaction Alert at the former RAF base at Leuchars.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32260","32260"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485584","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many Army Air Corps pilots have resigned due to his Department's plans to recover over-payment of flying pay; how many of those pilots (a) are currently serving and (b) have retired; what assessment he has made of the effect on (i) staffing levels and (ii) the effectiveness of that corps; whether any of those pilots affected have been subject to disciplinary proceedings due to non-repayment of such over-payments; what the value is of such over payments; over what period such over-payments relate to; and if he will make it his policy to not recover such over-payments.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32302","32302"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485585","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how the UK economy has benefited from defence technology research and development.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32304","32304"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485586","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if she will make it her policy to provide long-term funding for the UCL Centre for Holocaust Education.","Biography information for Keir Starmer","Keir Starmer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32322","32322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485588","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether it is her policy that all children in households in receipt of Universal Credit will be entitled to free school meals.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32323","32323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485590","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department is taking to ensure that (a) female and (b) other students are encouraged to take modules in entrepreneurship and business mentoring.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32328","32328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485591","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to encourage nurseries to teach early language skills.","Biography information for Mr Khalid Mahmood","Mr Khalid Mahmood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32246","32246"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485592","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 11 March 2016 to Question 29817, whether her Department holds information on the number of children who have been further assessed after the strength and difficulties questionnaire score suggested that there may be a problem with that child's mental health.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32295","32295"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485594","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps she is taking to ensure that local authorities are required to take action on education and early years settings that intentionally exclude disabled children and do not meet their legal duties to such children under the Equality Act 2010.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32243","32243"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485596","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment she has made of the conclusion of the report from the charity Sense, Making the case for play, published in February 2016, that a misguided interpretation and approach to health and safety is creating a barrier to accessing play settings and activities for children with multiple needs.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32244","32244"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485597","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how much her Department has paid to Morning Lane Associates (a) directly and (b) through other organisations in (i) 2012-13, (ii) 2013-14, (iii) 2014-15 and (iv) 2015-16.","Biography information for Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","Mrs Emma Lewell-Buck","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32370","32370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485598","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps her Department has taken to provide additional support for educational studies to young carers.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32423","32423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485599","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence her Department holds on the relationship between the A-level grades achieved by prospective teachers and their later performance in the classroom.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32399","32399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485600","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what requirements or guidelines her Department issues on the reference or inclusion of digital and online resources in the curriculum (a) in general and (b) for students without access to broadband at home.","Biography information for Chi Onwurah","Chi Onwurah","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32409","32409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485602","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent guidance she has issued to schools about sexting; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32441","32441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485603","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, who has attended meetings of the Child Protection Task Force and on what dates; and what action has been decided at those meetings.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32442","32442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485604","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, if her Department will issue guidance to schools on the terminology used for children who do not reach the national standard grade under the proposed reforms to Key Stage 2.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32432","32432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485606","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of pupil premium on ensuring children who are classed as behind reach their expected grades at Key Stages 1 to 4.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32434","32434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485607","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment her Department has made of the effectiveness of the year 7 catch-up premium in raising pupil attainment at GCSE level.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32433","32433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485608","2016-04-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make it the policy of the Government that electricity customers across the UK should pay the same for electricity transportation.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32443","32443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485609","2016-04-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what the cost per kilowatt hour is of electricity transportation charged to consumers in (a) Orkney, (b) the north of Scotland and (c) the south of Scotland.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32398","32398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485610","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what funding her Department has allocated for projects to prevent flooding in Burnley and Padiham.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32236","32236"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485611","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the levels of toxic heavy metals, cadmium and mercury, in the sea on the brains and organs of pilot whales in 2012.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32259","32259"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485612","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, which flood defence maintenance works were undertaken in Middlesbrough South and East Cleveland constituency in each year since 2010; and what the cost to the public purse was of each of those works.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32242","32242"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485613","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps she is taking to ensure that public bodies under the Environmental Protection Act 1990 comply with their duty to pick up roadside litter.","Biography information for Sir Gary Streeter","Mr Gary Streeter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32247","32247"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485614","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how much her Department has paid in fines for what reasons to the EU in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32318","32318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485615","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many staff employed by the Environment Agency earn salaries of more than £100,000 per year.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32301","32301"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485617","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what the plans she has to reintroduce tick treatment for pet animals returning to the UK.","Biography information for Mr Mark Prisk","Mr Mark Prisk","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32374","32374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485618","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps her Department has taken in response to the Resolution of the House of 11 February on conservation of sea bass and the effect of related EU measures on the UK recreational fishing industry.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32444","32444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485619","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the letter from the National Security Adviser to the Joint Committee on the National Security Strategy of 10 March 2016, how many GCHQ staff were (a) recruited to and (b) completed the GCHQ cyber apprenticeship scheme in each year since 2012.","Biography information for Margaret Beckett","Margaret Beckett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32453","32453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485620","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to the letter from the National Security Adviser to the Joint Committee on the National Security Strategy of 10 March 2016, how many GCHQ staff have been (a) recruited to and (b) completed the CyberFirst scheme.","Biography information for Margaret Beckett","Margaret Beckett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32452","32452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485621","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, which academic and research bodies, which receive funding from the EU, are routinely used for research on the EU in departmental and ministerial briefings.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32440","32440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485622","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will estimate the proportion of rebel ground forces in Syria which could be considered moderate.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32307","32307"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485623","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, how many staff in his Department were in receipt of Continuity of Education Allowance in (a) 2012-13, (b) 2013-14 and (c) 2014-15; and what the cost to his Department was of providing that allowance for staff based (i) in the UK and (ii) overseas in each such year.","Biography information for Mr Douglas Carswell","Mr Douglas Carswell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32313","32313"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485624","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with the UN Special Adviser on the Prevention of Genocide on atrocities committed by Daesh.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32285","32285"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485625","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to his oral contribution of 12 January 2016, Official Report, column 697, whether UK personnel provided a quick check on whether the reported airstrike in Yemen on a market place in the Hajjah Governorate had broken international humanitarian law.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32281","32281"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485626","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what advice his Department has sought from the Swiss government on best practice in concluding a trade deal with (a) Japan, (b) China and (c) other non-EU states.","Biography information for Henry Smith","Henry Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32248","32248"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485627","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether his Department has made an assessment of the financial consequences of the EU sanctions on Russia on Serbia.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32252","32252"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485628","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has had discussions with his Serbian counterpart on the financial consequences of the EU sanctions on Russia on Serbia.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32253","32253"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485631","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the oral Answer of 12 January 2016, Official Report, column 697, what assessment he has made of whether evidence of the reported airstrike in Yemen on a market place in the Hajjah Governorate provides grounds for determining that international humanitarian law has been broken.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32282","32282"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485632","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, with reference to reports of his remarks in Ankara in January 2016, what recent estimate he has made of the number of UK citizens who have (a) entered and since left, (b) entered and remained in and (c) been prevented from entering (i) Syria and (ii) Iraq since April 2013.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32283","32283"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485633","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the incidence and nature of human rights violations in South Sudan.","Biography information for Hilary Benn","Hilary Benn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32284","32284"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485634","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the effect of the Common Agricultural Policy on the level of poverty among farmers in Africa.","Biography information for Mr David Nuttall","Mr David Nuttall","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32240","32240"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485635","2016-04-11","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment his Department has made of the human rights situation in Indonesia.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32231","32231"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485636","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he plans to encourage uptake of sight tests amongst children and adults with learning disabilities in the Learning Disability Action Plan.","Biography information for Maria Caulfield","Maria Caulfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32230","32230"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485637","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the number of patients who will have to use other hospitals if Calderstones Partnership NHS Foundation Trust is closed.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32238","32238"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485638","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to support children with Kawasaki disease.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32239","32239"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485639","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2016 to Question 30456, what proportion of (a) primiparous and (b) multiparous women are discharged from hospital less than 24 hours after giving birth.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32296","32296"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485640","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions his Department has had with NHS England on increasing the amount of funding available to GP practices.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32278","32278"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485641","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent assessment his Department has made of the effect of the use of steroids on the physical and mental health of people using such drugs.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32289","32289"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485642","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to increase the retention rate of doctors working in general practice.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32290","32290"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485643","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs retired in Halton constituency in the last 12 months; and how many GPs in that constituency have given notice of their intention to retire in 2016.","Biography information for Derek Twigg","Derek Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32291","32291"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485644","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the time taken to transfer women from abortion clinics to hospitals in cases of serious complications following abortions; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32305","32305"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485645","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will postpone the start date for the introduction of standardised packaging on tobacco products in order to undertake an assessment of the implications of the post-implementation review of a similar measure in Australia on his policies in this area.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32266","32266"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485646","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to NHS England and clinical commissioning groups on the account they should take of future residential developments with regard to GP service provision.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32267","32267"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485647","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what statutory duty there is on individual general practitioners to provide notice of closure of a GP practice to NHS England or clinical commissioning group.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32268","32268"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485648","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) MRI machines (b) CT Scanners (c) PET-CT scanners (d) Linear accelerators and (e) Robotic surgery systems in use in each NHS trust are older than ten years.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32314","32314"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485649","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2016 to Question 23756, what proportion of the cost of backlog maintenance for each level of assessed risk in each NHS organisation relates to (a) MRI machines (b) CT Scanners (c) PET-CT scanners (d) Linear accelerators and (e) Robotic surgery systems.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32315","32315"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485650","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 27 January 2016 to Question 23756, what assessment his Department has made of the adequacy of funds within NHS organisations to eradicate backlog maintenance repairs which are considered to be high risk.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32316","32316"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485651","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the effects on the incidence of hearing loss of mobile phones and other similar devices which do not have a volume control; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32345","32345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485652","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that women are appropriately transferred from abortion clinics to hospitals at the earliest point in the case of emergencies.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32356","32356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485653","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that all women undergoing abortions are given the opportunity to decide on disposal arrangements following a termination.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32357","32357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485654","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2016 on Question 30222, what further work in the collection and publication of data on secondary breast cancer by hospital trusts in England is being scoped.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32368","32368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485655","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received about concerns identified by the Care Quality Commission at a British Pregnancy Advisory Service abortion clinic in Richmond; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32379","32379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485656","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 16 March 2016 on Question 30222, when he expects that data on secondary breast cancer will be complete.","Biography information for Heidi Alexander","Heidi Alexander","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32369","32369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485657","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure accurate and early diagnosis of Kawasaki disease.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32354","32354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485658","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what guidance his Department provides to medical practitioners on the similarities between Kawasaki disease and scarlet fever.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32355","32355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485659","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that safeguarding policies at British Pregnancy Advisory Service abortion clinics reflect national guidance on sexual exploitation of children and risks of female genital mutilation.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32358","32358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485660","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate his Department has made of the proportion of the NHS budget spent on general practice in each of the last five years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32366","32366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485661","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on Care Quality Commission findings that it was policy for a British Pregnancy Advisory Service clinic in Richmond to act outside of the licence for an anaesthetic; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32359","32359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485662","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many nurses (a) left the profession and (b) qualified in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32460","32460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485663","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of mental health trusts (a) offer female patients a choice of a female care coordinator, (b) conduct routine enquiries with female patients about experiences of abuse and violence and (c) provide gender-sensitive care.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32451","32451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485664","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will take steps to ensure that community pharmacies are not adversely affected by the localising of clinical pharmacists in GP surgeries.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32438","32438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485665","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2016 to Question 23217, on local transformation plans, for what reasons not all plans have been published online; and when he expects all those plans to be available online.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32447","32447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485666","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with community pharmacies on the proposals for a pharmacy access scheme.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32435","32435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485667","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 22 January 2016 to Question 30262, what plans Health Education England has to reform funding not related to the bursary scheme for postgraduate training in (a) child psychotherapy, (b) clinical psychology and (c) improving access to psychological therapies from 2017.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32448","32448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485668","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he plans to take to provide information to pharmacies on proposed changes to the community pharmacy sector.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32436","32436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485669","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of mental health trusts provide mental health services and support by female staff in female only settings; what funding is provided for such services; and what minimum standards are required for training, supervision and support for staff and volunteers providing those services.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32449","32449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485670","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with the Pharmaceutical Services Negotiating Committee.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32437","32437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485671","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department has undertaken a gender impact assessment of its mental health strategies.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32450","32450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485672","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the direct effect of drug eluting stents on the reduction of lower limb amputations.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32373","32373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485673","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to reduce regional variation of access to (a) minimally invasive technology and (b) drug eluting stents designed to tackle peripheral arterial disease.","Biography information for Derek Thomas","Derek Thomas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32371","32371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485674","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the availability in the UK of clinical expertise to treat scarlet fever and Kawasaki disease.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32365","32365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485676","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what statutory duty there is on NHS England or clinical commissioning groups to provide notice of closure of a GP practice to its patients.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32269","32269"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485677","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what recent discussions he has had with British Pregnancy Advisory Service (BPAS) about safety concerns in the Care Quality Commission Report on the BPAS abortion clinic in Richmond.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32400","32400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485678","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many paramedics have moved from that role to that of a hospital-based practitioner in each of the last five years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32411","32411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485679","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to (a) better identify visitors to the UK from other EEA countries who are being treated in NHS hospitals and (b) ensure that such visitors' home countries are charged for their treatment.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32403","32403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485681","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure compliance with safety regulations and basic standards of hygiene at abortion clinics.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32401","32401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485683","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether a visitor to the UK from another European Economic area state who is not in possession of an EHIC card can register as a temporary patient with a GP practice and receive treatment free of charge.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32408","32408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485685","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if will he take steps to ensure that British Pregnancy Advisory Service abortion clinics do not act outside the licence for anaesthetics and do not share single doses between patients.","Biography information for Robert Flello","Robert Flello","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32402","32402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485686","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what funding he plans to provide to local authorities for the provision of pre-exposure prophylaxis.","Biography information for Andrew Gwynne","Andrew Gwynne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32424","32424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485687","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the potential (a) effectiveness and (b) value for money of providing pre-exposure prophylaxis for HIV.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32412","32412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485688","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to improve recruitment and retention in the ambulance service.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32405","32405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485689","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure that pre-exposure prophylaxis commissioning is targeted at people most at risk of HIV infection.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32413","32413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485690","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effect that changes in qualification requirements for studying a BSc in paramedicine will have on recruitment into that profession.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32406","32406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485691","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many people were diagnosed with HIV in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32414","32414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485692","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with whom NHS England's specialised commissioning service has consulted in the past 18 months in preparation for the planned public consultation on pre-exposure prophylaxis.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32415","32415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485693","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate how many at-risk men in which areas will (a) not receive and (b) receive pre-exposure prophylaxis for HIV in each of the next five years.","Biography information for Sir Peter Bottomley","Sir Peter Bottomley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32416","32416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485694","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what representations he has received on the Royal College of Nursing's report, Connect for Change: an update on learning disability services in England, published in February 2016; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32418","32418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485695","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2016 to Question 30500, what assistance is provided by National Crime Agency CEOP Command staff to local force investigations into child sexual abuse.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32429","32429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485696","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the contribution of the UK's membership of the EU to the UK's work in identifying and detaining criminals.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32439","32439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485697","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2016 to Question 30500, what the alternative arrangements are that provide funding for National Crime Agency investigations into non-recent child sexual abuse.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32430","32430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485698","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what estimate her Department has made of the total cost of resettling refugees from Syria in each of the next five years; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32410","32410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485700","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Tier 2 intra-company transfers for what roles or job descriptions were issued to UK companies in each of the last five years; and what salary each such transferee received.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32376","32376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485702","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the potential effect of reductions in international student numbers on employment.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32270","32270"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485703","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what criteria she uses to assess a bid from a metro mayor to assume the additional role of police and crime commissioner.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32271","32271"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485704","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March 2016 to Question 31677, what the average salary is of people awarded Tier 2 (ICT) visas to work in the IT industry; and how many such visas have been awarded in each pay band in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32428","32428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485705","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March 2016 Question 31677, how many Tier 2 (ICT) visa applications were denied because the Certificate of Sponsorship does not specify a salary of at least £28,400 in the last three years.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32349","32349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485706","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether, when considering whether to acquire a bulk personal dataset from another government department under the Investigatory Powers Bill, she plans to consult the Secretary of State for that department.","Biography information for Dr Sarah Wollaston","Dr Sarah Wollaston","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32335","32335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485707","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March 2016 to Question 31677, what checks are undertaken to ensure that the terms of a Tier 2 (ICT) visa Certificate of Sponsorship are adhered to.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32350","32350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485708","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March 2016 to Question 31677, what the penalties are for an employer who has issued a Certificate of Sponsorship but does not adhere to the stated job description and salary.","Biography information for Ruth Smeeth","Ruth Smeeth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32351","32351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485709","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Tier 2 intra-company visas were issued for the IT industry in each of the last 10 years.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32341","32341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485711","2016-04-11","Cabinet Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what assessment he has made of the contribution of the UK's membership of the EU to the protection of the UK's critical national information infrastructure from cyber-attack.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32325","32325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485712","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the contribution of the UK's membership of the EU to the UK's work in (a) preventing and (b) identifying and detaining terrorists.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32324","32324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485714","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment she has made of the contribution of the UK's membership of the EU to the Government's aims of tackling terrorist and criminal networks.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32303","32303"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485715","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what mechanisms her Department has in place to determine the geographic distribution of asylum seekers awaiting decisions on asylum applications.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32286","32286"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485716","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions his Department has had with police forces on the level of enforcement of legislation on smoking in vehicles with children present; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Robert Syms","Mr Robert Syms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32262","32262"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485717","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what advice her Department provides to special constables seeking to claim for loss of earnings due to injuries sustained while on duty.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32299","32299"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485719","2016-04-12","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what support is provided to special constables injured on duty to support recovery from such injuries.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32300","32300"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485720","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to reduce the number of asylum seekers placed in hotels while awaiting decisions on asylum applications.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32287","32287"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485723","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many leave to remain applications have been refused as a result of the good character test in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32232","32232"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485724","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many asylum applications have been refused as a result of the good character test in each year for which information is available.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32233","32233"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485725","2016-04-11","House of Commons Commission","2016-03-23","To ask the Rt. hon. Member for Carshalton and Wallington representing the House of Commons Commission, how much it costs to post a franked envelope from the House of Commons.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32338","32338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485726","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent assessment she has made of the humanitarian situation in Yemen; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Evans","Chris Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32340","32340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485727","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 31131, for what reason the amount of financial assistance her Department has provided to UNOCHA for its work in Libya since 1 April 2015 was not supplied in that Answer.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32261","32261"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485728","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what steps she is taking to assist the Nigerian government to support access for internally displaced children in that country to (a) education and (b) healthcare.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32306","32306"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485729","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many full-time members of staff her Department employs in renegotiating tax treaties with developing countries.","Biography information for Imran Hussain","Imran Hussain","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32391","32391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485730","2016-04-12","Department for International Development","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, when the UK is joining the EU Consortium to support the construction of small-scale infrastructure in Area C; and whether such construction has received planning permission from the Israeli government.","Biography information for Mr Nigel Evans","Mr Nigel Evans","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32417","32417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485731","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what proportion of non-combat related deaths in the UK military were given an inquiry by jury in the last five years.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32308","32308"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485732","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many appeal hearings at the First-tier Tribunal (Social Security and Child Support) were (a) withdrawn and (b) adjourned as a result of the Department for Work and Pensions not sending a representative in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32293","32293"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485733","2016-04-11","Leader of the House","2016-03-23","To ask the Leader of the House, if he will make it the policy of the Government not to bring forward regulations seeking to implement EU Directives until the outcome of the EU referendum is known.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32458","32458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485734","2016-04-11","Prime Minister","2016-03-23","To ask the Prime Minister, whether representatives of the UK's Crown Dependencies and Overseas Territories will be invited to the anti-corruption summit in May.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32393","32393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485735","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25958, when he expects the revised guidance on the national minimum wage for seafarers to be published; and when he last discussed that matter with the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32385","32385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485736","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the adequacy of bus services in Middlesbrough, Redcar and Cleveland and Teesside.","Biography information for Tom Blenkinsop","Tom Blenkinsop","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32397","32397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485737","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what evidence he has received to demonstrate  that the construction of Phase One of High Speed 2 will not breach the requirements of Directive 2008/50/EC on ambient air quality and cleaner air for Europe.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32387","32387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485738","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make an assessment of whether the air quality objectives set out in Annex II of Directive 2008/50/EC on ambient air quality and cleaner air for Europe will be breached in any location scheduled to be affected by the construction of Phase One of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32386","32386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485739","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential for driverless cars to improve the efficiency of use of road space on motorways.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32419","32419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485740","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential for driverless cars to reduce motorway collisions.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32420","32420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485741","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has made an assessment of the potential for driverless cars to increase energy efficiency.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32421","32421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485743","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, how many public and private hospitals lie under the Heathrow final approach flight paths; and how many such hospitals would lie under the proposed flightpaths should the third runway be approved.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32254","32254"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485744","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the Heathrow Hub runway extension is being considered as an alternative to a third runway.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32255","32255"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485745","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what he expects the decision-making process after any announcement regarding a third runway at Heathrow to be.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32256","32256"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485746","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the construction activity required to construct Phase One of High Speed 2 will result in any household experiencing carbon monoxide levels in excess of the thresholds for that substance detailed in European Directive 2008/50/EC on ambient air quality and cleaner air for Europe.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32241","32241"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485748","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer to Question 31603, from which funding stream the additional  £130 million funding for repair of roads and bridges damaged by Storms Desmond and Eva will be taken.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32342","32342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485749","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25277, when he expects the memorandum of understanding to be agreed.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32352","32352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485750","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 9 February 2016 to Question 25276, on unmanned air vehicles: safety, when he expects his Department to complete the detailed analysis of risks posed by drones.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32353","32353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485751","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will assess the alternative Colne Valley tunnelling scheme for High Speed 2 as proposed by Hillingdon Council; and if he will meet the hon. Member for Richmond Park, the Leader of Hillingdon Council and the hon. Member for Uxbridge and Ruislip Northwood and Pinner to discuss that alternative.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32310","32310"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485752","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many employment support allowance claimants in (a) Scotland (b) Glasgow and (c) Glasgow Central constituency stopped claiming that allowance after participation in the Work Programme.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32348","32348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485753","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 14 March 2016 to Question 29818, what assessment he has made of the effect of a four-year freeze in local housing allowance (LHA) rates on people that rely on LHA if the cost of renting in the private rented sector continues to rise; and whether the four-year freeze will disproportionally affect those living in houses with more than four bedrooms.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32377","32377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485754","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on European Social Fund allocations for the Work programme.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32347","32347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485755","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people in Wythenshawe and Sale East constituency who are existing universal credit claimants and who are in work will have their universal credit decreased as a result of changes to the work allowance taking effect in April 2016.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32339","32339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485756","2016-04-11","Cabinet Office","2016-03-23","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many disabled people have found employment in the (a) private, (b) public and (c) charity sector in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32337","32337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485757","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations he has received on the effectiveness of the Pension Service helpline.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32235","32235"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485758","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment his Department has made of the ability of prospective claimants to complete the online application form for universal credit; and if he will estimate the number of eligible claimants who have failed to claim due to the complexity of that application form.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32228","32228"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485759","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 29 February 2016 to Question 28404, on Independent Living Fund, if he will publish (a) the timescale and (b) the terms of reference of the research which the Government plans to conduct.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32277","32277"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485760","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how long after being found to be ineligible for employment and support allowance as a result of a work capability assessment can an individual submit a new claim.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32294","32294"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485761","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how much his Department spent on consultancy costs examining possible proposals for the future of the Access to Work scheme.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32288","32288"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485762","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent estimate his Department has made of the number of people with a (a) physical disability, (b) mental disability and (c) physical and mental disability in (i) the UK and (ii) Twickenham constituency.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32462","32462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485763","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether his Department sets targets related to the closing of benefit claims of people referred to the work programme.","Biography information for Alison Thewliss","Alison Thewliss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32431","32431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485764","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people (a) of working age, (b) of retirement age and (c) younger than working age are in receipt of (i) disability living allowance and (ii) personal independence payments in (A) the UK and (B) Twickenham constituency.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32461","32461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485766","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 1.7 of his Department's response to the consultation on aids and appliances and the daily living component of personal independence payments, published in March 2016, if he will publish the equality analysis referred to in that paragraph.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32456","32456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485767","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to paragraph 4.10 of his Department's response to its consultation on aids and appliances and the daily living component of personal independence payment, published in March 2016, if he will publish the raw data referred to in that paragraph; and whether that data was subject to peer review.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32455","32455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485768","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will publish (a) the criteria used to select organisations invited to attend and (b) the organisations that attended personal independence payments consultation stakeholder events in January 2016.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32454","32454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485769","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will raise the threshold for carer's allowance to take into account increases in the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Simon Hart","Simon Hart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32372","32372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485770","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what discussions his Department has had with Compact Voice about the duration of the formal personal independent payment consultation.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32383","32383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485771","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average value is of a personal independence payment in (a) the UK and (b) Twickenham constituency.","Biography information for Dr Tania Mathias","Dr Tania Mathias","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32381","32381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485772","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to his Department's consultation on aids and appliances and the daily living component of personal independence payments, Cm 9171, if he will publish the impact assessment prepared for the five options in that consultation.","Biography information for Sue Hayman","Sue Hayman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32380","32380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485773","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the adequacy and timeliness of information given to women born in the 1950s of changes to the age at which they become eligible for the state pension; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Damian Green","Damian Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32272","32272"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485774","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease receive personal independence  payment at the (a) daily living standard, (b) daily living enhanced, (c) mobility standard and (d) mobility enhanced rate.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32392","32392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485775","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2016 to Question 30116, what proportion of job seekers allowance claimants who received a sanction in the past year did not subsequently resume their benefit claim.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32396","32396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485776","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with Parkinson's disease receive attendance allowance.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32394","32394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/485777","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-23","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants have found work through the Universal Jobmatch system.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32395","32395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484304","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the carbon emissions of UK forces operating abroad were in the most recent year for which figures are available.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32084","32084"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484305","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what attempts have been made to clean up contamination from bullets and shells used by UK forces in (a) Afghanistan, (b) Iraq and (c) Libya; what the cost has been of that work to date; and which UK companies have been awarded contracts to carry out that remediation.","Biography information for Paul Flynn","Paul Flynn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32085","32085"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484306","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what progress has been made on reaching a settlement with Gurkha soldiers who retired before 2000.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32156","32156"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484307","2016-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions she has had with her counterpart in the Northern Ireland Executive on the illegal dog trade.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32157","32157"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484308","2016-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, when she expects to have put in place comprehensive management plans for each of the existing Marine Conservation Zones.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32091","32091"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484309","2016-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if she will make an assessment of the potential merits of deploying ocean-going drones to help catch illegal trawlers in Marine Conservation Zones in place of staffed patrol vessels.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32113","32113"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484310","2016-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what resources she plans to allocate to enforcing comprehensive management plans in current and future Marine Conservation Zones.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32114","32114"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484311","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, when he expects effective processes to be in place to allow the issuing of fixed penalty notices to people who are smoking in cars when children are present.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32147","32147"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484312","2016-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate her Department has made of the potential costs of making necessary improvements to flood defences in Carlisle since the recent floods affecting that area.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32136","32136"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484313","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what discussions he has had with the Home Secretary and Secretary of State for Justice on establishing effective processes to allow fixed penalty notices to be issued to people smoking in cars with children present and the associated fines to be collected.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32153","32153"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484314","2016-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will seek evidence from (a) the NUM, (b) Unite, (c) Hargreaves Services plc, (d) Banks Mining, (e) Celtic Energy and (f) Miller Agent in her Department's consultation on the future of coal-fired power stations; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32067","32067"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484315","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2016 to Question 24713, if he will apply to the EU's Globalisation Adjustment Fund for funding for the UK steel industry.","Biography information for Stephen Kinnock","Stephen Kinnock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32135","32135"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484316","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many personnel who have made a claim under the Mercantile Marine Scheme as part of the War Pension Scheme have stated that their injury or illness was a result of deployment to Operation Granby whilst working in the Royal Fleet Auxiliary.","Biography information for Corri Wilson","Corri Wilson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32104","32104"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484317","2016-04-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what (a) evidence her Department holds and (b) research her Department has undertaken on the effect of smart meters on people with electromagnetic hypersensitivity.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32207","32207"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484318","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 22 March 2016 to Question 29759, which paragraphs of the White Paper, The Best of Both Worlds, disclose what data the Government used to assess the effect of its policy (a) to restrict the payment of child benefit to EU nationals resident in the UK in respect of their children resident outside the UK and (b) to restrict entitlement of some EU nationals to tax credits.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32221","32221"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484319","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 29775, in what format information is held on the value of child benefit claims in respect of children living in another EEA country or Switzerland.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32222","32222"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484320","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 30132, on repatriation: EEA Nationals, how many of those people who were served with administrative removal papers in 2014 are still in the UK; and how many of those people who were forcibly removed have since returned to the UK.","Biography information for Sir Christopher Chope","Mr Christopher Chope","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32223","32223"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484321","2016-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what steps her Department plan to take in response to the key themes set out in the discussion paper published by Ofgem in September 2015.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32138","32138"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484322","2016-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what plans she has to ensure that Smart Energy GB takes steps to reduce instances of engineers having to make more than one visit to an address because a customer was not at home.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32139","32139"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484323","2016-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, what her policy is on making hybrid-storage-renewables systems eligible for future Contract for Difference rounds.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32140","32140"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484324","2016-03-24","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, how her Department assesses the likely effectiveness of alternatives to in-home displays in changing consumer behaviour when applications for derogations to provide such alternatives are considered.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32126","32126"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484325","2016-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps to permit the European External Action Service to press for the release of Andargachew Tsege in Ethiopia.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32154","32154"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484326","2016-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to secure the release of Andargachew Tsege in Ethiopia.","Biography information for Matthew Pennycook","Matthew Pennycook","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32155","32155"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484327","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2016 to Question 27887, if he will publish a list of all those planning appeals allowed in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32210","32210"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484328","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 2 March 2016 to Question 27886, if he will publish a list of the planning appeals which were recovered in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32209","32209"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484329","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GP surgeries have a capped patient list in Leeds East constituency.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32206","32206"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484330","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many full-time equivalent GPs were employed in general practices in Leeds East constituency in (a) 2009-10, (b) 2010-11, (c) 2011-12, (d) 2012-13 and (e) 2013-14.","Biography information for Richard Burgon","Richard Burgon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32205","32205"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484331","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will publish the review carried out by McKinsey and Company into his Department's budget.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32189","32189"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484332","2016-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2016 to Question 29982, on local plans, which local authorities fall into each of the four categories of authority.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32134","32134"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484333","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, under what criteria local authorities will be compensated for the change in the updating of business rates from RPI to CPI.","Biography information for Mr Clive Betts","Mr Clive Betts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32161","32161"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484334","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what estimate he has made of the amount spent by the NHS on locum doctors in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32190","32190"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484335","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, if he will estimate the number of qualified doctors required in the NHS who are (a) GPs and (b) working in hospitals.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32191","32191"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484336","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what guidance his Department has given to Southampton City Council on the level of funding that will be available for discretionary housing payment in future years.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32200","32200"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484337","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the discretionary housing payments scheme in preventing households in exceptional circumstances having to pay the under-occupancy penalty.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32198","32198"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484338","2016-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps he plans to take to ensure that people in local authority areas with a larger ageing population do not have to pay disproportionately higher council tax as a result of the social care precept.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32196","32196"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484339","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps his Department plans to take after the new terms and conditions for doctors come into effect to encourage people to take up a career in medicine.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32197","32197"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484340","2016-03-24","Department for International Development","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what proportion of overseas development assistance was spent by departments other than her Department in each of the last six years; and what estimate her Department has made of that proportion for each year until 2019-20.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32101","32101"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484341","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) training, (b) financial and (c) materiel support his Department is providing to the Somali National Army.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32102","32102"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484342","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what (a) training and (b) materiel support is being provided by his Department to Yazidi militia forces.","Biography information for Stephen Doughty","Stephen Doughty","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32103","32103"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484343","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps he is taking to reduce the disability employment gap.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32066","32066"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484345","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on (a) English airports and (b) aviation connectivity of the devolution of Air Passenger Duty.","Biography information for Andrew Bridgen","Andrew Bridgen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32137","32137"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484346","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the rationale was for the reduction in the dairy food group from 15 to eight per cent in the revised Eatwell Guide; and on what scientific evidence the new recommendations on dairy consumption are based.","Biography information for Neil Parish","Neil Parish","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32093","32093"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484347","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what recent discussions she has had with her European counterparts on changes to the rules of the Dublin Regulation.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32141","32141"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484348","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable is for the European Commission's review of the Dublin Regulation.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32142","32142"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484349","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to the findings in the Epilepsy Society's report, Premature mortality and avoidable deaths in epilepsy, published in March 2016, on the proportion of sudden and unexpected epilepsy-related deaths that were avoidable with appropriate treatment and better access to speciality care, if he will commission a National Clinical Audit on epilepsy-related deaths.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32057","32057"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484350","2016-03-24","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many former workers of Remploy factories in each Parliamentary constituency are (a) looking for work, (b) in work, (c) retired, (d) in receipt of employment and support allowance and (e) in receipt of jobseeker's allowance.","Biography information for Ann Clwyd","Ann Clwyd","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32065","32065"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484351","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 16 February 2016 to Question 26010, when he plans to establish a reading room for hon. Members to access Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership documents.","Biography information for Julie Elliott","Julie Elliott","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32109","32109"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484352","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many SMART awards have been made to companies in Cambridge in each year since the introduction of that scheme.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32058","32058"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484353","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make an assessment of the effect of ring fencing funding from his Department for the Global Challenges Fund on other scientific research for which his Department provides funding.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32059","32059"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484354","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what assessment he has made of the effect on small and medium-sized enterprises of the decision to replace research grants for companies with loans.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32060","32060"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484355","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, for what reasons applicants for the fifth round of the SMART scheme will not be able to apply for a sixth round as initially advised.","Biography information for Daniel Zeichner","Daniel Zeichner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32061","32061"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484356","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the household median net income after the deduction of income tax and national insurance was for (a) all working-age adults, (b) working-age adults without children and (c) working-age adults with children, (i) including and (ii) excluding individuals in households without household earnings on the last date for which figures are available.","Biography information for Baroness Ritchie of Downpatrick","Ms Margaret Ritchie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32108","32108"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484357","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what his policy is on (a) setting a fixed price for Energy Performance Certificates and (b) ensuring that Energy Performance Certificates are valid for more than 10 years.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32184","32184"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484358","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that every property has an Energy Performance Certificate by 2020.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32182","32182"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484359","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what recent discussions his Department has had with the utility companies on contributions to the cost of Energy Performance Certificates.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32183","32183"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484360","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to maintain the Royal Irish Aftercare Service in support of veterans of Operation Banner in Northern Ireland.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32169","32169"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484361","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what funding he plans to allocate to the Royal Irish Aftercare Service in the next financial year.","Biography information for Sir Jeffrey M. Donaldson","Mr Jeffrey M. Donaldson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32170","32170"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484362","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of the three million apprenticeships planned by 2020 are expected to be at (a) degree and (b) masters level.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32224","32224"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484363","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether Equivalent or Lower Level Qualifications are exempted under (a) degree and (b) Masters level apprenticeships.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32225","32225"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484364","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate he has made of how much European Social Fund funding will be allocated to local enterprise partnerships by the end of March (a) 2017 and (b) 2018.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32227","32227"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484365","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 8 February 2016 to Question 25741, what criteria the Government plans to use to allocate the funds secured from the European Social Fund for the period 2014-2020.","Biography information for Gordon Marsden","Gordon Marsden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32226","32226"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484366","2016-03-24","Department for Education","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that examination marking is consistent and objective.","Biography information for Kevin Hollinrake","Kevin Hollinrake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32124","32124"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484367","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what recent representations he has received on commissioning an inquiry into casualised employment practices in UK universities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32172","32172"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484368","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether the money allocated to northern road infrastructure in Budget 2016, is in addition to £800 million allocated to the North West Road Infrastructure Programme.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32162","32162"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484369","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when he intends to reply to Question 31430, on Antisemitism, tabled on 16 March 2016 for named day answer on 21 March 2016.","Biography information for Richard Burden","Richard Burden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32163","32163"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484370","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.293 of Budget 2016, how his Department plans to support the establishment of a Life Chances Investment Fund; and how much funding will be allocated to that Fund.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32073","32073"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484371","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 1.293 of Budget 2016, which areas of criminal justice services he plans to devolve to Greater Manchester; which bodies will assume overall governance of such services; what legal framework he plans to put in place for the governance of service providers; and how such (a) governing bodies and (b) service providers will be funded.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32074","32074"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484372","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to paragraph 1.287 of Budget 2016, where those centres of expertise will be located; what those centres will be responsible for; and how those centres will be funded.","Biography information for Rebecca Long Bailey","Rebecca Long Bailey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32075","32075"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484373","2016-03-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, how many (a) assistant, (b) athletics, (c) level one, (d) level two, (e) level three and (f) level four coaches have been licensed to coach athletics in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Andrew Bingham","Andrew Bingham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32165","32165"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484374","2016-03-24","Department for Transport","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to encourage data-sharing between highway authorities, mapping providers and satellite navigation companies to limit the use of inappropriate routes by HGVs.","Biography information for Ms Nusrat Ghani","Nusrat Ghani","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32063","32063"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484375","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will estimate the level of creditor claims related to insolvency litigation in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32045","32045"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484376","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will estimate the forecast level of creditor claims related to insolvency litigation in each of the next five financial years.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32046","32046"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484377","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the report by Professor Walton, entitled The likely effect of the Jackson reforms on insolvency litigation - an empirical investigation, published in 2013, what his policy is on each of the conclusions of that report.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32047","32047"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484378","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the report by Professor Walton, entitled The likely effect of the Jackson reforms on insolvency litigation - an empirical investigation, published in 2013, what the evidential basis is for his policy on each of the conclusions of that report.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32048","32048"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484379","2016-04-11","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, on what date his Department met Professor Walton to discuss the findings of his interim report on the insolvency litigation landscape, published on 10 December 2015.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32049","32049"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484380","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the level of goods exports to the EU from (a) Scotland, (b) Wales, (c) Northern Ireland and (d) each English region as a proportion of (i) total exports and (ii) GVA from each of those areas.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32052","32052"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484381","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much (a) European Regional Development and (b) European Structural funding (i) Scotland, (ii) Wales, (iii) Northern Ireland and (iv) each region of England will receive in each year between 2014 and 2020.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32053","32053"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484382","2016-03-24","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what estimate she has made of the amount of Common Agricultural Policy funding that (a) Scotland, (b) Wales and (c) Northern Ireland will receive in each year between 2014 and 2020.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32054","32054"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484383","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the legal status of the UK's existing trade agreements agreed through membership of the EU of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Nick Herbert","Nick Herbert","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32166","32166"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484384","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, with reference to point three on page six of Public mental health leadership and workforce development framework: executive summary, published in March 2015, what specific action Public Health England has taken to inform the review of the UK Public Health Skills and Knowledge Framework.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32125","32125"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484385","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people who have not (a) attended a work capability assessment or (b) reported to a jobcentre when requested have been exempt from benefit sanctions because of extenuating circumstances relating to their mental health in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32217","32217"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484386","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) serving personnel and (b) veterans have had mental health issues in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32218","32218"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484387","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2016 to Question 31709, how many incidents of face-down restraints there have been in mental health services in (a) January and (b) February 2016.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32219","32219"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484388","2016-03-24","Women and Equalities","2016-03-22","To ask the Minister for Women and Equalities, pursuant to the Answer of 14 January 2016 to Question 22693, what information she holds on the number of teachers who have accessed the PSHE Association guidance on body image.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32220","32220"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484389","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps he is taking to ensure mental health service user groups are consulted in advance about arrangements for mental health conferences organised by his Department or NHS England.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32215","32215"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484390","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) female and (b) male adult inpatient mental health beds were available on average over weekends in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32216","32216"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484391","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many and what proportion of attendees at the NHS England Mental Health Crisis Care Summit were mental health service users.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32214","32214"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484392","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, whether the Government has conducted an (a) impact and (b) risk assessment of the potential effect of the investor protection clause of the (i) Transatlantic Trade and Investment Partnership and (ii) EU Canada Comprehensive Economic and Trade Agreement on the services and regulations devolved to the Scottish Government; and if he will place copies of any such assessment in the Library.","Biography information for Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","Ms Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32062","32062"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484393","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, when he plans to respond to the letter from the hon. Member for Walsall North, of 17 February 2016, on comments made by him on the Walsall borough; and what the reason is for the time taken to respond to that letter.","Biography information for Mr David Winnick","Mr David Winnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32050","32050"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484394","2016-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how much his Department has spent on sending out information on the Right to Buy scheme to people who are not housing association or council tenants.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32082","32082"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484395","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether the Government plans to pursue any initiatives similar to that announced in the joint statement made by President Obama and Prime Minister Modi in January 2016 during the President's visit to India on expanding the India-US health collaboration in health sectors including complementary and traditional medicine.","Biography information for David Tredinnick","David Tredinnick","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32128","32128"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484396","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the average cost is of the (a) DESMOND and (b) Empower structured education programmes in Leicester, Leicestershire and Rutland.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32115","32115"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484397","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, who was on the procurement board that recently awarded the new contract for type 2 diabetes education programme for Leicester, Leicestershire and Rutland.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32122","32122"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484398","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many (a) DESMOND and (b) DAFNE programmes, in which areas, are provided by clinical commissioning groups in England.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32123","32123"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484399","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of Spirit Healthcare's Empower programme on inequalities in diabetes care across Leicester, Leicestershire and Rutland.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32116","32116"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484400","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether his Department plans that Spirit Healthcare's type 2 diabetes education programme will provide education for those with established diabetes.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32117","32117"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484401","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the potential effect of Spirit Healthcare's Empower type 2 diabetes education programme on uptake of structured education by diabetics in Leicester, Leicestershire and Rutland.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32118","32118"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484402","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of the relative accessibility of (a) Spirit Healthcare's Empower type 2 diabetes education course and (b) the DESMOND programme for diabetes patients in Leicester, Leicestershire and Rutland.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32119","32119"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484403","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, in which areas other than Leicester, Leicestershire and Rutland Spirit Healthcare's Empower type 2 diabetes education programme is expected to be implemented.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32120","32120"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484404","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what the cost to the public purse is of the contract for providing type 2 diabetes education in Leicester, Leicestershire and Rutland.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32121","32121"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484405","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment he has made of the effects on general practices of increases in the number of patients presenting at GP surgeries in the last 12 months; and what steps he is taking to ensure that GP surgeries can cope with the number of patients presenting.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32076","32076"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484406","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what plans his Department has to ensure the continued development of GP networks.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32077","32077"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484407","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, how many GPs in Great Grimsby constituency have retired in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32078","32078"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484408","2016-04-11","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what information he holds on the number of GPs in Great Grimsby constituency who have given notice of their retirement.","Biography information for Melanie Onn","Melanie Onn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32079","32079"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484410","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what steps are being taken to improve the care offered to people with autism in order to reduce the difference in life expectancy between people with and people without autism.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32130","32130"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484411","2016-03-24","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 15 March 2016 to Question 30557, how many people who have arrived in the UK through the camp in Calais have successfully claimed asylum in the UK since June 2015.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32158","32158"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484412","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps he plans to take to monitor the location and use of the recently announced military equipment being given to Ukraine.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32159","32159"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484413","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, pursuant to the Answer of 7 March 2016 to Question 28925, if his Department will begin collecting information on the proportion of foreign graduates who take up employment in the NHS; and if he will bring forward legislative proposals to ensure that the public purse receives value for money when subsidising medicine degrees for foreign nationals.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32167","32167"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484414","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what reports he has received on progress made by Greece in implementing the conditions of the 2015 EU bailout package; and if he will press for steps to improve transparency and monitor use of the bailout funds.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32112","32112"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484415","2016-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent progress has been made in preventing members of the Islamic State/Daesh from travelling across the border between Syria and Turkey.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32129","32129"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484416","2016-03-24","Department for Education","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what criteria the Government plans to use to calculate each school's allocation of funds raised from the soft drinks industry levy for school sports.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32098","32098"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484417","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the UK economy of the use of helicopter funds by the European Central Bank.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32099","32099"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484418","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Governor of the Bank of England on the potential use of helicopter funds in the UK economy.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32100","32100"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484419","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that local authorities are properly informed and involved in decisions to distribute asylum seekers.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32107","32107"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484420","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to ensure that local authorities have appropriate resources to support and deal with increased demand for their services by asylum seekers.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32194","32194"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484421","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the level of hotel use to house asylum seekers is in each local authority area.","Biography information for Mike Kane","Mike Kane","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32195","32195"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484422","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on the availability of housing of plans to demolish homes in the event of a third runway being built at Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32051","32051"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484423","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what mechanisms are in place to monitor the use of HIV innovation funding; and when he plans to (a) conduct and (b) publish his review of the projects that have received such funding.","Biography information for Mike Freer","Mike Freer","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32055","32055"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484424","2016-04-11","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what her Department's contribution is to the Government's emissions reduction plan; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kerry McCarthy","Kerry McCarthy","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32143","32143"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484425","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of civil service apprentices in his Department are (a) over the age of 25 and (b) paid at the rate of the national living wage.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32110","32110"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484426","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many civil service apprentices have been appointed by his Department to date.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32111","32111"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484427","2016-04-11","Cabinet Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 31068, how many meetings the Government's Anti-Corruption Champion had with (a) Ministers and officials of other government departments and (b) representatives from civil society and business between July 2015 and the end of February 2016.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32148","32148"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484428","2016-04-11","Cabinet Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 31069 on corruption, what the usual practice is for disclosing such costs.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32149","32149"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484429","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimates his Department has made of the range for the value of liabilities arising from the sale of the Green Investment Bank.","Biography information for Barry Gardiner","Barry Gardiner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32151","32151"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484430","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will place a copy of his Department's (a) civilian casualty review procedure and (b) standard operating procedure in the Library.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32193","32193"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484431","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 29 January 2016 to Question 23886, whether asset-sharing in Syria, Iraq or Libya was considered at the meeting of the Reaper User Group that took place on 14 to 18 March.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32178","32178"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484432","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 10 March 2016 to Question 30084, if he will make the Attorney General's advice available for inspection by the (a) Chief of the Air Staff (b) Deputy Commander of Operations and (c) Staff Branch Air Command responsible for authorisation of the drone strike which killed Reyaad Khan on 21 August 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32179","32179"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484433","2016-04-11","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the Government approved or was consulted on the US airstrike in Syria that killed Junaid Hussain on 24 August 2015.","Biography information for Mr David Davis","Mr David Davis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32208","32208"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484434","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many higher-rate taxpayers there are in Solihull.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32211","32211"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484435","2016-04-12","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people in Solihull who will pay less income tax as a result of the increase in the personal allowance announced in Budget 2016.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32212","32212"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484436","2016-04-12","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his policy is on allowing for integration of the lifetime ISA and existing standard ISAs.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32133","32133"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484437","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the number of people likely to take up the lifetime ISA in the first year of its operation.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32131","32131"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484438","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he used any international systems to inform the formulation of his proposals to introduce a lifetime ISA.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32096","32096"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484439","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what definition her Department uses for BAME.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32146","32146"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484440","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if her Department will bring forward policies to tackle violence against women and girls in the BAME communities.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32150","32150"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484441","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26843, if he will publish the terms of reference for the Reaper User Group.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32105","32105"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484442","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to Answer of 29 January 2016 to Question 23886, which UK representatives attended the meeting of the Reaper User Group between 14 and 18 March 2016.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32106","32106"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484443","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, what assessment his Department has made of whether his target of implementing opt-out testing for blood-borne viruses in every adult prison in England by the end of financial year 2016-17 will be met.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32094","32094"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484444","2016-03-24","Department of Health","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Health, whether he has taken steps to provide national guidance to ensure that healthcare and wider staff in prisons are given adequate levels of training around blood-borne viruses as recommended by The Hepatitis C Trust's recent report, The blood-borne virus opt-out testing policy for prisons in England: An analysis of need towards full implementation, published on 3 March 2016.","Biography information for Sir David Amess","Sir David Amess","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32095","32095"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484445","2016-04-11","Department for International Development","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 26 February 2016 to Question 27899, what recent assessment she has made of the food security situation in Ethiopia.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32145","32145"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484446","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many jobs each of the 56 science capital projects his Department has funded since 2007 has created.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32144","32144"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484447","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of people between 18 and 24 from each social background defined by their father's occupation are participating in full or part-time education or training activity.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32127","32127"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484448","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much the Student Loans Company and HM Revenue and Customs spent on maintaining and collecting student loan repayments in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32087","32087"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484449","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, if he will make it his policy to conduct a systematic analysis of existing science and research-based infrastructure in the UK for the purpose of guiding his Department's future investment priorities.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32088","32088"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484450","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what progress his Department has made on implementing its plans to impose financial penalties of up to £20,000 per worker against companies who fail to pay the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32089","32089"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484451","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when she plans to publish her Department's proposals on repealing or amending Section 24 of the Animals (Scientific Procedures) Act 1986.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32160","32160"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484452","2016-04-11","Department for Energy and Climate Change","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Energy and Climate Change, if she will make it a condition of energy firms' licences that the staff of those firms' entire retail operation are directly employed in the UK.","Biography information for Kelvin Hopkins","Kelvin Hopkins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32181","32181"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484453","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will conduct a new review of the case for recommending a pardon for Dic Penderyn.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32201","32201"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484454","2016-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received from the UN High Commissioner on human rights and political prisoners in Bahrain and on the implications for UK policy on Bahrain of the human rights situation in that country.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32202","32202"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484455","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Court of Appeal's recent decision on domestic violence evidential requirements for legal aid, what interim steps his Department plans to make for victims of domestic violence whose evidence is more than 24 months old.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32203","32203"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484456","2016-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the government of Bahrain pressing for (a) the release of all people arrested in relation to peaceful protest and (b) reconsideration of the July 2014 amendments to the nationality laws in that country.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32204","32204"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484457","2016-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Israeli counterpart on settlement activity in the West Bank.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32092","32092"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484458","2016-03-24","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 1 February 2016 to Question 23143, when the Border Force's budget for 2016-17 will be agreed.","Biography information for Andy Burnham","Andy Burnham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32152","32152"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484459","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many partnerships are in operation between UK and non-UK EU-based companies in the area of defence; and what the total value of those partnerships is.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32064","32064"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484460","2016-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will make representations to the South Korean government on animal welfare as part of the preparations for the Winter Olympics in 2018.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32056","32056"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484461","2016-04-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the proportion of nuisance calls which appear to be from local numbers but which are being forwarded elsewhere; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32080","32080"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484462","2016-04-11","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, if he will make it his policy to prevent companies using local numbers from which calls are forwarded abroad for the purposes of marketing and other nuisance calls.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32086","32086"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484463","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what evidence she took into account before making it her policy to abolish the right of parents to be represented on school governing bodies; and if she will place copies of such evidence in the Library.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32192","32192"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484464","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department has had discussions with the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs on the effect on air quality of the construction of Phase One of High Speed 2.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32090","32090"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484465","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will make it his policy to pause plans to construct Phase One of HS2 until he has received assurances that they comply with the air quality standards and principles in the document Improving air quality in the UK: Tackling nitrogen dioxide in our towns and cities, published by the Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs in January 2016.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32174","32174"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484466","2016-04-11","Department for Transport","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assurances he has received that (a) construction of a new station in Curzon Street and (b) other construction activity in Birmingham will comply with air quality limit values for nitrogen dioxide.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Mrs Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32173","32173"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484467","2016-03-24","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 17 March 2016 to Question 30739, what information he holds on (a) the legal status of Telahoon Rata and Rev. Hassan Taour and (b) whether their legal team has been granted access to them.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32083","32083"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484468","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of measures in Budget 2016 on social mobility.","Biography information for Adam Afriyie","Adam Afriyie","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32097","32097"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484469","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps she is taking to encourage LGBTI refugees in Lebanon to apply for resettlement in the UK.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32176","32176"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484470","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many LGBTI Syrian refugees she estimates will be resettled in the UK by 2020.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32177","32177"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484471","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if she will estimate the proportion of Syrian refugees settled in the UK by 2020 who will be LGBTI.","Biography information for Mary Creagh","Mary Creagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32175","32175"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484472","2016-04-11","Department for Work and Pensions","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if he will undertake a cost-benefit analysis of (a) Access to Work expenditure and (b) the potential effect of that programme on (i) social security expenditure and (ii) income tax returns.","Biography information for Debbie Abrahams","Debbie Abrahams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32132","32132"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484473","2016-03-24","Department for International Development","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, pursuant to the Answer of 21 March 2016 to Question 31131, how much financial assistance her Department plans to provide UNOCHA for its work in Libya during the next financial year.","Biography information for Stephen Gethins","Stephen Gethins","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32081","32081"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484474","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with response to his contribution of 16 March 2016, Official Report, column 963-64, whether the proposed exemption from the sugar levy for fruit juices will apply to (a) fruit juices with added sugar and (b) fruit juices with natural sugars only.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32180","32180"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484475","2016-04-11","Home Office","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether a ban on travelling to the UK still applies to US citizen Mr Robert Spencer.","Biography information for Gavin Robinson","Gavin Robinson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32164","32164"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484476","2016-04-11","Department for Education","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when she plans for the statutory guidance for local authorities, entitled Post-16 transport to education and training, next to be reviewed to take account of the raising of the education and training participation age to 18; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32068","32068"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484477","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how many part-time students have taken higher education qualifications at a further education college in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32069","32069"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484478","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what proportion of higher education students continued to (a) further study and (b) employment when leaving (i) university and (ii) a further education  college in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32070","32070"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484479","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what the average age is of students studying for their first higher education qualification in (a) universities and (b)  further education colleges.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32071","32071"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484480","2016-04-11","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what average annual tuition fee is charged by further education colleges for higher education courses.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32072","32072"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484481","2016-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, how many full-time equivalent officials in his Department have worked on devolution deals in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32168","32168"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484482","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what assessment his Department has made of trends in home ownership since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32185","32185"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484483","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the annual amount saved in ISA accounts across each income group in financial year (a) 2010-11, (b) 2011-12 and (c) 2012-13; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32188","32188"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484484","2016-04-11","HM Treasury","2016-03-22","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the total contribution from the public purse to Lifetime ISAs in financial year (a) 2017-18 (b) 2018-19 and (c) 2019-20; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32187","32187"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484485","2016-04-11","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the total cost of administrating devolution deals in each of the last three years; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32186","32186"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484486","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many convictions for benefit fraud were overturned on appeal between 2010 and 2014.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32171","32171"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/484487","2016-03-24","Ministry of Justice","2016-03-22","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many prosecutions conducted by local authorities resulted in convictions for benefit fraud between 2010 and 2014.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 32213","32213"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482981","2016-03-24","Attorney General","2016-03-21","To ask the Attorney General, what estimate his Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the Fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment he has made of which of his Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31824","31824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482982","2016-03-23","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment she has made of the number of jobs supported by the Scotch whisky industry.","Biography information for Tom Brake","Tom Brake","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31798","31798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482983","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to Principle G of the Cabinet Office Consultation Principles 2016, what steps he took to (a) consider how the summer holiday period would affect consultation with stakeholders and (b) mitigate such effects when deciding on the consultation period on proposals relating to exit payments in the public sector.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31816","31816"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482984","2016-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, how much his Department owed in late payments to small and medium-sized enterprises in each year for which data is available.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31793","31793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482985","2016-03-23","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how much central government infrastructure investment was in each region of the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31794","31794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482986","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, what estimate his Department has made of the claims relating to national minimum wage have fallen under section 2 of the Deduction from Wages (Limitation) Regulations 2014 since their entry into force.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31879","31879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482987","2016-03-23","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, when the Government plans to implement its policy of providing three days' paid volunteering leave for employees of large organisations.","Biography information for Alan Johnson","Alan Johnson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31840","31840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482988","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2016 to Question 30689, when his Department plans to publish the declaration of actual or potential conflicts of interest made by Paul Newby for the role of Pubs Code Adjudicator.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31888","31888"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482989","2016-03-24","Department for Business, Innovation and Skills","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Innovation and Skills, pursuant to the Answer of 18 March 2016 to Question 30698, whether the person appointed as Pubs Code Adjudicator was the recommended choice of the panel.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31892","31892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482990","2016-03-24","Cabinet Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent progress his Department has made on allowing interns who successfully complete the Summer Diversity Internship Programme to pass straight to the Fast Stream assessment centre on the basis of having successfully completed that internship.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31803","31803"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482991","2016-03-24","Cabinet Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, how many people have participated in the Summer Diversity Internship Programme since its inception; and how many of those participants have subsequently been accepted onto the Civil Service Fast Stream.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31804","31804"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482992","2016-03-24","Cabinet Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what the eligibility criteria are for the Summer Diversity Internship Programme for socially or economically disadvantaged groups.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31813","31813"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482993","2016-03-24","Cabinet Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether the Summer Diversity Internship Programme weekly training allowance is taxed.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31809","31809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482994","2016-03-23","Cabinet Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, whether he plans to introduce a civil service wide socio-economic background census.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31792","31792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482995","2016-03-24","Cabinet Office","2016-03-21","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate his Department has made of the number of its senior civil servants who will potentially fall under the provisions of the Fourth EU Money Laundering Directive, 2015/849; and what assessment he has made of which of his Department's agencies or other public bodies will potentially be classed as holding a prominent public function for the purposes of that directive.","Biography information for Sir Charles Walker","Mr Charles Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31827","31827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482996","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 5 February 2016 to Question 24869, whether the (a) Royal Bank of Scotland, (b) Bradford and Bingley and c) Northern Rock banks have received any public funding since they were taken into public ownership.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31814","31814"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482997","2016-03-23","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to paragraph 1.205 of the Budget 2016, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on insurance policy take-up of an increase in the standard rate of insurance premium tax.","Biography information for Greg Mulholland","Greg Mulholland","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31863","31863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482998","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many (a) enforcement actions have been undertaken by HM Revenue and Customs (HMRC) involving victims of modern slavery and (b) victims of modern slavery HMRC recovered national minimum wage arrears for in each of the last five years; and how much in national minimum wage arrears HMRC has recovered for victims of modern slavery in that period.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31878","31878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/482999","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 22 February 2016 to Question 26995, what steps he has taken to support people who have moved home because of flooding and are unable to sell their primary home within the 18-month eligibility period for refund of stamp duty.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31881","31881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483000","2016-03-24","HM Treasury","2016-03-21","To ask Mr Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse of introducing the national living wage into social care from April 2016.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31874","31874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483001","2016-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, whether his Department has made an estimate of the number and proportion of councils which have decided to levy the social care precept in 2016-17.","Biography information for Barbara Keeley","Barbara Keeley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31882","31882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483002","2016-03-24","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 17 February 2016 to Question 26459, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of changes to the pay to stay scheme proposed in the Housing and Planning Bill on the number of residents who leave their local communities.","Biography information for Steve McCabe","Steve McCabe","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31883","31883"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483003","2016-03-23","Department for Communities and Local Government","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Communities and Local Government, what plans the Government has to help more homeless people rent privately.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31838","31838"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483004","2016-03-24","Department for Culture, Media and Sport","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 10 February 2016 to Question 24859, what funding options for Channel 4 the Government is considering.","Biography information for Tim Loughton","Tim Loughton","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31884","31884"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483005","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what steps his Department has taken to assess the basing and maintenance options for (a) the Type 26 frigate and (b) the new general purpose frigate.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31837","31837"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483006","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of whether there are circumstances under which the Government would consider deploying armed forces in the South China Sea.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31832","31832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483007","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the trained strength of the Royal Navy is by (a) officers and (b) non-commissioned ranks.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31833","31833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483008","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has to replace the fleet of mine countermeasure vessels after 2020.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31834","31834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483009","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the operations limitations are on the UK's ability to operate in the Pacific.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31835","31835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483010","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for the replacement of RFA (a) Diligence and (b) Argus after 2025.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31836","31836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483011","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which non-UK EU armed forces procure materiel from British companies.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31842","31842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483012","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on what defence technology research and development programmes the Government is cooperating with other EU member states.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31848","31848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483013","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which defence procurement projects the Government has been involved in that (a) have included other EU member states and (b) have been EU-led.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31844","31844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483014","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, from which non-UK EU-based companies his Department procures materiel.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31845","31845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483015","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of building the new general purpose frigate class in parallel with the Type 26 programme.","Biography information for Mrs Flick Drummond","Mrs Flick Drummond","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31851","31851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483016","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which military operations UK armed forces have been involved in that have (a) included other EU member states and (b) been EU-led.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31849","31849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483017","2016-03-23","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, which military exercises UK armed forces have been involved in that have (a) included other EU member states and (b) been EU-led.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31850","31850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483018","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the order of battle is of the Royal Fleet Auxiliary.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31821","31821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483019","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what plans he has for the Future Solid Support Programme; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31822","31822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483020","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what he plans the size of the Frigate fleet will be in 2025.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31828","31828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/483021","2016-03-24","Ministry of Defence","2016-03-21","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has received reports of Russian submarine activity in sea lanes considered vital to the UK.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2015/16 31829","31829"
