"uri","answer date","answering body","date tabled","question text","tabling member > label","tabling member printed","title","uin"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006046","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many independent domestic violence advisers have been employed in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190826","190826"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006047","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many hospitals have an independent domestic violence adviser service based permanently on-site.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190827","190827"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006048","2018-11-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the number of the tenants that are evicted by their landlord before the end date of their tenancy.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190754","190754"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006049","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what proportion of hospital independent domestic violence advisor clients, were (a) women, (b) from black and minority ethnic backgrounds  and (c) over the age of 55 in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190828","190828"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006050","2018-11-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment he has made of the effect of charging victims of domestic violence up to £175 for a medical letter to prove they were abused on the ability of victims to access legal aid.","Biography information for Dawn Butler","Dawn Butler","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190829","190829"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006051","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the proportion of new claims for universal credit that were paid in full and on time which contain the (a) standard allowance only, (b) carer element, (c) child element, (d) childcare element, (e) disabled child element, (f) housing element  and (g) limited capability for work element.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190903","190903"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006052","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the Government plans to publish its internal review of universal support.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190904","190904"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006053","2018-11-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2018 to Question 185569 on Wembley Stadium, if he will publish the minutes of the meeting between the Minister for Sport and Civil Society and the Chief Executive of the Football Association.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190859","190859"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006054","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what estimate she has made of the proportion of claims for universal credit that received a portion of the initial payment on time which contain the (a) the standard allowance, (b) carer element, (c) child element, (d) childcare element, (e) disabled child element, (f) housing element and (g) limited capability for work element.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190905","190905"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006055","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many and what proportion of new claimants of universal credit (a) requested and (b) received a new claim advance in each month from 31 December 2017 to the most recent month for which figures are available.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190906","190906"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006056","2018-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with Babcock on that company's financial position and any associated risk to his Department's programmes and to the capabilities of the armed forces.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190808","190808"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006057","2018-11-19","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many police stations have closed in each of the last eight years for which data is available.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190755","190755"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006058","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average monthly deduction to universal credit to repay debt was in the most recent year for which data is available.","Biography information for Margaret Greenwood","Margaret Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190907","190907"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006059","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department plans to maintain a central record of the number of people who use foodbanks in the UK.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190860","190860"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006060","2018-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of imposing special measures on the Vanguard-class life extension programme and sending officials from his Department to oversee the programme at Devonport.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190809","190809"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006061","2018-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the (a) effectiveness and (b) financial sustainability of the Vanguard-class life extension programme.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190810","190810"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006062","2018-11-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the volume of power generated from new domestic solar generators after the closure of the feed-in tariff scheme in (a)  2019, (b) 2020 and (c) 2021.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190842","190842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006063","2018-11-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policy on the future of the feed-in tariff scheme of the UK’s obligations under article 21 of the EU Renewable Energy Directive II.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190843","190843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006064","2018-11-19","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many and what proportion of imprisoned foreign national offenders have been transferred from the UK to a prison in the country of which they are a national under the EU prisoner Transfer Framework Decision since December 2011.","Biography information for Mr Philip Hollobone","Mr Philip Hollobone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190835","190835"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006065","2018-11-15","Department for Education","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to support the continuation of an independent land-based skills college in Suffolk.","Biography information for Dr Dan Poulter","Dr Dan Poulter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190844","190844"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006066","2018-11-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the validity of the case against Mr Nabeel Rajab; and what representations his Department has made to the Bahraini Government on Mr Rajab.","Biography information for Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","Dr Rosena Allin-Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190949","190949"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006067","2018-11-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were released from prison on 22 December 2017; and how many of those people were recalled within one month of release.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190796","190796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006068","2018-11-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were released from prison between 18 and 22 December 2017; and how many of those people were recalled within one month of release.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190797","190797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006069","2018-11-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many people were released from prison on each Friday in the last six months.","Biography information for David Hanson","David Hanson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190798","190798"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006070","2018-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent discussions he has had with Babcock on building dockyard (a) capacity and (b) capability at Devonport to (i) maintain and defuel currently operational and future SSBN submarines, (b) maintain attack submarines and (c) defuel attack submarines; and what estimate he has made of the cost to Babcock of that work.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190811","190811"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006071","2018-11-19","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether he has plans to return Devonport Dockyard to Government ownership.","Biography information for Mr Kevan Jones","Mr Kevan Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190812","190812"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006072","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2018 to Question 185514 on Housing Infrastructure Fund, if he will publish the amount of funding allocated to the Fund in each of the last five financial years.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190771","190771"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006073","2018-11-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has plans to apply to the International Commission for the Conservation of Atlantic Tunas for a quota for recreational catch and release game fishing of bluefin tuna after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190921","190921"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006074","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2018 to Question 180245 on Prescription Drugs, for what reason his Department did not include individual testimony; and what proportion of the published evidence was submitted by pharmaceutical companies.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190913","190913"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006075","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care,  whether a non-disclosure agreement was made between Public Health England and the National Guideline Centre in relation to the review of literature on prescribed medicines.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190914","190914"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006076","2018-11-19","Department for Transport","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, when he plans to publish the Christmas timetable for the West Coast Main Line.","Biography information for Maria Eagle","Maria Eagle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190794","190794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006077","2018-11-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 1.11 of his Department's feed-in-tariff consultation, what the final date by which community organisations can apply for pre-registration arrangements is; and what (a) generation and (b) export tariff those organisations will be eligible for.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190923","190923"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006078","2018-11-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to paragraph 1.11 of his Department's feed-in-tariff consultation, whether community organisations applying for pre-registration before March 2019 will be eligible for the same level of funding as organisations completing installation before March 2019.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190924","190924"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006079","2018-11-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his timetable is for (a) the publication of the final regulations and (b) his response to the consultation on the withdrawal of the Feed In Tariff scheme.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190925","190925"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006080","2018-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the 2018 EU Circular Economy Package.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190926","190926"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006081","2018-11-19","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Yazidi women have been admitted to the UK under the vulnerable persons resettlement scheme.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190781","190781"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006082","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he has made an assessment of the adequacy of local authority suicide prevention plans: and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190782","190782"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006083","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of (a) social rent, (b) affordable rent and (c) low-cost ownership homes held in local authority housing revenue accounts.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190772","190772"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006084","2018-11-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made tho his Bangladeshi counterpart on the proposed forced repatriation of Rohingya refugees from that country.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190783","190783"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006085","2018-11-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what diplomatic steps he is taking to protect women Rohingya refugees that are repatriated from gender-based violence; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Helen Jones","Helen Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190784","190784"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006086","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment his Department has made of trends in the level of (a) vandalism and (b) damage to (i) ambulances and (ii) other emergency response blue light vehicles; and what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on that matter.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190896","190896"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006087","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the Government’s policy is on tackling the vandalism of ambulances.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190897","190897"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006088","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government has plans to bring forward legislative proposals for tougher penalties for people that vandalise ambulances.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190898","190898"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006089","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to help protect ambulance workers from abusive and violent conduct.","Biography information for Jonathan Ashworth","Jonathan Ashworth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190899","190899"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006090","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 8 November to Question 187017 on Personal Independence Payment: Cancer, how many people with (a) leukaemia, (b) myeloma, (c) Hodgkin's lymphoma and (d) non-Hodgkin's lymphoma have (i) applied for personal independence payment and (ii) unsuccessfully appealed a decision not to award personal independence payment.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190873","190873"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006091","2018-11-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his Commonwealth counterparts on the current political and human rights situation in Cameroon after the October elections in that that country.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190744","190744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006092","2018-11-19","Cabinet Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, pursuant to the answer of 12 November to Question 188227 on Rendition and Torture: Inquiries, whether the Government plans to announce its decision on an independent judge-led inquiry before the House rises for Christmas recess.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190850","190850"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006093","2018-11-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether (a) he and (b) Ministers of his Department plan to visit Cameroon to discuss the Anglophone crisis in that country.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190745","190745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006094","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on SMEs in Kent of making customs declarations for the first time in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190735","190735"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006095","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what financial assistance he plans to provide to Kent Police in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190736","190736"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006096","2018-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the effect on Kent’s tourism industry of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Sir Michael Fallon","Sir Michael Fallon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190737","190737"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006097","2018-11-19","Cabinet Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions the Government has had with (a) President Trump, (b) members of the US administration and (c) senior officials in the US administration on an independent judge-led inquiry into UK involvement in torture and rendition.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190851","190851"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006098","2018-11-19","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what his Department's definition is of privately financed in relation to infrastructure projects.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190874","190874"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006099","2018-11-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment he has made of the effect of the expansion of Heathrow Airport on the ability of the UK to meet the net-zero emissions target by 2050.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190875","190875"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006100","2018-11-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he has plans to introduce legislation proposals to set the target of net-zero emissions by 2050.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190876","190876"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006101","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he plans to take to ensure that EU Settlement Scheme grant funding reaches groups (a) that have a real and established relationship with Roma communities and (b) in geographical areas where Roma communities are concentrated.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190877","190877"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006102","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will consider changing in the EU Settlement Scheme grant funding the eligibility criterion that applications can be for no more than 25 per cent of an organisation’s annual income so that smaller community groups are not disadvantaged.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190878","190878"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006103","2018-11-15","Department for International Development","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what the Government's policy is on the UK's (a) future membership of and (b) future funding to the United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190950","190950"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006104","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he plans to publish the findings of the second phase of the testing of settled status applications which includes testing with Roma applicants.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190879","190879"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006105","2018-11-19","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will commission a review of Operation Conifer.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190738","190738"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006106","2018-11-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in the African Union on renewing steps to find a peaceful solution to the conflict in Cameroon.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190746","190746"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006107","2018-11-19","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what was the cost to the public purse was of Operation Conifer; and what lessons have been learnt as a result of that operation.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190739","190739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006108","2018-11-19","Department for International Development","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what contribution the Government plans to make to the Global Compact for Migration.","Biography information for Sir Nicholas Soames","Sir Nicholas Soames","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190740","190740"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006109","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will (a) undertake a review of safety at the Sunderland assessment centre managed by the Centre for Health and Disability Assessments and (b) require the installation of CCTV recording equipment in that centre for the protection and security of staff and claimants.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190852","190852"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006110","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking in response to the consultation on the Transforming children and young people’s mental health provision Green Paper in order to improve mental health provision for 18 to 25-year-olds.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190880","190880"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006111","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to her Department's White Paper, Improving lives: the future of work, health and disability, what progress she has made on meeting the target for the recruitment of Community Partners.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190788","190788"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006112","2018-11-13","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many complaints have been revived from people left unable to access their childcare account as a result of technical difficulties in each year since the introduction of those accounts.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190785","190785"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006113","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many 30 hours free childcare codes have been issued manually as a result of faults in the childcare account system.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190786","190786"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006114","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many people have received financial compensation as a result of not having access to their online childcare account; and how much money has been paid out of the public purse for that compensation.","Biography information for Sir David Crausby","Sir David Crausby","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190787","190787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006115","2018-11-19","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Financial Ombudsman's Annual Report 2017-18, for what reasons the Financial Ombudsman upheld the lowest rate of complaints in the last 10 years in 2017-2018.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190951","190951"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006116","2018-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many cattle herds there were in the Somerset Central cull zone in the (a) cohort and (b) herds in existence monitoring groups; how many New Herd Incidents there were in each group; how many of those incidents were Officially TB Free Withdrawn; and what the (i) time at risk and (ii) calculated incidence rates were for each monitoring group between 26 August 2017 and 25 August 2018.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190853","190853"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006117","2018-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many cattle herds there were in the Dorset Central cull zone in the (a) cohort and (b) herds in existence monitoring groups; how many New Herd Incidents there were in each group; how many of those incidents were Officially TB Free Withdrawn; and what the (i) time at risk and (ii) calculated incidence rates were for each group between 31 August 2017 and 30 August 2018.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190854","190854"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006118","2018-11-19","Cabinet Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what discussions he has had with insurance providers on advising clients provided with legal advice funded by that insurer about when to pursue or decline a whistle blowing case.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190952","190952"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006119","2018-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many cattle herds there were in the Gloucestershire Central cull zone in the (a) cohort and (b) herds in existence monitoring groups; how many New Herd Incidents there were in each group; how many of those incidents were Officially TB Free Withdrawn; and what the (i) time at risk and (ii) calculated incidence rates were for each group between 3 September 2017 and 2 September 2018.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190855","190855"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006120","2018-11-19","Cabinet Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the cost to the public purse for legal defence of public sector institutions for whistle blowing cases broken down by Department.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190953","190953"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006121","2018-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, on 24th October 2018, how many cattle herds there were in the Gloucestershire Central cull zone in the (a) cohort and (b) herds in existence monitoring groups; how many and what proportion of herds were under restriction; and how many and what proportion of herds were Officially TB Free Withdrawn.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190856","190856"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006122","2018-11-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, if he will make it his policy to ensure that people who are asked to complete work trials at the outset of employment are classed as workers.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190917","190917"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006123","2018-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many herds in the Somerset central cull zone were (a) in the (i) cohort and (ii) herds in existence monitoring groups, (b) were under restriction and (c) were Officially Tuberculosis Free withdrawn on 24 October 2018; and what the prevalence in that zone was of (A) Herds Under Restriction and (B) herds that were Officially Tuberculosis Free withdrawn on that same date.","Biography information for Chris Williamson","Chris Williamson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190857","190857"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006124","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS England's consultation on contracting arrangements for Integrated Care Providers, which closed on 26 October 2018, what the timetable is for the publication of the outcome of that consultation.","Biography information for Sir George Howarth","Mr George Howarth","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190792","190792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006125","2018-11-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether he is taking steps to ensure that the November 2018 Government document Calculating the Minimum Wage includes guidance for people who are asked to complete unpaid work trials at the outset of employment.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190918","190918"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006126","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applicants there were for personal independence payment in the special rules for terminal illness stream in (a) 2017, (b) 2016 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190954","190954"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006127","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many successful applicants there were for personal independence payment in the special rules for terminal illness stream in (a) 2017, (b) 2016 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190955","190955"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006128","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average time taken to process personal independence applications in the special rules for terminal illness stream was in (a) 2017, (b) 2016 and (c) 2015.","Biography information for Anne-Marie Trevelyan","Anne-Marie Trevelyan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190956","190956"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006129","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2018 to Question 188715, what proportion of the 20,000 homes which were to be delivered would have been directly supported by the additional £800 million of grant funding.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190773","190773"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006130","2018-11-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, for what reasons the UK Government was not present at a meeting between Russia, France, Germany and Turkey in Istanbul on 28 October 2018 to discuss a ceasefire in Syria.","Biography information for Christine Jardine","Christine Jardine","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190957","190957"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006131","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2018 to Question 188715 on Council housing: construction, what the value was of the average grant requested per unit by the tenure types (a) social rent, (b) affordable rent and (c) other.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190774","190774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006132","2018-11-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the 31 October 2018 Government news release £200 million to kickstart full fibre broadband across the UK, how much of that funding will be allocated to South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190892","190892"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006133","2018-11-19","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to promote the use of the Urban Tree Manual announced by Government Tree Champion Sir William Worsley on 19 October 2018 in (a) Sheffield city region and (b) Barnsley.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190893","190893"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006134","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many people under the age of 18 were admitted to A&E for deliberate self harm in (a) the Sheffield City Region combined authority area and (b) Barnsley in the last two years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190894","190894"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006135","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the proportion of people admitted to A&E for attempted suicide who have later attempted it again in the last three years.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190895","190895"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006136","2018-11-19","Department for Education","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, how many colleges are currently subject to a notice to improve financial health; and how many are projected to be subject to such a notice in the next (a) five and (b) 10 years.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190900","190900"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006137","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November to Question 186185 on Affordable Housing, what proportion of the new affordable homes to be delivered by the Affordable Homes Programme will be for social rent.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190775","190775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006138","2018-11-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what his Department's definition is of the word excessive in relation to the number of hours people are asked to complete for unpaid work trials.","Biography information for Stewart Malcolm McDonald","Stewart Malcolm McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190919","190919"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006139","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November to Question 185505 on Sleeping Rough, in which local authority areas the Rough Sleepers Initiative operates; and in each of those local authority areas (a) how much has been spent from the targeted fund and (b) how many individuals have been relieved or prevented from rough sleeping.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190776","190776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006140","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November to Question 185506 on Sleeping Rough, how many (a) units of accommodation have been made available and (b) lettings have been taken up through the (i) Rapid Rehousing Pathway and (ii) Supported Lettings Fund.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190777","190777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006141","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many women are currently being held in immigration detention while their asylum claims are being processed.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190881","190881"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006142","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to page 28 of the independent report entitled Welfare in detention of vulnerable persons review: progress report, published on gov.uk in July 2018, what steps his Department is taking in response to the recommendation that it should take steps to identify women claiming asylum who are being held in detention whose cases would be better processed in the community.","Biography information for Kate Green","Kate Green","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190882","190882"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006143","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many universal credit cases were deleted in error; and what the time taken was for those cases to be rebuilt in the most recent 12 months for which data are available.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190789","190789"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006144","2018-11-15","Department for Transport","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will provide Access for All funding for the construction of a ramp from the car park on the London side of Lichfield Trent Valley railway station to enable disabled access from the car park to the station and its platforms; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Michael Fabricant","Michael Fabricant","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190750","190750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006145","2018-11-19","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the timetable for the review of Home Office structures and processes announced by the Secretary of State for the Home Department on 25 October 2018, Official Report, col 469 will be.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190958","190958"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006146","2018-11-19","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when he will plans to publish the Independent Chief Inspector of Borders and Immigration's reports on (a) Asylum Accommodation, (b) Country of Origin Information, (c) Vulnerable Adults and (d) Home Office (Borders, Immigration and Citizenship System) collaborative working with other government departments and agencies.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190959","190959"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006147","2018-11-19","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what assessment he has made of the capacity of his Department to publish independent chief inspector of border and immigration reports within the eight week timeframe.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190960","190960"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006148","2018-11-19","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what documentation will be provided to non-EU family members of EU citizens who are granted pre-settled status to enable them to travel to and from the UK.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190961","190961"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006149","2018-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, pursuant to the Answer of 13 November 2018 to Question 188095 on Emergencies: Climate Change, what steps he is taking to ensure that defence infrastructure is not compromised by incidents related to climate change.","Biography information for Mr Virendra Sharma","Mr Virendra Sharma","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190839","190839"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006150","2018-11-19","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether Calais leave status will be extended to minors present in Calais months before the demolition of the Calais camp in 2016 and who entered the UK through the family reunification route and now face deportation.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190962","190962"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006151","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps he is taking to ensure that minors residing in Calais that have family in the UK are able to access family reunification procedures.","Biography information for Afzal Khan","Afzal Khan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190963","190963"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006152","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether his Department has plans amend the regulation of debt collection agencies.","Biography information for Scott Mann","Scott Mann","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190922","190922"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006153","2018-11-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the article on the Guardian website on 8 November 2018 entitled Gig economy workers' rights to be given boost in overhaul, what legislative proposals he plans to bring forward on gig economy workers' rights; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190908","190908"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006154","2018-11-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the article on the Guardian website on 8 November 2018 entitled Gig economy workers' rights to be given boost in overhaul, if he will place in the Library copies of all documents provided to the media by the Government in relation to this article.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190909","190909"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006155","2018-11-19","Department for Transport","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if the Government will reverse its decision not to extend the lane rental scheme to trunk roads operated by Highways England.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190840","190840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006156","2018-11-19","Department for Transport","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what (a) incentives and (b) sanctions are available to Highways England to promote compliance with its instructions on roadworks undertaken by utility companies.","Biography information for John Woodcock","John Woodcock","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190841","190841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006157","2018-11-19","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of exempting General Practices from the General Data Protection Regulation that data controllers can no longer charge for processing subject access requests.","Biography information for Alex Norris","Alex Norris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190964","190964"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006158","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the Written Statement of 10 November 2015 on Government response to ‘No voice unheard, no right ignored’ consultation, HCWS302, how much of the £45 million in funding made available to Transforming Care Partnerships has been spent; and how that funding has been allocated.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190866","190866"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006159","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect changes in the level of Government funding for local authorities on their capacity to provide care in the community for people with learning disabilities and autism since 2010.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190867","190867"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006160","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of people with (a) learning disabilities and (b) autism living in the community who have a local care and support navigator or key worker.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190868","190868"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006161","2018-11-19","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2018 to Question 188218 on Immigrants: EU Nationals, when she plans to lay the immigration White Paper before the House.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190910","190910"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006162","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the October 2015 Government document Building the Right Support: A national implementation plan to develop community services and close inpatient facilities, whether he has made an assessment of the effectiveness of the process for collecting and sharing data on people with learning disabilities and autism.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190869","190869"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006163","2018-11-19","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2018 to Question 188216 on Immigrants: EU Nationals, how many of those 1,500 UKVI European Casework staff are in post.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190911","190911"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006164","2018-11-19","Home Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2018 to Question 188866 on Immigrants: EU Nationals, what guidance her Department will provide to employers on how to distinguish between a National Identity card from a non-UK EU citizen job applicant who arrived in the UK (a) before and (b) after March 2019.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190912","190912"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006165","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the October 2015 Government document Building the Right Support: A national implementation plan to develop community services and close inpatient facilities, how much money has accrued to the public purse from changes in the number of beds for people with learning disabilities and autism; and what proportion of that amount has been reallocated to local authorities.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190870","190870"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006166","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what criteria the Department provides to its partners to assess non-physical disabilities for clients applying for personal independence payment and disability living allowance.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190862","190862"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006167","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department undertakes to ensure the applicants for personal independence payment and disability living allowance are assessed by accredited healthcare professionals for their specific disability or impairment.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190863","190863"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006169","2018-11-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many (a) Crown post office and hosted Crown post office, (b) franchise post office, (c) Main post office, (d) post office Locals, (e) traditional sub-post office and (f) other types of post office branches there were on 1 November 2018 by (i) region and (ii) Local Enterprise Partnership area in England.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190965","190965"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006170","2018-11-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how many post offices offer Post Office Current Accounts in branch by (a) region and (b) Local Enterprise Partnership area in England.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190966","190966"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006171","2018-11-19","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what financial services the Post Office provides at (a) Crown post office and hosted Crown post office, (b) franchise post office, (c) Main post office, (d) post office Locals, (e) traditional sub-post office and (f) other types of post office branches.","Biography information for Gill Furniss","Gill Furniss","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190967","190967"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006172","2018-11-19","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations his Department has made to the Indian Government on the continuing imprisonment of Jagtar Singh Johal.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190760","190760"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006173","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will place in the Library a copy of all economic analyses the Government has undertaken on banning post duty point dilution or processing.","Biography information for Neil Coyle","Neil Coyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190902","190902"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006174","2018-11-19","Department for Education","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his appearance on the Andrew Marr Show on 11 November 2018, what the evidential basis was for his statement that the funding for the average class of 27 children in primary school is £132,000.","Biography information for Angela Rayner","Angela Rayner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190901","190901"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006175","2018-11-15","Department for International Development","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what (a) education and (b) interfaith initiatives her Department has funded in Pakistan to promote tolerance and interfaith harmony in schools in each year for which information is available, and how much her Department has spent on each such initiative.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190747","190747"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006176","2018-11-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Pakistan on ensuring the security and protection of (a) lawyers and judges in Pakistan who are involved in blasphemy cases and (b) (i) Asia Bibi's lawyer Saiful Malook and (ii) the three Supreme Court judges involved in Asia Bibi’s case.","Biography information for Siobhain McDonagh","Siobhain McDonagh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190748","190748"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006177","2018-11-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps he is taking to encourage more prison officers to stay in post.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190890","190890"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006178","2018-11-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps his Department plans to take against (a) drone operators and (b) prisoners involved in receiving messages or contraband.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190891","190891"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006179","2018-11-19","Department for Transport","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what plans his Department has to fund the construction of the North West Relief Road around Shrewsbury.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190836","190836"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006180","2018-11-19","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has plans to remove VAT from services and items included for the repair and maintenance of (a) churches and (b) other religious buildings.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190861","190861"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006181","2018-11-15","Department for Transport","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent assessment he has made of the potential effect on the viability of the aviation sector of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190968","190968"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006182","2018-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the UK mission to Afghanistan is assisting in the protection of Hazaras people in Ghazni and Uruzgan provinces.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190969","190969"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006183","2018-11-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, with reference to the Chair of the Building Better, Building Beautiful Commission (a) when and (b) where the position of Chair of that Commission was advertised.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190830","190830"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006184","2018-11-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many applicants there were for the position of Chair of the Building Better, Building Beautiful Commission.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190831","190831"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006185","2018-11-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many candidates were were shortlisted for the role of Chair of the Building Better, Building Beautiful Commission.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190832","190832"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006186","2018-11-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many of the candidates who applied for the Chair of the Building Better, Building Beautiful Commission were deemed appointable.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190833","190833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006187","2018-11-19","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what the selection process for the Chair of the Building Better, Building Beautiful Commission was.","Biography information for Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","Dr Roberta Blackman-Woods","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190834","190834"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006188","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, when his Department plans to publish the next Public Land for Housing Programme progress report.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190778","190778"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006189","2018-11-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Afghanistan Government on protecting Hazaras people in Ghazni and Uruzgan provinces.","Biography information for Kate Osamor","Kate Osamor","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190970","190970"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006190","2018-11-19","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has a target timescale for processing the mandatory reconsiderations of its decisions on the eligibility of people for universal credit.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190864","190864"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006191","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has a target timescale for hearing appeals against its decisions on the eligibility of people for universal credit.","Biography information for Lilian Greenwood","Lilian Greenwood","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190865","190865"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006192","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the total number of assets managed by NHS Property Service.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190761","190761"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006193","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the number of properties owned by NHS Property Services.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190762","190762"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006194","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate he has made of the annual rental income received from GP practices for NHS Property Services.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190763","190763"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006195","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he last met the Chief Executive of NHS Property Services.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190764","190764"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006196","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many complaints has he received from GP's about NHS Property Services.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190765","190765"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006197","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when he expects the agreement between the BMA and NHS Property Services concerning the leases given to GP practice to be concluded.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190766","190766"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006198","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many (a) properties and (b) assets are in each region of NHS Property Services.","Biography information for Keith Vaz","Keith Vaz","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190767","190767"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006199","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to prioritise end-of-life care in the NHS.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190790","190790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006200","2018-11-15","Department for Transport","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will consider the potential merits of widening the remit of the consultation on proposed new cycling offences to include other road traffic offences.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190791","190791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006201","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the incident reporting requirements are for recording Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority of adverse clinical effects associated with fertility treatment for (a) the HFEA and (b) hospitals; and who is responsible for such incident reporting when a patient is no longer receiving treatment at a fertility clinic.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190845","190845"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006202","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what information his Department holds on the number of IVF cycles in which 15 or more eggs were collected where at least some of which were used for (a) egg sharing, (b) donation and (c) research purposes since 2013.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190846","190846"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006203","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many adverse ovarian hypersensitivity syndrome incidents were recorded in licensed human fertilisation embryology authority clinics between 2011 and 2018; and what the severity grading of each such incident was.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190847","190847"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006204","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether he plans to link the human fertilisation and embryology authority registry with the hospital, cancer and death registries to record the links between IVF treatment cycles and the incidence of (a) severe or moderate ovarian hyperstimulation syndrome, (b) cancer and (c) mortality among women.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190848","190848"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006205","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment the Government has made of the potential merits of introducing free port schemes across the UK.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190815","190815"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006206","2018-11-19","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many abortions (a) Marie Stopes International and (b) British Pregnancy Advisory Service carried out in each year between 2007 to 2017.","Biography information for Fiona Bruce","Fiona Bruce","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190849","190849"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006208","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what effect has plain packaging had on the tax received from tobacco duty receipts in each financial year since that policy was introduced.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190817","190817"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006209","2018-11-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what assessment the Government has made of the potential effect on youth employment rates of the increase in the minimum wage to £8.21 per hour.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190818","190818"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006210","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the effect of lowering the rate of corporation tax on corporation tax receipts since 2017.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190819","190819"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006211","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-13","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many cases relating to universal credit have been referred to the Parliamentary and Health Service Ombudsman in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190820","190820"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006212","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate his Department has made of the net benefits to the economy of trade with the Channel Islands.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190821","190821"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006213","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what comparative assessment he has made of spending on public services in the UK and other EU member states.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190822","190822"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006214","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment his Department has made of the effect on the financial sector of the UK leaving the EU without a trade deal.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190823","190823"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006215","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the contribution of the UK internal market to the Northern Irish economy.","Biography information for Andrew Rosindell","Andrew Rosindell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190824","190824"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1006216","2018-11-19","Treasury","2018-11-13","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many Scottish higher rate taxpayers have contacted HM Revenue and Customs in the last 12 months to register elsewhere in the UK for tax purposes; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190920","190920"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005658","2018-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, if he will outline the key points of contention on the Government paying its debt obligations in relation to IMS Limited; and whether those points of contention inform the Government's position on the upcoming IMS Limited arbitration hearing.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190513","190513"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005659","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he has made an assessment of the effect of including non-UK EU citizens within the scope of the compliant environment policy immediately after the UK leaves the EU on the ability of those citizens to (a) access rental accommodation and (b) find employment in the period before the settled status scheme has concluded.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190491","190491"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005660","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that local elections in Turkey planned to take place in March 2019 are conducted in a free and fair manner.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190391","190391"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005661","2018-11-14","Department for International Development","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, what recent steps his Department is taking to support the humanitarian needs and safe return of the estimated 30,000 Anglophone refugees who have fled into Nigeria during the recent violence in Cameroon.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190392","190392"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005662","2018-11-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps the Government plans to take to increase food (a) production and (b) security when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190380","190380"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005663","2018-11-14","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the risk of liability to sanctions by the US of the Society for Worldwide Interbank Financial Telecommunication if it continues to process financial transactions from Iranian banks.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190393","190393"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005664","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effectiveness of encouraging people who smoke to switch to vaping to help them stop smoking.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190458","190458"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005665","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent comparative assessment he has made of the effect on health of (a) smoking and (b) vaping.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190459","190459"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005666","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps he is taking to make people who smoke aware of the effects on public health of vaping.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190460","190460"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005667","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the July 2018 report of the Science and Technology Committee on E-cigarettes HC 505, what assessment he has made of the potential effectiveness of urgently reviewing the policies of local stop smoking services on vape products.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190461","190461"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005668","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, which body is responsible for providing health information on vape products to smokers.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190462","190462"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005669","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department is taking steps to encourage smokers to take up vaping as one method of stopping smoking; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190463","190463"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005670","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effectiveness of removing vape products from the definition of tobacco products in the EU Tobacco Products Directive; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190464","190464"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005671","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the UK's potential ability to tackle (a) the concentration limit on nicotine in vape bottles, (b) the size of those bottles and (c) other aspects of the EU Tobacco Products Directive after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190465","190465"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005672","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the potential effect on public health of amending the Tobacco and Related Products Regulations 2016 after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190466","190466"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005673","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of current regulations in ensuring (a) the growth of the vaping sector and (b) high product manufacturing standards for consumers after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190467","190467"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005674","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether (a) nicotine shots and (b) shortfills are regulated under (i) UK and (ii) EU law.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190468","190468"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005675","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the (a) effectiveness of the regulation of non-nicotine liquid for vape products and (b) effect on public health of (i) shortfills and (ii) nicotine shots.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190469","190469"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005676","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what evidence his Department has collated on effect on people's health of the use of (a) Snus and (b) tobacco.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190470","190470"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005677","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make it his policy to direct  Public Health England to include the effect of Snus on people's health in future evidence reviews.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190471","190471"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005678","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of lifting the ban on Snus products.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190472","190472"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005679","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the accuracy of recent press reports on threats to members of the LGBT community in Tanzania.","Biography information for Christian Matheson","Christian Matheson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190481","190481"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005680","2018-11-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what assessment he has made of the validity of reports that local authorities are excluding people from social housing waiting lists due to (a) a history of rent arrears, (b) criminal convictions and (c) experience of rough sleeping.","Biography information for Bob Blackman","Bob Blackman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190431","190431"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005681","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many foreign-born UK armed forces service personnel have had an (a) Indefinite Leave to Remain and (b) citizenship application denied on the grounds of not meeting the good character requirement in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jo Stevens","Jo Stevens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190492","190492"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005682","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November to Question 186975 on Road Traffic Offences, whether the annual cost to the public purse of speed awareness courses is in the region of one hundred million pounds annually.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190381","190381"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005683","2018-11-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to the Home Office's news story entitled New fund to support vulnerable EU citizens apply for settled status, published on 25 October 2018, for what reasons that fund has been set up rather than his Department extending provision of legal aid to cover vulnerable EU citizens applying for pre-settled and settled status.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190453","190453"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005684","2018-11-15","Department for International Trade","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what plans his Department has to develop trade links with countries outside the EU in the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190382","190382"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005685","2018-11-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what estimate he has made of the number of people being held in prisons by the expected end of this Parliament.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190383","190383"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005686","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will publish the total number of asylum seekers accommodated in each local authority area in England, Scotland and Wales through the asylum dispersal programme in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Alex Cunningham","Alex Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190457","190457"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005687","2018-11-14","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what proportion of contracts issued by his Department and contractors include provisions to impose, as between parties to the subcontract, that any payment due from the contractor to a subcontractor under the contract is to be made no later than the end of a period of 30 days from the date on which the relevant invoice is regarded as valid and undisputed, as required by the Public Contract Regulations 2015.","Biography information for Jon Trickett","Jon Trickett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190359","190359"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005688","2018-11-14","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what assessment he has made of the progress of UK banks in ring-fencing retail services from investment banking.","Biography information for Ruth Cadbury","Ruth Cadbury","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190479","190479"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005689","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will support the British Society of Paediatric Dentistry campaign to encourage parents to take their children to the dentist before they are one year old.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190425","190425"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005690","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 17 October 2018 to Question 177313 on Driving under Influence, what assessment he has made of (a) the effectiveness of the rigorous enforcement and serious penalties for drink drivers; and (b) trends in the level of breath test performed between 2011 and 2015.","Biography information for Jim Shannon","Jim Shannon","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190473","190473"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005692","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether the Child Maintenance Service allocates an individual's payments first to their historical collection charges and then to their existing child maintenance liabilities.","Biography information for Martin Whitfield","Martin Whitfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190514","190514"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005693","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what (a) representations he has received and (b) assessment he has made of the implications for the constitution of Kosovo of proposals to change the Kosovo Security Force into a national army.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190394","190394"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005694","2018-11-14","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  if his Department will undertake a review of the length of time it takes for visa application decisions to be expedited for those experiencing financial hardship, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190505","190505"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005695","2018-11-14","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  if his Department will undertake a review of time taken for visa application decisions to be expedited for those applying for leave to remain on under Article 8 of the European Convention of Human Rights, and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Martyn Day","Martyn Day","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190506","190506"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005697","2018-11-15","Cabinet Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent assessment he has made of the level of compliance of Departments with their duty under the Equality Act 2010 to provide accessible documents for disabled people.","Biography information for Marsha De Cordova","Marsha De Cordova","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190516","190516"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005698","2018-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that agricultural products and food produced to lower standards than those of the UK are not imported and do not undermine UK agricultural production.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190414","190414"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005699","2018-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether a programme of capital grants will be continued and apply throughout the UK to assist farmers in adopting methods of agricultural production that maximise efficiency, environmental responsibility and welfare improvements.","Biography information for Daniel Kawczynski","Daniel Kawczynski","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190415","190415"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005700","2018-11-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he is taking to ensure that there is adequate veterinary capacity to meet the demand for (a) rabies (i) vaccinations and (ii) testing and (b) the issuing of health certificates for pets travelling to the EU in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190334","190334"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005701","2018-11-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether pet owners will be compensated for following Government advice on preparing for the UK leaving the EU without a deal by paying for blood titre testing of rabies antibody levels ahead of travelling to the EU after 29 March 2019 in the event that an agreement is then reached.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190335","190335"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005702","2018-11-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps he is taking to ensure that the transition to a new single authority in Buckinghamshire will not affect existing programmes to improve the provision of Children's Services.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190318","190318"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005703","2018-11-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what recent estimate he has made of the savings to be accrued as a result of the establishment of a single unitary district council in Buckinghamshire.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190319","190319"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005704","2018-11-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what additional financial support he plans to provide to the district councils in Buckinghamshire to enable them to fulfil the requirement to support town and parish councils in the production of neighbourhood plans during the period of preparation for a new single unitary district council.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190320","190320"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005705","2018-11-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the financial reserves held at 1 November 2018 by each of the local authorities in Buckinghamshire that will be abolished by the creation of a single unitary district council.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190321","190321"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005706","2018-11-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will take steps to ensure that the existing financial reserves held by Chiltern District Council will be spent in the Chiltern District Council area.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190322","190322"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005707","2018-11-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Written Statement of 1 November on Local Government Update, HCWS1058, what discussions he has had with district councils on implementation of proposals for a new unitary district council in Buckinghamshire; and what assessment his Department has made of the merits of using existing local structures to deliver services to residents.","Biography information for Dame Cheryl Gillan","Dame Cheryl Gillan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190323","190323"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005708","2018-11-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of spending by social housing providers on increasing the energy efficiency of their housing stock over the next (a) five and (b) 10 years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190336","190336"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005709","2018-11-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate his Department has made of the spending by social housing providers on reducing fuel poverty over the next (a) five and (b) 10 years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190337","190337"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005710","2018-11-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how much Homes England plans to spend on increasing the energy efficiency of housing stock over the next (a) five and (b) 10 years.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190338","190338"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005711","2018-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, whether he has made a comparative assessment of the heat produced by kiln dried wood and house coal on a domestic fire in his consultation on cleaner domestic burning of solid fuels and wood; and if he will make statement.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190412","190412"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005712","2018-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what Government funding is available to small and medium-sized businesses to help them achieve CyberEssentials certification.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190517","190517"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005713","2018-11-15","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether his Department plans to encourage the introduction of low emission buses outside London by amending the terms of the Bus Service Operators Grant.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190426","190426"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005714","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to NHS England’s appraisal of Kuvan, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the cost offset of dietary treatments is considered in its economic assessment of the cost of commissioning new medicines.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190518","190518"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005715","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what estimate his Department has made of the financial cost offset to the NHS including savings to the NHS from reduced acquisition costs of food supplements of commissioning Kuvan for the treatment of phenylketonuria.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190519","190519"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005716","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether a single technology appraisal process or a highly specialised technology appraisal process is used for (a) phenylketonuria and (b) other rare diseases.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190520","190520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005717","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what representations his Department has received from the Police Service of Northern Ireland on resources for policing after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190499","190499"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005718","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, how many times his Department has met with representatives of the Police Service of Northern Ireland to discuss resource requirements for policing after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190500","190500"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005719","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what additional resources for policing have been requested by the Police Service of Northern Ireland for when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190501","190501"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005720","2018-11-21","Department for International Trade","2018-11-12","What progress the Government has made on its export strategy.","Biography information for Alex Burghart","Alex Burghart","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190521","190521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005721","2018-11-14","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether his Department is working with the company Vivastreet on issues pertaining to prostitution.","Biography information for Sarah Champion","Sarah Champion","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190478","190478"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005722","2018-11-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what steps the Government is taking help older people maintain access to services in a modernising court system.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190522","190522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005723","2018-11-14","Women and Equalities","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Women and Equalities, what plans the Government has to use the centenary of the Parliament (Qualification of Women) Act 1918 to encourage more women to stand for public office.","Biography information for Giles Watling","Giles Watling","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190523","190523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005724","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Sri Lankan nationals have been granted refugee status after having previously been removed to Sri Lanka following a refused application for asylum since 18 May 2009.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190330","190330"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005725","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many Sri Lankan nationals have been (a) removed to Sri Lanka and (b) removed to Sri Lanka following a refused application for asylum since 26 October 2018.","Biography information for Joan Ryan","Joan Ryan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190331","190331"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005726","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, with reference to the Office for Budget Responsibility's Economic and Fiscal Outlook published in October 2018, if he will list the thirty groups identified using the United Nations Conference on Trade and Development World Investment Report and the commercial ORBIS database that could be in scope for the Digital Services Tax announced in Budget 2018.","Biography information for Liam Byrne","Liam Byrne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190368","190368"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005727","2018-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent steps he has taken to protect bees and insects.","Biography information for Sir John Hayes","Mr John Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190347","190347"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005728","2018-11-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the protection of human rights in the Philippines.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190341","190341"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005729","2018-11-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the security situation in Libya; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190342","190342"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005730","2018-11-15","Cabinet Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate she has made of the proportion of (a) men and (b) women in employment who do not receive the national minimum wage.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190343","190343"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005731","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of universal credit on levels of rent arrears.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190455","190455"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005732","2018-11-15","Cabinet Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what estimate he has made of the levels of net migration from EU countries to (a) Coventry, (b) the West Midlands and (c) the UK since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190344","190344"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005733","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, when the UK will submit its next report on the International Labour Organization Convention 182; and whether that report will be published.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190524","190524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005734","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to universal credit, what estimate she has made of the (a) proportion of claimants who apply for an advanced payment that are successful, (b) number of claimants who seek a deferred payment of three months when repaying an advanced payment and (c) proportion of claimants who receive an advanced payment and apply successfully for a deferred payment.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190525","190525"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005735","2018-11-15","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with Cabinet colleagues on the potential effect on transport infrastructure in the West Midlands of the UK leaving the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Mr Jim Cunningham","Mr Jim Cunningham","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190345","190345"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005736","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will publish the guidance issued by her Department on the thresholds for (a) financial hardship when a universal credit claimant applies for an advanced payment and (b) exceptional circumstances when a universal credit claimant with an advance payment applies for repayments to be delayed for up to three months.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190526","190526"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005737","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what tendering process was used to commission Citizens Advice to provide Universal Support from April 2019.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190527","190527"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005738","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will place in the Library a copy of the methodology for selecting Citizens Advice to provide Universal Support.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190528","190528"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005739","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect of the transfer of provision of Universal Support to Citizens Advice on (a) local authority costs for providing and (b) local availability of Universal Support after April 2019.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190529","190529"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005740","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department carried out an equalities impact assessment on the transfer of the delivery of Universal Support from local authorities to Citizens Advice.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190530","190530"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005741","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the extent of  geographical coverage provided by Citizens Advice for the delivery of Universal Support; and what progress Citizens Advice has made on plans to deliver Universal Support in areas with no local Citizens Advice service.","Biography information for Helen Hayes","Helen Hayes","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190531","190531"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005742","2018-11-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what steps his Department has taken to apply tariff caps on electricity suppliers since the Domestic Gas and Electricity (Tariff Cap) Act 2018 received royal assent in July 2018.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190532","190532"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005743","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, whether her Department has plans to revise the payment dates for universal credit payments over Christmas and new year to allow claimants whose specified payment date is on or after 25 December 2018 to be paid more than one working day in advance of 25 December 2018.","Biography information for Ged Killen","Ged Killen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190533","190533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005744","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many applicants have been refused industrial injuries disablement benefit for prescribed disease D12 in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190497","190497"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005745","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to speed up the process by which the Civil Aviation Authority issues private pilots' licenses.","Biography information for Mr Alistair Carmichael","Mr Alistair Carmichael","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190385","190385"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005746","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department has taken to ensure that the current occupational qualification to receive industrial injuries disablement benefit for prescribed disease D12 reflects current research into the industrial causes of chronic obstructive pulmonary disease.","Biography information for Angela Crawley","Angela Crawley","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190498","190498"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005747","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, if he will set up a Young Patient Travel Fund to assist families with the travel expense of attending specialist hospitals for cancer treatment; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Caroline Lucas","Caroline Lucas","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190424","190424"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005748","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what progress his Department has made on improving the availability of support and advice for children of alcoholic parents.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190348","190348"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005749","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his Department’s priorities are for expanding support services for children of alcoholic parents.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190349","190349"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005750","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what steps his Department is taking to reduce child vulnerability to alcohol-related harm.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190350","190350"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005751","2018-11-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what issues the UK Government plans to raise at the forthcoming meeting of the EU Competitiveness Council on 29 November 2018.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190351","190351"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005752","2018-11-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government would support another country putting public country by country reporting on the agenda for the EU Competitiveness Council meeting on 29 November 2018.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190352","190352"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005753","2018-11-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what plans the UK Government has to raise the issue of public country by country reporting at the EU Competitiveness Council meeting on 29 November 2018.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190353","190353"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005754","2018-11-14","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to secure multilateral support for public country-by-country reporting.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190354","190354"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005755","2018-11-14","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps his Department has taken to secure support from EU member states for the implementation of public country-by-country reporting throughout the EU.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190355","190355"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005756","2018-11-14","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, whether he has discussed public country by country reporting at multilateral meetings in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190356","190356"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005757","2018-11-14","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions his Department has had with the Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy on discussing public country by country reporting at the EU Competitiveness Council.","Biography information for Caroline Flint","Caroline Flint","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190357","190357"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005758","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the (a) number and (b) proportion of teachers that are on the (i) main, (ii) upper, and (iii) leadership pay scales in South Cambridgeshire constituency.","Biography information for Heidi Allen","Heidi Allen","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190534","190534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005759","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, if he will change section 215 of the Highway Code to incorporate greater protections for horse riders.","Biography information for Dr Rupa Huq","Dr Rupa Huq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190535","190535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005760","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, whether he plans to impose a cap on compensation payments for the Windrush generation and their descendants.","Biography information for Stephen Twigg","Stephen Twigg","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190332","190332"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005761","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what his policy is on the application of the special administration process to NHS trusts.","Biography information for Clive Lewis","Clive Lewis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190511","190511"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005762","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many home visits to applicants for universal credit have been conducted by the Centre for Health and Disability Assessments in the Easington constituency for each year in which information is available.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190427","190427"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005763","2018-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, whether the contract given to Willis Towers Watson to calculate the pay benchmarks for Defence Equipment and Support employees was funded from the total amount allocated for pay increases in 2017.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190409","190409"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005764","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what recent assessment he has made of the effectiveness of NHS and medical professional body guidelines on the prescription of medicinal cannabis in ensuring the eligibility for prescription of patients for whom that treatment might be advantageous.","Biography information for Frank Field","Frank Field","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190361","190361"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005765","2018-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what recent assessment he has made of trends in the level of pay and working conditions of Defence Equipment and Support employees since that organisation became a bespoke trading entity.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190410","190410"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005766","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to publish the results of the most recent Children and Young People’s Mental Health prevalence survey.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190384","190384"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005767","2018-11-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2018 to Question 186951 on Leasehold: Ground Rent, what the average ground rent paid was in each region based on the the latest English Housing Survey data.","Biography information for John Healey","John Healey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190358","190358"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005768","2018-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what proportion of Defence Equipment and Support employees received pay increases at each performance rating relative to the benchmarks set out in their 2018 pay deal.","Biography information for Jessica Morden","Jessica Morden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190411","190411"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005769","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 7 November 2018 to Question 185533 on Dartford-Thurrock Crossing, if his Department will collect data about average journey times during peak hours.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190369","190369"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005770","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to help improve reliability of rail services on the Bexleyheath line in advance of the new franchise agreement being agreed for services on that line.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190370","190370"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005771","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to help improve reliability of rail services on the Crayford and Sidcup line in advance of the new franchise agreement being agreed for services on that line.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190371","190371"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005772","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to help improve reliability of rail services on the Slade Green line in advance of the new franchise agreement being agreed for services on that line.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190372","190372"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005773","2018-11-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what recent steps his Department has taken to support people with a gambling addiction.","Biography information for Sir David Evennett","Sir David Evennett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190373","190373"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005774","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the merits of revising the Highway Code to include advice by the British Horse Society's dead slow campaign on how to pass horses safely while driving.","Biography information for Kate Hoey","Kate Hoey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190333","190333"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005775","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will suspend the sanctioning regime in universal credit areas until Jobcentre staff and claimants have a better understanding of the new system.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190428","190428"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005776","2018-11-14","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Northern Ireland, what assessment she has made with the Police Services Northern Ireland of the capability of the police to meet any potential (a) threats and (b) risks as a result of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190502","190502"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005777","2018-11-14","Northern Ireland Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for State for Northern Ireland, what assessment has been made of the capability of Police Service of Northern Ireland neighbourhood policing teams to respond to threats at the border after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190503","190503"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005778","2018-11-14","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an estimate of the number of police officers stationed at each major port in each part of the UK in each of the last 12 months.","Biography information for Louise Haigh","Louise Haigh","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190504","190504"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005779","2018-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of people under 18 years of age that applied to join the army in financial year 2013-14; and how many of those people have since started army training.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190536","190536"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005780","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2018 to Question 187143 on EU Internal Trade, how his Department plans to transpose provisions from EU law into UK law involving thresholds measuring the proportion of the entire market or a specified number of grouping of member states, in the Markets in Financial Instruments Regulations Article (a) 5(1)(a) and 1(b), subparagraphs (3) to (6) and subparagraph (9), (b) Article 9(5), (c) Article 14(5) and (d) Article 36(5) in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190537","190537"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005781","2018-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what estimate he has made of the number of people under 18 years of age that applied to join the army in the financial year 2014-15; and how many of those people have since started army training.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190538","190538"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005782","2018-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence,  what estimate he has made of the number of people under 18 years of age that applied to join the army in the financial year 2016-17; and how many of those people have since started army training.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190539","190539"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005783","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2018 to Question 187143 on EU Internal Trade, how his Department plans to transpose provisions from EU law into UK law involving thresholds measuring the proportion of the entire market or a specified number of grouping of member states, in Articles 12 to 16 of the Commission Delegated Regulation amending MiFID 565/2017 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190540","190540"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005784","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, pursuant to the Answer of his Department's written answer to parliamentary question 187143, how his Department plans to transpose provisions from EU law into UK law involving thresholds measuring the proportion of the entire market or a specified number of grouping of member states, in Article 5(1)(a) and (b)) of the Commission Delegated Regulation 2017/567 in the event that the UK leaves the EU without a deal.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190541","190541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005785","2018-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps he plans to take to increase the proportion of sites of specific scientific interest monitored every six years.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190542","190542"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005786","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will remove social security sanctions in circumstances where someone is (a) pregnant and (b) caring for a severely disabled person.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190429","190429"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005787","2018-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of people on boards of museums sponsored by his Department are (a) BAME and (b) female.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190375","190375"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005788","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that all airports reach at least a good standard of accessibility as measured by the Civil Aviation Authority.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190482","190482"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005789","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, with reference to page 53 of the Government's White Paper entitled Improving lives: the future of work, health and disability, in November 2017, what progress her Department has made with Initiative No.5 on reform of the work capability assessment; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190483","190483"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005790","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if her Department will make an assessment of the potential merits of reintroducing a disability employment target that measures progress against employment levels of non-disabled people.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190484","190484"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005791","2018-11-14","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what impact assessments have been conducted by the Government on the effect of the UK leaving the EU on the disabled community as a protected characteristic.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190485","190485"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005792","2018-11-14","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, which groups his Department has consulted to help ensure that the interests of disabled people are safeguarded in the process of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190486","190486"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005793","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure the inclusion of physically disabled children in schooling.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190487","190487"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005794","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to the report entitled It might be best if you looked elsewhere: An investigation into the schools admission process, whether his Department has acted on the recommendations made in that report.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190488","190488"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005795","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to help ensure that disabled people have fair and equal opportunities to become successful business leaders.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190489","190489"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005796","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department’s new strategy based on prevention will aim to prevent the onset of mental health disabilities.","Biography information for Dr Lisa Cameron","Dr Lisa Cameron","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190490","190490"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005797","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what the Government’s policy is on the status of the UN-led Geneva-based peace talks on Syria as the sole legitimate framework for a political solution to the civil war in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190395","190395"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005798","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of progress on the establishment of a Constitutional Committee in Syria under UN auspices, following the Syrian national dialogue conference held in Sochi in January 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190396","190396"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005799","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with his counterparts in (a) Russia and (b) Iran on the establishment of a Constitutional Committee in Syria under UN auspices, following the Syrian national dialogue conference held in Sochi in January 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190397","190397"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005800","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the number of members of (a) the High Negotiations Committee, (b) the Syrian Democratic Council, (c) the Kurdish National Council, (d) Local Coordination Committees, (e) Local councils and (f) other Syrian opposition groups that will be represented on the proposed Constitutional Committee in Syria.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190398","190398"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005801","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the scale of the damage caused to each Palestinian refugee camp in Syria as a result of the civil war in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190399","190399"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005802","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the effect on the prospects for the safe repatriation of Palestinian refugees displaced from Syria by the civil war in that country of the damage caused to Palestinian refugee camps in (a) Yarmouk, (b) Deraa and (c) elsewhere in Syria.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190400","190400"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005803","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent assessment he has made of the progress made in meeting the target number of work permits to be issued to Syrian refugees in Jordan under the EU-Jordan compact.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190401","190401"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005804","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has received on the (a) arrest and (b) arbitrary detention of (i) sub-Saharan migrants with valid residency permits and (b) other sub-Saharan migrants by the authorities in Morocco since June 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190402","190402"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005805","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what estimate he has made of the number of sub-Saharan African migrants (a) forcibly displaced and (b) expelled by the authorities in Morocco since June 2018.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190403","190403"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005806","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what recent representations he has made to his Moroccan counterpart on the human rights of (a) migrants, (b) asylum seekers and (c) refugees in that country.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190404","190404"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005807","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made a recent assessment of the effect of the anti-human smuggling law adopted by Niger in 2015 on the rate of human smuggling in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190405","190405"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005808","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, whether he has made a recent assessment of the effect of training provided to local security forces in Niger through the EU common security and defence policy field office in Agadez on the rate of human smuggling in that country; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190406","190406"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005809","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what assessment he has made of the progress  by the (a) EU Emergency Trust Fund for Africa and (b) EU Partnership Framework for Third Countries in establishing alternative means of income to the human smuggling trade in Niger.","Biography information for Emily Thornberry","Emily Thornberry","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190407","190407"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005810","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, if she will a publish a list of newspapers in which adverts on the change to the state pension age for women were placed since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190376","190376"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005811","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many letters were sent notifying recipients of the change in the state pension age for women since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190377","190377"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005812","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, on what date the first letters notifying recipients of the change in the state pension age for women were sent since 2010.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190378","190378"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005813","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the October 2015 document Building the Right Support: A national implementation plan to develop community services and close inpatient facilities, how many hospital beds at the Calderstones site have been closed.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190445","190445"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005814","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effectiveness of the implementation of each local plan in the fast-track areas referred to in the October 2015 document Building the Right Support: A national implementation plan to develop community services and close inpatient facilities.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190446","190446"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005815","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many beds for people with learning disabilities and autism have been closed since 2015 in each of the six fast-track areas referred to in the October 2015 document Building the Right Support: A national implementation plan to develop  community services and close inpatient facilities.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190447","190447"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005816","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many of the 49 new Transforming Care Partnerships had agreed implementation plans for the delivery of co-ordinated services by the April 2016 deadline referred to in the October 2015 document Building the Right Support: A national implementation plan to develop community services and close inpatient facilities.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190448","190448"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005817","2018-11-15","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what assessment he has made of the potential merits of increasing the national funding rate for sixth form students.","Biography information for Rosie Cooper","Rosie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190408","190408"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005818","2018-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what assessment he has made of the effect of burn pits used to dispose of military waste on the health of people who served in the British armed forces in Iraq and Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190543","190543"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005819","2018-11-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, What discussions he has had with steel companies on the effect of US steel tariffs on the UK steel sector.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190544","190544"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005820","2018-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what health guidance was issued to armed forces personnel who were exposed to military burn pits during their service in the 2003 Iraq War.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190545","190545"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005821","2018-11-15","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what support his Department provides to former armed forces personnel who have health concerns relating to their exposure to military burn pits during the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan.","Biography information for Tulip Siddiq","Tulip Siddiq","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190546","190546"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005822","2018-11-15","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he has taken to ensure that (a) the rail industry is ready for the timetable changes due to be implemented on 9 December 2018 and (b) those changes will be delivered without adverse effects on passengers.","Biography information for Mohammad Yasin","Mohammad Yasin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190547","190547"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005823","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 24 October 2018 to Question 180166 on Shipping: training, whether the three-year pilot of the ratings training option has been extended; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190442","190442"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005824","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2018 to Question 185578 on Ferries: Registration, how many roll-on roll-off ferries on the (a) UK and (b) Red Ensign registers are UK-owned.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190443","190443"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005825","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, pursuant to the written answer of 6 November 2018 to Question 185578 on Ferries: Registration, what the Maritime and Coastguard Agency-agreed safe crewing level is on each roll-on roll-off ferry on the (a) UK and (b) Red Ensign registers.","Biography information for Karl Turner","Karl Turner","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190444","190444"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005826","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether the Government plans to increase funding for end-of-life care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190548","190548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005827","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what powers Ofsted has to investigate the (a) level of and (b) reason for school exclusions through its (i) school inspections and (ii) joint area inspections with the Care Quality Commission.","Biography information for Julie Cooper","Julie Cooper","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190480","190480"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005828","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what steps the Government is taking to ensure that the social housing system supports people with mental health problems.","Biography information for Thelma Walker","Thelma Walker","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190549","190549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005829","2018-11-15","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what discussions he has had with (a) the Home Secretary and (b) his counterpart in Pakistan on offering asylum in the UK to Asia Bibi and her family.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190550","190550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005830","2018-11-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) service personnel and (b) veterans have been awarded (i) a War Disablement Pension and (ii) lump sum compensation for mesothelioma in each year since December 2015.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190551","190551"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005831","2018-11-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how much money was loaned to (a) service personnel and (b) veterans through the Armed Forces Credit Union between (i) October 2015 and October 2017 and (ii) October 2017 and October 2018.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190552","190552"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005832","2018-11-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, how many (a) service personnel and (b) veterans have received payroll and pension deductions for the purposes of savings and loans in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190553","190553"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005833","2018-11-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, what the average loan amount was to members of the Armed Forces Credit Union in the last period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Jamie Stone","Jamie Stone","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190554","190554"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005834","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many home assessments have been provided for universal credit claimants in the (a) London borough of Lewisham and (b) Lewisham Deptford constituency.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190507","190507"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005835","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many home assessments have been provided for personal independence payment claimants living in the (a) London borough of Lewisham and (b) Lewisham Deptford constituency in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190508","190508"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005836","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claims have been made for universal credit hardship payments in the (a) London borough of Lewisham and (b) Lewisham Deptford constituency.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190509","190509"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005837","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to the Government of Israel on the negotiations regarding the status of Khan al-Ahmar; and with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for the Middle East of 4 July 2018, Official Report column 323, what urgent steps he is taking to demonstrate the international community’s support for that community.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190555","190555"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005838","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what discussions the Government has had with the family of Asia Bibi on granting them asylum following her release from prison in Pakistan.","Biography information for Wayne David","Wayne David","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190374","190374"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005839","2018-11-14","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many landlords who own properties in the (a) London borough of Lewisham and b) Lewisham Deptford constituency are on the Government's register of rogue landlords.","Biography information for Vicky Foxcroft","Vicky Foxcroft","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190510","190510"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005840","2018-11-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what recent assessment he has made of the contribution to the UK economy of (a) design and (b) design skills.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190416","190416"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005841","2018-11-14","Department for International Trade","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what assessment he has made of the economic contribution of (a) design and (b) design skills to UK exports.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190417","190417"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005842","2018-11-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, how much money the Government has received from the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme (a) since 1994 and (b) in each of the last three financial years for which data is available.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190420","190420"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005843","2018-11-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, whether the Government has made direct payments to the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme under the guarantee arrangements.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190421","190421"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005844","2018-11-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what sums are held in the investment reserve fund for the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190422","190422"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005845","2018-11-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate he has made of the value of digital design to (a) the UK economy and (b) UK exports.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190418","190418"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005846","2018-11-15","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the sums that the Government will receive from the Mineworkers' Pension Scheme in (a) 2018-19, (b) 2019-20 and (c) 2020-21.","Biography information for Gloria De Piero","Gloria De Piero","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190423","190423"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005847","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what plans he has to promote and support the development of design skills as part of STEM education.","Biography information for Mr Edward Vaizey","Mr Edward Vaizey","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190419","190419"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005848","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to support the development of hydrogen fuelled heavy duty vehicles.","Biography information for Steve Double","Steve Double","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190495","190495"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005849","2018-11-14","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of the allocation of funds to the Tyne and Wear Fire and Rescue Service; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190362","190362"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005850","2018-11-14","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what financial support his Department provides to the Tyne and Wear Fire and Rescue Service.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190363","190363"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005851","2018-11-14","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how much central Government funding the Tyne and Wear Fire and Rescue Service has received in each year since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190364","190364"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005852","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, with reference to Budget 2018, how much of the the £420 million to be provided to councils to fix potholes and carry out other road repairs will be allocated to (a) South Tyneside Council and (b) Gateshead Council.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190365","190365"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005853","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what her Department's policy is on supporting benefit claimants who must pay for the funeral of a family member; and if her Department will introduce an allowance for benefit claimants who must pay for the funeral of a family member to ensure that their benefit claims are not adversely affected.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190493","190493"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005854","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to Budget 2018 how much of the £400 million capital funding for schools will be allocated to schools in (a) Jarrow Constituency, (b) South Tyneside, (c) Tyne and Wear and (d) the North East.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190366","190366"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005855","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent representations she has received from women in Jarrow constituency affected by measures taken to equalise the state pension age; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Stephen Hepburn","Mr Stephen Hepburn","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190367","190367"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005856","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with (a) sight loss or (b) a visual impairment that are new claimants of personal independence payments (PIP) did not receive an award during their initial PIP assessment but received an award at (a) mandatory reconsideration and (b) tribunal in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Chris Stephens","Chris Stephens","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190496","190496"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005857","2018-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2018 to Question 187322 on Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport: Departmental Responsibilities, if he will publish an official note of his meeting with the hon Member for Shipley and the hon Member for Tewkesbury.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190386","190386"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005858","2018-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2018 to Question 187322 on Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport: Departmental Responsibilities, whether the commercial terms of the takeover of Ladbrokes by GVC was discussed at his meeting with the hon Member for Shipley and the hon Member for Tewkesbury.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190387","190387"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005859","2018-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November to 2018 to Question 187322 on Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport: Departmental Responsibilities, whether officials in his Department were present at his meeting with the hon Member for Shipley and the hon Member for Tewkesbury.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190388","190388"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005860","2018-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether he has met any representatives from (a) the Association of British Bookmakers and (b) the Remote Gambling Association since his appointment.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190389","190389"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005861","2018-11-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2018 to Question 172523 on Prisons: Private Sector, when his Department stopped holding data on the number of staff certified under Section 89 of the Criminal Justice Act 1991.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190556","190556"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005862","2018-11-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2018 to Question 172523 on Prisons: Private Sector, for what reason his Department stopped holding data on the number of staff at each privately operated prison certified under Section 89 of the Criminal Justice Act 1991.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190557","190557"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005863","2018-11-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2018 to Question 172523 on Prisons: Private Sector, what grades of staff are covered by the term funded posts.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190558","190558"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005864","2018-11-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 18 September 2018 to Question 172523, on Prisons: Private Sector, who decides (a) which posts are classed as funded posts and (b) the number of funded posts.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190559","190559"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005865","2018-11-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many new Officer Certificates under Section 89 of the Criminal Justice Act 1991 have been issued by his Department in each month since January 2018.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190560","190560"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005866","2018-11-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, how many officer certificates under Section 89 of the Criminal Justice Act 1991 have been withdrawn by his Department in each month since January 2018.","Biography information for Liz Saville Roberts","Liz Saville Roberts","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190561","190561"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005867","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, if he will publish the report prepared by KPMG on behalf of the Association of British Bookmakers which was submitted to his Department as part of its consultations on the reduction in maximum stakes on fixed odds betting terminals and increasing remote gaming duty.","Biography information for Tom Watson","Tom Watson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190390","190390"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005868","2018-11-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what plans he has to commence Section 151 of the Criminal Justice Act 2003; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Emma Reynolds","Emma Reynolds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190456","190456"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005869","2018-11-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what steps his Department is taking to implement the forthcoming cyber security skills strategy; and what plans his Department has to consult the devolved Administrations on that strategy.","Biography information for Margaret Beckett","Margaret Beckett","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190346","190346"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005870","2018-11-15","Department for International Trade","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Trade, what meetings he has had with companies that source palm oil in their supply chain as part of preparing for future trade deals after the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Bill Esterson","Bill Esterson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190454","190454"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005871","2018-11-15","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what proportion of people on the boards of bodies sponsored by his Department are (a) BAME and (b) female.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190379","190379"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005872","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to Answer of 5 November 2018 to Question 907432 on Housing Benefit, how much discretionary housing payment was (a) awarded to and (b) spent by North East Lincolnshire Council in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190450","190450"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005873","2018-11-15","Department for Transport","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress has been made on confirming the final proposed route for Crossrail 2.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190562","190562"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005874","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to Answer of 5 November to Question 907432 on Housing Benefit, how much discretionary housing payment was (a) awarded to and (b) spent by East Riding of Yorkshire Council in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190451","190451"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005875","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what steps the National Retail Crime Steering Group has taken to tackle violence in the retail sector.","Biography information for Graham P Jones","Graham P Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190430","190430"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005876","2018-11-15","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's news story entitled Record numbers learning instruments in class thanks to music hubs, published on 24 October 2018, how many pupils were taught an instrument in class in each region in 2016-17.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190474","190474"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005877","2018-11-15","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's news story entitled Record numbers learning instruments in class thanks to music hubs, published on 24 October 2018, how many of those music hubs are located in each region.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190475","190475"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005878","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, when his Department plans to publish the progress review on Building the Right Support: A national implementation plan to develop community services and close inpatient facilities.","Biography information for Luciana Berger","Luciana Berger","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190449","190449"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005879","2018-11-15","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, with reference to his Department's news story entitled Record numbers learning instruments in class thanks to music hubs, published on 24 October 2018, how many schools benefited from such music hubs in each of the region in 2016-17.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190476","190476"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005880","2018-11-15","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, with reference to his Department's press release entitled Ministry of Justice secures extra £52 million for targeted expenditure, published in 30 October 2018, how much of the £52 million for targeted expenditure is planned to be allocated to help reduce violence in prisons in South Yorkshire.","Biography information for Dan Jarvis","Dan Jarvis","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190477","190477"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005881","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what recent assessment her Department has of trends in the level of incidences of (a) stress, (b) anxiety and (c) depression in the workplace.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190563","190563"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005882","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what steps her Department is taking to provide (a) compensation and (b) repayments to claimants who were underpaid employment and support allowance.","Biography information for Hugh Gaffney","Hugh Gaffney","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190564","190564"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005883","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of people over 65 years old that are are homeless in (a) the London Borough of Southwark, (b) London and (c) England.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190326","190326"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005884","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, how many people in receipt of a state pension are recognised as homeless in (a) London Borough of Southwark, (b) London and (c) the UK.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190327","190327"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005885","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of children with autism living in temporary accommodation in (a) London Borough of Southwark, (b) London and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190328","190328"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005886","2018-11-15","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, what estimate he has made of the number of adults with autism that are homeless in (a) London Borough of Southwark, (b) London and (c) England in each of the last five years.","Biography information for Ms Harriet Harman","Ms Harriet Harman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190329","190329"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005887","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the effect on (a) the Post Office and (b) Postmaster pay of encouraging universal credit claimants to use a bank account to receive payments.","Biography information for Marion Fellows","Marion Fellows","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190494","190494"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005888","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November 2018 to Question 907432 on Housing Benefit, how much discretionary housing payment was (a) awarded to and (b) spent by Kingston-upon-Hull City Council in each of the last three years.","Biography information for Nic Dakin","Nic Dakin","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190452","190452"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005889","2018-11-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, what estimate he has made of the cost of a barrel of crude oil over the next 12 months.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190432","190432"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005890","2018-11-15","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, whether his Department has undertaken a baseline audit of levels of (a) investment, (b) capacity and (c) in (i) inpatient and (ii) community services for adults with eating disorders.","Biography information for Anneliese Dodds","Anneliese Dodds","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190565","190565"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005891","2018-11-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, when the Parliamentary Under Secretary of State last visited a family court in his official capacity.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190433","190433"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005892","2018-11-15","Department for International Development","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, how many projects funded by her Department support the long-term needs of victims of (a) explosive violence, (b) land mines and (c) other weapons.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190566","190566"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005893","2018-11-15","Department for International Development","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for International Development, if she will publish the programmes to (a) promote peace-building and (b) prevent conflict that are in receipt of funding by her Department.","Biography information for Dan Carden","Dan Carden","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190567","190567"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005894","2018-11-15","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, pursuant to the Answer of 12 November 2018 to Question 188901 on on Government Departments: Disclosure of Information, how many non-disclosure agreements comprise a limited number.","Biography information for Layla Moran","Layla Moran","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190568","190568"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005895","2018-11-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations he has received on the implementation by local authorities of (a) the Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities involving animals) (England) Regulations 2018 and (b) the statutory guidance on home boarding and dog stay care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190324","190324"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005896","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many 101 calls have been (a) unanswered and (b) abandoned in the last 12 months.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190569","190569"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005897","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, what the average time is that a caller to the 101 number has waited for their call to be answered in the last (a) six and (b) 12 months.","Biography information for Peter Kyle","Peter Kyle","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190570","190570"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005898","2018-11-15","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what representations he has received on the implementation of (a) the Animal Welfare (Licensing of Activities involving animals) (England) Regulations 2018 and (b) the statutory guidance on home boarding and dog day care; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Sir Desmond Swayne","Sir Desmond Swayne","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190325","190325"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005899","2018-11-15","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many benefit claimants have been migrated to universal credit since June 2018 in (a) the Merthyr Tydfil County Borough Council area and (b) the South Wales Region; and what percentage of benefit claimants have been migrated to universal credit since June 2018 in (i) the Merthyr Tydfil County Borough Council area and (ii) the South Wales Region.","Biography information for Gerald Jones","Gerald Jones","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190512","190512"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005900","2018-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, how many new licences to cull badgers he plans to issue in badger cull areas in the next twelve months; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190339","190339"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005901","2018-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what recent discussions he has had with landowning bodies about the need to cover complete badger cull areas.","Biography information for Mr Laurence Robertson","Mr Laurence Robertson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190340","190340"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005902","2018-11-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, pursuant to the Answer of 3 July 2018 to Question 157090 on Ministry of Justice: Buildings, how many days each Minister in his Department spent in Petty France between 4 September 2017 and 4 October 2017.","Biography information for Philip Davies","Philip Davies","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190413","190413"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005903","2018-11-15","Cabinet Office","2018-11-12","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to page 51 of the National Cyber Security Strategy 2016 to 2021, what recent estimate he has made of the cost per annum to Government of procuring private sector cryptography skills and technologies.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190571","190571"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005904","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what guidance his Department has issued to schools to help them manage their cost pressures.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190434","190434"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005905","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what estimate he has made of the public purse of supporting the introduction of the national funding formula.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190435","190435"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005906","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that the EBACC allows young people to keep their future education options open.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190436","190436"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005907","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to reduce the attainment gap in early years education.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190437","190437"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005908","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what recent steps his Department has taken to improve options for young people outside of academic study and qualifications.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190438","190438"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005909","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that teaching is an attractive and fulfilling profession.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190439","190439"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005910","2018-11-15","Treasury","2018-11-12","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what estimate he has made of the take-up the VAT flat rate scheme (a) in actual numbers and (b) in terms of the percentage of eligible companies.","Biography information for Sir Graham Brady","Sir Graham Brady","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190360","190360"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005911","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps the Government is taking to remove barriers preventing students from disadvantaged backgrounds participate in further education.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190440","190440"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1005912","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-12","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps his Department is taking to improve the provision of education services to children with a hearing impairment.","Biography information for Dr Matthew Offord","Dr Matthew Offord","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 190441","190441"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003576","2018-11-14","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the adequacy of support for the Civil Legal Advice housing and debt telephone service in order to ensure continued provision of specialist advice and assistance through contracted firms and that those firms are properly paid for the services they provide.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189790","189790"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003577","2018-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, if he will make an assessment of the potential merits of applying the so-called escape fee to the Civil Legal Advice scheme to ensure that advisers are paid above the fixed fees that apply where costs exceed the national fixed fee by a multiplier of three, in line with other parts of the Legal Aid system.","Biography information for Tonia Antoniazzi","Tonia Antoniazzi","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189791","189791"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003578","2018-11-13","Cabinet Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, what recent estimate he has made of the average day rate paid by the Government for contracted in staff working on digital projects.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189792","189792"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003579","2018-11-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 164527 on Buildings: Insulation, what assessment he has made of the level of risk combustible cladding poses to (a) schools, (b) care homes and (c) hospitals.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189775","189775"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003580","2018-11-13","Department for Education","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, pursuant to the Answer of 25 July 2018 to Question 164527 on Buildings: Insulation, what estimate the Government has made of the number of planned (a) school, (b) hospital and (c) care home buildings where (i) planning permission has been granted or (ii) work has commenced on site and which include the use of combustible cladding or insulation.","Biography information for Chris Elmore","Chris Elmore","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189840","189840"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003581","2018-11-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what assessment he has made of the effect of recent reductions to the local authority public health grant on health inequalities at a (a) regional and (b) socio-economic group level.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189625","189625"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003582","2018-11-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to the report entitled Taking our health for granted: plugging the public health grant funding gap, published in October 2018, what assessment he has made of the implications for his policies of that report's finding that the reduction in public health spending per person will be 23.5% between 2014-15 and 2019-20.","Biography information for Mrs Sharon Hodgson","Mrs Sharon Hodgson","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189626","189626"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003583","2018-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what assessment has been made of the ability of sponsors to meet the costs of legal advice on completing refugee family reunion applications.","Biography information for Bambos Charalambous","Bambos Charalambous","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189787","189787"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003584","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate his Department has made of the number of additional full-time equivalent permanent members of staff that will need to be employed by the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency to cover the work dealing with European Conference of Ministers of Transport permit applications after the UK leaves the EU; and where such staff are planned to be based.","Biography information for Grahame Morris","Grahame Morris","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189661","189661"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003585","2018-11-13","Department for Education","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what representations he has received from bodies in the education sector on the potential effect of the ending of supplementary funding in 2019-20 on the number of maintained nursery schools.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189793","189793"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003586","2018-11-14","Home Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to (a) the Asylum Migration and Integration Fund and (b) other sources of funding available to his Department, what recent steps his Department has taken to develop and implement new guidance on the conduct of asylum interviews, and how the effectiveness of that guidance is being monitored and evaluated; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Ian Murray","Ian Murray","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189650","189650"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003587","2018-11-14","Treasury","2018-11-09","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what steps he is taking to publicise the Help to Save scheme to working families.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189603","189603"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003588","2018-11-14","Home Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, how many people living in Northern Ireland who were born in the Irish Republic after 1948 have been unable to obtain a UK passport.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189604","189604"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003589","2018-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what steps his Department is taking to increase the red squirrel population over the next five years.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189605","189605"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003590","2018-11-14","Cabinet Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Minister for the Cabinet Office, with reference to recommendations outlined in the Electoral Commission's statutory evaluation of the 2018 voter ID pilot schemes, what guidance the Government will be providing for the May 2019 voter ID pilot schemes.","Biography information for Cat Smith","Cat Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189733","189733"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003591","2018-11-14","Ministry of Defence","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Defence, on how many occasions Army bomb disposal teams in Northern Ireland were called out between (a) 1 July 2014 and 30 June 2016 and (b) 1 July 2016 and 30 June 2018 as a result of (i) viable and (ii) hoax devices.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189606","189606"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003592","2018-11-15","Home Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department,  what estimate he has made of the number of people who made an illegal sea crossing from north Africa to Europe between April and October 2018.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189607","189607"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003593","2018-11-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department has any plans to extend the availability of the National Cyber Security Centre's Mail check tool to those with private sector email addresses.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189794","189794"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003594","2018-11-13","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, if he will take steps with his international counterparts to impose sanctions on the leading figures in the Venezuelan Maduro regime.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189833","189833"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003595","2018-11-14","Home Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department’s announcement of 25 October 2018, New fund to support vulnerable EU citizens apply for settled status, whether that grant funding will be available to law firms.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189673","189673"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003596","2018-11-13","Home Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, with reference to his Department’s announcement of 25 October 2018 of a new fund to support vulnerable EU citizens apply for settled status, what assessment his Department has made of (a) the number of voluntary and community organisations which will be able to receive funds under this scheme, (b) the geographical coverage of those organisations and (c) whether the level of funding will be sufficient to meet demand for that support.","Biography information for Paul Blomfield","Paul Blomfield","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189674","189674"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003597","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, what representations he has made to his Pakistani counterpart on religious freedom in that country since the Pakistani Supreme Court ruling on Asia Bibi.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189608","189608"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003598","2018-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, if he will hold discussions with the US Administration on the importation of American hormone-free beef products for when the UK leaves the EU.","Biography information for Mr Gregory Campbell","Mr Gregory Campbell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189609","189609"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003599","2018-11-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, with reference to the oral contribution of the Minister for Universities, Science, Research and Innovation, of 16 October 2018, Official Report, column 494, what the projects are for which Cammell Laird has received £150 million.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189726","189726"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003600","2018-11-13","Ministry of Housing, Communities and Local Government","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Housing, Communities and Local Government, if he will publish the (a) people and (b) organisations that were invited to the roundtable event on leasehold reform on Thursday 8 November.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189727","189727"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003601","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many claimants in Inverclyde were in receipt of severe disability premium before transferring to universal credit.","Biography information for Ronnie Cowan","Ronnie Cowan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189739","189739"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003602","2018-11-13","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations she has received from the public on universal credit; and how many of those representations were (a) positive and (b) negative of its introduction.","Biography information for Justin Madders","Justin Madders","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189728","189728"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003603","2018-11-14","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how much has been spent by (a) Health Education England and (b) Lewisham and Greenwich NHS Trust on (i) legal fees and (ii) other costs associated with defending legal action brought by Dr Chris Day.","Biography information for Norman Lamb","Norman Lamb","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189610","189610"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003604","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what assessment her Department has made of the potential dangers associated with the use of the chemical Dichloromethane in the workplace.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189520","189520"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003605","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis who were previously in receipt of disability living allowance and have undergone a reassessment for personal independence payments applied for mandatory reconsideration of the decision in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189521","189521"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003606","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis who were in receipt of disability living allowance and have undergone a reassessment for personal independence payments appealed the decision at tribunal in each year since 2013; and how many of those people had (a) the decision overturned and (b) their mobility award increased from none or standard rate to the higher rate.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189522","189522"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003607","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, how many people with multiple sclerosis who are new claimants of personal independence payments (PIP) did not receive an award during their initial PIP assessment but subsequently received an award at (a) mandatory reconsideration and (b) tribunal in each year since 2013.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189523","189523"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003608","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what the average waiting time was for payment of universal credit for a claimant diagnosed with terminal cancer and a prognosis of  less than six months to live in the most recent period for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stephen Timms","Stephen Timms","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189524","189524"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003609","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made of the capital contribution required by his Department to ensure the delivery of (a) southern rail access and (b) western rail access into Heathrow airport.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189684","189684"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003610","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the effect on (a) air pollution, (b) noise pollution and (c) congestion of lifting the air traffic movement cap at Heathrow Airport.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189685","189685"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003611","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps he is taking to ensure that expansion at Heathrow airport is compatible with legal air quality limits.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189841","189841"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003612","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, whether he has received assurances from Heathrow Airport that there are no plans to increase landing charges; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189686","189686"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003613","2018-11-14","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what his Department's definition is of private finance in relation to infrastructure projects.","Biography information for Zac Goldsmith","Zac Goldsmith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189687","189687"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003614","2018-11-13","Department for Education","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what proportion of (a) children and (b) children eligible for free schools meals reached a Good Level of Development at age five in Bury North in each of the last three years.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189795","189795"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003615","2018-11-14","Department for Education","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, when he plans to respond to the letter of 12 September 2018 from the hon. Member for Croydon North on Chestnut Park Primary School and the early identification of social, emotional and mental health needs in children and young people.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189693","189693"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003616","2018-11-13","Treasury","2018-11-09","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Governor of the Bank of England on managing the risk to the financial system posed by climate change.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189774","189774"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003617","2018-11-13","Treasury","2018-11-09","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Governor of the Bank of England on the effect of climate change on the Bank’s ability to preserve macroeconomic stability.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189842","189842"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003618","2018-11-13","Treasury","2018-11-09","To ask the Chancellor of the Exchequer, what discussions he has had with the Governor of the Bank of England on the Bank’s role in mobilising finance for the low-carbon transition.","Biography information for Catherine West","Catherine West","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189843","189843"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003619","2018-11-14","Home Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for the Home Department, when the review into the use of paragraph 322(5) to refuse applications for leave to remain is planned to be completed.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189694","189694"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003620","2018-11-13","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of the expansion of Heathrow Airport on local road networks.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189623","189623"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003621","2018-11-13","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the number of (a) light goods vehicles, (b) heavy goods vehicles and (c) private cars that access Heathrow airport on a daily basis.","Biography information for Andy Slaughter","Andy Slaughter","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189624","189624"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003622","2018-11-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, what estimate his Department has made of the savings social impact bonds have made to the public purse since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189695","189695"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003623","2018-11-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, how much his Department has spent promoting social impact bonds since 2010.","Biography information for Mr Steve Reed","Mr Steve Reed","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189696","189696"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003624","2018-11-14","Department for Work and Pensions","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Work and Pensions, what representations she has received on the HSBC Midland Bank pension clawback; and if she will make a statement.","Biography information for Kevin Brennan","Kevin Brennan","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189598","189598"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003625","2018-11-13","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment his Department has made of the risk to motorcyclists of inexperienced (a) HGV and (b) car drivers; and what plans he has to improve the driver education on motorcyclists.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189742","189742"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003626","2018-11-13","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made on the number of motorcyclists (a) killed and (b) seriously injured in each year between 2014 and 2017.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189743","189743"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003627","2018-11-13","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made on the proportion of motorcycle fatalities that occurred on (a) urban roads, (b) rural roads and (c) motorways in each year between 2014 and 2017.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189744","189744"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003628","2018-11-13","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what estimate he has made on the average weekly number of (a) deaths and (b) serious injuries to motorcyclists from 2014 to 2017.","Biography information for Royston Smith","Royston Smith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189745","189745"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003629","2018-11-14","Foreign and Commonwealth Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Foreign and Commonwealth Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November Question 185485 on Sudan: Military Attachés, whether the UK military attaché has been present at a graduation ceremony for the Rapid Support Forces soldiers since May 2017.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189533","189533"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003630","2018-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November to Questions 185481 and 185482 on Bovine Tuberculosis: Cumbria, what criteria Natural England uses to specify minimum effort in culling badgers in Cumbria; and how does Natural England measure the effectiveness and success of that effort.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189534","189534"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003631","2018-11-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, whether his Department still plans to publish the Cyber Skills strategy in December 2018.","Biography information for Jo Platt","Jo Platt","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189796","189796"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003632","2018-11-14","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, pursuant to the Answer of 5 November to Question 185483 on Bovine Tuberculosis: Cumbria, how many of the 14 County Parish Holdings in Cumbria that submitted samples for gamma tests are in the badger cull zone.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189535","189535"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003633","2018-11-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with the (a) Secretary of State for Wales, (b) Welsh Government and (c) Welsh Language Commissioner on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on (i) Welsh speakers and (ii) Welsh-speaking communities.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189593","189593"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003634","2018-11-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what discussions he has had with (a) the Secretary of State for Wales, (b) the Welsh Government and (c) the Welsh Language Commissioner on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on Welsh speakers and Welsh-speaking communities.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189594","189594"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003635","2018-11-13","Department for Exiting the European Union ","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Exiting the European Union, what representations he has received from (a) the Secretary of State for Wales, (b) the Welsh Government and (c) the Welsh Language Commissioner on the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on (i) Welsh speakers and (ii) Welsh-speaking communities.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189595","189595"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003636","2018-11-13","Wales Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, if he will make an assessment of the potential effect of the UK leaving the EU on Welsh speakers and Welsh-speaking communities.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189596","189596"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003637","2018-11-13","Wales Office","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Wales, what discussions he has had with (a) Cabinet colleagues, (b) the Welsh Government, (c) the Welsh Language Commissioner and (d) the Culture, Welsh Language and Communications Committee in the National Assembly for Wales on the potential effect on (i) Welsh speakers and (ii) Welsh-speaking communities of the UK leaving the EU.","Biography information for Hywel Williams","Hywel Williams","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189597","189597"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003638","2018-11-14","Department for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Business, Energy and Industrial Strategy, pursuant to the Answer of 6 November 2018 to Question 186935 on Carbon Budgets: Climate Change, whether the Committee on Climate Change’s response to the IPCC report on 1.5 degrees will be permitted to include recommendations on amending the UK's third, fourth and fifth carbon budgets.","Biography information for Mr Roger Godsiff","Mr Roger Godsiff","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189541","189541"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003639","2018-11-13","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what progress Highways England is making on reducing levels of NO2 on the strategic road network.","Biography information for James Frith","James Frith","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189797","189797"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003640","2018-11-13","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what assessment he has made of the potential effect of implementing the EU Directive set out in Regulation EC No. 1073/2009 on local charity groups who provide free or reduced cost transport.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189776","189776"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003641","2018-11-13","Department for Education","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what progress his Department has made on its 2015 target of increasing the value of educational exports to £30 billion by 2020; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189580","189580"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003642","2018-11-13","Department for Education","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, whether he plans to set a growth target for international student numbers studying at UK universities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189581","189581"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003643","2018-11-13","Department for Education","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Education, what steps he is taking increase the number of Indian students studying at UK universities; and if he will make a statement.","Biography information for Mr Barry Sheerman","Mr Barry Sheerman","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189582","189582"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003644","2018-11-13","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what steps his Department is taking to ensure that implementing Eu Directive set out in Regulation EC No.1073/2009 will not prevent people with a disability from accessing local transport services.","Biography information for Wera Hobhouse","Wera Hobhouse","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189777","189777"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003645","2018-11-14","Department for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Digital, Culture, Media and Sport, with reference to the recommendations of the WebRoots Democracy report, Kinder, Gentler Politics: Tackling the rise of online abuse in political debate, published on 16 October 2018, what assessment his Department has made of the potential merits of (a) creating an online abusers register and (b) commissioning research into the links between anonymity and online abuse.","Biography information for Hannah Bardell","Hannah Bardell","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189750","189750"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003646","2018-11-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, how many penalty prescription charges have been issued in the last year for which figures are available.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189548","189548"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003647","2018-11-13","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what guidance his Department has issued to Highways England on the permitted length of roadworks in any one stretch.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189549","189549"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003648","2018-11-13","Ministry of Justice","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Justice, what progress has been made on helping families affected by the Birmingham pub bombings in securing legal aid for the upcoming inquest.","Biography information for Julian Knight","Julian Knight","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189725","189725"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003649","2018-11-13","Department for Transport","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Transport, what recent estimate he has made of the comparative output of CO2 per mile of diesel and petrol cars.","Biography information for John Spellar","John Spellar","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189550","189550"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003650","2018-11-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, with reference to paragraph 6.10 of the UK Five Year Antimicrobial Resistance Strategy 2013 to 2018, published in September 2013, when he plans to publish the evaluation report.","Biography information for Thangam Debbonaire","Thangam Debbonaire","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189732","189732"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003651","2018-11-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the quantity was of (a) electricity and (b) natural gas used by (i) his Department, (ii) the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency, (iii) Public Health England, (iv) the Care Quality Commission, (v) the Health Research Authority, (vi) the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority, (vii) the Human Tissue Authority and (viii) Porton Biopharma Limited in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189702","189702"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003652","2018-11-13","Department of Health and Social Care","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Health and Social Care, what the cost was of (a) electricity and (b) natural gas used by (i) his Department, (ii) the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency, (iii) Public Health England, (iv) the Care Quality Commission, (v) the Health Research Authority, (vi) the Human Fertilisation and Embryology Authority, (vii) the Human Tissue Authority and (viii) Porton Biopharma Limited in each of the last three years for which figures are available.","Biography information for Stuart C. McDonald","Stuart C. McDonald","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189703","189703"
"http://data.parliament.uk/resources/1003653","2018-11-13","Department for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs","2018-11-09","To ask the Secretary of State for Environment, Food and Rural Affairs, what his Department's strategy is for cutting the amount of ammonia from farms.","Biography information for Dr David Drew","Dr David Drew","House of Commons Tabled Parliamentary Question 2017/19 189536","189536"
